<?xml-model href="sw_schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<root>
<title>STAR WARS Episode IV A NEW HOPE (1977)</title>
by <writer>George Lucas</writer>


<script>
<subTitle epNum="4">EPISODE 4 A NEW HOPE</subTitle>
<crawl>A long time ago, in a galaxy far, far, away...</crawl>

<sd>A vast sea of stars serves as the backdrop for the main title. 
War drums echo through the heavens as a rollup slowly crawls 
into infinity.</sd>

<crawl>     It is a period of civil war. Rebel spaceships, 
     striking from a hidden base, have won their first 
     victory against the evil Galactic <name type="GPE">Empire</name>.

     During the battle, Rebel spies managed to steal 
     secret plans to the <name type="GPE">Empire</name>'s ultimate weapon, the 
     Death Star, an armored space station with enough 
     power to destroy an entire planet.

     Pursued by the <name type="GPE">Empire</name>'s sinister agents, Princess 
     Leia races home aboard her starship, custodian of 
     the stolen plans that can save her people and 
     restore freedom to the galaxy...</crawl>

<sd>The awesome yellow planet of Tatooine emerges from a total 
eclipse, her two moons glowing against the darkness. A tiny 
silver spacecraft, a Rebel Blockade Runner firing lasers 
from the back of the ship, races through space. It is pursed 
by a giant <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> Stardestroyer. Hundreds of deadly 
laserbolts streak from the <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> Stardestroyer, causing 
the main solar fin of the Rebel craft to disintegrate.</sd>

<setting>INT. REBEL BLOCKADE RUNNER - MAIN PASSAGEWAY</setting>

<sd>An explosion rocks the ship as two robots, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>-Detoo (R2-
D2) and See-<name type="ORG">Threepio</name> (C-3PO) struggle to make their way 
through the shaking, bouncing passageway. Both robots are 
old and battered. <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> is a short, claw-armed tripod. His 
face is a mass of computer lights surrounding a radar eye. 
<name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, on the other hand, is a tall, slender robot of 
human proportions. He has a gleaming bronze-like metallic 
surface of an Art Deco design.</sd>

<sd>Another blast shakes them as they struggle along their way.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>Rebel troopers rush past the robots and take up positions in 
the main passageway. They aim their weapons toward the door.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>The little R2 unit makes a series of electronic sounds that 
only another robot could understand.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> continues making beeping sounds. Tension mounts as 
loud metallic latches clank and the scream of heavy equipment 
are heard moving around the outside hull of the ship.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACECRAFT IN SPACE</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> craft has easily overtaken the Rebel Blockade 
Runner. The smaller Rebel ship is being drawn into the 
underside dock of the giant <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> starship.</sd>

<setting>INT. REBEL BLOCKADE RUNNER</setting>

<sd>The nervous Rebel troopers aim their weapons. Suddenly a 
tremendous blast opens up a hole in the main passageway and 
a score of fearsome armored spacesuited stormtroopers make 
their way into the smoke-filled corridor.</sd>

<sd>In a few minutes the entire passageway is ablaze with 
laserfire. The deadly bolts ricochet in wild random patterns 
creating huge explosions. Stormtroopers scatter and duck 
behind storage lockers. Laserbolts hit several Rebel soldiers 
who scream and stagger through the smoke, holding shattered 
arms and faces.</sd>

<sd>An explosion hits near the robots.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> counters with an angry rebuttal as the battle rages 
around the two hapless robots.</sd>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - DESERT WASTELAND - DAY</setting>

<sd>A death-white wasteland stretches from horizon to horizon. 
The tremendous heat of two huge twin suns settle on a lone 
figure, Luke Skywalker, a farm boy with heroic aspirations 
who looks much younger than his eighteen years. His shaggy 
hair and baggy tunic give him the air of a simple but lovable 
lad with a prize-winning smile.</sd>

<sd>A light wind whips at him as he adjusts several valves on a 
large battered moisture vaporator which sticks out of the 
desert floor much like an oil pipe with valves. He is aided 
by a beatup tread-robot with six claw arms. The little robot 
appears to be barely functioning and moves with jerky motions.  
A bright sparkle in the morning sky catches Luke's eye and 
he instinctively grabs a pair of electrobinoculars from his 
utility belt. He stands transfixed for a few moments studying 
the heavens, then dashed toward his dented, crudely repaired 
Landspeeder (an auto-like transport that travels a few feet 
above the ground on a magnetic-field). He motions for the 
tiny robot to follow him.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>The robot scoots around in a tight circle, stops short, and 
smoke begins to pour out of every joint. Luke throws his 
arms up in disgust. Exasperated, the young farm boy jumps 
into his Landspeeder leaving the smoldering robot to hum 
madly.</sd>

<setting>INT. REBEL BLOCKADE RUNNER - MAIN HALLWAY</setting>

<sd>The awesome, seven-foot-tall Dark Lord of the Sith makes his 
way into the blinding light of the main passageway. This is 
Darth Vader, right hand of the Emperor. His face is obscured 
by his flowing black robes and grotesque breath mask, which 
stands out next to the fascist white armored suits of the 
<name type="ORG">Imperial</name> stormtroopers. Everyone instinctively backs away 
from the imposing warrior and a deathly quiet sweeps through 
the Rebel troops. Several of the Rebel troops break and run 
in a frenzied panic.</sd>

<setting>INT. REBEL BLOCKADE RUNNER</setting>

<sd>A woman's hand puts a card into an opening in <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>'s dome.  
<name type="GPE">Artoo</name> makes beeping sounds.</sd>

<setting>INT. REBEL BLOCKADE RUNNER</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> stands in a hallway, somewhat bewildered. <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> is 
nowhere in sight. The pitiful screams of the doomed Rebel 
soldiers can be heard in the distance.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>A familiar clanking sound attacks <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>'s attention and 
he spots little <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> at the end of the hallway in a smoke-
filled alcove. A beautiful young girl (about sixteen years 
old) stands in front of <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>. Surreal and out of place, 
dreamlike and half hidden in the smoke, she finishes adjusting 
something on <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>'s computer face, then watches as the little 
robot joins his companion.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>Stormtroopers can be heard battling in the distance.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> scoots past his bronze friend and races down the 
subhallway. <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> chases after him.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> responds with electronic beeps.</sd>

<setting>INT. REBEL BLOCKADE RUNNER - CORRIDOR</setting>

<sd>The evil Darth Vader stands amid the broken and twisted bodies 
of his foes. He grabs a wounded Rebel Officer by the neck as 
an <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> Officer rushes up to the Dark Lord.</sd>

<speaker>IMPERIAL OFFICER</speaker>

<sd>Vader squeezes the neck of the Rebel Officer, who struggles 
in vain.</sd>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<sd>Vader lifts the Rebel off his feet by his throat.</sd>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<speaker>REBEL OFFICER</speaker>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<sd>The Rebel refuses to speak but eventually cries out as the 
Dark Lord begins to squeeze the officer's throat, creating a 
gruesome snapping and choking, until the soldier goes limp. 
Vader tosses the dead soldier against the wall and turns to 
his troops.</sd>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<sd>The stormtroopers scurry into the subhallways.</sd>

<setting>INT. REBEL BLOCKADE RUNNER - SUBHALLWAY</setting>

<sd>The lovely young girl huddles in a small alcove as the 
stormtroopers search through the ship. She is Princess Leia 
Organa, a member of the <name type="ORG">Alderaan</name> <name type="ORG">Senate</name>. The fear in her 
eyes slowly gives way to anger as the muted crushing sounds 
of the approaching stormtroopers grow louder. One of the 
troopers spots her.</sd>

<speaker>TROOPER</speaker>

<sd>Leia steps from her hiding place and blasts a trooper with 
her laser pistol. She starts to run but is felled by a 
paralyzing ray. The troopers inspect her inert body.</sd>

<speaker>TROOPER</speaker>

<setting>INT. REBEL BLOCKADE RUNNER - SUBHALLWAY</setting>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> stops before the small hatch of an emergency lifepod. 
He snaps the seal on the main latch and a red warning light 
begins to flash. The stubby astro-robot works his way into 
the cramped four-man pod.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps something to him.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> whistles something at his reluctant friend regarding 
the mission he is about to perform.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> isn't happy with <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>'s stubbornness, and he beeps 
and twangs angrily.</sd>

<sd>A new explosion, this time very close, sends dust and debris 
through the narrow subhallway. Flames lick at <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> and, 
after a flurry of electronic swearing from <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, the lanky 
robot jumps into the lifepod.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<setting>INT. IMPERIAL STARDESTROYER</setting>

<sd>On the main viewscreen, the lifepod carrying the two terrified 
robots speeds away from the stricken Rebel spacecraft.</sd>

<speaker>CHIEF PILOT</speaker>

<speaker>CAPTAIN</speaker>

<setting>INT. LIFEPOD</setting>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> and <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> look out at the receding <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> starship.  
Stars circle as the pod rotates through the galaxy.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps an assuring response.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - ANCHORHEAD SETTLEMENT - POWER STATION - DAY</setting>

<sd>Heat waves radiate from the dozen or so bleached white 
buildings. Luke pilots his Landspeeder through the dusty 
empty street of the tiny settlement. An old woman runs to 
get out of the way of the speeding vehicle, shaking her fist 
at Luke as he flies past.</sd>

<speaker>WOMAN</speaker>

<setting>INT. POWER STATION - DAY</setting>

<sd>Luke bursts into the power station, waking The Fixer, a rugged 
mechanic and Camie, a sexy, disheveled girl who has been 
asleep in his lap. They grumbled as he races through the 
office, yelling wildly.</sd>

<speaker>FIXER</speaker>

<speaker>CAMIE</speaker>

<sd>Luke bounces into a small room behind the office where Deak 
and Windy, two tough boys about the same age as Luke, are 
playing a computer pool-like game with Biggs, a burly, 
handsome boy a few years older than the rest. His flashy 
city attire is a sharp contrast to the loose-fitting tunics 
of the farm boys. A robot repairs some equipment in the 
background.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke's surprise at the appearance of Biggs gives way to great 
joy and emotion. They give each other a great bear hug.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Biggs has an air of cool that seems slightly phony.</sd>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<sd>Everyone laughs. The dazzling spectacle of his dashing friend 
is almost too much for Luke, but suddenly he snaps out of 
it.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>DEAK</speaker>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - ANCHORHEAD - SETTLEMENT - POWER STATION - </setting>
DAY

<sd>The group stumbles out into the stifling desert sun. Camie 
and The Fixer complain and are forced to shade their eyes. 
Luke has his binoculars out scanning the heavens.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Biggs takes the binoculars from Luke as the others strain to 
see something with the naked eye. Through the binoculars 
Biggs sees two small silver specks.</sd>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Camie grabs the binoculars away banging them against the 
building in the process. Luke grabs them.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>CAMIE</speaker>

<sd>The Fixer gives Luke a hard look and the young farm boy shrugs 
his shoulders in resignation.</sd>

<speaker>FIXER</speaker>

<sd>Luke agrees, although it's obvious he isn't sure why. The 
group stumbles back into the power station, grumbling about 
Luke's ineptitude.</sd>

<setting>INT. REBEL BLOCKADE RUNNER - HALLWAY</setting>

<sd>Princess Leia is led down a low-ceilinged hallway by a squad 
of armored stormtroopers. Her hands are bound and she is 
brutally shoved when she is unable to keep up with the briskly 
marching troops. They stop in a smoky hallway as Darth Vader 
emerges from the shadows. The sinister Dark Lord stares hard 
at the frail young senator, but she doesn't move.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<sd>Leia is marched away down the hallway and into the smoldering 
hole blasted in the side of the ship. An <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> Commander 
turns to Vader.</sd>

<speaker>COMMANDER</speaker>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<speaker>COMMANDER</speaker>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<sd>Another <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> Officer approaches Vader and the Commander. 
They stop and snap to attention.</sd>

<speaker>SECOND OFFICER</speaker>

<sd>Vader turns to the Commander.</sd>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<speaker>COMMANDER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> Stardestroyer comes over the surface of the 
planet Tatooine.</sd>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - DESERT</setting>

<sd>Jundland, or "No Man's Land", where the rugged desert <name type="ORG">mesa</name>s 
meet the foreboding dune sea. The two helpless astro-droids 
kick up clouds of sand as they leave the lifepod and clumsily 
work their way across the desert wasteland. The lifepod in 
the distance rests half buried in the sand.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> answers with beeping sounds.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> continues to respond with beeping sounds.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>Suddenly <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> whistles, makes a sharp right turn and starts 
off in the direction of the rocky desert <name type="ORG">mesa</name>s. <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> 
stops and yells at him.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>A stream of electronic noises pours forth from the small 
robot.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> counters with a long whistle.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> continues to make beeping sounds.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> continues to make beeping sounds.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> gives the little robot a kick and starts off in the 
direction of the vast dune sea.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name>'s reply is a rather rude sound. He turns and trudges 
off in the direction of the towering <name type="ORG">mesa</name>s.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps to himself as he makes his way toward the distant 
mountains.</sd>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - DUNE SEA</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, hot and tired, struggles up over the ridge of a 
dune; only to find more dunes, which seem to go on for endless 
miles.  He looks back in the direction of the now distant 
rock <name type="ORG">mesa</name>s.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>In a huff of anger and frustration, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> knocks the sand 
from his joints. His plight seems hopeless, when a glint of 
reflected light in the distance reveals an object moving 
towards him.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>The bronze android waves frantically and yells at the 
approaching transport.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - ANCHORHEAD SETTLEMENT - POWER STATION - DAY</setting>

<sd>Luke and Biggs are walking and drinking a malt brew. Fixer 
and the others can be heard working inside.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Biggs looks around then leans close to Luke.</sd>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<sd>Luke's eyes are wide with Biggs' seriousness and loyalty.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<sd>Luke, amazed and stunned, is almost speechless.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Biggs shakes his head angrily and then continues.</sd>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<sd>Biggs turns away from his old friend and heads towards the 
power station.</sd>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - ROCK CANYON - SUNSET</setting>

<sd>The gargantuan rock formations are shrouded in a strange 
foreboding mist and the onimous sounds of unearthly creatures 
fill the air. <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> moves cautiously through the creepy rock 
canyon, inadvertently making a loud clicking noise as he 
goes. He hears a distant, hard, metallic sound and stops for 
a moment. Convinced he is alone, he continues on his way.</sd>

<sd>In the distance, a pebble tumbles down the steep canyon wall 
and a small dark figure darts into the shadows. A little 
further up the canyon a slight flicker of light reveals a 
pair of eyes in the dark recesses only a few feet from the 
narrow path.</sd>

<sd>The unsuspecting robot waddles along the rugged trail until 
suddenly, out of nowhere, a powerful magnetic ray shoots out 
of the rocks and engulfs him in an eerie glow. He manages 
one short electronic squeak before he topples over onto his 
back. His bright computer lights flicker off, then on, then 
off again. Out of the rocks scurry three Jawas, no taller 
than <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>. They holster strange and complex weapons as they 
cautiously approach the robot. They wear grubby cloaks and 
their faces are shrouded so only their glowing eyes can be 
seen. They hiss and make odd guttural sounds as they heave 
the heavy robot onto their shoulders and carry him off down 
the trail.</sd>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - ROCK CANYON - SANDCRAWLER - SUNSET</setting>

<sd>The eight Jawas carry <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> out of the canyon to a huge tank-
like vehicle the size of a four-story house. They weld a 
small disk on the side of <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> and then put him under a 
large tube on the side of the vehicle and the little robot 
is sucked into the giant machine.</sd>

<sd>The filthy little Jawas scurry like rats up small ladders 
and enter the main cabin of the behemoth transport.</sd>

<setting>INT. SANDCRAWLER - HOLD AREA</setting>

<sd>It is dim inside the hold area of the Sandcrawler. <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> 
switches on a small floodlight on his forehead and stumbles 
around the scrap heap. The narrow beam swings across rusty 
metal rocket parts and an array of grotesquely twisted and 
maimed astro-robots. He lets out a pathetic electronic whimper 
and stumbles off toward what appears to be a door at the end 
of the chamber.</sd>

<setting>INT. SANDCRAWLER - PRISON AREA</setting>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> enters a wide room with a four-foot ceiling. In the 
middle of the scrap heap sit a dozen or so robots of various 
shapes and sizes. Some are engaged in electronic conversation, 
while others simply mill about. A voice of recognition calls 
out from the gloom.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>A battered <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> scrambles up to <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> and embraces him.</sd>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - ROCK CANYON - SANDCRAWLER - SUNSET</setting>

<sd>The enormous Sandcrawler lumbers off toward the magnificent 
twin suns, which are slowly setting over a distant mountain 
ridge.</sd>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - DESERT - DAY</setting>

<sd>Four <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> stormtroopers mill about in front of the half-
buried lifepod that brought <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> and <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> to Tatooine. 
A trooper yells to an officer some distance away.</sd>

<speaker>FIRST TROOPER</speaker>

<sd>A second trooper picks a small bit of metal out of the sand 
and gives it to the first trooper.</sd>

<speaker>SECOND TROOPER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - DUNES</setting>

<sd>The Sandcrawler moves slowly down a great sand dune.</sd>

<setting>INT. SANDCRAWLER</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> and <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> noisily bounce along inside the cramped 
prison chamber. <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> appears to be shut off.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>Suddenly the shaking and bouncing of the Sandcrawler stops, 
creating quite a commotion among the mechanical men.  
<name type="ORG">Threepio</name>'s fist bangs the head of <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> whose computer lights 
pop on as he begins beeping. At the far end of the long 
chamber a hatch opens, filling the chamber with blinding 
white light. a dozen or so Jawas make their way through the 
odd assortment of robots.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>A Jawa starts moving toward them.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> responds, making beeping sounds.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - DESERT - LARS HOMESTEAD - AFTERNOON</setting>

<sd>The Jawas mutter gibberish as they busily line up their 
battered captives, including <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> and <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, in front of 
the enormous Sandcrawler, which is parked beside a small 
homestead consisting of three large holes in the ground 
surrounded by several tall moisture vaporators and one small 
adobe block house.</sd>

<sd>The Jawas scurry around fussing over the robots, straightening 
them up or brushing some dust from a dented metallic elbow. 
The shrouded little creatures smell horribly, attracting 
small insects to the dark areas when their mouths and nostrils 
should be.</sd>

<sd>Out of the shadows of a dingy side-building limps Owen Lars, 
a large burly man in his mid-fifties. His reddish eyes are 
sunken in a dust-covered face. As the farmer carefully 
inspects each robot, he is closely followed by his slump- 
shouldered nephew, Luke Skywalker. One of the vile little 
Jawas walks ahead of the farmer spouting an animated sales 
pitch in a queer, unintelligible language.</sd>

<sd>A voice calls out from one of the huge holes that form the 
homestead. Luke goes over to the edge and sees his Aunt Beru 
standing in the main courtyard.</sd>

<speaker>BERU</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke returns to his uncle as they look over the equipment 
for sale with the Jawa leader.</sd>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>As the Jawas start to lead the three remaining robots back 
into the Sandcrawler, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> lets out a pathetic little beep 
and starts after his old friend <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>. He is restrained 
by a slimy Jawa, who zaps him with a control box.</sd>

<sd>Owen is negotiating with the head Jawa. Luke and the two 
robots start off for the garage when a plate pops off the 
head of the red astro-droid's head plate and it sparks wildly.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<sd>The Jawa goes into a loud spiel. Meanwhile, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> has sneaked 
out of line and is moving up and down trying to attract 
attention. He lets out with a low whistle. <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> taps 
Luke on the shoulder.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<sd>With a little reluctance the scruffy dwarf trades the damaged 
astro-droid for <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>Owen pays off the whining Jawa as Luke and the two robots 
trudge off toward a grimy homestead entry.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<setting>INT. LARS HOMESTEAD - GARAGE AREA - LATE AFTERNOON</setting>

<sd>The garage is cluttered and worn, but a friendly peaceful 
atmosphere permeates the low grey chamber. <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> lowers 
himself into a large tub filled with warm oil. Near the 
battered Landspeeder little <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> rests on a large battery 
with a cord to his face.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps a muffled reply. Luke seems to be lost in thought 
as he runs his hand over the damaged fin of a small two-man 
Skyhopper spaceship resting in a low hangar off the garage. 
Finally Luke's frustrations get the better of him and he 
slams a wrench across the workbench.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>Luke glances at the battered robot. A bit of his anger drains 
and a tiny smile creeps across his face.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps in response. Luke unplugs <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> and begins to 
scrape several connectors on the robot's head with a chrome 
pick. <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> climbs out of the oil tub and begins wiping 
oil from his bronze body.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>Luke struggles to remove a small metal fragment from <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>'s 
neck joint. He uses a larger pick.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>The fragment breaks loose with a snap, sending Luke tumbling 
head over heels. He sits up and sees a twelve-inch three-
dimensional hologram of Leia Organa, the Rebel senator, being 
projected from the face of little <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>. The image is a 
rainbow of colors as it flickers and jiggles in the dimly 
lit garage. Luke's mouth hangs open in awe.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> looks around and sheepishly beeps an answer for <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> 
to translate. Leia continues to repeat the sentence fragment 
over and over.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> whistles his surprise as he pretends to just notice 
the hologram. He looks around and sheepishly beeps an answer 
for <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> to translate. Leia continues to repeat the 
sentence fragment over and over.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>Luke becomes intrigued by the beautiful girl.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke reaches out for <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> but he lets out several frantic 
squeaks and a whistle.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> whistles and beeps a long message to <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke's gazes at the beautiful young princess for a few 
moments.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps something to <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>Luke looks longingly at the lovely, little princess and hasn't 
really heard what <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> has been saying.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke takes a wedged bar and pops the restraining bolt off 
<name type="GPE">Artoo</name>'s side.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>The princess immediately disappears...</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps an innocent reply as <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> sits up in 
embarrassment.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>A women's voice calls out from another room.</sd>

<speaker>AUNT BERU</speaker>

<sd>Luke stands up and shakes his head at the malfunctioning 
robot.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>Luke tosses <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>'s restraining bolt on the workbench and 
hurries out of the room.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps in response.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<setting>INT. LARS HOMESTEAD - DINING AREA</setting>

<sd>Luke's Aunt Beru, a warm, motherly woman, fills a pitcher 
with blue fluid from a refrigerated container in the well-
used kitchen. She puts the pitcher on a tray with some bowls 
of food and starts for the dining area.</sd>

<sd>Luke sits with his Uncle Owen before a table covered with 
steaming bowls of food as Aunt Beru carries in a bowl of red 
grain.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Owen is greatly alarmed at the mention of his name, but 
manages to control himself.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Owen breaks loose with a fit of uncontrolled anger.</sd>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Owen's face becomes a scowl, although he tries to suppress 
it.</sd>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<sd>Luke continues to toy with his food, not looking at his uncle.</sd>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<sd>Luke pushes his half-eaten plate of food aside and stands.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>AUNT BERU</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Resigned to his fate, Luke paddles out of the room. Owen 
mechanically finishes his dinner.</sd>

<speaker>AUNT BERU</speaker>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<speaker>AUNT BERU</speaker>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - LARS HOMESTEAD</setting>

<sd>The giant twin suns of Tatooine slowly disappear behind a 
distant dune range. Luke stands watching them for a few 
moments, then reluctantly enters the doomed entrance to the 
homestead.</sd>

<setting>INT. LARS HOMESTEAD - GARAGE</setting>

<sd>Luke enters the garage to discover the robots nowhere in 
sight. He takes a small control box from his utility belt 
similar to the one the Jawas were carrying. He activates the 
box, which creates a low hum, and <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, letting out a 
short yell, pops up from behind the Skyhopper spaceship.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> stumbles forward, but <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> is still nowhere in 
sight.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke races out of the garage followed by <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>.</sd>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - LARS HOMESTEAD</setting>

<sd>Luke rushes out of the small doomed entry to the homestead 
and searches the darkening horizon for the small triped astro-
robot. <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> struggles out of the homestead and on the 
salt flat as Luke scans the landscape with his 
electrobinoculars.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Owen yells up from the homestead plaza.</sd>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>He takes one final look across the dim horizon.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<setting>INT. LARS HOMESTEAD - PLAZA</setting>

<sd>Morning slowly creeps into the sparse but sparkling oasis of 
the open courtyard. The idyll is broken be the yelling of 
Uncle Owen, his voice echoing throughout the homestead.</sd>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<setting>INT. LARS HOMESTEAD - KITCHEN</setting>

<sd>The interior of the kitchen is a worm glow as Aunt Beru 
prepares the morning breakfast. Owen enters in a huff.</sd>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<speaker>AUNT BERU</speaker>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<speaker>AUNT BERU</speaker>

<speaker>OWEN</speaker>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - DESERT WASTELAND - LUKE'S SPEEDER - DAY</setting>

<sd>The rock and sand of the desert floor are a blur as <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> 
pilots the sleek Landspeeder gracefully across the vast 
wasteland.</sd>

<setting>INT./EXT. LUKE'S SPEEDER - DESERT WASTELAND - TRAVELING -</setting>
DAY

<sd>Luke leans over the back of the speeder and adjusts something 
in the motor compartment.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> signals that is fine and Luke turns back into the 
wind-whipped cockpit and pops the canopy shut.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - ROCK MESA - DUNE SEA - COASTLINE - DAY</setting>

<sd>From high on a rock <name type="ORG">mesa</name>, the tiny Landspeeder can be seen 
gliding across the desert floor. Suddenly in the foreground 
two weather-beaten Sandpeople shrouded in their grimy desert 
cloaks peer over the edge of the rock <name type="ORG">mesa</name>. One of the 
marginally human creatures raises a long ominous laser rifle 
and points it at the speeder but the second creature grabs 
the gun before it can be fired.</sd>

<sd>The Sandpeople, or Tusken Raiders as they're sometimes called, 
speak in a coarse barbaric language as they get into an 
animated argument. The second Tusken Raider seems to get in 
the final word and the nomads scurry over the rocky terrain.</sd>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - ROCK MESA - CANYON</setting>

<sd>The Tusken Raider approaches two large <name type="ORG">Banthas</name> standing tied 
to a rock. The monstrous, bear-like creatures are as large 
as elephants, with huge red eyes, tremendous looped horns, 
and long, furry, dinosaur-like tails. The Tusken Raiders 
mount saddles strapped to the huge creatures' shaggy backs 
and ride off down the rugged bluff.</sd>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - ROCK CANYON - FLOOR</setting>

<sd>The speeder is parked on the floor of a massive canyon. Luke, 
with his long laser rifle slung over his shoulder, stands 
before little <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>The little droid whistles a feeble reply, as <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> poses 
menacingly behind the little runaway.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Suddenly the little robot jumps to life with a mass of frantic 
whistles and screams.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>Luke swings his rifle into position and looks to the south.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - ROCK CANYON - RIDGE - DAY</setting>

<sd>Luke carefully makes his way to the top of a rock ridge and 
scans the canyon with his electrobinoculars. He spots the 
two riderless <name type="ORG">Banthas</name>. <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> struggles up behind the young 
adventurer.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke watches the distant Tusken Raider through his 
electrobinoculars. Suddenly something huge moves in front of 
his field of view. Before Luke or <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> can react, a large, 
gruesome Tusken Raider looms over them. <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> is startled 
and backs away, right off the side if the cliff. He can be 
heard for several moments as he clangs, bangs and rattles 
down the side of the mountain.</sd>

<sd>The towering creature brings down his curved, double-pointed 
gaderffii -- the dreaded axe blade that has struck terror in 
the heart of the local settlers. But Luke manages to block 
the blow with his laser rifle, which is smashed to pieces. 
The terrified farm boy scrambles backward until he is forced 
to the edge of a deep crevice. The sinister Raider stands 
over him with his weapon raised and lets out a horrible 
shrieking laugh.</sd>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - ROCK CANYON - FLOOR - DAY</setting>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> forces himself into the shadows of a small alcove in 
the rocks as the vicious Sandpeople walk past carrying the 
inert Luke Skywalker, who is dropped in a heap before the 
speeder.  The Sandpeople ransack the speeder, throwing parts 
and supplies in all directions. Suddenly they stop. Then 
everything is quiet for a few moments. A great howling moan 
is heard echoing throughout the canyon which sends the 
Sandpeople fleeing in terror.</sd>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> moves even tighter into the shadows as the slight 
swishing sound that frightened off the Sandpeople grows even 
closer, until a shabby old desert-rat-of-a-man appears and 
leans over Luke. His ancient leathery face, cracked and 
weathered by exotic climates is set off by dark, penetrating 
eyes and a scraggly white beard. Ben <name type="ORG">Kenobi</name> squints his eyes 
as he scrutinizes the unconscious farm boy. <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> makes a 
slight sound and Ben turns and looks right at him.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> waddles over to were Luke lies crumpled in a heap and 
begins to whistle and beep his concern. Ben puts his hand on 
Luke's forehead and he begins to come around.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Ben ponders this for a moment, scratching his scruffy beard.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd>He suddenly looks up at the overhanging cliffs.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd>Luke sits up and rubs his head. <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> lets out a pathetic 
beep causing Luke to remember something. He looks around.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - SAND PIT - ROCK MESA - DAY</setting>

<sd>Little <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> stands at the edge of a large sand pit and begins 
to chatter away in electronic whistles and beeps. Luke and 
Ben stand over a very dented and tangled <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> lying half 
buried in the sand. One of his arms has broken off.</sd>

<sd>Luke tries to revive the inert robot by shaking him and then 
flips a hidden switch on his back several times until finally 
the mechanical man's systems turn on.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> makes a beeping sound.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke and Ben help the battered robot to his feet. Little 
<name type="GPE">Artoo</name> watches from the top of the pit. Ben glances around 
suspiciously. Sensing something, he stands up and sniffs the 
air.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<setting>INT. KENOBI'S DWELLING</setting>

<sd>The small, spartan hovel is cluttered with desert junk but 
still manages to radiate an air of time-worn comfort and 
security. Luke is in one corner repairing <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>'s arm, as 
old Ben sits thinking.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd>Ben gets up and goes to a chest where he rummages around.  
As Luke finishes repairing <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> and starts to fit the 
restraining bolt back on, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> looks at him nervously.  
Luke thinks about the bolt for a moment then puts it on the 
table. Ben shuffles up and presents Luke with a short handle 
with several electronic gadgets attached to it.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Ben hands Luke the saber.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd>Luke pushes a button on the handle. A long beam shoots out 
about four feet and flickers there. The light plays across 
the ceiling.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd>Luke hasn't really been listening.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> makes beeping sounds.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke is cut short as the recorded image of the beautiful 
young Rebel princess is projected from <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>'s face.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd>Luke stops his work as the lovely girl's image flickers before 
his eyes.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<sd>There is a little static and the transmission is cut short.  
Old Ben leans back and scratches his head. He silently puffs 
on a tarnished chrome water pipe. Luke has stars in his eyes.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE.</setting>

<sd>An <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> Stardestroyer heads toward the evil planet-like 
battle station: <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name>!</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - CONFERENCE ROOM</setting>

<sd>Eight <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> senators and generals sit around a black 
conference table. <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> stormtroopers stand guard around 
the room. Commander Tagge, a young, slimy-looking general, 
is speaking.</sd>

<speaker>TAGGE</speaker>

<sd>The bitter Admiral Motti twists nervously in his chair.</sd>

<speaker>MOTTI</speaker>

<speaker>TAGGE</speaker>

<sd>Suddenly all heads turn as Commander Tagge's speech is cut 
short and the Grand Moff Tarkin, governor of the <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> 
outland regions, enters. He is followed by his powerful ally, 
The Sith Lord, Darth Vader. All of the generals stand and 
bow before the thin, evil-looking governor as he takes his 
place at the head of the table. The Dark Lord stands behind 
him.</sd>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<speaker>TAGGE</speaker>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<speaker>TAGGE</speaker>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<speaker>MOTTI</speaker>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<speaker>MOTTI</speaker>

<sd>Suddenly Motti chokes and starts to turn blue under Vader's 
spell.</sd>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - WASTELAND</setting>

<sd>The speeder stops before what remains of the huge Jawas 
Sandcrawler. Luke and Ben walk among the smoldering rubble 
and scattered bodies.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Ben is crouching in the sand studying the tracks.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke looks back at the speeder where <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> and <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> are 
inspecting the dead Jawas, and put two and two together.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke reaches a sudden horrible realization, then races for 
the speeder and jumps it.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd>Luke races off leaving Ben and the two robots alone with the 
burning Sandcrawler.</sd>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - WASTELAND</setting>

<sd>Luke races across the wasteland in his battered Landspeeder.</sd>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - LARS HOMESTEAD</setting>

<sd>The speeder roars up to the burning homestead. Luke jumps 
out and runs to the smoking holes that were once his home. 
Debris is scattered everywhere and it looks as if a great 
battle has taken place.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke stumbles around in a daze looking for his aunt and uncle. 
Suddenly he comes upon their smoldering remains. He is 
stunned, and cannot speak. Hate replaces fear and a new 
resolve comes over him.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter races toward <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name>.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - DETENTION CORRIDOR</setting>

<sd>Two stormtroopers open an electronic cell door and allow 
several <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> guards to enter. Princess Leia's face is 
filled with defiance, which slowly gives way to fear as a 
giant black torture robot enters, followed by Darth Vader.</sd>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<sd>The torture robot gives off a steady beeping sound as it 
approaches Princess Leia and extends one of its mechanical 
arms bearing a large hypodermic needle. The door slides shut 
and the long cell block hallway appears peaceful. The muffled 
screams of the Rebel princess are barely heard.</sd>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - WASTELAND</setting>

<sd>There is a large bonfire of Jawa bodies blazing in front of 
the Sandcrawler as Ben and the robots finish burning the 
dead.  Luke drives up in the speeder and Ben walks over to 
him.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - WASTELAND</setting>

<sd>The Landspeeder with Luke, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, and Ben in it 
zooms across the desert. The speeder stops on a bluff 
overlooking the spaceport at Mos Eisley. It is a haphazard 
array of low, grey, concrete structures and semi-domes. A 
harsh gale blows across the stark canyon floor. Luke adjusts 
his goggles and walks to the edge of the craggy bluff where 
Ben is standing.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd>Ben looks over at Luke, who gives the old <name type="ORG">Jedi</name> a determined 
smile.</sd>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - MOS EISLEY - STREET</setting>

<sd>The speeder is stopped on a crowded street by several combat-
hardend stormtroopers who look over the two robots. A Trooper 
questions Luke.</sd>

<speaker>TROOPER</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>TROOPER</speaker>

<sd>Luke becomes very nervous as he fumbles to find his ID while 
Ben speaks to the Trooper in a very controlled voice.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>TROOPER</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>TROOPER</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>TROOPER</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>TROOPER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - MOS EISLEY - STREET</setting>

<sd>The speeder pulls up in front of a rundown blockhouse cantina 
on the outskirts of the spaceport. Various strange forms of 
transport, including several unusual beasts of burden, are 
parked outside the bar. A Jawa runs up and begins to fondle 
the speeder.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>As Luke gets out of the speeder he tries to shoo the Jawa 
away.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<setting>INT. TATOOINE - MOS EISLEY - CANTINA</setting>

<sd>The young adventurer and his two mechanical servants follow 
Ben <name type="ORG">Kenobi</name> into the smoke-filled cantina. The murky, moldy 
den is filled with a startling array of weird and exotic 
alien creatures and monsters at the long metallic bar. At 
first the sight is horrifying. One-eyed, thousand-eyed, slimy, 
furry, scaly, tentacled, and clawed creatures huddle over 
drinks. Ben moves to an empty spot at the bar near a group 
of repulsive but human scum. A huge, rough-looking Bartender 
stops Luke and the robots.</sd>

<speaker>BARTENDER</speaker>

<sd>Luke still recovering from the shock of seeing so many 
outlandish creatures, doesn't quite catch the bartender's 
drift.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BARTENDER</speaker>

<sd>Luke looks at old Ben, who is busy talking to one of the 
Galactic pirates. He notices several of the gruesome creatures 
along the bar are giving him a very unfriendly glare.</sd>

<sd>Luke pats <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> on the shoulder.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> and his stubby partner go outside and most of the 
creatures at the bar go back to their drinks.</sd>

<sd>Ben is standing next to Chewbacca, an eight-foot-tall savage-
looking creature resembling a huge grey bushbaby monkey with 
fierce baboon-like fangs. His large blue eyes dominate a fur-
covered face and soften his otherwise awesome appearance.  
Over his matted, furry body he wears two chrome bandoliers, 
and little else. He is a two-hundred-year-old <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> and a 
sight to behold.</sd>

<sd>Ben speaks to the <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name>, pointing to Luke several times 
during his conversation and the huge creature suddenly lets 
out a horrifying laugh. Luke is more than a little bit 
disconcerted and pretends not to hear the conversation between 
Ben and the giant <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name>.</sd>

<sd>Luke is terrified but tries not to show it. He quietly sips 
his drink, looking over the crowd for a more sympathetic ear 
or whatever.</sd>

<sd>A large, multiple-eyed Creature gives Luke a rough shove.</sd>

<speaker>CREATURE</speaker>

<sd>The hideous freak is obviously drunk. Luke tries to ignore 
the creature and turns back on his drink. A short, grubby 
Human and an even smaller rodent-like beast join the 
belligerent monstrosity.</sd>

<speaker>HUMAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HUMAN</speaker>

<sd>The big creature is getting agitated and yells out some 
unintelligible gibberish at the now rather nervous, young 
adventurer.</sd>

<speaker>HUMAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HUMAN</speaker>

<sd>The rodent lets out a loud grunt and everything at the bar 
moves away. Luke tries to remain cool but it isn't easy. His 
three adversaries ready their weapons. Old Ben moves in behind 
Luke.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd>A powerful blow from the unpleasant creature sends the young 
would-be <name type="ORG">Jedi</name> sailing across the room, crashing through tables 
and breaking a large jug filled with a foul-looking liquid. 
With a blood curdling shriek, the monster draws a wicked 
chrome laser pistol from his belt and levels it at old Ben. 
The bartender panics.</sd>

<speaker>BARTENDER</speaker>

<sd>With astounding agility old Ben's laser sword sparks to life 
and in a flash an arm lies on the floor. The rodent is cut 
in two and the giant multiple-eyed creature lies doubled, 
cut from chin to groin. Ben carefully and precisely turns 
off his laser sword and replaces it on his utility belt. 
Luke, shaking and totally amazed at the old man's abilities, 
attempts to stand. The entire fight has lasted only a matter 
of seconds. The cantina goes back to normal, although Ben is 
given a respectable amount of room at the bar. Luke, rubbing 
his bruised head, approaches the old man with new awe. Ben 
points the the <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name>.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - MOS EISLEY - STREET</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> paces in front of the cantina as <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> carries on 
an electronic conversation with another little red astro-
droid. A creature comes out of the cantina and approaches 
two stormtroopers in the street.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<setting>INT. TATOOINE - MOS EISLEY - CANTINA</setting>

<sd>Strange creatures play exotic big band music on odd-looking 
instruments as Luke, still giddy, downs a fresh drink and 
follows Ben and Chewbacca to a booth where <name type="NORP">Han</name> Solo is 
sitting. <name type="NORP">Han</name> is a tough, roguish starpilot about thirty years 
old. A mercenary on a starship, he is simple, sentimental, 
and cocksure.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Ben reacts to Solo's stupid attempt to impress them with 
obvious misinformation.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> ponders this for a few moments.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Ben and Luke turn around to see four <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> stormtroopers 
looking at the dead bodies and asking the bartenders some 
questions. The bartender points to the booth.</sd>

<speaker>TROOPER</speaker>

<sd>The stormtroopers look over at the booth but Luke and Ben 
are gone. The bartender shrugs his shoulders in puzzlement.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - MOS EISLEY - STREET</setting>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. MOS EISLEY - CANTINA</setting>

<sd>As <name type="NORP">Han</name> is about to leave, Greedo, a slimy green-faced alien 
with a short trunk-nose, pokes a gun in his side. The creature 
speaks in a foreign tongue translated into English subtitles.</sd>

<speaker>GREEDO</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> sits down and the alien sits across from him holding the 
gun on him.</sd>

<speaker>GREEDO</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>GREEDO</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>GREEDO</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> Solo slowly reaches for his gun under the table.</sd>

<speaker>GREEDO</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>GREEDO</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Suddenly the slimy alien disappears in a blinding flash of 
light. <name type="NORP">Han</name> pulls his smoking gun from beneath the table as 
the other patron look on in bemused amazement. <name type="NORP">Han</name> gets up 
and starts out of the cantina, flipping the bartender some 
coins as he leaves.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>Several <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters approach <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name>.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - CONTROL ROOM</setting>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<sd>An <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> Officer interrupts the meeting.</sd>

<speaker>IMPERIAL OFFICER</speaker>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<speaker>TROOPER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - MOS EISLEY - STREET</setting>

<sd>Four heavily-armed stormtroopers move menacingly along a 
narrow slum alleyway crowed with darkly clad creatures hawking 
exotic goods in the dingy little stalls. Men, monsters, and 
robots crouch in the waste-filled doorways, whispering and 
hiding from the hot winds.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>One of the troopers checks a tightly locked door and moves 
on down the alleyway. The door slides open a crack and 
<name type="ORG">Threepio</name> peeks out. <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> is barely visible in the background.</sd>

<speaker>TROOPER</speaker>

<sd>The door opens, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> moves into the doorway.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> makes beeping sounds.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - MOS EISLEY - STREET - ALLEYWAY - USED </setting>
SPEEDER LOT

<sd>Ben and Luke are standing in a sleazy used speeder lot, 
talking with a tall, grotesque, insect-like used speeder 
dealer. Strange exotic bodies and spindly-legged beasts pass 
by as the insect concludes the sale by giving Luke some coins.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd>Ben and Luke leave the speeder lot and walk down the dusty 
alleyway past a small robot herding a bunch of anteater-like 
creatures. Luke turns and gives one last forlorn look at his 
faithful speeder as he rounds a corner. A darkly clad creature 
moves out of the shadows as they pass and watches them as 
they disappear down another alley.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<setting>INT. DOCKING BAY 94 - DAY</setting>

<sd>Jabba the <name type="ORG">Hut</name> and a half-dozen grisly alien pirates and purple 
creatures stand in the middle of the docking bay. Jabba is 
the grossest of the slavering hulks and his scarred face is 
a grim testimonial to his prowess as a vicious killer. He is 
a fat, slug-like creature with eyes on extended feelers and 
a huge ugly mouth.</sd>

<speaker>JABBA</speaker>

<sd>A voice from directly behind the pirates startles them and 
they turn around to see <name type="NORP">Han</name> Solo and the giant <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name>, 
Chewbacca, standing behind them with no weapons in sight.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>JABBA</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>JABBA</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>JABBA</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>JABBA</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>JABBA</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<setting>EXT. DOCKING PORT ENTRY - ALLEYWAY</setting>

<sd>Chewbacca waits restlessly at the entrance to Docking Bay 
94.  Ben, Luke, and the robots make their way up the street.  
Chewbacca jabbers excitedly and signals for them to hurry. 
The darkly clad creature has followed them from the speeder 
lot.  He stops in a nearby doorway and speaks into a small 
transmitter.</sd>

<setting>INT. MOS EISLEY SPACEPORT - DOCKING BAY 94</setting>

<sd>Chewbacca leads the group into a giant dirt pit that is 
Docking Bay 94. Resting in the middle of the huge hole is a 
large, round, beat-up, pieced-together hunk of junk that 
could only loosely be called a starship.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>The tall figure of <name type="NORP">Han</name> Solo comes down the boarding ramp.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Luke scratches his head. It's obvious he isn't sure about 
all this. Chewbacca rushes up the ramp and urges the others 
to follow.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>The group rushes up the gang plank, passing a grinning <name type="NORP">Han</name> 
Solo.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON</setting>

<sd>Chewbacca settles into the pilot's chair and starts the mighty 
engines of the starship.</sd>

<setting>INT. MOS EISLEY SPACEPORT - DOCKING BAY 94</setting>

<sd>Luke, Ben, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, and <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> move toward the Millennium 
<name type="ORG">Falcon</name> passing Solo.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - MOS EISLEY - STREET</setting>

<sd>Eight <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> stormtroopers rush up to the darkly clad 
creature.</sd>

<speaker>TROOPER</speaker>

<sd>The darkly clad creature points to the door of the docking 
bay.</sd>

<speaker>TROOPER</speaker>

<setting>INT. MOS EISLEY SPACEPORT - DOCKING BAY 94]</setting>

<sd>The troops hold their guns at the ready and charge down the 
docking bay entrance.</sd>

<speaker>TROOPER</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> Solo looks up and sees the <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> stormtroopers rushing 
into the docking bay. Several of the troopers fire at <name type="NORP">Han</name> as 
he ducks into the spaceship.</sd>

<speaker>TROOPER</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> draws his laser pistol and pops off a couple of shots 
which force the stormtroopers to dive for safety. The 
pirateship engines whine as <name type="NORP">Han</name> hits the release button that 
slams the overhead entry shut.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON</setting>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>The group straps in for take off.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<setting>EXT. TATOOINE - MOS EISLEY - STREETS</setting>

<sd>The half-dozen stormtroopers at a check point hear the general 
alarm and look to the sky as the huge starship rises above 
the dingy slum dwellings and quickly disappears into the 
morning sky.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> climbs into the pilot's chair next to Chewbacca, who 
chatters away as he points to something on the radar scope.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - PLANET TATOOINE</setting>

<sd>The Corellian pirateship zooms from Tatooine into space.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> frantically types information into the ship's computer.  
Little <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> appears momentarily at the cockpit doorway, 
makes a few beeping remarks, then scurries away.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - PLANET TATOOINE</setting>

<sd>The Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> pirateship races away from the yellow 
planet, Tatooine. It is followed by two huge <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> 
stardestroyers.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Over the shoulders of Chewbacca and <name type="NORP">Han</name>, we can see the galaxy 
spread before them. Luke and Ben make their way into the 
cramped cockpit where <name type="NORP">Han</name> continues his calculation.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - PLANET TATOOINE</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Imperial</name> cruisers fire at the pirateship.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>The ship shudders as an explosion flashes outside the window.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>The ship begins to rock violently as lasers hit it.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>The ship is now constantly battered with laserfire as a red 
warning light begins to flash.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>The galaxy brightens and they move faster, almost as if 
crashing a barrier. Stars become streaks as the pirateship 
makes the jump to hyperspace.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>The Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> zooms into infinity in less than a 
second.</sd>

<setting>EXT. DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Alderaan</name> looms behind <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> battlestation.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - CONTROL ROOM</setting>

<sd>Admiral Motti enters the quiet control room and bows before 
Governor Tarkin, who stands before the huge wall screen 
displaying a small green planet.</sd>

<speaker>MOTTI</speaker>

<sd>Vader and two stormtroopers enter with Princess Leia. Her 
hands are bound.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<sd>Tarkin waves menacingly toward Leia.</sd>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<sd>Leia overhears an intercom voice announcing the approach to 
<name type="ORG">Alderaan</name>.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<sd>Leia lowers her head.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - BLAST CHAMBER</setting>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<sd>A button is pressed which switches on a panel of lights. A 
hooded <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> soldier reaches overhead and pulls a lever.  
Another lever is pulled. Vader reaches for still another 
lever and a bank of lights on a panel and wall light up. A 
huge beam of light emanates from within a cone-shaped area 
and converges into a single laser beam out toward <name type="ORG">Alderaan</name>. 
The small green planet of <name type="ORG">Alderaan</name> is blown into space dust.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - CENTRAL HOLD AREA</setting>

<sd>Ben watches Luke practice the lightsaber with a small "seeker" 
robot. Ben suddenly turns away and sits down. He falters, 
seems almost faint.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd>Ben rubs his forehead. He seems to drift into a trance. Then 
he fixes his gaze on Luke.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> Solo enters the room.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Luke is once again practicing with the lightsaber.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> watches Chewbacca and <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> who are engrossed in a 
game in which three-dimensional holographic figures move 
along a chess-type board.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Chewbacca and the two robots sit around the lighted table 
covered with small holographic monsters. Each side of the 
table has a small computer monitor embedded in it. Chewbacca 
seems very pleased with himself as he rests his lanky fur- 
covered arms over his head.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> immediately reaches up and taps the computer with his 
stubby claw hand, causing one of the holographic creatures 
to walk to the new square. A sudden frown crosses Chewbacca's 
face and he begins yelling gibberish at the tiny robot. 
<name type="ORG">Threepio</name> intercedes on behalf of his small companion and 
begins to argue with the huge <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name>.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>Luke stands in the middle of the small hold area; he seems 
frozen in place. A humming lightsaber is held high over his 
head. Ben watches him from the corner, studying his movements.  
<name type="NORP">Han</name> watches with a bit of smugness.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd>Suspended at eye level, about ten feet in front of Luke, a 
"seeker", a chrome baseball-like robot covered with antennae, 
hovers slowly in a wide arc. The ball floats to one side of 
the youth then the other. Suddenly it makes a lightning-swift 
lunge and stops within a few feet of Luke's face. Luke doesn't 
move and the ball backs off. It slowly moves behind the boy, 
then makes another quick lunge, this time emitting a blood 
red laser beam as it attacks. It hits Luke in the leg causing 
him to tumble over. <name type="NORP">Han</name> lets loose with a burst of laughter.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Ben smiles quietly.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd>Ben places a large helmet on Luke's head which covers his 
eyes.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> skeptically shakes his head as Ben throws the seeker 
into the air. The ball shoots straight up in the air, then 
drops like a rock. Luke swings the lightsaber around blindly 
missing the seeker, which fires off a laserbolt which hits 
Luke square on the seat of the pants. He lets out a painful 
yell and attempts to hit the seeker.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd>Luke stands in one place, seemingly frozen. The seeker makes 
a dive at Luke and, incredibly, he managed to deflect the 
bolt. The ball ceases fire and moves back to its original 
position.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Solo notices a small light flashing on the far side of the 
control panel.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> and Chewbacca head back to the cockpit.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - CONFERENCE ROOM</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Imperial</name> Officer Cass stands before Governor Tarkin and the 
evil Dark Lord Darth Vader.</sd>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<speaker>OFFICER CASS</speaker>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<setting>EXT. HYPERSPACE</setting>

<sd>The pirateship is just coming out of hyperspace; a strange 
surreal light show surrounds the ship.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> pulls back on a control lever. Outside the cockpit window 
stars begin streaking past, seem to decrease in speed, then 
stop. Suddenly the starship begins to shudder and violently 
shake about. Asteroids begin to race toward them, battering 
the sides of the ship.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>The <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> flips off several controls and seems very cool 
in the emergency. Luke makes his way into the bouncing 
cockpit.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Ben moves into the cockpit behind Luke as the ship begins to 
settle down.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>A signal starts flashing on the control panel and a muffled 
alarm starts humming.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd>Chewbacca barks his concern. A huge explosion bursts outside 
the cockpit window, shaking the ship violently. A tiny, finned 
<name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter races past the cockpit window.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>The fighter races past the Corellian pirateship.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>The pirateship zooms over the camera and away into the 
vastness of space after the <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>The tension mounts as the pirateship gains on the tiny 
fighter. In the distance, one of the stars becomes brighter 
until it is obvious that the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> ship is heading for it. Ben 
stands behind Chewbacca.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter is losing ground to the larger pirateship as 
they race toward camera and disappear over head.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>The distant star can be distinguished as a small moon or 
planet.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>The small moon begins to take on the appearance of a monstrous 
spherical battle station.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>The pirateship shudders and the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter accelerates away 
toward the gargantuan battle station.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Ben <name type="ORG">Kenobi</name> puts a hand on his shoulder.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>As the battered pirate starship is towed closer to the awesome 
metal moon, the immense size of the massive battle station 
becomes staggering. Running along the equator of the gigantic 
sphere is a mile-high band of huge docking ports into which 
the helpless pirateship is dragged.</sd>

<setting>EXT. DEATH STAR - HUGE PORT DOORS</setting>

<sd>The helpless Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> is pulled past a docking port 
control room and huge laser turret cannons.</sd>

<sd>VOICE OVER DEATH STAR INTERCOM</sd>

<sd>Clear Bay twenty-three-seven. We are opening the magnetic 
field.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - DOCKING BAY 2037</setting>

<sd>The pirateship is pulled in through port doors of the Death 
Star, coming to rest in a huge hangar. Thirty stormtroopers 
stand at attention in a central assembly area.</sd>

<speaker>OFFICER</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - HALLWAY</setting>

<sd>Stormtroopers run to their posts.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - HANGAR 2037</setting>

<sd>A line of stormtroopers march toward the pirateship in 
readiness to board it, while other troopers stand with weapons 
ready to fire.</sd>

<speaker>OFFICER</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - CONFERENCE ROOM</setting>

<sd>Tarkin pushes a button and responds to the intercom buzz.</sd>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<speaker>VOICE</speaker>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - DOCKING BAY 2037</setting>

<sd>Vader and a commander approach the troops as an Officer and 
several heavily armed troops exit the spacecraft.</sd>

<speaker>VOICE</speaker>

<speaker>OFFICER</speaker>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<speaker>OFFICER</speaker>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<speaker>OFFICER</speaker>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<sd>Vader turns quickly and exits the hangar.</sd>

<speaker>OFFICER</speaker>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - HALLWAY</setting>

<sd>A trooper runs through the hallway heading for the exit. In 
a few moments all is quiet. The muffled sounds of a distant 
officer giving orders finally fade. Two floor panels suddenly 
pop up revealing <name type="NORP">Han</name> Solo and Luke. Ben <name type="ORG">Kenobi</name> sticks his 
head out of a third locker.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> shakes his head, muttering to himself. Chewbacca agrees.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - MAIN FORWARD BAY</setting>

<sd>The crewmen carry a heavy box on board the ship, past the 
two stormtroopers guarding either side of the ramp.</sd>

<speaker>TROOPER</speaker>

<sd>The crewmen enter the pirateship and a loud crashing sound 
is followed by a voice calling to the guard below.</sd>

<speaker>HAN'S VOICE</speaker>

<sd>The stormtroopers enter the ship and a quick round of gunfire 
is heard.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - FORWARD BAY - COMMAND OFFICE</setting>

<sd>In a very small command office near the entrance to the 
pirateship, a Gantry Officer looks out his window and notices 
the guards are missing. He speaks into the comlink.</sd>

<speaker>GANTRY OFFICER</speaker>

<sd>A stormtrooper comes down the ramp of the pirateship and 
waves to the gantry officer, pointing to his ear indicating 
his comlink is not working. The gantry officer shakes his 
head in disgust and heads for the door, giving his aide an 
annoyed look.</sd>

<speaker>GANTRY OFFICER</speaker>

<sd>As the officer approaches the door, it slides open revealing 
the towering Chewbacca. The gantry officer, in a momentary 
state of shock, stumbles backward. With a bone- chilling 
howl, the giant <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> flattens the officer with one blow. 
The aide immediately reaches for his pistol, but is blasted 
by <name type="NORP">Han</name>, dressed as an <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> stormtrooper. Ben and the 
robots enter the room quickly followed by Luke, also dressed 
as a stormtrooper. Luke quickly removes his helmet.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>Ben feeds some information into the computer and a map of 
the city appears on the monitor. He begins to inspect it 
carefully. <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> and <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> look over the control panel.  
<name type="GPE">Artoo</name> finds something that makes him whistle wildly.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> punches his claw arm into the computer socket and the 
vast <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> brain network comes to life, feeding information 
to the little robot. After a few moments, he beeps something.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>The computer monitor flashes readouts.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>Ben studies the data on the monitor readout.</sd>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd>Ben adjusts the lightsaber on his belt and silently steps 
out of the command office, then disappears down a long grey 
hallway. Chewbacca barks a comment and <name type="NORP">Han</name> shakes his head 
in agreement.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> looks at Luke.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Suddenly <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> begins to whistle and beep a blue streak.  
Luke goes over to him.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> whistles a frantic reply.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Chewbacca growls.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> looks at Chewie, who grunts a short grunt.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke moves toward Chewbacca with electronic cuffs.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Chewie lets out a hideous growl.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke sheepishly hands the binders to <name type="NORP">Han</name>.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>The <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> has a worried and frightened look on his face as 
<name type="NORP">Han</name> binds him with the electronic cuffs.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>Luke and <name type="NORP">Han</name> put on their armored stormtrooper helmets and 
start off into the giant <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> Death Star.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - DETENTION AREA - ELEVATOR TUBE</setting>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> and Luke try to look inconspicuous in their armored suits 
as they wait for a vacuum elevator to arrive. Troops, 
bureaucrats, and robots bustle about, ignoring the trio 
completely. Only a few give the giant <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> a curious 
glance.</sd>

<sd>Finally a small elevator arrives and the trio enters.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>A bureaucrat races to get aboard also, but is signaled away 
by <name type="NORP">Han</name>. The door to the pod-like vehicle slides closed and 
the elevator car takes off through a vacuum tube.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - MAIN HALLWAY</setting>

<sd>Several <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> officers walk through the wide main 
passageway. They pass several stormtroopers and a robot 
similar to <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> but with an insect face. At the far end 
of the hallway, a passing flash of Ben <name type="ORG">Kenobi</name> appears, then 
disappears down a small hallway. His appearance is so fleeting 
that it is hard to tell if he is real or just an illusion. 
No one in the hallway seems to notice him.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - INTERIOR ELEVATOR - DETENTION SECURITY </setting>
AREA

<sd>Luke and <name type="NORP">Han</name> step forward to exit the elevator, but the door 
slides open behind them. The giant <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> and his two guards 
enter the old grey security station. Guards and laser gates 
are everywhere. <name type="NORP">Han</name> whispers to Luke under his breath.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<setting>INT. DETENTION AREA</setting>

<sd>Elevator doors open. A tall, grim looking Officer approaches 
the trio.</sd>

<speaker>OFFICER</speaker>

<sd>Chewie growls a bit at the remark but <name type="NORP">Han</name> nudges him to shut 
up.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>OFFICER</speaker>

<sd>The officer goes back to his console and begins to punch in 
the information. There are only three other troopers in the 
area. Luke and <name type="NORP">Han</name> survey the situation, checking all of the 
alarms, laser gates, and camera eyes. <name type="NORP">Han</name> unfastens one of 
Chewbacca's electronic cuffs and shrugs to Luke.</sd>

<sd>Suddenly Chewbacca throws up his hands and lets out with one 
of his ear-piercing howls. He grabs <name type="NORP">Han</name>'s laser rifle.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>The startled guards are momentarily dumbfounded. Luke and 
<name type="NORP">Han</name> have already pulled out their laser pistols and are 
blasting away at the terrifying <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name>. Their barrage of 
laserfire misses Chewbacca, but hits the camera eyes, laser 
gate controls, and the <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> guards. The officer is the 
last of the guards to fall under the laserfire just as he is 
about to push the alarm system. <name type="NORP">Han</name> rushes to the comlink 
system, which is screeching questions about what is going 
on.  He quickly checks the computer readout.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Luke races down one of the cell corridors. <name type="NORP">Han</name> speaks into 
the buzzing comlink.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

		<setting>INTERCOM VOICE</setting>
		   What happened?

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

		<setting>INTERCOM VOICE</setting>
		   We're sending a squad up.

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

		<setting>INTERCOM VOICE</setting>
		   Who is this? What's your operating 
		   number?

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> blasts the comlink and it explodes.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - CELL ROW</setting>

<sd>Luke stops in front of one of the cells and blasts the door 
away with a laser pistol. When the smoke clears, Luke sees 
the dazzling young princess-senator. She had been sleeping 
and is now looking at him with an uncomprehending look on 
her face. Luke is stunned by her incredible beauty and stands 
staring at her with his mouth hanging open.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<sd>Luke takes off his helmet, coming out of it.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - CONFERENCE ROOM</setting>

<sd>Darth Vader paces the room as Governor Tarkin sits at the 
far end of the conference table.</sd>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<sd>There is a quiet buzz on the comlink.</sd>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

		<setting>INTERCOM VOICE</setting>
		   Governor Tarkin, we have an emergency 
		   alert in detention block A A-twenty-
		   three.

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - DETENTION AREA - HALLWAY</setting>

<sd>An ominous buzzing sound is heard on the other side of the 
elevator door.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Chewbacca responds with a growling noise.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>A series of explosions knock a hole in the elevator door 
through which several <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> troops begin to emerge.</sd>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> and Chewie fire laser pistols at them through the smoke 
and flame. They turn and run down the cell hallway, meeting 
up with Luke and Leia rushing toward them.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Luke takes a small comlink transmitter from his belt as they 
continue to exchange fire with stormtroopers making their 
way down the corridor.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - MAIN BAY GANTRY - CONTROL TOWER</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> paces the control center as little <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps and 
whistles a blue streak. <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> yells into the small comlink 
transmitter.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>Someone begins banging on the door.</sd>

<speaker>TROOPER VOICE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - DETENTION CORRIDOR</setting>

<sd>Luke and Leia crouch together in an alcove for protection as 
they continue to exchange fire with troops. <name type="NORP">Han</name> and Chewbacca 
are barely able to keep the stormtroopers at bay at the far 
and of the hallway. The laserfire is very intense, and smoke 
fills the narrow cell corridor.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Luke manages a sheepish grin and shrugs his shoulders.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>The princess grabs Luke's gun and fires at a small grate in 
the wall next to <name type="NORP">Han</name>, almost frying him.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<sd>She jumps through the narrow opening as <name type="NORP">Han</name> and Chewbacca 
look on in amazement. Chewbacca sniffs the garbage chute and 
says something.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> gives him a kick and the <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> disappears into the 
tiny opening. Luke and <name type="NORP">Han</name> continue firing as they work their 
way toward the opening.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Luke ducks laserfire as he jumps into the darkness. <name type="NORP">Han</name> fires 
off a couple of quick blasts creating a smokey cover, then 
slides into the chute himself and is gone.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - GARBAGE ROOM</setting>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> tumbles into the large room filled with garbage and muck.  
Luke is already stumbling around looking for an exit. He 
finds a small hatchway and struggles to get it open. It won't 
budge.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> draws his laser pistol and fires at the hatch. The 
laserbolt ricochets wildly around the small metal room.  
Everyone dives for cover in the garbage as the bolt explodes 
almost on top of them. Leia climbs out of the garbage with a 
rather grim look on her face.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<sd>A loud, horrible, inhuman moan works its way up from the 
murky depths. Chewbacca lets out a terrified howl and begins 
to back away. <name type="NORP">Han</name> and Luke stand fast with their laser pistols 
drawn. The <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> is cowering near one of the walls.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Suddenly Luke is yanked under the garbage.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Solo tries to get to Luke. Luke surfaces with a gasp of air 
and thrashing of limbs. A membrane tentacle is wrapped around 
his throat.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<sd>Leia extends a long pipe toward him.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Solo fires his gun downward. Luke is pulled back into the 
muck by the slimy tentacle.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Suddenly the walls of the garbage receptacle shudder and 
move in a couple of inches. Then everything is deathly quiet.  
<name type="NORP">Han</name> and Leia give each other a worried look as Chewbacca 
howls in the corner. With a rush of bubbles and muck Luke 
suddenly bobs to the surface.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<sd>Luke seems to be released by the thing.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Before anyone can say anything the walls begin to rumble and 
edge toward the <name type="ORG">Rebels</name>.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<sd>They place poles and long metal beams between the closing 
walls, but they are simply snapped and bent as the giant 
trashmasher rumbles on. The situation doesn't look too good.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke pulls out his comlink.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - MAIN GANTRY - COMMAND OFFICE</setting>

<sd>A soft buzzer and the muted voice of Luke calling out for 
See-<name type="ORG">Threepio</name> can be heard on <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>'s hand comlink, which 
is sitting on the deserted computer console. <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> and 
<name type="ORG">Threepio</name> are nowhere in sight. Suddenly there is a great 
explosion and the door of the control tower flies across the 
floor. Four armed stormtroopers enter the chamber.</sd>

<speaker>FIRST TROOPER</speaker>

<sd>A trooper pushes a button and the supply cabinet door slides 
open. See-<name type="ORG">Threepio</name> and <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>-Detoo are inside. <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> follows 
his bronze companion out into the office.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>FIRST OFFICER</speaker>

<sd>The troops hustle off down the hallway, leaving a guard to 
watch over the command office.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>The guard aims a blaster at them.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>TROOPER</speaker>

<sd>The guard nods and <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, with little <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> in tow, hurries 
out the door.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - GARBAGE ROOM</setting>

<sd>As the walls rumble closed, the room gets smaller and smaller.  
Chewie is whining and trying to hold a wall back with his 
giant paws.</sd>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> is leaning back against the other wall. Garbage is 
snapping and popping. Luke is trying to reach <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> and Leia try to brace the contracting walls with a pole. 
Leia begins to sink into the trash.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - MAIN FORWARD BAY - SERVICE PANEL</setting>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd>Little <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> carefully plugs his claw arm into a new wall 
socket and a complex array of electronic sounds spew from 
the tiny robot.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - GARBAGE ROOM</setting>

<sd>The walls are only feet apart. Leia and <name type="NORP">Han</name> are braced against 
the walls. The princess is frightened. They look at each 
other. Leia reaches out and takes <name type="NORP">Han</name>'s hand and she holds 
it tightly. She's terrified and suddenly groans as she feels 
the first crushing pressure against her body.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - MAIN FORWARD BAY - SERVICE PANEL</setting>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> frantically beeps something to See-<name type="ORG">Threepio</name>.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - GARBAGE ROOM</setting>

<sd>Meanwhile, Luke is lying on his side, trying to keep his 
head above the rising ooze. Luke's comlink begins to buzz 
and he rips it off his belt.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - MAIN FORWARD BAY - SERVICE PANEL</setting>

<sd>Muffled sounds of Luke's voice over the comlink can be heard, 
but not distinctly.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - GARBAGE ROOM</setting>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - MAIN FORWARD BAY - SERVICE PANEL</setting>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - GARBAGE ROOM</setting>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - MAIN FORWARD BAY - SERVICE PANEL</setting>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> holds his head in agony as he hears the incredible 
screaming and hollering from Luke's comlink.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - GARBAGE ROOM</setting>

<sd>The screaming and hollering is the sound of joyous relief. 
The walls have stopped moving. <name type="NORP">Han</name>, Chewie and Leia embrace 
in the background.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke moves to the pressure sensitive hatch, looking for a 
number.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - MAIN FORWARD BAY - SERVICE PANEL</setting>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - TRACTOR BEAM - POWER GENERATOR TRENCH</setting>

<sd>Ben enters a humming service trench that powers the huge 
tractor beam. The trench seems to be a hundred miles deep. 
The clacking sound of huge switching devices can be heard. 
The old <name type="ORG">Jedi</name> edges his his way along a narrow ledge leading 
to a control panel that connects two large cables. He 
carefully makes several adjustments in the computer terminal, 
and several lights on the board go from red to blue.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - UNUSED HALLWAY</setting>

<sd>The group exits the garbage room into a dusty, unused hallway.  
<name type="NORP">Han</name> and Luke remove the trooper suits and strap on the blaster 
belts.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Luke smiles and scratches his head as he takes a blaster 
from Solo.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Chewie begins growling and points to the hatch to the garbage 
room, as he runs away and then stops howling.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>The Dia Nogu bangs against the hatch and a long, slimy 
tentacle works its way out of the doorway searching for a 
victim. <name type="NORP">Han</name> aims his pistol.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> fires at the doorway. The noise of the blast echoes 
relentlessly throughout the empty passageway. Luke simply 
shakes his head in disgust.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Chewie shakes his head "no."</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> is stunned at the command of the petite young girl.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> watches her start away. He looks at Luke.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>They follow her, moving swiftly down the deserted corridor.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - POWER TRENCH</setting>

<sd>Suddenly a door behind Ben slides open and a detachment of 
stormtroopers marches to the power trench. Ben instantly 
slips into the shadows as an Officer moves to within a few 
feet of him.</sd>

<speaker>OFFICER</speaker>

<speaker>FIRST TROOPER</speaker>

<sd>All but two of the stormtroopers leave.</sd>

<speaker>FIRST TROOPER</speaker>

<speaker>SECOND TROOPER</speaker>

<sd>Ben moves around the tractor beam, watching the stormtroopers 
as they turn their backs to him. Ben gestures with his hand 
toward them, as the troops think they hear something in the 
other hallway. With the help of the <name type="ORG">Force</name>, Ben deftly slips 
past the troopers and into the main hallway.</sd>

<speaker>SECOND TROOPER</speaker>

<speaker>FIRST TROOPER</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - HALLWAY</setting>

<sd>Luke, <name type="NORP">Han</name>, Chewbacca, and Leia run down an empty hallway and 
stop before a bay window overlooking the pirateship. Troopers 
are milling about the ship. Luke takes out his pocket comlink.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> is watching the dozen or so troops moving in and out of 
the pirateship. Leia moves towards <name type="NORP">Han</name>, touches his arm and 
points out the window to the ship.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> gives her a dirty look, and they start off down the 
hallway. They round a corner and run right into twenty 
<name type="ORG">Imperial</name> stormtroopers heading toward them. Both groups are 
taken by surprise and stop in their tracks.</sd>

<speaker>FIRST TROOPER</speaker>

<sd>Before even thinking, <name type="NORP">Han</name> draws his laser pistol and charges 
the troops, firing. His blaster knocks one of the 
stormtroopers into the air. Chewie follows his captain down 
the corridor, stepping over the fallen trooper on the floor.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> has already rounded a corner and does not hear.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke is furious but doesn't have time to think about it for 
muted alarms begin to go off down on the hangar deck. Luke 
and Leia start off toward the starship hangar.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - SUBHALLWAY</setting>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> chases the stormtroopers down a long subhallway. He is 
yelling and brandishing his laser pistol. The troops reach a 
dead end and are forced to turn and fight. <name type="NORP">Han</name> stops a few 
feet from them and assumes a defensive position. The troops 
begin to raise their laser guns. Soon all ten troopers are 
moving into an attack position in front of the lone 
starpirate. <name type="NORP">Han</name>'s determined look begins to fade as the troops 
begin to advance. Solo jumps backward as they fire at him.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - SUBHALLWAY</setting>

<sd>Chewbacca runs down the subhallway in a last-ditch attempt 
to save his bold captain. Suddenly he hears the firing of 
laser guns and yelling. Around the corner shoots <name type="NORP">Han</name>, pirate 
extraordinaire, running for his life, followed by a host of 
furious stormtroopers. Chewbacca turns and starts running 
the other way also.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - SUBHALLWAY</setting>

<sd>Luke fires his laser pistol wildly as he and Leia rush down 
a narrow subhallway, chased by several stormtroopers. They 
quickly reach the end of the subhallway and race through an 
open hatchway.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - CENTRAL CORE SHAFT</setting>

<sd>Luke and Leia race through the hatch onto a narrow bridge 
that spans a huge, deep shaft that seems to go into infinity. 
The bridge has been retracted into the wall of the shaft, 
and Luke almost rushes into the abyss. He loses his balance 
off the end of the bridge as Leia, behind him, takes hold of 
his arm and pulls him back.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Blasts from the stormtroopers' laser guns explode nearby 
reminding them of the oncoming danger. Luke fires back at 
the advancing troops. Leia reaches over and hits a switch 
that pops the hatch door shut with a resounding boom, leaving 
them precariously perched on a short piece of bridge overhang.  
Laserfire from the troopers continues to hit the steel door.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<sd>Luke blasts the controls with his laser pistol.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke looks at the blasted bridge control while the 
stormtroopers on the opposite side of the door begin making 
ominous drilling and pounding sounds.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<sd>Luke notices something on his stormtrooper belt, when 
laserfire hits the wall behind him. Luke aims his laser pistol 
at a stormtrooper perched on a higher bridge overhang across 
the abyss from them. They exchange fire. Two more troops 
appear on another overhang, also firing. A trooper is hit, 
and grabs at his chest.</sd>

<sd>Another trooper standing on the bridge overhang is hit by 
Luke's laserfire, and plummets down the shaft. Troopers move 
back off the bridge; Luke hands the gun to Leia.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke pulls a thin nylon cable from his trooper utility belt. 
It has a grappler hook on it. A trooper appears on a bridge 
overhang and fires at Luke and Leia. As Luke works with the 
rope, Leia returns the laser volley. Another trooper appears 
and fires at them, as Leia returns his fire as well.  
Suddenly, the hatch door begins to open, revealing the feet 
of more troops.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<sd>Leia hits one of the stormtroopers on the bridge above, and 
he falls into the abyss. Luke tosses the rope across the 
gorge and it wraps itself around an outcropping of pipes. He 
tugs on the rope to make sure it is secure, then grabs the 
princess in his arms. Leia looks at Luke, then kisses him 
quickly on the lips. Luke is very surprised.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<sd>Luke pushes off and they swing across the treacherous abyss 
to the corresponding hatchway on the opposite side. Just as 
Luke and Leia reach the far side of the canyon, the 
stormtroopers break through the hatch and begin to fire at 
the escaping duo. Luke returns the fire before ducking into 
the tiny subhallway.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - NARROW PASSAGEWAY</setting>

<sd>Ben hides in the shadows of the narrow passageway as several 
stormtroopers rush past him in the main hallway. He checks 
to make sure they're gone, then runs down the hallway in the 
opposite direction. Darth Vader appears at the far end of 
the hallway and starts after the old <name type="ORG">Jedi</name>.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - MAIN FORWARD BAY</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> looks around at the troops milling about the 
pirateship entry ramp.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, plugged into the computer socket, turns his dome left 
and right, beeping a response.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - CORRIDOR - BLAST SHIELDS DOOR</setting>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> and Chewbacca run down a long corridor with several 
troopers hot on their trail.</sd>

<speaker>TROOPER</speaker>

<sd>At the end of the hallway, blast doors begin to close in 
front of them. The young starpilot and his furry companion 
race past the huge doors just as they are closing, and manage 
to get off a couple off laserblasts at the pursuing troops 
before the doors slam shut.</sd>

<speaker>TROOPER</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - HALLWAY LEADING TO MAIN FORWARD BAY</setting>

<sd>Ben hurries along one of the tunnels leading to the hangar 
where the pirateship waits. Just before he reaches the hangar, 
Darth Vader steps into view at the end of the tunnel, not 
ten feet away. Vader lights his saber. Ben also ignites his 
and steps slowly forward.</sd>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<sd>Ben <name type="ORG">Kenobi</name> moves with elegant ease into a classical offensive 
position. The fearsome Dark Knight takes a defensive stance.</sd>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd>The two Galactic warriors stand perfectly still for a few 
moments, sizing each other up and waiting for the right 
moment. Ben seems to be under increasing pressure and strain, 
as if an invisible weight were being placed upon him. He 
shakes his head and, blinking, tries to clear his eyes.</sd>

<sd>Ben makes a sudden lunge at the huge warrior but is checked 
by a lightning movement of The Sith. A masterful slash stroke 
by Vader is blocked by the old <name type="ORG">Jedi</name>. Another of the <name type="ORG">Jedi</name>'s 
blows is blocked, then countered. Ben moves around the Dark 
Lord and starts backing into the massive starship hangar. 
The two powerful warriors stand motionless for a few moments 
with laser swords locked in mid-air, creating a low buzzing 
sound.</sd>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<speaker>BEN</speaker>

<sd>Their lightsabers continue to meet in combat.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - MAIN FORWARD BAY</setting>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> Solo and Chewbacca, their weapons in hand, lean back 
against the wall surveying the forward bay, watching the 
<name type="ORG">Imperial</name> stormtroopers make their rounds of the hangar.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Chewbacca growls a reply, as Luke and the princess join them.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - HALLWAY</setting>

<sd>Vader and Ben <name type="ORG">Kenobi</name> continue their powerful duel. As they 
hit their lightsabers together, lightning flashes on impact. 
Troopers look on in interest as the old <name type="ORG">Jedi</name> and Dark Lord 
of The Sith fight. Suddenly Luke spots the battle from his 
group's vantage point.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke, Leia, <name type="NORP">Han</name>, and Chewie look up and see Ben and Vader 
emerging from the hallways on the far side of the docking 
bay.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - DOCKING BAY</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> and <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>-Detoo are in the center of <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name>'s 
<name type="ORG">Imperial</name> docking bay.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> ducks out of sight as the seven stormtroopers who 
were guarding the starship rush past them heading towards 
Ben and The Sith Knight. He pulls on <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - HALLWAY</setting>

<sd>Solo, Chewie, Luke, and Leia tensely watch the duel. The 
troops rush toward the battling knights.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>They start for the Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>. Ben sees the troops 
charging toward him and realizes that he is trapped. Vader 
takes advantage of Ben's momentary distraction and brings 
his mighty lightsaber down on the old man. Ben manages to 
deflect the blow and swiftly turns around.</sd>

<sd>The old <name type="ORG">Jedi</name> Knight looks over his shoulder at Luke, lifts 
his sword from Vader's then watches his opponent with a serene 
look on his face.</sd>

<sd>Vader brings his sword down, cutting old Ben in half. Ben's 
cloak falls to the floor in two parts, but Ben is not in it.  
Vader is puzzled at Ben's disappearance and pokes at the 
empty cloak. As the guards are distracted, the adventurers 
and the robots reach the starship. Luke sees Ben cut in two 
and starts for him. Aghast, he yells out.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>The stormtroopers turn toward Luke and begin firing at him.  
The robots are already moving up the ramp into the Millennium 
<name type="ORG">Falcon</name>, while Luke, transfixed by anger and awe, returns 
their fire. Solo joins in the laserfire. Vader looks up and 
advances toward them, as one of his troopers is struck down.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Luke fires his pistol at the door control panel, and it 
explodes. The door begins to slide shut. Three troopers charge 
forward firing laser bolts, as the door slides to a close 
behind them, shutting Vader and the other troops out of the 
docking bay. A stormtrooper lies dead at the feet of his 
onrushing compatriots. Luke starts for the advancing troops, 
as Solo and Leia move up the ramp into the pirateship. He 
fires, hitting a stormtrooper, who crumbles to the floor.</sd>

<speaker>BEN'S VOICE</speaker>

<sd>Luke looks around to see where the voice came from. He turns 
toward the pirateship, ducking <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> gunfire from the 
troopers and races into the ship.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> pulls back on the controls and the ship begins to move. 
The dull thud of laser bolts bouncing off the outside of the 
ship as Chewie adjusts his controls.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Chewbacca growls in agreement.</sd>

<setting>EXT. MILLENNIUM FALCON</setting>

<sd>The Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> powers away from <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> docking 
bay, makes a spectacular turn and disappears into the vastness 
of space.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - CENTRAL HOLD AREA</setting>

<sd>Luke, saddened by the loss of Obi-Wan <name type="ORG">Kenobi</name>, stares off 
blankly as the robots look on. Leia puts a blanket around 
him protectively, and Luke turns and looks up at her. She 
sits down beside him.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Solo spots approaching enemy ships.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - CENTRAL HOLD AREA</setting>

<sd>Luke looks downward sadly, shaking his head back and forth, 
as the princess smiles comfortingly at him.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name>-Detoo beeps a reply.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> rushes into the hold area where Luke is sitting with the 
princess.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - GUNPORTS - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Solo climbs into his attack position in the topside gunport.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - HOLD AREA</setting>

<sd>Luke gets up and moves out toward the gunports as Leia heads 
for the cockpit.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - GUNPORTS - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke climbs down the ladder into the gunport cockpit, settling 
into one of the two main laser cannons mounted in large 
rotating turrets on either side of the ship.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - SOLO'S GUNPORT</setting>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> adjusts his headset as he sits before the controls of 
his laser cannon, then speaks into the attached microphone.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - GUNPORTS - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Chewbacca and Princess Leia search the heavens for attacking 
<name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters. The <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> pulls back on the speed controls 
as the ship bounces slightly.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - SOLO'S GUNPORT - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Computer graphic readouts form on Solo's target screen, as 
<name type="NORP">Han</name> reaches for controls.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - GUNPORT - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke sits in readiness for the attack, his hand on the laser 
cannon's control button.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT.</setting>

<sd>Chewbacca spots the enemy ships and barks.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT - POV (POINT OF VIEW) - </setting>
SPACE

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters move towards the Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>, 
one each veering off to the left and right of the pirateship.</sd>

<setting>INT. <name type="ORG">TIE</name> FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>The stars whip past behind the <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> pilot as he adjusts 
his maneuvering joy stick.</sd>

<setting>EXT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - IN SPACE</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter races past the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>, firing laser beams as 
it passes.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - HOLD AREA</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> is seated in the hold area, next to <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>-Detoo. 
The pirateship bounces and vibrates as the power goes out in 
the room and then comes back on.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT - GUNPORTS</setting>

<sd>A <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter maneuvers in front of <name type="NORP">Han</name>, who follows it and 
fires at it with the laser cannon. Luke does likewise, as 
the fighter streaks into view. The ship has suffered a minor 
hit, and bounces slightly.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>Two <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters dive down toward the pirateship.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - GUNPORTS</setting>

<sd>Luke fires at an unseen fighter.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - MILLENNIUM FALCON/<name type="ORG">TIE</name> FIGHTERS</setting>

<sd>Pan with pirateship as two <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters charge through the 
background. Laserbolts streak from all the craft.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - CHEWBACCA</setting>

<sd>The ship shudders as a laserbolt hits very close to the 
cockpit. The <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> chatters something to Leia.</sd>

<setting>EXT. <name type="ORG">TIE</name> FIGHTER - SPACE</setting>

<sd>Full shot of a <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter as it moves fast through the frame, 
firing on the pirate starship.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - <name type="ORG">TIE</name> FIGHTERS</setting>

<sd>The two <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters fire a barrage of laserbeams at the 
pirateship.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - MAIN PASSAGEWAY</setting>

<sd>A laserbolt streaks into the side of the pirateship. The 
ship lurches violently, throwing poor <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> into a cabinet 
fill of small computer chips.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT - GUNPORTS</setting>

<sd>Leia watches the computer readout as Chewbacca manipulates 
the ship's controls.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>An enemy laserbolt hits the pirateship's control panel, 
causing it to blow out in a shower of sparks.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name>-Detoo advances toward the smoking sparking control 
panel, dousing the inferno by spraying it with fire retardant 
beeping all the while.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - GUNPORT</setting>

<sd>Luke swivels in his gun mount, following the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter 
with his laser cannon.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - GUNPORT</setting>

<sd>Solo aims his laser cannon at the enemy fighter.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>A <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter streaks in front of the starship.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Leia watches the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter ship fly over.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>A <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter heads right for the pirateship, then zooms 
overhead.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - GUNPORTS</setting>

<sd>Luke follows the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter across his field of view, firing 
laserbeams from his cannon.</sd>

<setting>EXT. <name type="ORG">TIE</name> FIGHTER</setting>

<sd>A <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter dives past the pirateship.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - GUNPORTS</setting>

<sd>Luke fires at a <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter. At his port, <name type="NORP">Han</name> follows a 
fighter in his sights, releasing a blast of laserfire. He 
connects, and the fighter explodes into fiery dust. <name type="NORP">Han</name> laughs 
victoriously.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>Two <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters move toward and over the Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>, 
unleashing a barrage of laserbolts at the ship.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - GUNPORTS</setting>

<sd>Another <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter moves in on the pirateship and Luke, 
smiling, fires the laser cannon at it, scoring a spectacular 
direct hit.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> turns and gives Luke a victory wave which Luke gleefully 
returns.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> turns back to his laser cannon.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>Two more <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters cross in front of the pirateship.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>While Chewbacca manipulates the controls, Leia turns, looking 
over her shoulder out the ports.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>A <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter moves up over the pirateship, firing laserblasts 
at it.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - GUNPORTS</setting>

<sd>Luke and <name type="NORP">Han</name> look into their respective projected target 
screens. An <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> fighter crosses Solo's port, and <name type="NORP">Han</name> 
swivels in his chair, following it with blasts from his laser 
cannon. Another fighter crosses Luke's port, and he reacts 
in a like manner, the glow of his target screen lighting his 
face.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter zooms toward the pirateship, firing 
destructive blasts at it.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - GUNPORTS</setting>

<sd>Luke fires a laserblast at the approaching enemy fighter, 
and it bursts into a spectacular explosion. Luke's projected 
screen gives a readout of the hit. The pirateship bounces 
slightly as it is struck by the enemy fire.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - <name type="ORG">TIE</name> FIGHTER</setting>

<sd>The last of the attacking <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters looms in, 
firing upon the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - GUNPORT</setting>

<sd>Solo swivels behind his cannon, his aim describing the arc 
of the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter. The fighter comes closer, firing at the 
pirateship, but a well-aimed blast from Solo's laser cannon 
hits the attacker, which blows up in a small atomic shower 
of burning fragments.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>The princess jumps up and gives Chewie a congratulatory hug.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - PASSAGEWAY</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> lies on the floor of the ship, completely tangled 
in the smoking, sparking wires.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> turns his dome from side to side, beeping in response.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - MILLENNIUM FALCON</setting>

<sd>The victorious Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> moves off majestically 
through space.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - CONTROL ROOM</setting>

<sd>Darth Vader strides into the control room, where Tarkin is 
watching the huge view screen. A sea of stars is before him.</sd>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name>, removes his gloves and smiling, is at the controls of 
the ship. Chewie moves into the aft section to check the 
damage. Leia is seated near <name type="NORP">Han</name>.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Frustrated, Leia shakes her head.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<sd>She angrily turns, and as she starts out of the cockpit, 
passes Luke coming in.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke, shaking his head, sits in the copilot seat. He and <name type="NORP">Han</name> 
stare out at the vast blackness of space.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke says it with finality and looks away. <name type="NORP">Han</name> smiles at 
young Luke's jealousy.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND FOURTH MOON OF YAVIN</setting>

<sd>The battered pirateship drifts into orbit around the planet 
Yavin and proceeds to one of its tiny green moons.</sd>

<setting>EXT. FOURTH MOON OF YAVIN</setting>

<sd>The pirateship soars over the dense jungle.</sd>

<setting>EXT. MASSASSI OUTPOST</setting>

<sd>An alert guard, his laser gun in hand, scans the countryside.  
He sets the gun down and looks toward the temple, barely 
visible in the foliage.</sd>

<setting>EXT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - JUNGLE TEMPLE</setting>

<sd>Rotting in a forest of gargantuan trees, an ancient temple 
lies shrouded in an eerie mist. The air is heavy with the 
fantastic cries of unimaginable creatures. <name type="NORP">Han</name>, Luke and the 
others are greeted by the Rebel troops.</sd>

<sd>Luke and the group ride into the massive temple on an armored 
military speeder.</sd>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI - MAIN HANGAR DECK</setting>

<sd>The military speeder stops in a huge spaceship hangar, set 
up in the interior of the crumbling temple. Willard, the 
commander of the Rebel forces, rushes up to the group and 
gives Leia a big hug. Every one is pleased to see her.</sd>

<speaker>WILLARD</speaker>

<sd>Willard composes himself, steps back and bows formally.</sd>

<speaker>WILLARD</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>The surface of <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> ominously approaches the red 
planet Yavin.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - CONTROL ROOM</setting>

<sd>Grand Moff Tarkin and Lord Vader are interrupted in their 
discussion by the buzz of the comlink. Tarkin moves to answer 
the call.</sd>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<sd>DEATH STAR INTERCOM VOICE</sd>

<sd>We are approaching the planet Yavin. The Rebel base is on a 
moon on the far side. We are preparing to orbit the planet.</sd>

<setting>EXT. YAVIN - JUNGLE</setting>

<sd>A lone guard stands in a tower high above the Yavin landscape, 
surveying the countryside. A mist hangs over the jungle of 
twisted green.</sd>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI - WAR ROOM BRIEFING AREA</setting>

<sd>Dodonna stands before a large electronic wall display. Leia 
and several other senators are to one side of the giant 
readout. The low-ceilinged room is filled with starpilots, 
navigators, and a sprinkling of R2-type robots. Everyone is 
listening intently to what Dodonna is saying. <name type="NORP">Han</name> and 
Chewbacca are standing near the back.</sd>

<speaker>DODONNA</speaker>

<sd><name type="ORG">Gold Leader</name>, a rough looking man in his early thirties, stands 
and addresses Dodonna.</sd>

<speaker>GOLD LEADER</speaker>

<speaker>DODONNA</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name>-Detoo stands next to a similar robot, makes beeping 
sounds, and turns his head from right to left.</sd>

<speaker>DODONNA</speaker>

<sd>A murmer of disbelief runs through the room.</sd>

<speaker>DODONNA</speaker>

<sd>Luke is sitting next to Wedge <name type="GPE">Antilles</name>, a hotshot pilot about 
sixteen years old.</sd>

<speaker>WEDGE</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>DODONNA</speaker>

<sd>The group rises and begins to leave.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>The Death Star begins to move around the planet toward the 
tiny green moon.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Tarkin and Vader watch the computer projected screen with 
interest, as a circle of lights intertwines around one another 
on the screen showing it's position in relation to Yavin and 
the forth moon.</sd>

<sd>DEATH STAR INTERCOM VOICE</sd>

<sd>Orbiting the planet at maximum velocity. The moon with the 
Rebel base will be in range in thirty minutes.</sd>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - MAIN HANGAR DECK</setting>

<sd>Luke, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> and little <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> enter the huge spaceship 
hangar and hurry along a long line of gleaming spacefighters.  
Flight crews rush around loading last-minute armaments and 
unlocking power couplings. In an area isolated from this 
activity Luke finds <name type="NORP">Han</name> and Chewbacca loading small boxes 
onto an armored speeder.</sd>

<speaker>MAN'S VOICE</speaker>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> is deliberately ignoring the activity of the fighter 
pilots' preparation. Luke is quite saddened at the sight of 
his friend's departure.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Luke goes off and <name type="NORP">Han</name> hesitates, then calls to him.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Luke turns and sees <name type="NORP">Han</name> wink at him. Luke lifts his hand in 
a small wave and then goes off.</sd>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> turns to Chewie who growls at his captain,</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<setting>INT. MAIN HANGAR DECK - LUKE'S SHIP</setting>

<sd>Luke, Leia, and Dodonna meet under a huge space fighter.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>Leia gives Luke a little kiss, turns, and goes off. As Luke 
heads for his ship, another pilot rushes up to him and grabs 
his arm.</sd>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd><name type="ORG">Red Leader</name>, a rugged handsome man in his forties, comes up 
behind Luke and Biggs. He has the confident smile of a born 
leader.</sd>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<sd><name type="ORG">Red Leader</name> pats Luke on the back as they stop in front of 
his fighter.</sd>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd><name type="ORG">Red Leader</name> hurries to his own ship.</sd>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<sd>Luke laughs and shakes his head in agreement. He heads for 
his ship.</sd>

<sd>As Luke begins to climb up the ladder into his sleek, deadly 
spaceship, the crew chief, who is working on the craft, points 
to little <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, who is being hoisted into a socket on the 
back of the fighter.</sd>

<speaker>CHIEF</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>The crewmen lower <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>-Detoo into the craft. Now a part of 
the exterior shell of the starship, the little droid beeps 
that he is fine.</sd>

<sd>Luke climbs up into the cockpit of his fighter and puts an 
his helmet. <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> looks on from the floor of the massive 
hangar as the crewmen secure his little electronic partner 
into Luke's X-wing. It's an emotional-filled moment as <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> 
beeps good-bye.</sd>

<speaker>CHIEF</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps in agreement.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> whistles his reply.</sd>

<sd>All final preparations are made for the approaching battle.  
The hangar is buzzing with the last minute activity as the 
pilots and crewmen alike make their final adjustments. The 
hum of activity is occasionally trespassed by the distorted 
voice of the loudspeaker issuing commands. Coupling hoses 
are disconnected from the ships as they are fueled. Cockpit 
shields roll smoothly into place over each pilot. A signalman, 
holding red guiding lights, directs the ships. Luke, a trace 
of a smile gracing his lips, peers about through his goggles.</sd>

<speaker>BEN'S VOICE</speaker>

<sd>Luke is confused at the voice and taps his headphones.</sd>

<setting>EXT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - JUNGLE</setting>

<sd>All that can be seen of the fortress is a lone guard standing 
on a small pedestal jutting out above the dense jungle. The 
muted gruesome crying sounds that naturally permeate this 
eerie purgatory are overwhelmed by the thundering din of ion 
rockets as four silver starships catapult from the foliage 
in a tight formation and disappears into the morning cloud 
cover.</sd>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - WAR ROOM</setting>

<sd>The princess, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, and a field commander sit quietly 
before the giant display showing the planet Yavin and its 
four moons. The red dot that represents <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> moves 
ever closer to the system. A series of green dots appear 
around the fourth moon. A din of indistinct chatter fills 
the war room.</sd>

<speaker>MASSASSI INTERCOM VOICE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>The Death Star slowly moves behind the massive yellow surface 
of Yavin in the foreground, as many X-wing fighters flying 
in formation zoom toward us and out of the frame.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - ANOTHER ANGLE</setting>

<sd>Light from a distant sun creates an eerie atmospheric glow 
around a huge planet, Yavin. Rebel fighters flying in 
formation settle ominously in the foreground and very slowly 
pull away.</sd>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER STARSHIP - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Red Leader</name> lowers his visor and adjusts his gun sights, 
looking to each side at his wing men.</sd>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. ANOTHER COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>One of the Rebel fighters checks in through his mike.</sd>

<speaker>RED TEN</speaker>

<setting>INT. BIGGS' COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Biggs checks his fighter's controls, alert and ready for 
combat.</sd>

<speaker>RED SEVEN</speaker>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<setting>INT. PORKINS' COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>PORKINS</speaker>

<speaker>RED NINE</speaker>

<setting>INT. WEDGE'S FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>WEDGE</speaker>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>RED ELEVEN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER</setting>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name>-Detoo, in position outside of the fighter, turns his 
head from side to side and makes beeping sounds.</sd>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER'S FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>The group of X-wing fighters move in formation toward the 
Death Star, unfolding the wings and locking them in the "X" 
position.</sd>

<setting>INT. BIGGS' COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>READ LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke adjusts his controls as he concentrates on the 
approaching Death Star. The ship begins to be buffeted 
slightly.</sd>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. ANOTHER COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>The fighters, now X-shaped darts, move in formation. The 
Death Star now appears to be a small moon growing rapidly in 
size as the Rebel fighters approach. Complex patterns on the 
metallic surface begin to become visible. A large dish antenna 
is built into the surface on one side.</sd>

<setting>INT. WEDGE'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Wedge is amazed and slightly frightened at the awesome 
spectacle.</sd>

<speaker>WEDGE</speaker>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>As the fighters move closer to <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name>, the awesome 
size of the gargantuan <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> fortress is revealed. Half 
of the deadly space station is in shadow and this area 
sparkles with thousands of small lights running in thin lines 
and occasionally grouped in large clusters; somewhat like a 
city at night as seen from a weather satellite.</sd>

<setting>INT. GOLD LEADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>GOLD LEADER</speaker>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<speaker>GOLD LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Red Leader</name> looks around at his wingmen; <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> looming 
in from behind. Two Y-wing fighters bob back and forth in 
the background. He moves his computer targeting device into 
position.</sd>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>Two squads of Rebel fighters peel off. The X-wings dive 
towards <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> surface. A thousand lights glow across 
the dark grey expanse of the huge station.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Alarm sirens scream as soldiers scramble to large turbo- 
powered laser gun emplacements. Electronic drivers rotate 
the huge guns into position as crew adjust their targeting 
devices.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Laserbolts streak through the star-filled night. The Rebel X-
wing fighters move in toward the <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> base, as the Death 
Star aims its massive laser guns at the Rebel forces and 
fires.</sd>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - WAR ROOM</setting>

<sd>Princess Leia listens to the battle over the intercom.  
<name type="ORG">Threepio</name> is at her side.</sd>

<speaker>WEDGE</speaker>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>An X-wing zooms across the surface of <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name>.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Technical crews scurry here and there loading last-minute 
armaments and unlocking power cables.</sd>

<setting>INT. WEDGE'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Wedge maneuvers his fighter toward the menacing Death Star.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>X-wings continue in their attack course on <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name>.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke nosedives radically, starting his attack on the monstrous 
fortress. The Death Star surface streaks past the cockpit 
window.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>Luke's X-wing races toward <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name>. Laserbolts streak 
from Luke's weapons, creating a huge fireball explosion on 
the dim surface.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Terror crosses Luke's face as he realizes he won't be able 
to pull out in time to avoid the fireball.</sd>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Luke's ship emerges from the fireball, with the leading edges 
of his wings slightly scorched.</sd>

<setting>INT. BIGGS' COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke adjusts his controls and breathes a sigh of relief. 
Flak bursts outside the cockpit window.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Rebel fighters continue to strafe <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name>'s surface 
with laserbolts.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Walls buckle and cave in. Troops and equipment are blown in 
all directions. Stormtroopers stagger out of the rubble.  
Standing in the middle of the chaos, a vision of calm and 
foreboding, is Darth Vader. One of his <name type="ORG">Astro</name>-Officers rushes 
up to him.</sd>

<speaker>ASTRO-OFFICER</speaker>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Smoke belches from the giant laser guns as they wind up their 
turbine generators to create sufficient power. The crew rushes 
about preparing for another blast. Even the troopers head 
gear is not adequate to protect them from the overwhelming 
noise of the monstrous weapon. One troopers bangs his helmet 
with his hand in an attempt to stop the ringing.</sd>

<setting>INT. READ LEADER'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT - TRAVELING</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Red Leader</name> flies through a heavy hail of flak.</sd>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING - COCKPIT - TRAVELING</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Red Leader</name>'s X-wing flies past Luke as he puts his nose 
down and starts his attack dive.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Luke flings his X-wing into a twisting dive across the horizon 
and down onto the dim grey surface.</sd>

<setting>EXT. LUKE'S X-WING TRAVELING</setting>

<sd>A shot hurls from Luke's guns. Laserbolts streak toward the 
onrushing Death Star surface. Several small radar emplacements 
erupt in flame. Laserfire erupts from a protruding tower on 
the surface.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING - COCKPIT - TRAVELING</setting>

<sd>The blurry Death Star surface races past the cockpit window 
as a big smile sweeps across Luke's face at the success of 
his run. Flak thunders on all sides of him.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>The Death Star superstructure races past Luke as he maneuvers 
his craft through a wall of laserfire and peels away from 
the surface towards the heavens.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>The thunder and smoke of the big guns reverberate throughout 
the massive structure. Many soldiers rush about in the smoke 
and chaos, silhouetted by the almost continual flash of 
explosions.</sd>

<setting>INT. BIGGS' COCKPIT - TRAVELING</setting>

<sd>Biggs dives through a forest of radar domes, antennae, and 
gun towers as he shoots low across <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> surface. A 
dense barrage of laserfire streaks by on all sides.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Imperial</name> star pilots dash in unison to a line of small 
auxiliary hatches that lead to <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters.</sd>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - WAR ROOM</setting>

<sd>Princess Leia, surrounded by her generals and aides, paces 
nervously before a lighted computer table. On all sides 
technicians work in front of many lighted glass walls. Dodonna 
watches quietly from one corner. One of the officers working 
over a screen speaks into his headset.</sd>

<speaker>CONTROL OFFICER</speaker>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING - COCKPIT - TRAVELING</setting>

<sd>Luke looks around to see if he can spot the approaching 
<name type="ORG">Imperial</name> fighters.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER'S X-WING - COCKPIT - TRAVELING</setting>

<sd>The Death Star's surface sweeps past as <name type="ORG">Red Leader</name> searches 
the sky for the <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> fighters. Flak pounds at his ship.</sd>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Silhouetted against the rim lights of <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> horizon, 
four ferocious <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">TIE</name> ships dive on the Rebel fighters.  
Two of the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters peel off and drop out of frame. Pan 
with the remaining two <name type="ORG">TIE</name> ships.</sd>

<setting>INT. BIGGS' COCKPIT - TRAVELING</setting>

<sd>Biggs panics when he discovers a <name type="ORG">TIE</name> ship on his tail. The 
horizon in the background twists around as he peels off, 
hoping to lose the <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> fighter.</sd>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Biggs zooms off the surface and into space, closely followed 
by an <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter. The <name type="ORG">TIE</name> ship fires several 
laserbolts at Biggs, but misses.</sd>

<setting>INT. BIGGS' COCKPIT - TRAVELING</setting>

<sd>Biggs see the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> ship behind him and swings around, trying 
to avoid him.</sd>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Biggs, flying at high altitude, peels off and dives toward 
<name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> surface, but he is unable to lose the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> 
fighter, who sticks close to his tail.</sd>

<setting>INT. X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT - TRAVELING</setting>

<sd>Luke is flying upside down. He rotates his ship around to 
normal attitude as he comes out of his dive.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Biggs and the tailing <name type="ORG">TIE</name> ship dive for the surface, now 
followed by a fast-gaining Luke. After Biggs dives out of 
sight, Luke chases the <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> fighter.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>In the foreground, the <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> fighter races across the 
Death Star's surface, closely followed by Luke in the 
background.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT - TRAVELING</setting>

<sd>There is a shot from Luke's X-wing of the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> ship exploding 
in a mass of flames.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Darth Vader strides purposefully down a Death Star corridor, 
flanked by <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> stormtroopers.</sd>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - WAR ROOM</setting>

<sd>A concerned Princess Leia, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, Dodonna, and other 
officers of the Rebellion stand around the huge round readout 
screen, listening to the ship-to-ship communication on the 
room's loudspeaker.</sd>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<speaker>WEDGE</speaker>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>WEDGE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>Luke's ship soars away from <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name>'s surface as he 
spots the tailing <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter.</sd>

<setting>INT. <name type="ORG">TIE</name> FIGHTER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">TIE</name> pilot takes aim at Luke's X-wing.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter pilot scores a hit on Luke's ship.  
Fire breaks out on the right side of the X-wing.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke looks out of his cockpit at the flames on his ship.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER</setting>

<sd>Smoke pours out from behind <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>-Detoo.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE'S VOICE</speaker>

<sd>Green laserfire moves past the beeping little robot as his 
head turns.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke nervously works his controls.</sd>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - WAR ROOM</setting>

<sd>In the war room, Leia stands frozen as she listens and worries 
about Luke.</sd>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<speaker>RED TEN</speaker>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke spots the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter behind him and soars away from 
<name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> surface.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Luke's ship soars closer to the surface of <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name>, 
an <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter closing in on him in hot pursuit.</sd>

<setting>INT. WEDGE'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>The Death Star whips below Wedge.</sd>

<speaker>WEDGE</speaker>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>WEDGE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Wedge dives across the horizon toward Luke and the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> 
fighter.</sd>

<setting>INT. WEDGE'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Wedge moves his X-wing in rapidly.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke reacts frantically.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. <name type="ORG">TIE</name> FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>The fighter pilot watches Wedge's X-wing approach. Another X-
wing joins him, and both unleash a volley of laserfire on 
the <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> fighter.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter explodes, filling the screen with white light.  
Luke's ship can be seen far in the distance.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke looks about in relief.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - WAR ROOM</setting>

<sd>Leia, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, Dodonna and other Rebel officers are listening 
to the Rebel Fighter's radio transmissions over the war room 
intercom.</sd>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<speaker>GOLD LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. GOLD LEADER'S Y-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Gold Leader</name> peels off and starts toward the long trenches at 
<name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> surface pole.</sd>

<speaker>GOLD LEADER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Three Y-wing fighters of the Gold group dive out of the stars 
toward <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> surface.</sd>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - WAR ROOM</setting>

<sd>Leia and the others are grouped around the screen, as 
technicians move about attending to their duties.</sd>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Three <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">TIE</name> ships in precise formation dive toward 
<name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> surface.</sd>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Darth Vader calmly adjusts his control stick as the stars 
whip past in the window above his head.</sd>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - WAR ROOM</setting>

<sd>Technicians are seated at the computer readout table.</sd>

<speaker>GOLD LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. GOLD LEADER'S Y-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>GOLD LEADER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Gold Leader</name> approaches the surface and pulls out to skim the 
surface of the huge station. The ship moves into a deep 
trench, firing laserbolts. The surface streaks past as 
laserfire is returned by <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name>.</sd>

<setting>INT. GOLD FIVE'S Y-WING - COCKPIT - TRAVELING</setting>

<sd>Gold Five is a pilot in his early fifties with a very battered 
helmet that looks like it's been through many battles. He 
looks around to see if enemy ships are near. His fighter is 
buffeted by <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> flak.</sd>

<setting>INT. GOLD LEADER'S Y-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Gold Leader</name> races down the enormous trench that leads to the 
exhaust port. Laserbolts blast toward him in increasing 
numbers, occasionally exploding near the ship causing it to 
bounce about.</sd>

<speaker>GOLD LEADER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Three Y-wing skim <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> surface deep in the trench, 
as laserbolts streak past on all sides.</sd>

<setting>EXT. DEATH STAR SURFACE - GUN EMPLACEMENTS</setting>

<sd>An exterior surface gun blazes away at the oncoming Rebel 
fighters.</sd>

<setting>INT. GOLD LEADER'S Y-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>GOLD LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - WAR ROOM</setting>

<speaker>GOLD FIVE</speaker>

<sd>Leia, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, and the technicians view the projected target 
screen, as red and blue target lights glow. The red target 
near the center blinks on and off.</sd>

<speaker>MASSASSI INTERCOM VOICE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>The three Y-wing fighters race toward camera and zoom overhead 
through a hail of laserfire.</sd>

<setting>INT. GOLD LEADER'S Y-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Gold Leader</name> pulls his computer targeting device down in front 
of his eye. Laserbolts continue to batter the Rebel craft.</sd>

<speaker>GOLD LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. GOLD TWO'S Y-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Gold Two, a younger pilot about Luke's age, pulls down his 
targeting eye viewer and adjusts it. His ship shudders under 
intense laser barrage.</sd>

<speaker>GOLD TWO</speaker>

<sd>As the fighters begin to approach the target area, suddenly 
all the laserfire stops. An eerie clam clings over the trench 
as the surface whips past in a blur.</sd>

<speaker>GOLD TWO</speaker>

<setting>EXT. GOLD FIVE'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Gold Five looks behind him.</sd>

<speaker>GOLD FIVE</speaker>

<setting>INT. GOLD LEADER'S Y-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>GOLD LEADER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Three <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">TIE</name> ships, Darth Vader in the center flanked 
by two wingmen, dive in precise formation almost vertically 
toward <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> surface.</sd>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Darth Vader calmly adjusts his control stick as the stars 
zoom by.</sd>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<speaker>WINGMAN'S VOICE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Three <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters zoom across the surface of <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name>.</sd>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Vader lines up Gold Two in his targeting computer. Vader's 
hands grip the control stick as he presses the button.</sd>

<setting>INT. GOLD LEADER'S Y-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>The cockpit explodes around Gold Two. His head falls forward.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>As Gold Two's ship explodes, debris is flung out into space.</sd>

<setting>INT. GOLD LEADER'S Y-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Gold Leader</name> looks over his shoulder at the scene.</sd>

<setting>EXT. DEATH STAR TRENCH</setting>

<sd>The three <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters race along in the trench in a tight 
formation.</sd>

<setting>INT. GOLD LEADER'S Y-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Gold Leader</name> panics.</sd>

<speaker>GOLD LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. GOLD FIVE'S Y-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Gold Five, the old veteran, trys to calm <name type="ORG">Gold Leader</name>.</sd>

<speaker>GOLD FIVE</speaker>

<setting>INT. GOLD LEADER'S Y-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>The Death Star races by outside the cockpit window as he 
adjusts his targeting device.</sd>

<speaker>GOLD LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. GOLD FIVE'S Y-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>The older pilot remains calm.</sd>

<speaker>GOLD FIVE</speaker>

<setting>INT. GOLD LEADER'S Y-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Now he's really panicked.</sd>

<speaker>GOLD LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Vader calmly adjusts his targeting computer and pushes the 
fire button.</sd>

<setting>INT. GOLD LEADER'S Y-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Gold Leader</name>'s ship is hit by Vader's laser.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Gold Leader</name> explodes in a ball of flames, throwing debris in 
all directions.</sd>

<setting>INT. GOLD FIVE'S Y-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Gold Five moves in on the exhaust port.</sd>

<speaker>GOLD FIVE</speaker>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke looks over his shoulder at the action outside of his 
cockpit.</sd>

<speaker>GOLD FIVE</speaker>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. GOLD FIVE'S Y-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>GOLD FIVE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>One of the engines explodes on Gold Five's Y-wing fighter, 
blazing out of control. He dives past the horizon toward the 
Death Star's surface, passing a <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter during his 
descent. Gold Five, a veteran of countless campaigns, spins 
toward his death.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke looks nervously about him at the explosive battle.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - CONTROL ROOM</setting>

<sd>Grant Moff Tarkin and a Chief Officer stand in the Death 
Star's control room.</sd>

<speaker>OFFICER</speaker>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<sd>Tarkin turns to the computer readout screen. Flames move 
around the green disk at the center of the screen, as numbers 
read across the bottom.</sd>

<speaker>VOICE</speaker>

<setting>INT. READ LEADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Red Leader</name> looks over at his wingmen.</sd>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - WAR ROOM</setting>

<sd>Dodonna moves to the intercom as he fiddles with the computer 
keys.</sd>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<speaker>WEDGE</speaker>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>DODONNA</speaker>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>RED LEADER'S VOICE</speaker>

<sd>Luke nods his head.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>The X-wing fighters of Luke, Biggs, and Wedge fly in formation 
high above <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name>'s surface.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke peers out from his cockpit.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Two X-wings move across the surface of <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name>. Red 
Leader's X-wing drops down to the surface leading to the 
exhaust port.</sd>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Red Leader</name> looks around to watch for the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters. He 
begins to perspire.</sd>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Red Leader</name> roams down the trench of <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> as lasers 
streak across the black heavens.</sd>

<setting>EXT. DEATH STAR SURFACE - GUN EMPLACEMENTS</setting>

<sd>A huge remote-control laser cannon fires at the approaching 
Rebel fighters.</sd>

<setting>EXT. DEATH STAR TRENCH</setting>

<sd>The Rebel fighters evade the <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> laser blasts.</sd>

<setting>INT. RED TEN'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Red Ten looks around for the <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> fighters.</sd>

<speaker>RED TEN</speaker>

<setting>EXT. DEATH STAR TRENCH</setting>

<sd>From the cockpits of the Rebel pilots, the surface of the 
Death Star streaks by, with <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> laserfire shooting toward 
them.</sd>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. RED TEN'S COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>RED TEN</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - DEATH STAR TRENCH</setting>

<sd>Three X-wing fighters move in formation down <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> 
trench.</sd>

<speaker>RED TEN'S VOICE</speaker>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke looks down at <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> surface below.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. RED TEN'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Red Ten looks up and sees the <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> fighters.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>RED TEN</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Three <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters, Vader flanked by two wingmen, dive in a 
tight formation. The sun reflects off their dominate solar 
fins as they loop toward <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name>'s surface.</sd>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Red Leader</name> pulls his targeting device in front of his eyes 
and makes several adjustments.</sd>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Red Leader</name>'s X-wing moves up <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> trench.</sd>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<sd><name type="ORG">Red Leader</name> looks at his computer target readout screen. He 
then looks into his targeting device.</sd>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Vader adjusts his control lever and dives on the X-wing 
fighters.</sd>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. DEATH STAR TRENCH</setting>

<sd>The three <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters move in formation across the Death 
Star surface.</sd>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Red Leader</name> lines up his target on the targeting device cross 
hairs.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Vader and his wingmen zoom down the trench.</sd>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Vader rapidly approaches the two X-wings of Red Ten and Red 
Twelve. Vader's laser cannon flashes below the view of the 
front porthole. the X-wings show in the center of Vader's 
computer screen.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>Red Twelve's X-wing fighter is hit by Vader's laserfire, and 
it explodes into flames against the trench.</sd>

<setting>INT. RED TEN'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Red Ten works at his controls furiously, trying to avoid 
Vader's fighter behind him.</sd>

<sd>RED TEN: You'd better let her loose.</sd>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Red Leader</name> is concentrating on his targeting device.</sd>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. RED TEN'S COCKPIT.</setting>

<sd>Red Ten panics.</sd>

<speaker>RED TEN</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Vader and his wingmen whip through the trench in pursuit of 
the Rebel fighters.</sd>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Vader cooly pushes the fire button on his control stick.</sd>

<setting>INT. RED TEN'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Darth Vader's well-aimed laserfire proves to be unavoidable, 
and strikes Red Ten's ship. Red Ten screams in anguish and 
pain.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Red Ten's ship explodes and bursts into flames.</sd>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Grimly, <name type="ORG">Red Leader</name> takes careful aim and watches his computer 
targeting device, which shows the target lined up in the 
cross hairs, and fires.</sd>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>An armed <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> stormtrooper is knocked to the floor from 
the attack explosion. Other troopers scurrying about the 
corridors are knocked against the wall and lose their balance.</sd>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - WAR ROOM</setting>

<sd>Leia and the others stare at the computer screen.</sd>

<speaker>RED NINE'S VOICE</speaker>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Red Leader</name> looks back at the receding Death Star. Tiny 
explosions are visible in the distance.</sd>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR - <name type="ORG">TIE</name> FIGHTER</setting>

<sd>Darth Vader peels off in pursuit as <name type="ORG">Red Leader</name>'s X-wing passes 
<name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> horizon.</sd>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Vader swings his ship around for the next kill.</sd>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke tries to spot <name type="ORG">Red Leader</name>. He looks down at the Death 
Star surface.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>A wary <name type="ORG">Red Leader</name> looks about nervously.</sd>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke looks excitedly toward <name type="ORG">Red Leader</name>'s X-wing.</sd>

<speaker>RED LEADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Vader's gloved hands make contact with the control sticks, 
and he presses their firing buttons.</sd>

<setting>INT. RED LEADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Red Leader</name> fights to gain control of his ship.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Laserbolts are flung from Vader's <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter, connecting 
with <name type="ORG">Red Leader</name>'s Rebel X-wing fighter. <name type="ORG">Red Leader</name> buys it, 
creating a tremendous explosion far below. He screams and is 
destroyed.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke looks out the window of his X-wing at the explosion far 
below. For the first time, he feels the helplessness of his 
situation.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Grand Moff Tarkin casts a sinister eye at the computer screen.</sd>

<speaker>DEATH STAR INTERCOM VOICE</speaker>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - WAR ROOM</setting>

<sd>Dodonna and Princess Leia, with <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> beside them, listen 
intently to the talk between the pilots. The room is grim 
after <name type="ORG">Red Leader</name>'s death. Princess Leia nervously paces the 
room.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. WEDGE'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>The horizon twists as Wedge begins to pull out.</sd>

<speaker>WEDGE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>The two X-wings peel off against a background of stars and 
dive toward <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name>.</sd>

<setting>INT. BIGGS' COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>The three X-wings move in, unleashing a barrage of laserfire.  
Laserbolts are returned from <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name>.</sd>

<setting>INT. BIGGS' COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke's lifelong friend struggles with his controls.</sd>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Flak and laserbolts flash outside Luke's cockpit window.</sd>

<speaker>WEDGE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. DEATH STAR - GUN EMPLACEMENTS</setting>

<sd>The Death Star laser cannon slowly rotates as it shoots 
laserbolts.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke looks around for the <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters. He thinks 
for a moment and then moves his targeting device into 
position.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. WEDGE'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Wedge looks excitedly about for any sign of the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters.</sd>

<speaker>WEDGE</speaker>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. DEATH STAR SURFACE</setting>

<sd>Luke's X-wing streaks through the trench, firing lasers.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke breaks into a nervous sweat as the laserfire is returned, 
knicking one of his wings close to the engine.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER</setting>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> works to repair the damages. The canyon wall rushes by 
in the background, making his delicate task seem even more 
precarious.</sd>

<setting>EXT. DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Two laser cannons are firing on the Rebel fighters.</sd>

<setting>INT. WEDGE'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Wedge looks up and sees the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> ships.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke's targeting device marks off the distance to the target.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Vader and his wingmen zoom closer.</sd>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Vader adjusts his controls and fires laserbolts at two X-
wings flying down the trench. He scores a direct hit on Wedge.</sd>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - WAR ROOM</setting>

<sd>Leia and the others are grouped around the computer board.</sd>

<speaker>WEDGE</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. WEDGE'S COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>WEDGE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Wedge pulls his crippled X-wing back away from the battle.</sd>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Vader watches the escape but issues a command to his wingmen.</sd>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Luke's X-wing speeds down the trench; the three <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters, 
still in perfect unbroken formation, tail close behind.</sd>

<setting>INT. BIGGS' COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Biggs looks around at the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters. He is worried.</sd>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>The three <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters move ever closer, closing in on Luke 
and Biggs.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke looks back anxiously at little <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER</setting>

<sd>Ignoring the bumpy ride, flak, and lasers, a beeping <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>-
Detoo struggles to increase the power, his dome turning from 
side to side.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Stealthily, the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> formation creeps closer.</sd>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Vader adjusts his control stick.</sd>

<setting>INT. BIGGS' COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Biggs looks around at the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER</setting>

<sd>Luke looks into his targeting device. He moves it away for a 
moment and ponders its use. He looks back into the computer 
targeter.</sd>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Vader and his wingmen race through <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> trench.  
Biggs moves in to cover for Luke, but Vader gains on him.</sd>

<setting>INT. BIGGS' COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Biggs sees the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter aiming at him.</sd>

<speaker>BIGGS</speaker>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Vader squeezes the fire button on his controls.</sd>

<setting>INT. BIGGS' COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Biggs' cockpit explodes around him, lighting him in red.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Biggs' ship bursts into a million flaming bits and scatters 
across the surface.</sd>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - WAR ROOM</setting>

<sd>Leia and the others stare at the computer board.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke is stunned by Biggs' death. His eyes are watering, but 
his anger is also growing.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - CONTROL ROOM</setting>

<sd>Grand Moff Tarkin watches the projected target screen with 
satisfaction.</sd>

<speaker>DEATH STAR INTERCOM VOICE</speaker>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Vader takes aim on Luke and talks to the wingmen.</sd>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR - LUKE'S SHIP</setting>

<sd>Luke's ship streaks through the trench of <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name>.</sd>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - WAR ROOM</setting>

<sd>Princess Leia returns her general's worried and doubtful 
glances with solid, grim determination. <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> seems 
nervous.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke concentrates on his targeting device.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Three <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters charge away down the trench toward Luke.</sd>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Vader's finger's curls around the control stick.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke adjusts the lens of his targeting device.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Luke's ship charges down the trench.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke lines up the yellow cross-hair lines of the targeting 
device's screen. He looks into the targeting device, then 
starts at a voice he hears.</sd>

<speaker>BEN'S VOICE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>The Death Star trench zooms by.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke looks up, then starts to look back into the targeting 
device. He has second thoughts.</sd>

<speaker>BEN'S VOICE</speaker>

<sd>A grim determination sweeps across Luke's face as he closes 
his eyes and starts to mumble Ben's training to himself.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Luke's fighter streaks through the trench.</sd>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Vader follows Luke's X-wing down the trench.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke looks to the targeting device, then away as he hears 
Ben's voice.</sd>

<speaker>BEN'S VOICE</speaker>

<sd>Luke's hand reaches for the control panel and presses the 
button. The targeting device moves away.</sd>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - WAR ROOM</setting>

<sd>Leia and the others stand watching the projected screen.</sd>

<speaker>BASE VOICE</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Luke's ship streaks ever close to the exhaust port.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke looks at <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> surface streaking by.</sd>

<setting>EXT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER</setting>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name>-Detoo turns his head from side to side, beeping in 
anticipation.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>The three <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters, manned by Vader and his two wingmen, 
follow Luke's X-wing down the trench.</sd>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Vader maneuvers his controls as he looks at his doomed target.  
He presses the fire buttons on his control sticks. Laserfire 
shoots toward Luke's X-wing fighter.</sd>

<setting>EXT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER</setting>

<sd>A large burst of Vader's laserfire engulfs <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>. The arms 
go limp on the smoking little droid as he makes a high-pitched 
sound.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke looks frantically back over his shoulder at <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>.</sd>

<setting>EXT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER</setting>

<sd>Smoke billows out around little <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> and sparks begin to 
fly.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name>'s beeping sounds die out.</sd>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - WAR ROOM</setting>

<sd>Leia and the others stare intently at the projected screen, 
while <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> watches the Princess. Lights representing the 
Death Star and targets glow brightly.</sd>

<speaker>MASSASSI INTERCOM VOICE</speaker>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR - CONTROL ROOM</setting>

<sd>Tarkin glares at the projected target screen.</sd>

<speaker>DEATH STAR INTERCOM VOICE</speaker>

<speaker>TARKIN</speaker>

<speaker>DEATH STAR INTERCOM VOICE</speaker>

<sd>An officer reaches up and pushes buttons on the control panel, 
as green lighted buttons turn to red.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>The three <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters zoom down <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> trench in 
pursuit of Luke, never breaking formation.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke looks anxiously at the exhaust port.</sd>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Vader adjusts his control sticks, checking his projected 
targeting screen.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Luke's ship barrels down the trench.</sd>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Vader's targeting computer swings around into position. Vader 
takes careful aim on Luke's X-wing fighter.</sd>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<sd>He pushes the fire buttons.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>The three <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters move in on Luke. As Vader's center 
fighter unleashes a volley of laserfire, one of the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> ships 
at his side is hit and explodes into flame. The two remaining 
ships continue to move in.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke looks about, wondering whose laserfire destroyed Vader's 
wingman.</sd>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Vader is taken by surprise, and looks out from his cockpit.</sd>

<speaker>VADER</speaker>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S WINGMAN - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Vader's wingman searches around him trying to locate the 
unknown attacker.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> and Chewbacca grin from ear to ear.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>The Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> heads right at the two <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters.  
It's a collision course.</sd>

<setting>INT. WINGMAN'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>The wingman spots the pirateship coming at him and warns the 
Dark Lord.</sd>

<speaker>WINGMAN</speaker>

<setting>EXT. DEATH STAR TRENCH</setting>

<sd>Vader's wingman panics at the sight of the oncoming pirate 
starship and veers radically to one side, colliding with 
Vader's <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighter in the process. Vader's wingman crashes 
into the side wall of the trench and explodes. Vader's damaged 
ship spins out of the trench with a damaged wing.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Vader's ship spins out of control with a bent solar fin, 
heading for deep space.</sd>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Vader turns round and round in circles as his ship spins 
into space.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Solo's ship moves in toward <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> trench.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Solo, smiling, speaks to Luke over his headset mike.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - WAR ROOM</setting>

<sd>Leia and the others listen to Solo's transmission.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke looks up and smiles. He concentrates on the exhaust 
port, then fires his laser torpedoes.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SURFACE OF THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Luke's torpedoes shoot toward the port and seems to simply 
disappear into the surface and not explode. But the shots do 
find their mark and have gone into the exhaust port and are 
heading for the main reactor.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke throws his head back in relief.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>An <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> soldier runs to the control panel board and pulls 
the attack lever as the board behind him lights up.</sd>

		<setting>INTERCOM VOICE</setting>
		   Stand by to fire at Rebel base.

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Two X-wings, a Y-wing, and the pirateship race toward Yavin 
in the distance.</sd>

<setting>INT. DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>Several <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> soldiers, flanking a pensive Grand Moff 
Tarkin, busily push control levers and buttons.</sd>

		<setting>INTERCOM VOICE</setting>
		   Standing by.

<sd>The rumble of a distant explosion begins.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE AROUND THE DEATH STAR</setting>

<sd>The Rebel ships race out of sight, leaving <name type="LOC">the moon</name>-like 
Death Star alone against a blanket of stars. Several small 
flashes appear on the surface. The Death Star bursts into a 
supernova, creating a spectacular heavenly display.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S X-WING FIGHTER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke is at ease, and his eyes are closed.</sd>

<speaker>BEN'S VOICE</speaker>

<sd>The ship rocks back and forth.</sd>

<setting>EXT. DARTH VADER'S <name type="ORG">TIE</name> FIGHTER</setting>

<sd>Vader's ship spins off into space.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>The Rebel ships race toward the fourth moon of Yavin.</sd>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - MAIN HANGAR</setting>

<sd>Luke climbs out of his starship fighter and is cheered by a 
throng of ground crew and pilots. Luke climbs down the ladder 
as they all welcome him with laughter, cheers, and shouting. 
Princess Leia rushes toward him.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<sd>She throws her arms around Luke and hugs him as they dance 
around in a circle. Solo runs in toward Luke and they embrace 
one another, slapping each other on the back.</sd>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<speaker>HAN</speaker>

<sd>Luke and <name type="NORP">Han</name> look at one another, as Solo playfully shoves 
at Luke's face. Leia moves in between them.</sd>

<speaker>LEIA</speaker>

<sd>Luke looks toward the ship.</sd>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<sd>The fried little <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>-Detoo is lifted off the back of the 
fighter and carried off under the worried eyes of <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>.</sd>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>TECHNICIAN</speaker>

<speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>

<speaker>LUKE</speaker>

<setting>INT. MASSASSI OUTPOST - MAIN THRONE ROOM</setting>

<sd>Luke, <name type="NORP">Han</name>, and Chewbacca enter the huge ruins of the main 
temple. Hundreds of troops are lined up in neat rows. Banners 
are flying and at the far end stands a vision in white, the 
beautiful young Senator Leia. Luke and the others solemnly 
march up the long aisle and kneel before Senator Leia. From 
one side of the temple marches a shined-up and fully repaired 
<name type="GPE">Artoo</name>-Detoo. He waddles up to the group and stands next to 
an equally pristine <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, who is rather awestruck by the 
whole event. Chewbacca is confused. Dodonna and several other 
dignitaries sit on the left of the Princess Leia. Leia is 
dressed in a long white dress and is staggeringly beautiful.  
She rises and places a gold medallion around <name type="NORP">Han</name>'s neck. He 
winks at her. She then repeats the ceremony with Luke, who 
is moved by the event. They turn and face the assembled 
troops, who all bow before them. Chewbacca growls and <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> 
beeps with happiness.</sd>

<sd>FADE OUT:</sd>

<sd>END CREDITS OVER STARS</sd>

<sd>THE END</sd>
</script>
</root>