<?xml-model href="sw_schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<root>
<title>Star Wars: Episode V - The <name type="GPE">Empire</name> Strikes Back (1980)</title>
by <writer>Lawrence Kasdan &amp; Leigh Brackett</writer>

<script>
<subTitle epNum="5">EPISODE 5 THE EMPIRE STRIKES BACK</subTitle>

<crawl>It is a dark time for the Rebellion. Although <name type="ORG">the Death Star</name> has been destroyed, <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> troops have driven the Rebel forces from their hidden base and pursued them across the galaxy.Evading the dreaded <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> Starfleet, a group of freedom fighters led by Luke Skywalker have established a new secret base on the remote ice world of <name type="GPE">Hoth</name>.The evil lord Darth Vader, obsessed with finding young Skywalker, has dispatched thousands of remote probes into the far reaches of space....</crawl>

<setting>EXT. GALAXY - PLANET HOTH</setting>

<sd>A <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name> moves through space, releasing <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> probe robots 
from its underside.  </sd>

<sd>One of these probes zooms toward the planet <name type="GPE">Hoth</name> and lands on its ice-
covered surface.  An explosion marks the point of
impact.  </sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - METEORITE CRATER - SNOW PLAIN - DAY</setting>

<sd>A weird mechanical sound rises above the whining of the wind.  A 
strange probe robot, with several extended sensors, emerges from the 
smoke-shrouded crater.  The ominous mechanical probe floats across the 
snow plain and disappears into the distance.</sd>

<setting>EXT. PLAIN OF HOTH - DAY</setting>

<sd>A small figure gallops across the windswept ice slope.  The bundled 
rider is mounted on a large gray snow lizard, a Tauntaun.  Curving 
plumes of snow rise from beneath the speeding paws of the two-legged 
beast.</sd>

<sd>The rider gallops up a slope and reins his lizard to a stop.  Pulling 
off his protective goggles, Luke Skywalker notices something in the 
sky.  He takes a pair of electrobinoculars from his utility belt and 
through them sees smoke rising from where the probe robot has crashed.</sd>

<sd>The wind whips at Luke's fur-lined cap and he activates a comlink 
transmitter.  His Tauntaun shifts and moans nervously beneath him.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		Echo Three to <name type="FAC">Echo Seven</name>.  <name type="NORP">Han</name>, 
		old buddy, do you read me?</sp>

<sd>After a little static a familiar voice is heard.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(over comlink)
		Loud and clear, kid.  What's up?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		Well, I finished my circle.  I 
		don't pick up any life readings.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(over comlink)
		There isn't enough life on this 
		ice cube to fill a space cruiser.  
		The sensors are placed, I'm going 
		back.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		Right.  I'll see you shortly.  
		There's a meteorite that hit the 
		ground near here.  I want to check 
		it out.  It won't take long.</sp>

<sd>Luke clicks off his transmitter and reins back on his nervous lizard.  
He pats the beast on the head to calm it.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Hey, steady girl.  What's the 
		matter?  You smell something?</sp>

<sd>Luke takes a small device from his belt and starts to adjust it when 
suddenly a large shadow falls over him from behind.  He hears a 
monstrous howl and turns to see an eleven-foot-tall shape towering over 
him.  It is a Wampa Ice Creature, lunging at him ferociously.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Aaargh!</sp>

<sd>Luke grabs for his pistol, but is hit flat in the face by a huge white 
claw.  He falls unconscious into the snow and in a moment the terrified 
screams of the Tauntaun are cut short by the horrible snap of a neck 
being broken.</sd>

<sd>The Wampa Ice Creature grabs Luke by one ankle and drags him away 
across the frozen plain.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - REBEL BASE ENTRANCE - DAY</setting>

<sd>A stalwart figure rides his Tauntaun up to the entrance of an enormous 
ice cave.</sd>

<setting>INT. HOTH - REBEL BASE - MAIN HANGAR DECK</setting>

<sd>Rebel troopers rush about unloading supplies and otherwise securing 
their new base.  The rider, <name type="NORP">Han</name> Solo, swings off his lizard and pulls 
off his goggles.</sd>

<sd>He walks into the main hangar deck toward the Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>, which 
is parked among several fighters.  Mechanics, R2 units, and various 
other droids hurry about.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> stops at the Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> where his 
<name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> copilot, Chewbacca, is welding on a central lifter.  Chewie 
stops his work and lifts his face shield, growling an irritated 
greeting to his boss.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Chewie!</sp>

<sd>The <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> grumbles a reply.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		All right, don't lose your temper.
		I'll come right back and give you 
		a hand.</sp>

<sd>Chewbacca puts his mask back on and returns to his welding as <name type="NORP">Han</name> 
leaves.</sd>

<setting>INT. HOTH - REBEL BASE - COMMAND CENTER</setting>

<sd>A makeshift command center has been set up in a blasted area of thick 
ice.  The low-ceilinged room is a beehive of activity. Controllers, 
troops, and droids move about setting up electronic equipment and 
monitoring radar signals.</sd>

<sd>General Rieekan straightens up from a console at <name type="NORP">Han</name>'s approach.</sd>

<sp><speaker>RIEEKAN</speaker>
		Solo?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
No sign of life out there, General.
The sensors are in place.  You'll 
know if anything comes around.</sp>

<sp><speaker>RIEEKAN</speaker>
		Commander Skywalker reported in yet?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		No.  He's checking out a meteorite 
		that hit near him.</sp>

<sp><speaker>RIEEKAN</speaker>
			(indicates radar 
			 screen)
		With all the meteor activity in this
		system, it's going to be difficult 
		to spot approaching ships.</sp>

<sd>Taking a deep breath, <name type="NORP">Han</name> blurts out what is on his mind.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		General, I've got to leave.  I 
		can't stay anymore.</sp>

<sd>Princess Leia, standing at a console nearby, is dressed in a short 
white combat jacket and pants.  Her hair is braided across her head in 
a Nordic fashion.  She overhears their  conversation and seems somewhat 
distressed.</sd>

<sp><speaker>RIEEKAN</speaker>
		I'm sorry to hear that.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Well, there's a price on my head.
		If I don't pay off Jabba the <name type="ORG">Hut</name>, 
		I'm a dead man.</sp>

<sp><speaker>RIEEKAN</speaker>
		A death mark's not an easy thing 
		to live with.  You're a good
		fighter, Solo.  I hate to lose you.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Thank you, General.</sp>

<sd>He turns to Leia as Rieekan moves away.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(with feeling)
		Well, Your Highness, I guess this 
		is it.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		That's right.</sp>

<sd>Leia is angry.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> sees she has no warmth to offer him.  He shakes his 
head and adopts a sarcastic tone.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(cooly)
		Well, don't get all mushy on me.
		So long, Princess.</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> walks away into the quiet corridor adjoining the command center.  
Leia stews a moment, then hurries after him.</sd>

<setting>INT. HOTH - REBEL BASE - ICE CORRIDOR</setting>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		<name type="NORP">Han</name>!</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> stops in the corridor and turns to face Leia.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Yes, Your Highnessness?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		I thought you decided to stay.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Well, the bounty hunter we ran 
		into on Ord Mantell changed my
		mind.  </sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		<name type="NORP">Han</name>, we need you!</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		We?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Yes.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Oh, what about you need?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
			(mystified)
		I need?  I don't know what you're 
		talking about.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(shakes his head, 
			 fed up) 
		You probably don't.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		And what precisely am I supposed 
		to know?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Come on!  You want me to stay 
		because of the way you feel about
		me.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Yes.  You're a great help to us.
		You're a natural leader...</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		No!  That's not it.  Come on.  
		Aahhh - uh huh!  Come on.</sp>

<sd>Leia stares at him, understanding, then laughs.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
You're imagining things.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Am I?  Then why are you following 
		me?  Afraid I was going to leave
		without giving you a goodbye kiss?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		I'd just as soon kiss a <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name>.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		I can arrange that.  You could use 
		a good kiss!</sp>

<sd>Angrily, <name type="NORP">Han</name> strides down the corridor as Leia stares after him.</sd>

<setting>INT. HOTH - REBEL BASE - ANOTHER ICE CORRIDOR</setting>

<sd>A familiar stream of beeps and whistles herald the approach of <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>-
Detoo and See-<name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, who appear around a corner and move along an 
ice wall toward the main hangar.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Don't try to blame me.  I didn't 
		ask you to turn on the thermal 
		heater.  I merely commented that it 
		was freezing in the princess' 
		chamber.  But it's supposed to be 
		freezing.  How are we going to dry 
		out all her clothes?  I really don't 
		know.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps a stream of protesting whistles.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Oh, switch off.</sp>

<setting>INT. HOTH - REBEL BASE - MAIN HANGAR DECK</setting>

<sd>The two robots stop at <name type="NORP">Han</name> Solo's space freighter.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> and Chewie are 
struggling with their central lifters.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(to Chewie)
		Why do you take this apart now? 
		I'm trying to get us out of here 
		and you pull both of these.</sp>

<sd>Chewie grumbles in irritation.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Excuse me, sir.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(to Chewie)
		Put them back together right now.</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Might I have a word with you, 
		please?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		What do you want?</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Well, it's Princess Leia, sir.
		She's been trying to get you on 
		the communicator.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		I turned it off.  I don't want to 
		talk to her.</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Oh.  Well, Princess Leia is wondering 
		about Master Luke.  He hasn't come 
		back yet.  She doesn't know where he 
		is.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		I don't know where he is.</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Nobody knows where he is.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		What do you mean, "nobody knows"?</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> glances at the fading light at the entrance of the ice cave as 
night slowly begins to fall on the planet.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Well, uh, you see...</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> jumps down off the lift, as <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> follows him.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Deck Officer.  Deck Officer!</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Excuse me, sir.  Might I inqu...</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> abruptly puts his hand over <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>'s mouth as the deck officer 
approaches.</sd>

<sp><speaker>DECK OFFICER</speaker>
		Yes, sir?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Do you know where Commander 
		Skywalker is?</sp>

<sp><speaker>DECK OFFICER</speaker>
		I haven't seen him.  It's possible 
		he came in through the south entrance.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		It's possible?  Why don't you go 
		find out?  It's getting dark out there.</sp>

<sp><speaker>DECK OFFICER</speaker>
		Yes, sir.</sp>

<sd>The deck officer leaves hurriedly, as <name type="NORP">Han</name> takes his hand off <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>'s 
mouth.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Excuse me, sir.  Might I inquire 
		what's going on?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Why not?</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Impossible man.  Come along, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, 
		let's find Princess Leia.  Between 
		ourselves, I think Master Luke is 
		in considerable danger.</sp>

<setting>INT. HOTH - REBEL BASE - MAIN ICE TUNNEL</setting>

<sd>The deck officer and his assistant hurry toward <name type="NORP">Han</name> as he enters the 
tunnel.</sd>

<sp><speaker>DECK OFFICER</speaker>
		Sir, Commander Skywalker hasn't 
		come in through the south entrance.
		He might have forgotten to check in.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Not likely.  Are the speeders ready?</sp>

<sp><speaker>DECK OFFICER</speaker>
		Not yet.  We're having some trouble 
		adapting them to the cold.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Then we'll have to go out on 
		Tauntauns.</sp>

<sp><speaker>DECK OFFICER</speaker>
		Sir, the temperature's dropping too 
		rapidly.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		That's right.  And my friends out 
		in it.</sp>

<sp><speaker>ASSISTANT OFFICER</speaker>
		I'll cover sector twelve.  Have 
		com-control set screen alpha.</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> pushes through the troops and mounts a Tauntaun.</sd>

<sp><speaker>DECK OFFICER</speaker>
		Your Tauntaun'll freeze before you 
		reach the first marker.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Then I'll see you in hell!</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> maneuvers his mount out of the cave and races into the dark bitter 
night.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - ICE GORGE - DUSK</setting>

<sd>The jagged face of a huge ice wall sits gloomily in the dim twilight of 
a <name type="GPE">Hoth</name> day.  Luke hangs upside down, ankles frozen into icy 
stalactites, his extended arms within a foot of the snow floor.  One 
side of his face is covered in a dried mask of frozen blood.  He opens 
his eyes as a chilling moan of the hideous ice creature echoes off the 
gorge walls.  Luke pulls himself up, grabs hold of his ankles, and 
futilely tries to unfasten the throngs.</sd>

<sd>Exhausted, he drops back into his hanging position.  As he hangs there, 
he spies his lightsaber lying near a pile of his discarded gear, about 
three feet out of reach.</sd>

<sd>He focuses on the saber and, as his hand strains toward the weapon, he 
squeezes his eyes tight in concentration.</sd>

<sd>Just as the ice creature looms over Luke, the lightsaber jumps into 
Luke's hand.</sd>

<sd>The young warrior instantly ignites his sword, swinging up, and cuts 
himself loose from the ice.  He flops to the snow in a heap.  The 
startled creature moves back, his giant yellow eyes blinking.  Luke 
scrambles to his feet.  He swings his lightsaber and the beast screams 
in pain.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - ENTRANCE TO ICE GORGE - DUSK</setting>

<sd>Luke staggers out of the gorge into the dark and snowy twilight.  Weak 
and exhausted, he stumbles down a snow bank.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - SNOW PLAIN - DUSK</setting>

<sd>A small, lone figure riding a Tauntaun races through the hostile 
vastness of snow and cold.  As it runs, the Tauntaun's legs kick up 
large clouds of snow and ice into the snowy air.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - OUTSIDE ICE				 HANGAR - DUSK</setting>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> stands in the falling snow, beeping worriedly.  <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> moves 
stiffly over to him.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		You must come along now, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>.  
		There's really nothing more we can 
		do.  And my joints are freezing up.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps, long and low.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Don't say thing like that!  Of 
		course we'll see Master Luke again.
		He'll be quite all right, you'll see.
			(to himself)
		Stupid little short-circuit.  He'll 
		be quite all right.</sp>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> turns to go back inside the main hangar as <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> mournfully 
keeps his vigil.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - SNOW DRIFT - DUSK</setting>

<sd>The wind is blowing quite strong now.  Luke struggles to stay upright, 
but a blast of freezing snow knocks him over.  He struggles to get up, 
but he can't.  The young warrior from Tatooine drags himself a couple 
of feet and then collapses.</sd>

<setting>INT. REBEL BASE - MAIN HANGAR DECK - ENTRANCE - NIGHT</setting>

<sd>Princess Leia stands inside the dark entrance to the Rebel base, 
waiting for a sign of the two Rebel heroes.  She shivers in the cold 
wind as, nearby, Chewie sits with his head in his hands.  In the 
background, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> and <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> move through the doors.  </sd>

<sd>A Rebel lieutenant moves to Major Derlin, an officer keeping watch with 
the princess.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LIEUTENANT</speaker>
		Sir, all the patrols are in.
		There's still no contact from 
		Skywalker or Solo.</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Mistress Leia, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> says he's been 
		quite unable to pick up any signals, 
		although he does admit that his own 
		range is far too weak to abandon 
		all hope.</sp>

<sd>Leia nods an acknowledgment, but she is lost in thought.</sd>

<sp><speaker>DERLIN</speaker>
		Your Highness, there's nothing 
		more we can do tonight.  The shield 
		doors must be closed.</sp>

<sd>He turns to the lieutenant.</sd>

<sp><speaker>DERLIN</speaker>
		Close the doors.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LIEUTENANT</speaker>
		Yes, sir.</sp>

<sd>The lieutenant walks away.  Chewie lets out a long, mournful howl, 
somewhat like a coyote.  At the same moment, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> begins a complex 
series of efficient beeps.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		<name type="GPE">Artoo</name> says the chances of survival 
		are seven hundred seventy-five...
		to one.</sp>

<sd>Leia stands praying to herself as the huge metal doors slam across the 
entrance of the ice cave.  The loud booms echo throughout the huge 
cavern.  Chewie lets out another suffering howl.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Actually, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> has been known to 
		make mistakes... from time to time.
		Oh, dear, oh, dear.  Don't worry 
		about Master Luke.  I'm sure he'll 
		be all right.  He's quite clever, 
		you know... for a human being.</sp>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - SNOW DRIFT - DUSK</setting>

<sd>Luke lies face down in the snow, nearly unconscious.  Slowly he looks 
up and sees Ben <name type="ORG">Kenobi</name>, barely visible through the blowing snow.  It is 
hard to tell if <name type="ORG">Kenobi</name> is real or a hallucination.</sd>

<sp><speaker>BEN</speaker>
		Luke... Luke.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(weakly)
		Ben?</sp>

<sp><speaker>BEN</speaker>
		You will go to the <name type="FAC">Dagobah</name> system.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		<name type="FAC">Dagobah</name> system?</sp>

<sp><speaker>BEN</speaker>
		There you will learn from Yoda, 
		the <name type="ORG">Jedi</name> Master who instructed me.</sp>

<sd>The image of Ben fades, revealing a lone Tauntaun rider approaching 
from the windswept horizon.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(groaning faintly)
		Ben... Ben.</sp>

<sd>Luke drops into unconsciousness.</sd>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> pulls up and leaps off his mount.  He hurries to his snow-covered 
friend, cradling him in his arms.  <name type="NORP">Han</name>'s Tauntaun lets out a low, 
pitiful bellow.  But <name type="NORP">Han</name>'s concern is with Luke, and he shakes him 
urgently.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Luke!  Luke!  Don't do this, Luke.  
		Come on, give me a sign here.</sp>

<sd>Luke doesn't respond.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> begins frantically rubbing and slapping 
Luke's unconscious face.  As he starts to lift the youth, <name type="NORP">Han</name> hears a 
rasping sound behind him.  He turns, just in time to see his Tauntaun 
stagger and then fall over into the snow.</sd>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> carries Luke to the moaning beast.  Then, with a final groan, the 
Tauntaun expires.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN </speaker>
		Not much time.</sp>

<sd>He pushes Luke's inert form against the belly of the dead beast.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(moaning)
		Ben... Ben...</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		<name type="NORP">Han</name>g on, kid.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		<name type="FAC">Dagobah</name> system...</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> ignites Luke's saber and cuts the beast from head to toe.  He 
quickly tosses it's steaming innards into the snow, then lifts Luke's 
inert form and stuffs him inside the carcass.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(reeling from the 
			 odor) 
		Whew...</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		<name type="FAC">Dagobah</name>...</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		This may smell bad, kid...</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(moaning)
		Yoda...</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		...but it will keep you warm... 
		til I get the shelter built.
			(struggling to get 
			 Luke inside the 
			 carcass) 
		Ooh... I thought they smelled bad 
		on the outside!</sp>

<sd>The wind has picked up considerably, making it difficult to move.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> 
removes a pack from the dead creature's back, taking out a shelter 
container.  He begins to set up what can only be a pitiful protection 
against a bitter <name type="GPE">Hoth</name> night.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - SNOWDRIFT - DAWN</setting>

<sd>Four snub-nosed armored snowspeeders race across the white landscape.</sd>

<setting>INT. SNOWSPEEDER COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>There is only one pilot, Zev, in the enclosed two-man craft.  He 
concentrates on the scopes which ring his cockpit.  He hears a low beep 
from one of his monitors.</sd>

<sp><speaker>ZEV</speaker>
			(into transmitter) 
		Echo Base... I've got something!  Not 
		much, but it could be a life form.</sp>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - SNOWDRIFT</setting>

<sd>The small craft banks and makes a slow arc, then races off in a new 
direction.</sd>

<setting>INT. SNOWSPEEDER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>The pilot switches over to a new transmitter.</sd>

<sp><speaker>ZEV</speaker>
			(into transmitter)
		This is <name type="ORG">Rogue</name> Two.  this is <name type="ORG">Rogue</name> 
		Two.  Captain Solo, so you copy?  
		Commander Skywalker, do you copy? 
		This is <name type="ORG">Rogue</name> Two.</sp>

<sd>There is a sharp crackle of static, then a faint voice.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(filtered over 
			 Zev's receiver)
		Good morning.  Nice of you guys 
		to drop by.</sp>

<sp><speaker>ZEV</speaker>
			(switching transmitters) 
		Echo Base... this is <name type="ORG">Rogue</name> Two.  I 
		found them.  Repeat, I found them.</sp>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - SNOWDRIFT - DAY</setting>

<sd>The small shelter <name type="NORP">Han</name> set up is covered with snow on the windward side.  
A makeshift antenna rests gingerly on top the snowdrift.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> spots 
Zev's snowspeeder approaching in the distance, and begins waving his 
arms frantically at the tiny craft.</sd>

<setting>INT. REBEL BASE - MEDICAL CENTER</setting>

<sd>Strange robot surgeons adjust a mass of electronic equipment.  A switch 
is thrown and a sudden blinding flash obscures Luke in a bacta tank 
filled with a thick, gelatinous slime.  He begins to thrash about, 
raving in delirium.</sd>

<setting>INT. REBEL BASE - MEDICAL CENTER - RECOVERY ROOM</setting>

<sd>Luke sits up in a recovery-room bed, weak but smiling.  His face shows 
terrible wounds from the Wampa's attack.  <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> and <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> enter the 
room.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Master Luke, sir, it's so good 
		to see you fully functional again.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps his good wishes.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		<name type="GPE">Artoo</name> expresses his relief, also.</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> and Chewie make their entrance.  The <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> growls a greeting.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		How are you feeling, kid?  You 
		don't look so bad to me.  In 
		fact, you look strong enough to 
		pull the ears off a <name type="ORG">Gundark</name>.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Thanks to you.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		That's two you owe me, junior.</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> turns as Leia enters the room.  He looks at her with a big, 
devilish grin.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Well your Worship, looks like 
		you managed to keep me around for
		a little while longer.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
			(haughtily)
		I had nothing to do with it.  General 
		Rieekan thinks it's dangerous for 
		any ships to leave the system until 
		we've activated the energy shield.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		That's a good story.  I think you 
		just can't bear to let a gorgeous 
		guy like me out of your sight.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		I don't know where you get your 
		delusions, laser brain.</sp>

<sd>Chewie is amused; he laughs in his manner.  <name type="NORP">Han</name>, enjoying himself, 
regards Chewie good-humoredly.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Laugh it up, fuzzball.  But you 
		didn't see us alone in the south 
		passage.</sp>

<sd>Luke sparks to this; he looks at Leia.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		She expressed her true feelings 
		for me.</sp>

<sd>Leia is flushed, eyes darting between Luke and <name type="NORP">Han</name>.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		My...!  Why, you stuck up,... half-
		witted... scruffy-looking ...nerf-
		herder!</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Who's scruffy-looking? 
			(to Luke) 
		I must have hit pretty close to 
		the mark to get her all riled up 
		like that, huh, kid?</sp>

<sd>Leia looks vulnerable for a moment, then the mask falls again, and she 
focuses on Luke.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Why, I guess you don't know 
		everything about women yet?</sp>

<sd>With that she leans over and kisses Luke on the lips.  Then she turns 
on her heel and walks out, leaving everyone in the room slightly 
dumbstruck.  With some smugness, Luke puts his hands behind his head 
and grins.</sd>

<sd>Suddenly, in the distance, the muffled sound of an alarm is heard.</sd>

<sp><speaker>ANNOUNCER</speaker>
			(over loudspeaker)
		Headquarters personnel, report to 
		command center.</sp>

<sd>The voice repeats the order and <name type="NORP">Han</name>, Chewie, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, and <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> hurry 
out of the room, bidding farewell to Luke.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Take it easy.</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Excuse us, please.</sp>

<setting>INT. HOTH - REBEL BASE - COMMAND CENTER</setting>

<sd>Rieekan looks up grimly from a console screen.  He calls over to Leia 
and <name type="NORP">Han</name>.</sd>

<sp><speaker>RIEEKAN</speaker>
		Princess... we have a visitor.</sp>

<sd>The group hurries over to Rieekan.</sd>

<sp><speaker>RIEEKAN</speaker>
		We've picked up something outside 
		the base in zone twelve, moving 
		east.</sp>

<sp><speaker>SENIOR CONTROLLER</speaker>
		It's metal.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Then it couldn't be one of those 
		creatures that attacked Luke.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		It could be a speeder, one of ours.</sp>

<sp><speaker>SENIOR CONTROLLER</speaker>
		No.  Wait - there's something very 
		weak coming through.</sp>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> steps up to the control panel and listens intently to the 
strange signal.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Sir, I am fluent in six million 
		forms of communication.  This signal 
		is not used by the <name type="ORG">Alliance</name>.  It 
		could be an <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> code.</sp>

<sd>The transmission ends in static.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		It isn't friendly, whatever it is.  
		Come on, Chewie, let's check it out.</sp>

<sp><speaker>RIEEKAN</speaker>
		Send <name type="ORG">Rogue</name>s Ten and Eleven to 
		station three-eight.</sp>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - SNOW PLAIN - DAY</setting>

<sd>The dark probe robot moves past the smoldering ruins of station three-
eight and down a ridge toward the Rebel base.  It raises a large 
antenna from the top of its head and begins to send out a piercing 
signal.</sd>

<sd>The probe droid has spotted Chewbacca who, not thirty feet away, has 
popped his head over a snow bank.  Instantly, the probe robot swings 
around, its deadly ray ready to fire.  But before it can get a shot 
off, it is hit from behind by a laser bolt, and explodes in a million 
pieces.</sd>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> Solo replaces his blaster in its holster and peers intently at the 
smoldering remains of the <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> probe.</sd>

<setting>INT. HOTH - REBEL BASE - COMMAND CENTER</setting>

<sd>Leia and Rieekan listen to <name type="NORP">Han</name> on the comlink.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(over comlink)
		Afraid there's not much left.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		What was it?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(over comlink)
		Droid of some kind.  I didn't hit 
		it that hard.  It must have had a 
		self-destruct.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		An <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> probe droid.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(over comlink)
		It's a good bet the <name type="GPE">Empire</name> knows 
		we're here.</sp>

<sp><speaker>RIEEKAN</speaker>
		We'd better start the evacuation.</sp>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - IMPERIAL FLEET</setting>

<sd>Darth Vader's <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name>, larger and more awesome than the five 
<name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name>s that surround it, sits in the vastness of 
space.  The six huge ships are surrounded by a convoy of smaller 
spacecraft.  <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters dart to and fro.</sd>

<setting>INT. DARTH VADER'S STAR DESTROYER - BRIDGE - MAIN CONTROL DECK</setting>

<sd>Controllers working the vast complex of electronic controls hear 
ominous approaching footsteps and look up from their controls.  The 
squat, evil-looking Admiral Ozzel and the young, powerfully built 
<name type="ORG">General Veers</name>, who have been conferring near the front, also feel the 
approaching presence and turn toward it.  Darth Vader, Lord of the 
Sith, enters like a chill wind.  As Vader moves across the wide bridge, 
Captain Piett hurries up to Ozzel.</sd>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		Admiral.</sp>

<sp><speaker>OZZEL</speaker>
		Yes, Captain</sp>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		I think we've got something, sir.  
		The report is only a fragment from 
		a probe droid in the <name type="GPE">Hoth</name> system, 
		but it's the best lead we've had.</sp>

<sp><speaker>OZZEL</speaker>
			(irritated) 
		We have thousands of probe droids 
		searching the galaxy.  I want proof, 
		not leads!</sp>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		The visuals indicate life readings.</sp>

<sp><speaker>OZZEL</speaker>
		It could mean anything.  If we 
		followed every lead...</sp>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		But, sir, the <name type="GPE">Hoth</name> system is supposed 
		to be devoid of human forms.</sp>

<sd>Vader moves to a large screen showing an image of the Rebel snow base.  
Rebel speeders can be seen approaching the base in the distance.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		You found something?</sp>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		Yes, my lord.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
			(studying the image 
			 on the console screen) 
		That's it.  The <name type="ORG">Rebels</name> are there.</sp>

<sp><speaker>OZZEL</speaker>
		My lord, there are so many uncharted 
		settlements.  It could be smugglers, 
		it could be...</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		That is the system.  And I'm sure 
		Skywalker is with them.  Set your 
		course for the <name type="GPE">Hoth</name> system.  General 
		Veers, prepare you men.</sp>

<setting>INT. HOTH - REBEL BASE - TRANSPORT BAY</setting>

<sd>A captain issues instructions to two of his men at the entrance to the 
main transport bay.  Several Rebel transports behind them are being 
loaded by men carrying heavy boxes and moving quickly, but not in 
panic.</sd>

<sp><speaker>REBEL CAPTAIN</speaker>
		Groups seven and ten will stay 
		behind to fly the speeders.  As 
		soon as each transport is loaded, 
		evacuation control will give 
		clearance for immediate launch.</sp>

<sp><speaker>REBEL FIGHTER</speaker>
		Right, sir.</sp>

<setting>INT. HOTH - REBEL BASE - MAIN HANGAR DECK</setting>

<sd>Alarms sound.  Troops, ground crews, and droids rush to their alert 
stations.  Armored snowspeeders are lined up in attack formation near 
the main entrance.</sd>

<sd>In the midst of all this activity, <name type="NORP">Han</name> does some frantic welding on the 
lifters of the Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>.</sd>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> finishes his work and hops down to the hangar floor.  He pulls out 
his comlink, all the while eyeing problematic lifters.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(into comlink, to 
			 Chewie)
		Okay, that's it.  Try it... Off! 
		Turn it off!  Turn it off!  Off!</sp>

<sd>Smoke rises from a minor explosion on the lifter.  Exasperated, <name type="NORP">Han</name> 
surveys the new damage.</sd>

<setting>INT. REBEL BASE - MEDICAL CENTER</setting>

<sd>Luke dresses in readiness for the evacuation as his attending medical 
droid stands by.</sd>

<sp><speaker>MEDICAL DROID</speaker>
		Sir, it will take quite a while 
		to evacuate the T-forty- sevens.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Well, forget the heavy equipment.
		There's plenty of time to get the 
		smaller modules on the transports.</sp>

<sp><speaker>MEDICAL DROID</speaker>
		Take care, sir.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Thanks.</sp>

<setting>INT. REBEL BASE - MAIN HANGAR DECK</setting>

<sd>Pilots, gunners, and R2 units scurry about.  Luke, pulling on his 
heavy-weather jacket, is headed toward a row of armored speeders.  He 
stops at the rear of the Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>, where <name type="NORP">Han</name> and Chewie are 
trying to repair the right lifter with even more haste than before.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Chewie, take care of yourself, 
		okay?</sp>

<sd>As Luke pats Chewie on the arm, Chewie puts his arms around Luke and 
gives him a tight hug.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> is discussing the lifter with a repair 
droid when he sees Luke.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Hi, kid.
			(to droid)
		There's got to be a reason for 
		it.  Check it at the other end.
		Wait a second.
			(to Luke)
		You all right?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Yeah.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Be careful.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		You, too.</sp>

<sd>Luke smiles, then waves at his friend and walks on.  After a few steps, 
he stops and looks back.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> glances up and the two exchange a silent 
communication, each wishing the other safety, happiness - many things, 
all difficult to verbalize.</sd>

<setting>INT. REBEL BASE - CONTROL ROOM.</setting>

<sd>Alarms sound throughout the hidden Rebel base.  In the control room, a 
controller urgently gestures for General Rieekan to check a computer 
scan.</sd>

<sp><speaker>CONTROLLER</speaker>
		General, there's a fleet of Star 
		Destroyers coming out of hyperspace 
		in sector four.</sp>

<sp><speaker>RIEEKAN</speaker>
		Reroute all power to the energy 
		shield.  We've got to hold them till 
		all transports are away.  Prepare 
		for ground assault.</sp>

<sd>Rieekan exits hurriedly.</sd>

<setting>INT. VADER'S STAR DESTROYER - VADER'S CHAMBER - MEDITATION CUBICLE</setting>

<sd>The dark cubicle is illuminated by a single shaft of light which falls 
on the brooding Dark Lord as he sits on a raised meditation cube.  
<name type="ORG">General Veers</name> enters the room and approaches the silent, unmoving 
Vader.  Although seemingly very sure of himself, Veers is still not 
bold enough to interrupt the meditating lord.  The younger general 
stands quietly at attention until the evil presence speaks.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		What is it, General?</sp>

<sp><speaker>VEERS</speaker>
		My lord, the fleet has moves out 
		of light-speed.  Com-Scan has 
		detected an energy field protecting 
		an area around the sixth planet of 
		the <name type="GPE">Hoth</name> system.  The field is 
		strong enough to deflect any 
		bombardment.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
			(angrily)
		The <name type="ORG">Rebels</name> are alerted to our 
		presence.  Admiral Ozzel came out 
		of light-speed too close to the 
		system.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VEERS</speaker>
		He felt surprise was wiser...</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		He is as clumsy as he is stupid.
		General, prepare your troops for a 
		surface attack.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VEERS</speaker>
		Yes, my lord.</sp>

<sd>Veers turns smartly and leaves as Vader activates a large viewscreen 
showing the bridge of his mighty ship.  Admiral Ozzel appears on the 
viewscreen, standing slightly in front of Captain Piett.</sd>

<sp><speaker>OZZEL</speaker>
		Lord Vader, the fleet has moved 
		out of light-speed, and we're 
		preparing to... Aaagh!</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		You have failed me for the last 
		time, Admiral.  Captain Piett.</sp>

<sd>Piett steps forward, as the admiral moves away, slightly confused, 
touching his throat as it begins to constrict painfully.</sd>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		Yes, my lord.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
Make ready to land out troops beyond 
the energy shield and deploy the 
fleet so that nothing gets off that 
system.  You are in command now, 
Admiral Piett.</sp>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		Thank you, Lord Vader.</sp>

<sd>Piett's pleasure about his unexpected promotion is not an unmixed 
emotion.  He glances warily at the struggling Admiral Ozzel who, with a 
final choke, stumbles and falls in a lifeless heap before him.</sd>

<setting>INT. REBEL BASE - MAIN HANGAR DECK</setting>

<sd>With a sense of urgency, Leia quickly briefs a group of pilots gathered 
in the center of the hangar.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		All troop carriers will assemble 
		at the north entrance.  The heavy 
		transport ships will leave as 
		soon as they're loaded.  Only two 
		fighter escorts per ship.  The 
		energy shield can only be opened 
		for a short time, so you'll have 
		to stay very close to your transports.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HOBBIE</speaker>
		Two fighters against a <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name>?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		The ion cannon will fire several 
		shots to make sure that any enemy 
		ships will be out of your flight 
		path.  When you've gotten past the 
		energy shield, proceed directly to 
		the rendezvous point.  Understood?</sp>

<sp><speaker>PILOTS</speaker>
			(in unison)
		Right.  Okay.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Good luck.</sp>

<sp><speaker>DERLIN</speaker>
		Okay.  Everyone to your stations.  
		Let's go!</sp>

<sd>The pilots hurry away.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - ICE PLAIN - SNOW TRENCH - DAY</setting>

<sd>Rebel troops carry heavy bazooka-type weapons and position them along 
the snow trench.  Men hurriedly respond to their officers' yelled 
orders and brace themselves against the rhythmic gusts of bitter-cold 
wind.</sd>

<sd>Other troops load power packs into a gun turret and swing its guns into 
position.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - ICE PLAIN - POWER GENERATORS</setting>

<sd>Near the base power generators, troops rush to set up their heavy 
battle equipment.  Buzzing loudly, the generators send along, sparking 
fingers of energy into the bitter <name type="GPE">Hoth</name> wind.</sd>

<setting>INT. REBEL BASE - COMMAND CENTER</setting>

<sd>The long line of Rebel controllers is tense, as are Princess Leia and 
General Rieekan, who are trying very hard not to show any fear.</sd>

<sp><speaker>RIEEKAN</speaker>
		Their primary target will be the 
		power generators.  Prepare to 
		open the shield.</sp>

<setting>EXT. ICE PLAIN</setting>

<sd>The Rebel transport and two escort fighters begin their departure from 
the ice planet.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - IMPERIAL STAR DESTROYER</setting>

<sd>A huge <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name> rest against a sea of stars, far above 
the white surface of the planet <name type="GPE">Hoth</name>.</sd>

<setting>INT. IMPERIAL STAR DESTROYER - BRIDGE</setting>

<sd>An <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> controller approaches his commander.</sd>

<sp><speaker>CONTROLLER</speaker>
		Sir, Rebel ships are coming into 
		our sector.</sp>

<sp><speaker>CAPTAIN</speaker>
		Good.  Our first catch of the day.</sp>

<setting>INT. REBEL BASE - COMMAND CENTER</setting>

<sp><speaker>WOMAN CONTROLLER</speaker>
		Stand by, ion control... Fire!</sp>

<setting>EXT. REBEL BASE ICE CAVE - ION CANNON</setting>

<sd>The giant ball-shaped ion cannon rotates into position and blasts two 
red energy beams skyward.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - HOTH - REBEL TRANSPORT</setting>

<sd>The Rebel transport and its escort race away from the white planet, 
closely followed by the two red energy beams.</sd>

<sd>As the Rebel transport races toward the waiting <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> Star 
Destroyer, it is overtaken by the two scarlet energy bolts.  The 
<name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name> is hit in the conning tower by the powerful 
bolts, which set up fiery explosions on its metal hull.</sd>

<sd>The big <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name> veers, then spins wildly out of control.  As the 
<name type="ORG">Imperial</name> ship careers into deep space, the Rebel transport races away 
to safety.</sd>

<setting>INT. REBEL BASE - MAIN HANGAR DECK</setting>

<sd>Pilots, gunners, and troopers hurry to their stations and their 
vehicles.</sd>

<sp><speaker>ANNOUNCER</speaker>
			(over loudspeaker)
		The first transport is away.</sp>

<sd>Everyone cheers at the announcement, which echoes through the hangar.  
Luke turns and walks on, heading toward his snowspeeder.  His gunner, 
Dack, a fresh-faced, eager kid, is glad to see him.  They climb in.</sd>

<sp><speaker>DACK</speaker>
		Feeling all right, sir?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Just like new, Dack.  How about 
		you?</sp>

<sp><speaker>DACK</speaker>
		Right now I feel like I could take 
		on the whole <name type="GPE">Empire</name> myself.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(quietly, strapping 
			 in)
		I know what you mean.</sp>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - ICE PLAIN</setting>

<sd>A thin horizon line cuts across the bleak landscape.  Small dot-size 
objects begin to appear on the horizon, moving in the direction of the 
Rebel base.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - ICE PLAIN - SNOW TRENCH</setting>

<sd>A Rebel officer lifts a pair of electrobinoculars to his eyes.  Through 
the lens he sees a very close view of a giant <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> snow walker.  He 
adjusts the view which then zooms back to reveal three more of the 
ominous battle machines.  Small flashes of yellow fire billow from the 
guns of the lumbering snow walkers.</sd>

<sd>The officer lowers his binoculars as the regular rhythmic pounding 
begins to make the ground vibrate.  The pounding grows louder and is 
accompanied by a high-pitched, metallic rattling.  The officer speaks 
into his comlink.</sd>

<sp><speaker>TRENCH OFFICER</speaker>
		Echo Station Three-T-Eight.</sp>

<setting>INT. REBEL BASE - CORRIDOR</setting>

<sd>Pilots and gunners race to their waiting snowspeeders.  Ice and snow 
begin falling from the walls of the corridor, shaken by the pounding 
<name type="ORG">Imperial</name> snow walker as they draw ever nearer.</sd>

<sp><speaker>TRENCH OFFICER</speaker>
			(over comlink) 
		We have spotted <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> walkers!</sp>

<sp><speaker>CONTROLLER</speaker>
<name type="ORG">Imperial</name> walkers on the north 
ridge.</sp>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - ICE PLAIN - SNOW TRENCH</setting>

<sd>The Rebel troops aim their weapons at the horizon as explosions erupt 
all around them.  They are nervous and their grip on their weapons 
tightens from the cold and from fear.</sd>

<sd>Behind the troops a dozen snowspeeders race through the sky.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE LEADER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink) 
		Echo station Five-Seven.  We're 
		on our way.</sp>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - ICE PLAIN - BATTLEFIELD</setting>

<sd>The fleet of snowspeeders races above the ice field at full throttle.  
They accelerate away from the base and head toward the distant walkers.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE LEADER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink) 
		All right, boys, keep tight now.</sp>

<sp><speaker>DACK</speaker>
		Luke, I have no approach vector.  
		I'm not set.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		<name type="NORP">Steady</name>, Dack.  Attack pattern 
		delta.  Go now!</sp>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - ICE PLAIN - BATTLEFIELD</setting>

<sd>The cannons mounted on the walker head fire at the speeders.  Other 
walkers loom in the background.  Two speeders race away past two of the 
enormous walkers and bank to the right.</sd>

<setting>INT.  LUKE'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE LEADER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		All right, I'm coming in.</sp>

<sd>He turns his speeder and heads directly at one of the walkers, flying 
toward its towering legs.  The horizon twists as the speeder banks 
between the legs.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		<name type="ORG">Hobbie</name>, you still with me?</sp>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - ICE PLAIN - BATTLEFIELD</setting>

<sd>Two speeders race directly at the head of a walker, then split and fly 
past it.</sd>

<sd>Three other walkers march onward, firing all cannons.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - ICE PLAIN - SNOWTRENCH</setting>

<sd>Rebel troops fire on the approaching walkers, as the snow and ice 
explode all around them.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - ICE PLAIN - BATTLEFIELD</setting>

<sd>A speeder banks through and away from the legs of a walker.  Two other 
speeders pass the first speeder from the opposite direction.  Other 
Rebel craft race just above the icy plain.</sd>

<sd>A giant walker head swivels and fires, striking a snowspeeder and 
sending it crashing in a ball of flames.</sd>

<setting>INT. IMPERIAL SNOW WALKER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">General Veers</name> and two walker pilots keep a careful eye on the racing 
Rebel snowspeeders as they maneuver their lumbering war machine 
forward.</sd>

<sd>Luke's speeder banks in from the side of Veers's walker and heads 
straight for its viewport, blasting away.  An explosion hits the walker 
window, but dissipates, doing no harm.  The speeder roars up and over 
the impregnable war machine.</sd>

<setting>INT.  LUKE'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE LEADER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke looks back at the walker as it grows smaller in the distance.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		That armor's too strong for 
		blasters.</sp>

<sd>On the horizon, another walker moves up past Luke's cockpit window, 
twisting out of sight as Luke banks and starts another run.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		<name type="ORG">Rogue</name> Group, use your harpoons 
		and tow cables.  Go for the legs.
		It might be our only chance of 
		stopping them.
			(to Dack)
		All right, stand by, Dack.</sp>

<sd>Dack is at the gunner's controls.</sd>

<sp><speaker>DACK</speaker>
		Luke, we've got a malfunction in 
		fire control.  I'll have to cut in 
		the auxiliary.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Just hang on.  <name type="NORP">Han</name>g on, Dack.  Get 
		ready to fire that tow cable.</sp>

<sd>Barely keeping his seat in the tumbling ship, Dack struggles to set up 
his harpoon gun.</sd>

<sd>Luke swings his speeder around and heads toward an oncoming walker.  
Laser bolts and flak fill the air, creating a deadly obstacle course 
for the tiny craft.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - ICE PLAIN - BATTLEFIELD</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Rogue</name> Leader and another snowspeeder fly in tight formation toward the 
walker as explosions burst all around them.</sd>

<setting>INT.  LUKE'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE LEADER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>After sustaining a heavy volley of fire, Luke turns around to see if 
Dack is all right.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Dack?  Dack!</sp>

<sd>Dack is lost.  Blood streams down his forehead, which rests on his 
smoldering controls.  Out the back window, an <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> walker recedes 
in the distance.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - ICE PLAIN - SNOW TRENCH AREA</setting>

<sd>Rebel troops fire the dishlike ray gun while explosions erupt around 
them.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - ICE PLAIN - BATTLEFIELD</setting>

<sd>Two walkers lumber toward the Rebel base as a speeder between them 
explodes in a ball of flames.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - ICE PLAIN - SNOW TRENCH</setting>

<sd>The dislike ray gun is hit by a laser bolt and instantly explodes.</sd>

<setting>INT. IMPERIAL SNOW WALKER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Through the cockpit window, Veers and his pilot can see the Rebel power 
generators in the distance.</sd>

<sd>A hologram of Darth Vader appears on a control panel screen.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VEERS</speaker>
		Yes, Lord Vader.  I've reached the 
		main power generator.  The shield 
		will be down in moments.  You may 
		start your landing.</sp>

<setting>INT.  LUKE'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE LEADER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink) 
		<name type="ORG">Rogue</name> Three.</sp>

<setting>INT. WEDGE'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE THREE - COCKPIT</setting>

<sp><speaker>WEDGE</speaker>
			(into comlink) 
		Copy, <name type="ORG">Rogue</name> Leader</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE </speaker>
			(over comlink) 
		Wedge, I've lost my gunner.  You'll 
		have to make this shot.  I'll cover 
		for you.  Set your harpoon.  Follow 
		me on the next pass.</sp>

<sp><speaker>WEDGE</speaker>
			(into comlink) 
		Coming around, <name type="ORG">Rogue</name> Leader.</sp>

<setting>INT.  LUKE'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE LEADER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink) 
		<name type="NORP">Steady</name>, <name type="ORG">Rogue</name> Two</sp>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - BATTLEFIELD</setting>

<sd>Wedge's speeder races through the legs of one of the monstrous walkers.</sd>

<setting>INT. WEDGE'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE THREE - COCKPIT</setting>

<sp><speaker>WEDGE</speaker>
			(to gunner) 
		Activate harpoon.</sp>

<sd>Wedge's gunner reaches for a firing switch to activate the harpoon.  
The harpoon flashes out, and speeds toward the receding legs of the 
walker.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - BATTLEFIELD</setting>

<sd>The harpoon hurtles toward the walker, In an instant it is embedded in 
one of the walker's legs.</sd>

<setting>INT. WEDGE'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE THREE - COCKPIT</setting>

<sp><speaker>WEDGE </speaker>
			(to gunner) 
		Good shot, Janson.</sp>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - BATTLEFIELD</setting>

<sd>The speeder <name type="ORG">Rogue</name> Three races around one of the giant walker's feet, 
trailing the cable behind it.  Continuing around the back foot, <name type="ORG">Rogue</name> 
Three then circles the walker around the tail end.</sd>

<setting>INT. WEDGE'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE THREE - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Wedge checks his controls and banks around the front of the walker.</sd>

<sp><speaker>WEDGE</speaker>
		One more pass.</sp>

<sp><speaker>JANSON </speaker>
		Coming around.  Once more.</sp>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - BATTLEFIELD</setting>

<sd>The speeder sweeps left to right in front of the giant legs, towing the 
cable behind it.</sd>

<setting>INT. WEDGE'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE THREE - COCKPIT</setting>

<sp><speaker>JANSON</speaker>
		Once more.</sp>

<sd>Wedge swings the speeder between the legs of the giant walker.</sd>

<sp><speaker>JANSON</speaker>
		Cable out!  Let her go!</sp>

<sp><speaker>WEDGE</speaker>
		Detach cable.</sp>

<setting>EXT. WEDGE'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE THREE</setting>

<sd>The cable release on the back of the speeder snaps loose and the cable 
drops away.</sd>

<setting>INT. WEDGE'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE THREE - COCKPIT</setting>

<sp><speaker>JANSON</speaker>
		Cable detached.</sp>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - BATTLEFIELD</setting>

<sd>The speeder zooms away into the distance.  The tangled legs of the 
enormous war machine attempt a step, but as they do the giant <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> 
walker begins to topple.  It teeters for a moment, and then crashes 
onto the icy ground, sending snow and metal pieces flying.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - ICE PLAIN - SNOW TRENCH</setting>

<sd>The troops in the trenches cheer at the sight of the crashing walker.</sd>

<sd>An officer gives a signal to his men and Rebel troops charge the fallen 
war machine.</sd>

<sp><speaker>TRENCH OFFICER</speaker>
		Come on!</sp>

<sd>The troops run toward the downed walker, followed by two Rebel speeders 
flying overhead.  Just as they reach the walker, it explodes, the 
impact throwing some of the men onto the frozen ground.</sd>

<setting>INT. WEDGE'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE THREE - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Wedge lets out a triumphant yell, banking his speeder away from the 
fallen walker.</sd>

<sp><speaker>WEDGE</speaker>
			(into comlink) 
		<name type="ORG">Whooha</name>!  That got him!</sp>

<setting>INT.  LUKE'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE LEADER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink) 
		I see it, Wedge.  Good work.</sp>

<setting>INT. REBEL BASE - COMMAND CENTER</setting>

<sd>Large chunks of ice tumble into the command center as Leia and General 
Rieekan monitor computer screens.</sd>

<sp><speaker>RIEEKAN</speaker>
		I don't think we can protect two 
		transports at a time.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA </speaker>
		It's risky, but we can't hold out 
		much longer.  We have no choice.</sp>

<sp><speaker>RIEEKAN</speaker>
			(into comlink) 
		Launch patrols.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
			(to an aide) 
		Evacuate remaining ground staff.</sp>

<setting>INT. REBEL BASE - MAIN HANGAR</setting>

<sd>Muffled distant explosions create widening cracks in the ice roof of 
the hangar.  Trying to ignore the noise and falling bits of snow, <name type="NORP">Han</name> 
works on one of the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>'s lifters while Chewie works on one of the 
wings.  Noticing Chewie attach a wrong part, <name type="NORP">Han</name> grows impatient.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		No, no!  No!  This one goes there, 
		that one goes there.  Right?</sp>

<sd>In another area of the hangar, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> watches as <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> is raised up 
into Luke's X-wing fighter.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		<name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, you take good care of 
		Master Luke now, understand?  And
		... do take good care of yourself.  
		Oh, dear, oh, dear.</sp>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - BATTLEFIELD</setting>

<sd>The fierce battle on the vast snow plains of <name type="GPE">Hoth</name> rages on.  The 
<name type="ORG">Imperial</name> walkers continue their slow, steady assault on the Rebel base, 
firing lasers as they lumber ever onward.  In the snow trench, Rebel 
troops fire large bazookalike guns and dishlike ray guns as explosions 
erupt around them.  A gun tower is hit by a laser bolt and instantly 
explodes.  Another blast destroys a ray gun.</sd>

<setting>INT. IMPERIAL SNOW WALKER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">General Veers</name> studies various readouts on his control panel.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VEERS</speaker>
		All troops will debark for ground 
		assault.  Prepare to target the 
		main generator.</sp>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - BATTLEFIELD</setting>

<sd>Luke's speeder and <name type="ORG">Rogue</name> Two fly in formation, banking from right to 
left and flying above the erupting battlefield.  Flak bursts all around 
them.</sd>

<setting>INT.  LUKE'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE LEADER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke, glancing over, sees <name type="ORG">Rogue</name> Two on his left.  His ship shudders as 
flak bursts nearby.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink) 
		<name type="ORG">Rogue</name> Two, are you all right?</sp>

<setting>INT. ZEV'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE TWO - COCKPIT</setting>

<sp><speaker>ZEV</speaker>
			(into comlink) 
		Yeah.  I'm with you, <name type="ORG">Rogue</name> Leader.</sp>

<setting>INT.  LUKE'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE LEADER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink) 
		We'll set harpoon.  I'll cover for you.</sp>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - BATTLEFIELD</setting>

<sd>The two speeders race across the horizon toward the giant walkers.</sd>

<setting>INT. ZEV'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE TWO - COCKPIT</setting>

<sp><speaker>ZEV</speaker>
			(into comlink) 
		Coming around.</sp>

<setting>INT.  LUKE'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE LEADER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink) 
		Watch that cross fire, boys.</sp>

<setting>INT. ZEV'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE TWO - COCKPIT</setting>

<sp><speaker>ZEV</speaker>
			(into comlink) 
		Set for position three.
			(to gunner) 
		<name type="NORP">Steady</name>.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(over comlink) 
		Stay tight and low.</sp>

<setting>EXT. ZEV'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE TWO</setting>

<sd>Luke's speeder moves in formation with <name type="ORG">Rogue</name> Two, when suddenly Zev's 
speeder is hit by a laser bolt.  His ship bucks violently under the 
impact and the cockpit explodes in a ball of flame.</sd>

<sd>Spewing smoke, the speeder hurtles toward a looming walker.  Before 
they collide.  <name type="ORG">Rogue</name> Two explodes in a million flaming pieces.</sd>

<setting>INT. LUKE'S SNOWSPEEDER, ROGUE LEADER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Desperately, Luke works the controls of his flak-buffeted ship.  
Suddenly, the speeder is rocked by a huge explosion.  Luke struggles 
with the controls with a look of terror on his face.  The speeder fills 
with smoke, and electrical sparks jump about the cockpit.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink) 
		<name type="ORG">Hobbie</name>, I've been hit!</sp>

<setting>INT. REBEL BASE - COMMAND CENTER</setting>

<sd>Apart from the distant thunder of laser blasts, the corridor is 
strangely quiet and empty.  Running footsteps echo through the freezing 
hallway, then <name type="NORP">Han</name> appears.  Cracks have appeared in some of the walls 
and some pipes have broken, sending hot steam billowing into the 
underground hallways.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> hurries into the command center.  It is a 
shambles, but some people are still at their posts.  As he enters, a 
gigantic cave-in almost obliterates the room.  He finds Leia and 
<name type="ORG">Threepio</name> near one of the control boards.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		You all right?</sp>

<sd>Leia nods.  She is surprised to see him.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Why are you still here?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		I heard the command center had 
		been hit.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		You got your clearance to leave.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Don't worry.  I'll leave.  First 
		I'm going to get you to your ship.</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Your Highness, we must take this 
		last transport.  It's our only hope.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
			(to controller) 
		Send all troops in sector twelve 
		to <name type="LOC">the south slope</name> to protect the 
		fighters.</sp>

<sd>A blast rocks the command center, throwing <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> backward into <name type="NORP">Han</name>'s 
arms.</sd>

<sp><speaker>ANNOUNCER</speaker>
			(over loudspeaker) 
		<name type="ORG">Imperial</name> troops have entered the 
		base.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Come on... that's it.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
			(to head controller) 
		Give the evacuation code signal.  
		And get to your transports!</sp>

<sd>Leia looks exhausted.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> grabs her and starts to lead her out.</sd>

<sd>As <name type="NORP">Han</name>, Leia, and <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> run out of the command center, the code 
signal can be heard echoing off the corridor walls.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HEAD CONTROLLER</speaker>
		K-one-zero... all troops disengage.</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
			(to <name type="NORP">Han</name> and Leia) 
		Oh!  Wait for me!</sp>

<setting>EXT. BATTLEFIELD - SNOW TRENCH</setting>

<sd>Rebel troops retreat under the awesome <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> onslaught.</sd>

<sp><speaker>OFFICER</speaker>
		Begin retreat!</sp>

<sp><speaker>SECOND OFFICER</speaker>
		Fall back!</sp>

<sd>Troops flee from the battle, the ground exploding around them.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - BATTLEFIELD</setting>

<sd>Three of the giant walkers, firing lasers, advance toward the Rebel 
headquarters.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - SNOW TRENCH</setting>

<sd>Continuing their retreat, the <name type="ORG">Rebels</name> see the walkers looming ever 
nearer.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - BATTLEFIELD - ICE PLAIN</setting>

<sd>On the battlefield, Luke watches as a walker foot rises and moves over 
him.  He looks up at the underbelly of the huge walker, passing 
overhead.</sd>

<sd>Running beneath the monstrous machine, Luke fires his harpoon gun at 
the walker's underside.  A thin cable follows the projectile from the 
gun.  The magnetic head and cable attach firmly to the metal hull.</sd>

<sd>Still running under the walker, Luke attaches the cable drum to his 
belt buckle.  Soon he is pulled up the cable and hangs dangling 
underneath the walker.</sd>

<sd>The walker's giant feet continue to pound onward across the frozen 
snow.  Stray laser bolts whistle by Luke as he climbs up the cable to 
the walker's hull, reaching a small hatch.  <name type="NORP">Han</name>ging precariously, Luke 
cuts the solid metal hatch with his laser sword.</sd>

<sd>He takes a landmine from around his neck and throws it inside the 
<name type="ORG">Imperial</name> machine.  Quickly, Luke starts down the cable and crashes onto 
the icy ground far below.  He lies unconscious as a giant rear leg 
passes by - and just misses him.</sd>

<sd>The giant walker stops in mid-step.  A muffled explosion comes from 
within - and then the walker's mechanical insides  are spewed out every 
conceivable opening.  The machine sits dead in its tracks, smoking like 
a locomotive on stilts.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - BATTLEFIELD</setting>

<sd>Veers's walker continues to advance toward the Rebel base.  The 
smoldering walker that Luke exploded stands smoking just to the right 
of Veers's path.</sd>

<setting>INT. IMPERIAL SNOW WALKER - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Inside his walker, <name type="ORG">General Veers</name> prepares to fire on the Rebel power 
generators.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VEERS</speaker>
		Distance to power generators?</sp>

<sp><speaker>PILOT</speaker>
		One-seven, decimal two-eight.</sp>

<sd>Veers reaches for the electrorangefinder and lines up the main 
generator.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VEERS</speaker>
		<name type="ORG">Target</name>.  Maximum fire power.</sp>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - BATTLEFIELD</setting>

<sd>The Rebel troops continue their desperate retreat, pushed back by the 
relentless <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> assault.</sd>

<setting>INT. HOTH - REBEL BASE - ICE CORRIDORS</setting>

<sd>With <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> lagging behind, <name type="NORP">Han</name> and Leia race through the crumbling 
ice corridors.  Suddenly, there is an explosion.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> turns, grabs the 
princess, and pulls her to the wall as a tremendous cave-in blacks 
their path.</sd>

<sd>He takes the comlink from his pocket.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN </speaker>
			(into comlink) 
		Transport, this is Solo.  Better 
		take off - I can't get to you.  
		I'll get the princess out on the 
		<name type="ORG">Falcon</name>.</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> and Leia turn and race down the corridor.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		But... but... but... where are 
		you going?  Uh... come back!!</sp>

<setting>INT. HOTH - REBEL BASE - COMMAND CENTER</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Imperial</name> troops have reached the base.  As they push through the 
blocked passageway, Darth Vader strides behind them.</sd>

<setting>INT. HOTH - REBEL BASE - ICE CORRIDOR</setting>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> and Leia run toward the entrance of the main hangar where the 
Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> is docked.  <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> still lags behind.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Wait!  Wait for me!  Wait!  Stop!</sp>

<sd>The door to the hangar closes in his face.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
			(exasperated) 
		How typical.</sp>

<sd>Quickly, the door reopens as <name type="NORP">Han</name> reaches out and pulls the golden droid 
through.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Come on.</sp>

<setting>INT. HOTH - REBEL BASE - MAIN HANGAR</setting>

<sd>Chewie paces under the shelter of the Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>'s landing gear.  
The giant <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> pats the underbelly of his beloved ship and barks a 
few reassuring words.  As he searches worriedly for his captain, 
something at last catches his eye.</sd>

<sd>Chewie lets out a relieved shriek at seeing <name type="NORP">Han</name> and Leia running toward 
the ship.  The <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> runs out into the falling ice, lets out a howl, 
then runs up the ship's ramp.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> and Leia run up the ramp after him, 
closely followed by <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Hurry up, goldenrod, or you're 
		going to be a permanent resident!</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Wait!  Wait!</sp>

<setting>INT. HOTH - REBEL BASE - ICE CORRIDOR</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Imperial</name> troops run through the base corridors.  Vader surveys the 
place.  A huge chunk falls, almost hitting him, but  he calmly, 
purposefully, continues around it.</sd>

<setting>INT. REBEL BASE - MAIN HANGER - MILLENNIUM FALCON</setting>

<sd>A distant, huge, explosion rocks the hangar deck.  Ice cakes come 
crashing down on the Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>.</sd>

<setting>INT. MAIN HANGAR - MILLENNIUM FALCON - MAIN HOLD</setting>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name>, standing before a control panel, is busy flipping switches as 
Chewie watches a troublesome gauge.  A worried Leia observes their 
efforts.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(to Chewie)
		How's this?</sp>

<sd>The <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> barks a negative reply.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Would it helped if I got out and 
		pushed?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		It might.</sp>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> clanks into the hold.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Captain Solo, Captain Solo... sir, 
		might I suggest that you...</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> gives the gold robot a devastating look.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		It can wait.</sp>

<setting>INT. MAIN HANGAR - MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>They move to the cockpit where <name type="NORP">Han</name> flips some more switches.  Leia 
watches him, impatient, disbelieving.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		This bucket of bolts is never going 
		to get us past that blockade.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		This baby's got a few surprises 
		left in her, sweetheart.</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> and Leia look out the cockpit window and see a squad of 
stormtroopers rushing into the far side of the hangar.</sd>

<sd>Quickly, <name type="NORP">Han</name> straps himself into the pilot's seat and Leia into the 
navigator's chair.</sd>

<setting>INT. HOTH - REBEL BASE - MAIN HANGAR</setting>

<sd>Stormtroopers hurriedly set up a large bazookalike weapon.  Behind them 
the giant hangar doors open slowly.</sd>

<setting>EXT. MAIN HANGAR - MILLENNIUM FALCON</setting>

<sd>A laser gun appears on the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> and swings around to aim at the 
<name type="ORG">Imperial</name> troops.</sd>

<sd>The stormtroopers, preparing to fire their bazooka cannon, are hit by 
the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>'s fire and are thrown about in all directions.</sd>

<setting>INT. MAIN HANGAR - MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Chewie rushes into the cockpit.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Come on!  Come on!  Switch over.
		Let's hope we don't have a burnout.</sp>

<sd>A laser hits the window near Chewie as he is settling into his chair.  
Letting out a loud whelp, Chewie quickly pulls back on the controls and 
the first stage of engine fire can be heard.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> flashes a big grin at 
Leia.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		See?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Someday you're going to be wrong, 
		and I hope I'm there to see it.</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> looks at Chewie.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Punch it!</sp>

<sd>The roar of the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>'s main engines blasts out everything as the ice-
cave wall rushes by outside the cockpit window.</sd>

<setting>INT. REBEL BASE - MAIN HANGAR</setting>

<sd>More stormtroopers run into the hangar, closely followed by Vader.  
Hearing the loud roar of the Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>'s engines, Vader looks 
toward the main hangar doors just in time to see the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> lift up and 
disappear outside the cave.</sd>

<setting>EXT. HOTH - ICE SLOPE - DAY</setting>

<sd>Luke and two other pilots look up as the Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> races above 
them, flying very close to the ground.</sd>

<sd>The three pilots turn then, and trudge onward toward their X-wing 
fighters, each going to his own ship.  Luke waves farewell, then heads 
toward his own fighter.  </sd>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, seated on his cubbyhole, chirps an excited greeting as Luke 
climbs aboard the spacecraft.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		<name type="GPE">Artoo</name>!  Get her ready for takeoff.</sp>

<sd>From his ship, Luke sees Wedge in his own X-wing, preparing for 
takeoff.</sd>

<sp><speaker>WEDGE</speaker>
		Good luck, Luke.  See you at 
		the rendezvous.</sp>

<sd>Luke smiles and nods at Wedge, then lowers himself into the cockpit of 
his X-wing while <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> waits in the cubbyhole, beeping impatiently.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Don't worry, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>.  We're going, 
		we're going.</sp>

<sd>The canopy over the X-wing lowers and snaps shut.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE -  LUKE'S X-WING</setting>

<sd>Luke's fighter, its wings closed, speeds away from the icy planet.  
Soon it disappears into the stars.</sd>

<setting>INT.  LUKE'S X-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke, looking thoughtful, suddenly makes a decision.  He flips several 
switches.  The stars shift as he takes his fighter into a steep turn.  
The X-wing banks sharply and flies away in a new direction.</sd>

<sd>The monitor screen on Luke's control panel prints out a question from 
the concerned <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		There's nothing wrong, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>.
		I'm just setting a new course.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps once again.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		We're not going to regroup with 
		the others.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> begins a protest, whistling an unbelieving, "What?!"</sd>

<sd>Luke reads <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>'s exclamation on his control panel.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		We're going to the <name type="FAC">Dagobah</name> system.</sp>

<sd>Luke checks his readouts and makes a few adjustments.  He rides along 
with only the soft hum of the instruments to break the silence.  
Finally, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> chirps up.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		Yes, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>?</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> utters a soft, carefully phrased steam of whistles.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink, chuckling)
		That's all right.  I'd like to 
		keep it on manual control for a 
		while.</sp>

<sd>The little droid lets out a defeated whimper.  Luke smiles, and 
continues on his course.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - MILLENNIUM FALCON</setting>

<sd>The Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> speeds away from <name type="GPE">Hoth</name>, closely followed by one 
huge <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name> and four tiny <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters.</sd>

<sd>As it is pursued, the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> races toward two very bright star-sized 
objects.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Inside the cockpit, Chewie lets out a loud howl.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> checks as the 
ship is buffeted by exploding flak.  He appears to be doing six things 
at once.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(harried)
		I saw them!  I saw them!</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Saw what?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		<name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name>s, two of them, 
		coming right at us.</sp>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> bumps and bangs his way into the cockpit.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Sir, sir!  Might I suggest...</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(to Leia)
		Shut him up or shut him down!
			(to Chewie)
		Check the deflector shield!</sp>

<sd>Chewie barks a reply as he readjusts an overhead switch.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Oh, great.  Well, we can still 
		outmaneuver them.</sp>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - MILLENNIUM FALCON - STAR DESTROYERS</setting>

<sd>The Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> races toward one of the huge oncoming Star 
Destroyers.  Suddenly, the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> starts into a deep dive straight 
down, closely followed by four <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters.  The underside of the Star 
Destroyer continues on a collision course with two oncoming Star 
Destroyers.  Slowly, it starts to veer to the left.</sd>

<setting>INT. STAR DESTROYER - BRIDGE</setting>
Out the front window, the two approaching <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name>s can be seen 
veering to the left.

<sp><speaker>IMPERIAL OFFICER</speaker>
		Take evasive action!</sp>

<sd>Alarms sound all over the huge ship.  The two other <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name>s get 
closer, one of them moving over the bridge so close that it makes 
brushing contact with it.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - MILLENNIUM FALCON - <name type="ORG">TIE</name> FIGHTERS</setting>

<sd>The Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> races away from the colliding <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name>s, 
still followed by four <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters.  Laser bolts spark the pitch-black 
skies.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Things have calmed down a bit, but the race isn't over yet.  Chewie 
barks at <name type="NORP">Han</name>.  Leia is still trying to recover from the steep dive.  
The ship is buffeted by laser blasts.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Prepare to make the jump to light-
		speed.</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		But, sir!</sp>

<sd>The buffeting of lasers becomes louder and stronger.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		They're getting closer!</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(with a gleam in his 
			 eye)
		Oh yeah?  Watch this.</sp>

<sd>Expectantly, they look out the cockpit window as stars do not go into 
hyperspace, but just sit there.</sd>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> and Chewie look at each other and are thrown into an acute state of 
concern.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Watch what?</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> tries again.  Still nothing.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		I think we're in trouble.</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		If I may say so, sir, I noticed 
		earlier that the hyperdrive 
		motivator has been damaged.  It's 
		impossible to go to light-speed!</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		We're in trouble!</sp>

<sd>The explosions become heavier.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - MILLENNIUM FALCON - <name type="ORG">TIE</name> FIGHTERS - STAR DESTROYER</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> races into the starry vastness, followed by the four 
<name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters and an <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name>.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Stars race by as flak bursts outside the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>'s window.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - HOLD</setting>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> works furiously at some control panels while giving various orders 
to Chewie.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Horizontal boosters...!
			(Chewie barks)
		Alluvial dampers...!  Well that's 
		not it.
			(Chewie barks)
		Bring me the hydrospanners!</sp>

<sd>Chewie hurries over to the pit and places the tools on the edge.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		I don't know how we're going to 
		get out of this one.</sp>

<sd>Suddenly, a loud thump hits the side of the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>, causing it to lurch 
radically.  Chewie barks.  The tools fall into the pit on top of <name type="NORP">Han</name>.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Oww!  Chewie!</sp>

<sd>More turbulence rocks the ship.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		That was no laser blast!  Something 
		hit us.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
			(over comlink)
		<name type="NORP">Han</name>, get up here!</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Come on, Chewie!</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> climbs out of the hold like a shot.  Both he and Chewie run out of 
the hold and toward the cockpit.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Out the front cockpit window, they see hundreds of asteroids racing by.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Asteroids!</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> changes places with Leia who has been at the controls, and Chewie 
gets into his chair.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> works his controls as a chunk of rock crosses 
in front of the ship.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Oh, no!  Chewie, set two-seven-
		one.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		What are you doing?  You're not 
		actually going into an asteroid 
		field?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		They'd be crazy to follow us, 
		wouldn't they?</sp>

<sd>Another asteroid thumps against the ship and Leia winces at the jolt.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		You don't have to do this to 
		impress me.</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Sir, the possibility of successfully 
		navigating an asteroid field is 
		approximately three thousand, seven 
		hundred and twenty to one.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Never tell me the odds!</sp>

<setting>EXT. ASTEROID BELT - MILLENNIUM FALCON</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> turns into the asteroid storm and as the ship completes its 
turn, asteroids start coming straight at the cockpit windows.</sd>

<sd>A large asteroid tumbles away from the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>'s path at top speed.  
Several smaller asteroids crash into the big one, creating small 
explosions on its surface.  Other asteroids of all sizes pass by in 
every direction, some colliding and exploding.  The tiny Millennium 
<name type="ORG">Falcon</name> veers around the big asteroid and races past it through the rain 
of rocks, followed by four <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters, which bob and weave around the 
asteroids.</sd>

<sd>One of the pursuing <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters connects with an asteroid and 
explodes.  The other fighters are pelted with a steady stream of 
smaller explosions.</sd>

<sd>Two huge asteroids tumble toward the Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>, which quickly 
banks around both of them.  The three <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters follow in hot 
pursuit until one of the fighters scrapes an asteroid and tumbles out 
of control into deep space.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - STAR DESTROYER - ASTEROID BELT</setting>

<sd>The massive <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name> blasts oncoming asteroids as it follows the 
<name type="ORG">Falcon</name>.  Smaller asteroids explode across its vast surface.</sd>

<setting>EXT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - <name type="ORG">TIE</name> FIGHTERS - ASTEROID BELT</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> twists on its side as it races around an oncoming asteroid.  
Two <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters follow in the distance, coming from either side.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Asteroids race by the cockpit window as <name type="NORP">Han</name> pilots his trusty craft 
through the dangerous field.</sd>

<sd>Looking out the cockpit window, the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> crew sees a big asteroid 
drop past the window, narrowly missing their ship.</sd>

<sd>Chewie barks in terror as a slightly smaller asteroid comes especially 
close - to close - and bounces off the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> with a loud crunch.  
<name type="ORG">Threepio</name>'s hands cover his eyes.  He manages a short peek at the 
cockpit window.  Princess Leia sits stone-faced, staring at the action.  
<name type="NORP">Han</name> gives her a quick look.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		You said you wanted to be around 
		when I made a mistake; well, this 
		could be it, sweetheart.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		I take it back.  We're going to 
		get pulverized if we stay out here 
		much longer.</sp>

<sd>The group watches as more asteroids race by outside the window.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		I'm not going to argue with that.</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Pulverized?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		I'm going in closer to one of 
		those big ones.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Closer?</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Closer?!</sp>

<sd>Chewbacca barks the same word, only louder.</sd>

<setting>EXT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - ASTEROID BELT</setting>

<sd>The Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> dives toward the surface of one of <name type="LOC">the moon</name>-sized 
asteroids.  There is a continued display of explosions against the 
starry void as smaller asteroids collide with larger chunks of rock.  
The two remaining <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters follow the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> to the large asteroid.  
The <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> skims the surface of the giant asteroid as, all the while, 
small asteroids explode on the surface of the ship.</sd>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters approach the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>, but a giant asteroid hurtles 
directly into their path.  As the asteroid continues on its way, it 
leaves remains of the two exploded <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters to tumble into deep 
space.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Rattled by the violent rocking of the starship, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> is nearly in 
hysterics.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Oh, this is suicide!</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> notices something on his main scope and nudges his faithful 
<name type="NORP">Wookiee</name>, pointing.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		There.  That looks pretty good.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		What looks pretty good?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Yeah.  That'll do nicely.</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
			(to Leia)
		Excuse me, ma'am, but where are 
		we going?</sp>

<sd>Out the cockpit window, they see that they are skimming the surface of 
the enormous asteroid and nearing a large crater.</sd>

<setting>EXT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - GIANT ASTEROID CRATER</setting>

<sd>The Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> dives into the huge crater and disappears.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		I hope you know what you're doing.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Yeah, me too.</sp>

<setting>INT. GIANT ASTEROID CRATER</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> races down into the crater.  The walls are barely visible as 
the ship speed through the tunnellike opening.  A small cave appears on 
one side of the crater, and the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> turns, slows, and scoots into 
it.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE -  LUKE'S X-WING</setting>

<sd>The tiny X-wing speeds toward the cloud cover of <name type="FAC">Dagobah</name>.  <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, 
riding on the back of the fighter, turns his head back and forth with 
some anxiety.</sd>

<setting>INT.  LUKE'S X-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke watches <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>'s words as they are translated and screened on the 
computer scope.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		Yes, that's it.  <name type="FAC">Dagobah</name>.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps a hopeful inquiry.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		No, I'm not going to change my 
		mind about this.
			(getting a little nervous)
		I'm not picking up any cities or
		technology.  Massive life-form 
		readings, though.  There's something
		alive down there...</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps, this time a slightly worried question.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		Yes, I'm sure it's perfectly safe 
		for droids.</sp>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - DAGOBAH -  LUKE'S X-WING</setting>

<sd>The X-wing continues its flight through the twilight above the cloud-
covered planet.</sd>

<setting>INT.  LUKE'S X-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke sees the cloud race by as he takes his craft closer to the planet.  
He must operate his controls carefully since the cloud cover has 
completely obscured his vision.  An alarm buzzes in the background, 
<name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps and whistles frantically.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		I know, I know!  All the scopes are 
		dead.  I can't see a thing!  Just 
		hang on, I'm going to start the 
		landing cycle...</sp>

<sd>The blast of the retrorockets is deafening, drowning out <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>'s 
electronic squeals.  Suddenly, there is a cracking sound as if limbs 
were being broken off trees and then a tremendous jolt as the 
spacecraft stops.  Luke pulls a switch and his canopy pops open.</sd>

<setting>EXT. DAGOBAH - DUSK</setting>

<sd>The mist-shrouded X-wing fighter is almost invisible in the thick fog.  
Luke climbs out onto the long nose of the spacecraft as <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> pops out 
of his cubbyhole on the back.  The young warrior surveys the fog, which 
is barely pierced by the ship's landing lights.  About all he can make 
out are some giant, twisted trees nearby.  <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> whistles anxiously.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		No, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, you stay put.  I'll 
		have a look around.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> lets out a short beep.  As Luke moves along the nose, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> loses 
his balance and disappears with a splash into the boggy lake.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		<name type="GPE">Artoo</name>?</sp>

<sd>Luke kneels and leans over the plane looking for <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, but the water 
is still and reveals no sign of the little droid.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		<name type="GPE">Artoo</name>!  Where are you?</sp>

<sd>A small periscope breaks the surface of the water and a gurgly beep is 
heard.  The periscope starts to move to shore.  Relieved, Luke starts 
running along the nose of the fighter to its tip.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		<name type="GPE">Artoo</name>!  You be more careful.</sp>

<sd>The outline of the shore is now more than ten feet away.</sd>

<sd>Luke jumps off the plane into the water, scrambles up to the shore, and 
turns to look for <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>.  The periscope still steadily moves toward 
shore.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		<name type="GPE">Artoo</name> - that way!</sp>

<sd>Suddenly, through the thick fog layer, a dark shape appears, moving 
toward the little droid.  The dark, sinuous bog beast dives beneath the 
swampy water, making a loud clunk against <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>'s metal hull.  The 
droid disappears from sight, uttering a pathetic electronic scream.</sd>

<sd>Holding his ignited lightsaber before him, Luke wades a few feet into 
the murky pool, looking for any sign of his little friend.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		<name type="GPE">Artoo</name>!</sp>

<sd>The black surface is still as death itself... until a few bubbles begin 
to appear.  Then, phheewaat!! The runt-size robot is spit out of the 
water, makes a graceful arc, and comes crashing down into a patch of 
soft gray moss.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Oh, no!  Are you all right?  Come 
		on.  You're lucky you don't taste 
		very good.  Anything broken?</sp>

<sd>Luke helps <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> to his feet and begins wiping the mud and roots from 
his round metal body.  <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> responds with feeble, soggy beeps.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		If you're saying coming here was 
		a bad idea, I'm beginning to agree 
		with you.  Oh, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, what are we 
		doing here?  It's like... something 
		out of a dream, or, I don't know.  
		Maybe I'm just going crazy.</sp>

<sd>As Luke glances around at the spooky swamp jungle that surrounds him, 
<name type="GPE">Artoo</name> ejects a stream of muddy water from one of his cranial ports.</sd>

<setting>EXT. VADER'S STAR DESTROYER - VADER'S CHAMBER</setting>

<sd>Admiral Piett hesitates in the entryway to Vader's private cubicle.</sd>

<sd>After a moment, he steps into the room and pauses at the surprising 
sight before him.</sd>

<sd>Darth Vader, his back turned, is silhouetted in the gloom on the far 
side of the chamber.  A black, insectlike droid attends him.  Among the 
various apparatuses surrounding them, a respirator tube now retracts 
from Vader's uncovered head.  The head is bald with a mass of ugly scar 
tissue covering it.  The black droid then lowers the mask and helmet 
onto Vader's head.  When it is in place, the Dark Lord turns to face 
Piett.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Yes, Admiral?</sp>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
Our ships have sighted the 
Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>, lord.  But... 
it has entered an asteroid field 
and we cannot risk...</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
			(interrupting)
		Asteroids do not concern me, 
		Admiral.  I want that ship and 
		not excuses.</sp>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		Yes, lord.</sp>

<setting>EXT. ASTEROID CAVE - MILLENNIUM FALCON</setting>

<sd>The pirate starship rests in a dark, dripping asteroid cave.  It is so 
dark that the cave's exact dimensions are impossible to determine.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> and Chewie busily shut down the engine and all electronic systems.  
<name type="ORG">Threepio</name> and Leia watch worriedly.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		I'm going to shut down everything 
		but the emergency power systems.  </sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Sir, I'm almost afraid to ask, 
		but... does that include shutting 
		me down, too?</sp>

<sd>Chewie barks "yes".  But <name type="NORP">Han</name> thinks otherwise.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		No, I need you to talk to the 
		<name type="ORG">Falcon</name>, find out what's wrong with 
		the hyperdrive.</sp>

<sd>Suddenly, the ship lurches, causing all the loose items in the cockpit 
to go flying.  Chewie howls.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Sir, it's quite possible this 
		asteroid is not entirely stable.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Not entirely stable?  I'm glad you're 
		here to tell us these things.  Chewie, 
		take the professor in the back and 
		plug him into the hyperdrive.</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Oh!  Sometimes I just don't 
		understand human behavior.  After 
		all, I'm only trying to do my job 
		in the most...</sp>

<sd>The sliding door closes behind the indignant <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> as Chewie and he 
move back to the hold.  Suddenly, the ship lurches again, throwing Leia 
across the cabin into <name type="NORP">Han</name>'s arms.  Then, abruptly, the motion stops as 
suddenly as it started.  With some surprise, <name type="NORP">Han</name> and Leia realize they 
are in each other's arms.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Let go.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Sshh!</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Let go, please.</sp>

<sd>Leia flushes, averting her eyes.  She's not exactly fighting to get 
free.  But, of course, <name type="NORP">Han</name> blows it...</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Don't get excited.</sp>

<sd>The anger rises in Leia.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Captain, being held by you isn't 
		quite enough to get me excited.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Sorry, sweetheart.  We haven't 
		got time for anything else.</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> grins quickly wickedly at Leia as he turns and exits through the 
door.  Leia's confused emotions show clearly on her lovely face.</sd>

<setting>EXT. DAGOBAH - BOG CLEARING - DUSK</setting>

<sd>The mist has dispersed a bit, but it is still a very gloomy-looking 
swamp.</sd>

<sd>Luke pulls an equipment box from the shore to the clearing.  He ignites 
a little fusion furnace and warms his hands before it.  Taking a power 
cable, he plugs it into <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>'s noselike socket.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Ready for some power?  Okay.  
		Let's see now.  Put that in 
		there.  There you go.</sp>

<sd>The droid whistles his appreciation.  Luke then opens a container of 
processed food and sits before the thermal heater.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(sighs)
		Now all I have to do is find this 
		Yoda... if he even exists.</sp>

<sd>Nervously, he looks around at the foreboding jungle.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Still... there's something familiar 
		about this place.  I feel like... 
		I don't know...</sp>

<sp><speaker>STRANGE VOICE</speaker>
		Feel like what?</sp>

<sd>Luke jumps out of his skin.  <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> screeches in terror.  The young 
warrior grabs for his lightsaber as he spins around, looking for the 
speaker.  Mysteriously standing right in front of Luke is a strange, 
bluish creature, not more than two feet tall.  The wizened little thing 
is dressed in rags.  It motions toward Luke's sword.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(looking at the 
			 creature)
		Like we're being watched!</sp>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
		Away with your weapon!  I mean 
		you no harm.</sp>

<sd>After some hesitation, Luke puts away his weapon, although he really 
doesn't understand why.  <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> watches with interest.</sd>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
		I am wondering, why are you here?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		I'm looking for someone.</sp>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
		Looking?  Found someone, you have, 
		I would say, hmmm?</sp>

<sd>The little creature laughs.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(Trying to keep from 
			 smiling)
		Right.</sp>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
		Help you I can.  Yes, <name type="GPE">mmmm</name>.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		I don't think so.  I'm looking 
		for a great warrior.</sp>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
		Ahhh!  A great warrior.
			(laughs and shakes 
			 his head)
		Wars not make one great.</sp>

<sd>With the aid of a walking stick, the tiny stranger moves over to one of 
the cases of supplies.  He begins to rummage around.</sd>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> moves to the edge of the case - standing almost eye level to the 
creature who is carelessly handling the supplies - and squeaks his 
disapproval.</sd>

<sd>Their tiny visitor pick up the container of food Luke was eating from 
and takes a bite.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Put that down.  Hey!  That's my 
		dinner!</sp>

<sd>The creature spits out the bite he has taken.  He makes a face.</sd>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
		How you get so big, eating food 
		of this kind?</sp>

<sd>He flips the container in Luke's direction and reaches into one of 
Luke's supply cases.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Listen, friend, we didn't mean to 
		land in that puddle, and if we 
		could get our ship out, we would, 
		but we can't, so why don't you just...</sp>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
			(teasing)
		Aww, cannot get your ship out?</sp>

<sd>The creature spots something of interest in Luke's case.  Luke loses 
patience and grabs the case away.  The creature retains his prize - a 
tiny power lamp - and examines it with delight.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Hey, you could have broken this.
		Don't do that.  Ohhh... you're 
		making a mess.  Hey, give me that!</sp>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
			(retreating with 
			 the lamp)
		Mine!  Or I will help you not.</sp>

<sd>Clutching its treasure, the creature backs away from Luke, drawing 
closer to <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>.  As Luke and the creature argue, one of <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>'s little 
arms slowly moves out toward the power lamp, completely unnoticed by 
the creature.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		I don't want your help.  I want 
		my lamp back.  I'll need it to 
		get out of this slimy mudhole.</sp>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
		Mudhole?  Slimy?  My home this is.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> grabs hold of the lamp and the two little figures are immediately 
engaged in a tug-of-war over it.</sd>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps a few angry, "Give me thats."</sd>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
		Ah, ah, ah!</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Oh, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, let him have it!</sp>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
		Mine!  Mine!</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		<name type="GPE">Artoo</name>!</sp>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
		Mine!</sp>

<sd>The creature lets go with one hand and pokes <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> lightly with one 
finger.  <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> reacts with a startled squeal, and lets go.</sd>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
		Mine!</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(fed up)
		Now will you move along, little 
		fella?  We're got a lot of work 
		to do.</sp>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
		No!  No, no!  Stay and help you, 
		I will.
			(laughs)
		Find your friend, hmm?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		I'm not looking for a friend. 
		I'm looking for a <name type="ORG">Jedi</name> Master.</sp>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
		Oohhh.  <name type="ORG">Jedi</name> Master.  Yoda.  You 
		seek Yoda.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		You know him?</sp>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
		Mmm.  Take you to him, I will.
			(laughs)
		Yes, yes.  But now, we must eat.
		Come.  Good food.  Come.</sp>

<sd>With that, the creature scurries out of the clearing, laughing merrily.  
Luke stares after him.  All he sees is the faint light from the small 
power lamp moving through the fog.  Luke makes his decision and starts 
after the creature.</sd>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
			(in the distance)
		Come, come.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, very upset, whistles a blue streak of protest.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Stay here and watch after the 
		camp, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps even more frantically.  But as Luke disappears from view, 
the worried little droid grows quieter, and utters a soft electronic 
sigh.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - MAIN HOLD AREA</setting>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> whistles and beeps a strange dialect into the control panel in 
front of him.  The control panel whistles back a few mystifying beeps.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Oh, where is <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> when I need 
		him?</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> enters the hold area and kneels on the floor near the control box.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Sir, I don't know where your ship 
		learned to communicate, but it 
		has the most peculiar dialect.  I 
		believe, sir, it says that the 
		power coupling on the negative 
		axis has been polarized.  I'm 
		afraid you'll have to replace it.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Well, of course I'll have to replace 
		it.</sp>

<sd>He hands a wire coil up to Chewie who is working near the ceiling.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Here!  And Chewie...</sp>

<sd>Chewie brings his head back through the trap door in the ceiling and 
whines.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> glances back at <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, then speaks quietly to Chewie so 
only he can hear.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(continuing)
		... I think we'd better replace 
		the negative power coupling.</sp>

<sd>Leia finishes welding the valves she has been working on and attempts 
to reengage the system by pulling a lever attached to the valve.  It 
doesn't budge.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> notices her struggle, and moves to help her.  She 
rebuffs him.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Hey, Your Worship, I'm only 
		trying to help.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
			(still struggling)
		Would you please stop calling me 
		that?</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> hears a new tone in her voice.  He watches her pull on the lever.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Sure, Leia.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Oh, you make it so difficult 
		sometimes.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		I do, I really do.  You could be 
		a little nicer, though.
			(he watches her 
			 reaction)
		Come on, admit it.  Sometimes you 
		think I'm all right.</sp>

<sd>She lets go of the lever and rubs her sore hand.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Occasionally...
			(a little smile, 
			 haltingly)
		... when you aren't acting like 
		a scoundrel.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(laughs)
		Scoundrel?  Scoundrel?  I like 
		the sound of that.</sp>

<sd>With that, <name type="NORP">Han</name> takes her hand and starts to massage it.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Stop that.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Stop what?</sp>

<sd>Leia is flushes, confused.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Stop that!  My hands are dirty.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		My hands are dirty, too.  What 
		are you afraid of?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
			(looking right 
			 into his eyes)
		Afraid?</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> looks at her with a piercing look.  He's never looked more 
handsome, more dashing, more confident.  He reaches out slowly and 
takes Leia's hand again from where it is resting on a console.  He 
draws it toward him.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		You're trembling.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		I'm not trembling.</sp>

<sd>Then with an irresistible combination of physical strength and 
emotional power, the space pirate begins to draw Leia toward him... 
very slowly.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		You like me because I'm a scoundrel.
		There aren't enough scoundrels in 
		your life.</sp>

<sd>Leia is now very close to <name type="NORP">Han</name> and as she speaks, her voice becomes an 
excited whisper, a tone completely in opposition to her words.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		I happen to like nice men.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		I'm a nice man.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		No, you're not.  You're...</sp>

<sd>He kisses her now, with slow, hot lips.  He takes his time, as though 
he had forever, bending her body backward.  She has never been kissed 
like this before, and it almost makes her faint.  When he stops, she 
regains her breath and tries to work up some indignation, but finds it 
hard to talk.</sd>

<sd>Suddenly, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> appears in the doorway, speaking excitedly.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Sir, sir!  I've isolated the 
		reverse power flux coupling.</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> turns slowly, icily, from their embrace.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Thank you.  Thank you very much.</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Oh, you're perfectly welcome, sir.</sp>

<sd>The moment spoiled, <name type="NORP">Han</name> marches out after <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - ASTEROID FIELD</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> fleet moves through the asteroid-filled void, intently 
seeking its prey.</sd>

<setting>INT. VADER'S STAR DESTROYER - BRIDGE</setting>

<sd>Asteroids collide, creating a fireworks display outside the bridge 
window.  Darth Vader stands, staring out the window above the control 
deck.  Then slowly turns toward the bridge.  Before him are the 
hologram images of twenty battleship commanders.  One of these images, 
the commander of a ship that has just exploded, is fading away quickly.  
Another image, in the center and a little apart from the others, is 
faded and continually disrupted by static.  It is the image of Captain 
Needa, commander of the <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name> most hotly on the tail of the 
Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>.  Admiral Piett and an aide stand behind the Dark 
Lord.</sd>

<sp><speaker>NEEDA</speaker>
			(in hologram)
		... and that, Lord Vader, was the 
		last time they appeared in any of 
		our scopes.  Considering the amount 
		of damage we've sustained, they 
		must have been destroyed.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		No, Captain, they're alive.  I 
		want every ship available to 
		sweep the asteroid field until 
		they are found.</sp>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> star captains fade out one by one as Vader turns to 
Admiral Piett.</sd>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
Lord Vader.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Yes, Admiral, what is it?</sp>

<sd>The admiral is scared, his face white as a sheet.</sd>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		The Emperor commands you make 
		contact with him.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Move the ship out of the asteroid 
		field so that we can send a clear 
		transmission.</sp>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		Yes, my lord.</sp>

<setting>EXT. ASTEROID FIELD - VADER'S STAR DESTROYER</setting>

<sd>Vader's <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name> moves against the vast sea of stars 
away from the rest of the fleet.</sd>

<setting>INT. VADER'S STAR DESTROYER - VADER'S CHAMBER</setting>

<sd>The Dark Lord, Darth Vader, is alone in his chamber.  A strange sound 
enters the room and a light begins to play across Vader's black figure.  
He looks up and bows quickly.</sd>

<sd>A twelve-foot hologram of the Galactic Emperor materializes before 
Vader.  The Emperor's dark robes and monk's hood are reminiscent of the 
cloak worn by Ben <name type="ORG">Kenobi</name>.  His voice is even deeper and more 
frightening than Vader's.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		What is thy bidding, my master?</sp>

<sp><speaker>EMPEROR</speaker>
		There is a great disturbance in 
		the <name type="ORG">Force</name>.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		I have felt it.</sp>

<sp><speaker>EMPEROR</speaker>
		We have a new enemy - Luke 
		Skywalker.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Yes, my master.</sp>

<sp><speaker>EMPEROR</speaker>
		He could destroy us.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		He's just a boy.  Obi-Wan can no 
		longer help him.</sp>

<sp><speaker>EMPEROR</speaker>
		The <name type="ORG">Force</name> is strong with him.  The 
		son of Skywalker must not become a 
		<name type="ORG">Jedi</name>.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		If he could be turned, he would 
		become a powerful ally.</sp>

<sp><speaker>EMPEROR</speaker>
		Yes.  Yes.  He would be a great 
		asset.  Can it be done?</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		He will join us or die, my 
		master.</sp>

<sd>Vader kneels.  The supreme Emperor passes a hand over the crouched Lord 
of the Sith and fades away.</sd>

<setting>EXT. DAGOBAH - CREATURE'S HOUSE - NIGHT</setting>

<sd>A heavy downpour of rain pounds through the gnarled trees.  A strange 
baroque mud house sits on a moss-covered knoll on the edge of a small 
lagoon.  The small, gnomish structure radiates a warm glow from its 
thick glass windows.  As rain tap-dances a merry tune on <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>'s head, 
the stubby little droid rises up on his tip-toes to peek into one of 
the glowing portals.</sd>

<setting>INT. CREATURE'S HOUSE</setting>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, peeking in the window, sees the inside of the house - a very 
plain, but cozy dwelling.  Everything is in the same small scale as the 
creature.  The only thing out of place in the miniature room is Luke, 
whose height makes the four-foot ceiling seem even lower.  He sits 
cross-legged on the floor of the living room.</sd>

<sd>The creature is in an adjoining area - his little kitchen - cooking up 
an incredible meal.  The stove is a steaming hodgepodge of pots and 
pans.  The wizened little host scurries about chopping this, shredding 
that, and showering everything with exotic herbs and spices.  He rushes 
back and forth putting platters on the table in front of Luke, who 
watches the creature impatiently.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Look, I'm sure it's delicious.  
		I just don't understand why we 
		can't see Yoda now.</sp>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
		Patience!  For the <name type="ORG">Jedi</name> it is 
		time to eat as well.  Eat, eat.  
		Hot.  Good food, hm? Good, hmm?</sp>

<sd>Moving with some difficulty in the cramped quarters, Luke sits down 
near the fire and serves himself from the pot.  Tasting the unfamiliar 
concoction, he is pleasantly surprised.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		How far away is Yoda?  Will it 
		take us long to get there?</sp>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
		Not far.  Yoda not far.  Patience.
		Soon you will be with him.
			(tasting food from 
			 the pot)
		<name type="ORG">Rootleaf</name>, I cook.  Why wish you 
		become <name type="ORG">Jedi</name>?  Hm?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Mostly because of my father, I 
		guess.</sp>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
		Ah, your father.  Powerful <name type="ORG">Jedi</name> 
		was he, powerful <name type="ORG">Jedi</name>, mmm.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(a little angry)
		Oh, come on.  How could you know 
		my father?  You don't even know 
		who I am.
			(fed up)
		Oh, I don't know what I'm doing 
		here.  We're wasting our time.</sp>

<sd>The creature turns away from Luke and speaks to a third party.</sd>

<sp><speaker>CREATURE</speaker>
			(irritated)
		I cannot teach him.  The boy has 
		no patience.</sp>

<sd>Luke's head spins in the direction the creature faces.  But there is no 
one there.  The boy is bewildered, but it gradually dawns on him that 
the little creature is Yoda, the <name type="ORG">Jedi</name> Master, and that he is speaking 
with Ben.</sd>

<sp><speaker>BEN'S VOICE</speaker>
		He will learn patience.</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		Hmmm.  Much anger in him, like his father.</sp>

<sp><speaker>BEN'S VOICE</speaker>
		Was I any different when you 
		taught me?</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		Hah.  He is not ready.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Yoda!  I am ready.  I... Ben!  I 
		can be a <name type="ORG">Jedi</name>.  Ben, tell him I'm 
		ready.</sp>

<sd>Trying to see Ben, Luke starts to get up but hits his head on the low 
ceiling.</sd>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		Ready, are you?  What know you 
		of ready?  For eight hundred years 
		have I trained <name type="ORG">Jedi</name>.  My own counsel 
		will I keep on who is to be trained!
		A <name type="ORG">Jedi</name> must have the deepest 
		commitment, the most serious mind.
			(to the invisible 
			 Ben, indicating Luke)
		This one a long time have I watched.
		All his life has he looked away...
		to the future, to the horizon.
		Never his mind on where he was.
		Hmm?  What he was doing.  Hmph.  
		Adventure.  Heh!  Excitement.  Heh!  
		A <name type="ORG">Jedi</name> craves not these things.
			(turning to Luke)
		You are reckless!</sp>

<sd>Luke looks down.  He knows it is true.</sd>

<sp><speaker>BEN'S VOICE</speaker>
		So was I, if you'll remember.</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		He is too old.  Yes, too old to 
		begin the training.</sp>

<sd>Luke thinks he detects a subtle softening in Yoda's voice.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		But I've learned so much.</sp>

<sd>Yoda turns his piercing gaze on Luke, as though the <name type="ORG">Jedi</name> Master's huge 
eyes could somehow determine how much the boy had learned.  After a 
long moment, the little <name type="ORG">Jedi</name> turns toward where he alone sees Ben.</sd>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
			(sighs)
		Will he finished what he begins?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		I won't fail you - I'm not afraid.</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
			(turns slowly toward 
			 him)
		Oh, you will be.  You will be.</sp>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - STAR DESTROYERS - ASTEROID FIELD</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> fleet around Vader's ship is surrounded by the asteroid 
storm.  Asteroids big and small pelt the vast exteriors of the menacing 
ships.  One of the smaller <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> vessels is hit by a huge asteroid 
and explodes in a brilliant flash of light.</sd>

<setting>INT. ASTEROID CAVE - MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>The cockpit is quiet and lit only by the indicator lights on the 
control panel.  Princess Leia sits in the pilot's seat.</sd>

<sd>She runs her hand across the control panel as she thinks of <name type="NORP">Han</name> and the 
confusion he has created within her.  Suddenly, something outside the 
cockpit window catches her eye.  The reflection of the panel lights 
obscures her vision until a soft suctionlike cup attaches itself to the 
windscreen.  Leia
moves closer to see what it might be.  Large, yellow eyes flash open 
and stare back at her.  Startled, she jumps back into her seat, her 
heart pounding.  There is a scurry of feet and a loud screech, and in 
an instant the eyes are gone.  The young princess catches her breath, 
jumps out of her chair, and races from the cockpit.</sd>

<setting>INT. ASTEROID CAVE - MILLENNIUM FALCON - HOLD AREA</setting>

<sd>The lights go bright for a second then out again.  <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> and 
Chewbacca watch as <name type="NORP">Han</name> finishes with some wires.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Sir, if I may venture an opinion...</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		I'm not really interested in your 
		opinion, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>.</sp>

<sd>Leia rushes into the cabin just as <name type="NORP">Han</name> drops the final floor panel into 
place.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
			(out of breath)
		There's something out there.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Where?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Outside, in the cave.</sp>

<sd>As she speaks, there comes a sharp banging on the hull.  Chewie looks 
up and barks anxiously.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		There it is.  Listen!  Listen!</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		I'm going out there.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Are you crazy?!</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		I just got this bucket back 
		together.  I'm not going to let 
		something tear it apart.</sp>

<sd>He and Chewie grab their breath masks off a rack and hurry out.  Leia 
follows.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Then I'm going with you.</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		I think it might be better if I 
		stay here and guard the ship.
			(hears another 
			 mysterious noise)
		Oh, no.</sp>

<setting>EXT. ASTEROID CAVE - MILLENNIUM FALCON</setting>

<sd>It is very dark inside the huge asteroid cave, too dark to see what is 
attacking the ship.</sd>

<sd>Leia stamps her foot on the floor of the cave.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		This ground sure feels strange.
		It doesn't feel like rock at all.</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> kneels and studies the ground, then attempts to study the outline 
of the cave.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		There's an awful lot of moisture 
		in here.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		I don't know.  I have a bad feeling 
		about this.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Yeah.</sp>

<sd>Chewie barks through his face mask, and points toward the ship's 
cockpit.  A five-foot-long shape can be seen moving across the top of 
the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>.  The leathery creature lets out a screech as <name type="NORP">Han</name> blasts it 
with a laser bolt.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(to Leia)
		Watch out!</sp>

<sd>The black shape tumbles off the spaceship and onto the ground in front 
of the princess.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> bends down to investigate the dead creature.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Yeah, that's what I thought.
		Mynock.  Chewie, check the rest 
		of the ship, make sure there 
		aren't any more attached.  They're 
		chewing on the power cables.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Mynocks?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Go on inside.  We'll clean them 
		off if there are any more.</sp>

<sd>Just then, a swarm of the ugly creatures swoops through the air.  Leia 
puts her arms over her head to protect herself as she runs toward the 
ship.  Chewie shoos another Mynock away with his blaster.  Several of 
the batlike creatures flap their wings loudly against the cockpit 
window of the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>.  Inside, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> shudders at their presence.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Ohhh!  Go away!  Go away!  Beastly 
		little thing.  Shoo!  Shoo!</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> looks around the strange, dripping cave.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Wait a minute...</sp>

<sd>He unholsters his blaster and fires at the far side of the huge cave.  
The cavern begins to shake and the ground starts to buckle.</sd>

<sd>Chewie barks and moves for the ship, followed closely by Leia and <name type="NORP">Han</name>.  
The large wings of the Mynocks flap past them as they protect their 
faces and run up the platform.</sd>

<setting>INT. ASTEROID CAVE - MILLENNIUM FALCON - ENTRY AREA</setting>

<sd>As soon as <name type="NORP">Han</name> and Leia are on board, Chewie closes the main hatch.  
The ship continues to shake and heave.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		All right, Chewie, let's get 
		out of here!</sp>

<sd>The <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> heads for the cockpit as <name type="NORP">Han</name>, followed by <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, rushes 
to the hold area and checks the scopes on the control panel.  Leia 
hurries after.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		The <name type="GPE">Empire</name> is still out there.
		I don't think it's wise to...</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> rushes past her and heads for the cockpit.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(interrupting)
		No time to discuss this in
		committee.</sp>

<sd>And with that he is gone.  The main engines of the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> begin to 
whine.  Leia races after him, bouncing around in the shaking ship.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
			(angry)
		I am not a committee!</sp>

<setting>INT. ASTEROID CAVE - MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> is already in the pilot's seat pulling back on the throttle.  The 
cave-quake has greatly diminished.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		You can't make the jump to light-
		speed in this asteroid field...</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Sit down, sweetheart.  We're 
		taking off!</sp>

<sd>As the ship begins to move forward, Chewie barks.  He notices something 
out the window ahead.  <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> sees it too.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Look!</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		I see it, I see it.</sp>

<sd>Suddenly, a row of jagged white stalagmites and stalactites can be seen 
surrounding the entrance.  And as the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> moves forward, the 
entrance to the cave grows ever smaller.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> pulls hard on the 
throttle, sending his ship surging forward.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		We're doomed!</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		The cave is collapsing.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		This is no cave.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		What?</sp>

<sd>Leia's mouth drops open .  She sees that the rocks of the cave entrance 
are not rocks at all, but giant teeth, quickly closing around the tiny 
ship.  Chewie howls.</sd>

<setting>INT. SPACE SLUG MOUTH</setting>

<sd>The Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>, zooming through the monster's mouth, rolls on 
its side and barely makes it between two of the gigantic white teeth 
before the huge jaws slams closed.</sd>

<setting>EXT. CAVE ENTRANCE - GIANT ASTEROID</setting>

<sd>The enormous space slug moves its head out of the cave as the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> 
flies out of its mouth.  The monster tilts its head, watching the 
starship fly away.</sd>

<setting>EXT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - GIANT ASTEROID</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> races out of the asteroid crater and into the deadly rain of 
the asteroid storm.</sd>

<setting>EXT. DAGOBAH - DAY</setting>

<sd>With Yoda strapped to his back, Luke climbs up one of the many thick 
vines that grow in the swamp.  Panting heavily, he continues his course 
- climbing, flipping through the air, jumping over roots, and racing in 
and out of the heavy ground fog.</sd>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		Run!  Yes.  A <name type="ORG">Jedi</name>'s strength 
		flows from the <name type="ORG">Force</name>.  But beware 
		of the dark side.  Anger... fear... 
		aggression.  The dark side of 
		the <name type="ORG">Force</name> are they.
		Easily they flow, quick to join 
		you in a fight.  If once you 
		start down the dark path, forever 
		will it dominate your destiny, 
		consume you it will, as it did 
		Obi-Wan's apprentice.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Vader.  Is the dark side stronger?</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		No... no... no.  Quicker, easier, 
		more seductive.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		But how am I to know the good side 
		from the bad?</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		You will know.  When you are calm, 
		at peace.  Passive.  A <name type="ORG">Jedi</name> uses 
		the <name type="ORG">Force</name> for knowledge and 
		defense, never for attack.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		But tell me why I can't...</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
			(interrupting)
		No, no, there is no why.  Nothing 
		more will I teach you today.
		Clear your mind of questions.  
		Mmm.  <name type="GPE">Mmmm</name><name type="GPE">mmmm</name>.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps in the distance as Luke lets Yoda down to the ground.  
Breathing heavily, he takes his shirt from a nearby tree branch and 
pulls it on.</sd>

<sd>He turns to see a huge, dead, black tree, its base surrounded by a few 
feet of water.  Giant, twisted roots form a dark and sinister cave on 
one side.  Luke stares at the tree, trembling.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		There's something not right here.</sp>

<sd>Yoda sits on a large root, poking his Gimer Stick into the dirt.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		I feel cold, death.</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		That place... is strong with the 
		dark side of the <name type="ORG">Force</name>.  A domain 
		of evil it is.  In you must go.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		What's in there?</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		Only what you take with you.</sp>

<sd>Luke looks warily between the tree and Yoda.  He starts to strap on his 
weapon belt.</sd>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		Your weapons... you will not 
		need them.</sp>

<sd>Luke gives the tree a long look, than shakes his head "no."  Yoda 
shrugs.  Luke reaches up to brush aside some hanging vines and enters 
the tree.</sd>

<setting>INT. DAGOBAH - TREE CAVE</setting>

<sd>Luke moves into the almost total darkness of the wet and slimy cave.  
The youth can barely make out the edge of the passage.  Holding his lit 
saber before him, he sees a lizard crawling up the side of the cave and 
a snake wrapped around the branches of a tree.  Luke draws a deep 
breath, then pushes deeper into the cave.</sd>

<sd>The space widens around him, but he feels that rather than sees it.  
His sword casts the only light as he peers into the darkness.  It is 
very quiet here.</sd>

<sd>Then, a loud HISS! Darth Vader appears across the blackness, 
illuminated by his own just-ignited laser sword.  Immediately, he 
charges Luke, saber held high.  He is upon the youth in seconds, but 
Luke sidesteps perfectly and slashes at Vader with his sword.</sd>

<sd>Vader is decapitated.  His helmet-encased head flies from his shoulders 
as his body disappears into the darkness.  The metallic banging of the 
helmet fills the cave as Vader's head spins and bounces, smashes on the 
floor, and finally stops. For an instant it rests on the floor, then it 
cracks vertically.  The black helmet and breath mask fall away to 
reveal... Luke's head.</sd>

<sd>Across the space, the standing Luke gasps at the sight, wide-eyed in 
terror.</sd>

<sd>The decapitated head fades away, as in a vision.</sd>

<setting>EXT. DAGOBAH - CAVE - DUSK</setting>

<sd>Meanwhile, Yoda sits on the root, calmly leaning on his Gimer Stick.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - VADER'S STAR DESTROYER</setting>

<sd>Vader's <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name> moves through space, guarded by its 
convoy of <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters.</sd>

<setting>INT. VADER'S STAR DESTROYER - BRIDGE - CONTROL DECK</setting>

<sd>Vader stands in the back control area of his ship's bridge with a 
motley group of men and creatures.  Admiral Piett and two controllers 
stand at the front of the bridge and watch the group with scorn.</sd>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		Bounty hunters.  We don't need 
		that scum.</sp>

<sp><speaker>FIRST CONTROLLER</speaker>
		Yes, sir.</sp>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		Those <name type="ORG">Rebels</name> won't escape us.</sp>

<sd>A second controller interrupts.</sd>

<sp><speaker>SECOND CONTROLLER</speaker>
		Sir, we have a priority signal 
		from the <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name> Avenger.</sp>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		Right.</sp>

<sd>The group standing before Vader is a bizarre array of galactic fortune 
hunters  There is Bossk, a slimy, tentacled monster with two huge, 
bloodshot eyes in a soft baggy face; Zuckuss and Dengar, two battle-
scarred, mangy human types; IG-88, a battered, tarnished chrome war 
droid; and Boba Fett, a man in a weapon-covered armored space suit.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		... there will be a substantial 
		reward for the one who finds the 
		Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>.  You are free 
		to use any methods necessary, but 
		I want them alive.  No disintegrations.</sp>

<sp><speaker>BOBA FETT</speaker>
		As you wish.</sp>

<sd>At that moment, Admiral Piett approaches Vader in a rush of excitement.</sd>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		Lord Vader!  My lord, we have 
		them.</sp>

<setting>EXT. IMPERIAL STAR DESTROYER, AVENGER - ASTEROID BELT</setting>

<sd>The Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> speeds through deep space, closely followed by a 
firing <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name>.  A large asteroid about the same size 
as the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> tumbles rapidly toward the starship.  The tiny <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> 
banks to avoid the giant asteroid as smaller rocks pelt its surface.  
Then the small craft roars under the asteroid which explodes harmlessly 
on the hull of the vast <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name>.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>The ship shudders as flak explodes near the cockpit window.  <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> 
checks a tracking scope an the side control panel while Leia watches 
tensely out the window.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Oh, thank goodness we're coming 
		out of the asteroid field.</sp>

<sd>Chewie barks excitedly as the rain of asteroids begins to subside.  A 
bolt from the <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name> sets up a fiery explosion on the back side 
of the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>, causing it to lurch to one side.</sd>

<setting>EXT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - STAR DESTROYER, AVENGER - ASTEROID FIELD</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> is hit hard by another bolt from the <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name> which 
creates a huge explosion near the cockpit of the smaller ship.  The 
<name type="ORG">Falcon</name> tilts steeply, then rights itself.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> corrects the angle of his ship.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Let's get out of here.  Ready for 
		light-speed?  One... two... three!</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> pulls back on the hyperspace throttle and - nothing happens.  Flak 
bursts continue to rock the ship.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(frantic)
		It's not fair!</sp>

<sd>Chewie is very angry and starts to growl and bark at his friend and 
captain.  Again, <name type="NORP">Han</name> desperately pulls back on the throttle.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		The transfer circuits are working.
		It's not my fault!</sp>

<sd>Chewie puts his head in his hands, whining.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
			(almost expecting 
			 it)
		No light-speed?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		It's not my fault.</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Sir, we just lost the main rear 
		deflector shield.  One more direct 
		hit on the back quarter and we're 
		done for.</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> pauses for a moment, makes a decision, and pulls back on a lever.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Turn her around.</sp>

<sd>Chewie barks in puzzlement.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		I said turn her around!  I'm 
		going to put all power in the 
		front shield.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		You're going to attack them?!</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Sir, the odds of surviving a 
		direct assault on an <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> 
		<name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name>...</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Shut up!</sp>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - MILLENNIUM FALCON - ASTEROID FIELD</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> banks, makes a steep, twisting turn.  In the next moment it 
is racing toward the <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name>, looking very small against the 
massive surface of the <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> ship.  As it moves across the surface 
of the <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name>, the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> bobs and weaves to avoid the numerous 
flak bursts.</sd>

<setting>INT. STAR DESTROYER, AVENGER - BRIDGE</setting>

<sd>The tiny <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> heads directly for the Avenger's bridge.  The <name type="ORG">Imperial</name>s 
stationed there are stunned to see the small spaceship racing low 
across the hull, headed directly at the huge windows of the bridge 
area.  Alarms go off everywhere.  The Destroyer's commander, Captain 
Needa, can scarcely believe his eyes.</sd>

<sp><speaker>NEEDA</speaker>
		They're moving to attack 
		position!  Shields up!</sp>

<sd>Needa and his men duck as the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> nears the bridge window.  At the 
last minute, the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> veers off and out of sight.  All is quiet.</sd>

<sp><speaker>NEEDA</speaker>
		Track them.  They may come 
		around for another pass.</sp>

<sp><speaker>TRACKING OFFICER</speaker>
		Captain Needa, the ship no longer 
		appears on our scopes.</sp>

<sp><speaker>NEEDA</speaker>
		They can't have disappeared.  No 
		ship that small has a cloaking 
		device.</sp>

<sp><speaker>TRACKING OFFICER</speaker>
		Well, there's no trace of them, 
		sir.</sp>

<sp><speaker>COMMUNICATIONS OFFICER</speaker>
		Captain, Lord Vader demands an 
		update on the pursuit.</sp>

<sp><speaker>NEEDA</speaker>
			(drawing a breath)
		Get a shuttle ready.  I shall 
		assume full responsibility for 
		losing them, and apologize to Lord 
		Vader. Meanwhile, continue to 
		scan the area.</sp>

<sp><speaker>COMMUNICATIONS OFFICER</speaker>
		Yes, Captain Needa.</sp>

<setting>EXT. DAGOBAH - BOG - DAY</setting>

<sd>Luke's face is upside-down and showing enormous strain.  He stands on 
his hands, with Yoda perched on his feet.  Opposite Luke and Yoda are 
two rocks the size of bowling balls.  Luke stares at the rocks and 
concentrates.  One of the rocks lifts from the ground and floats up to 
rest on the other.</sd>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		Use the <name type="ORG">Force</name>.  Yes...</sp>

<sd>Yoda taps Luke's leg.  Quickly, Luke lifts one hand from the ground.  
His body wavers, but he maintains his balance.  <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, standing nearby, 
is whistling and beeping frantically.</sd>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		Now... the stone.  Feel it.</sp>

<sd>Luke concentrates on trying to lift the top rock.  It rises a few feet, 
shaking under the strain.  But, distracted by <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>'s frantic beeping, 
Luke loses his balance and finally collapses.  Yoda jumps clear.</sd>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		Concentrate!</sp>

<sd>Annoyed at the disturbance, Luke looks over at <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, who is rocking 
urgently back and forth in front of him.</sd>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> waddles closer to Luke, chirping wildly, then scoots over the 
edge of the swamp.  Catching on, Luke rushes to the water's edge.  The 
X-wing fighter has sunk, and only the tip of its nose shows above the 
lake's surface.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Oh, no.  We'll never get it out 
		now.</sp>

<sd>Yoda stamps his foot in irritation.</sd>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		So certain are you.  Always with 
		you it cannot be done.  Hear you
		nothing that I say?</sp>

<sd>Luke looks uncertainly out at the ship.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Master, moving stones around is 
		one thing.  This is totally 
		different.</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		No!  No different!  Only different 
		in your mind.  You must unlearn 
		what you have learned.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(focusing, quietly)
		All right, I'll give it a try.</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		No!  Try not.  Do.  Or do not.  
		There is no try.</sp>

<sd>Luke closes his eyes and concentrates on thinking the ship out.</sd>

<sd>Slowly, the X-wing's nose begins to rise above the water.  It hovers 
for a moment and then slides back, disappearing once again.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(panting heavily)
		I can't.  It's too big.</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		Size matters not.  Look at me.  
		Judge me by my size, do you?  
		Hm?  <name type="GPE">Mmmm</name>.</sp>

<sd>Luke shakes his head.</sd>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		And well you should not.  For my 
		ally in the <name type="ORG">Force</name>.  And a powerful 
		ally it is.  Life creates it, makes 
		it grow.  Its energy surrounds us 
		and binds us.  Luminous beings 
		are we...
			(Yoda pinches 
			 Luke's shoulder)
		... not this crude matter.
			(a sweeping gesture)
		You must feel the <name type="ORG">Force</name> around you.
			(gesturing)
		Here, between you... me... the 
		tree... the rock... everywhere!  
		Yes, even between this land and 
		that ship!</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(discouraged)
		You want the impossible.</sp>

<sd>Quietly Yoda turns toward the X-wing fighter.  With his eyes closed and 
his head bowed, he raises his arm and points at the ship.</sd>

<sd>Soon, the fighter rises above the water and moves forward as <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> 
beeps in terror and scoots away.</sd>

<sd>The entire X-wing moves majestically, surely, toward the shore.  Yoda 
stands on a tree root and guides the fighter carefully down toward the 
beach.</sd>

<sd>Luke stares in astonishment as the fighter settles down onto the shore.  
He walks toward Yoda.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		I don't... I don't believe it.</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		That is why you fail.</sp>

<sd>Luke shakes his head, bewildered.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - IMPERIAL FLEET</setting>

<sd>The fleet around Vader's <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name> now includes Needa's Star 
Destroyer, the Avenger.</sd>

<setting>INT. VADER'S STAR DESTROYER - BRIDGE</setting>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Apology accepted, Captain Needa.</sp>

<sd>Clutching desperately at his throat, Captain Needa slumps down, then 
falls over on his back, at the feet of Darth Vader.  Two stormtroopers 
pick up the lifeless body and carry it quickly away as Admiral Piett 
and two of his captains hurry up to the Dark Lord.</sd>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		Lord Vader, our ships have 
		completed their scan of the area 
		and found nothing.  If the 
		Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> went into light-
		speed, it'll be on the other side 
		of the galaxy by now.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Alert all commands.  Calculate 
		every possible destination along 
		their last know trajectory.</sp>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		Yes, my lord.  We'll find them.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Don't fail me again, Admiral.</sp>

<sd>Vader exits as the admiral turns to an aide, a little more uneasy than 
when he arrived.</sd>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		Alert all commands.  Deploy the fleet.</sp>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - IMPERIAL FLEET</setting>

<sd>Vader's ship moves away, flanked by its fleet of smaller ships.  the 
Avenger glides off into space in the opposite direction.  No one on 
that ship or on Vader's is aware that, clinging to the side of the 
Avenger, is the pirateship, the Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Captain Solo, this time you have 
		gone too far.
			(Chewie growls)
		No, I will not be quiet, Chewbacca.
		Why doesn't anyone listen to me?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(to Chewie)
		The fleet is beginning to break 
		up.  Go back and stand by the 
		manual release for the landing claw.</sp>

<sd>Chewie barks, struggles from his seat, and climbs out of the cabin.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		I really don't see how that is 
		going to help.  Surrender is a 
		perfectly acceptable alternative 
		in extreme circumstances.  The 
		<name type="GPE">Empire</name> may be gracious enough...</sp>

<sd>Leia reaches over and shuts off <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, mid-sentence.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Thank you.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		What did you have in mind for 
		your next move?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Well, if they follow standard 
		<name type="ORG">Imperial</name> procedure, they'll dump 
		their garbage before they go to 
		light-speed, then we just float 
		away.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		With the rest of the garbage.
		Then what?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Then we've got to find a safe 
		port somewhere around here.  Got 
		any ideas?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		No.  Where are we?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		The Anoat system.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Anoat system.  There's not much 
		there.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		No.  Well, wait.  This is 
		interesting.  <name type="GPE">Lando</name>.</sp>

<sd>He points to a computer mapscreen on the control panel.  Leia slips out 
of her chair and moves next to the handsome pilot.  Small light points 
representing several systems flash by on the computer screen.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		<name type="GPE">Lando</name> system?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		<name type="GPE">Lando</name>'s not a system, he's a man.
		<name type="GPE">Lando</name> Calrissian.  He's a card 
		player, gambler, scoundrel.  You'd 
		like him.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Thanks.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Bespin.  It's pretty far, but I 
		think we can make it.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
			(reading from the 
			 computer)
		A mining colony?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Yeah, a <name type="GPE">Tibanna</name> gas mine.  <name type="GPE">Lando</name> 
		conned somebody out of it.  We 
		go back a long way, <name type="GPE">Lando</name> and me.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Can you trust him?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		No.  But he has no love for the
		<name type="GPE">Empire</name>, I can tell you that.</sp>

<sd>Chewie barks over the intercom.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> quickly changes his readouts and 
stretches to look out the cockpit window.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(into intercom)
		Here we go, Chewie.  Stand by.
		Detach!</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> leans back in his chair and gives Leia an invisible smile.  She 
thinks for a moment, shakes her head; a grin creeps across her face and 
she gives him a quick kiss.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		You do have your moments.  Not 
		many, but you have them.</sp>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - IMPERIAL STAR DESTROYER</setting>

<sd>As the Avenger <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name> moves slowly into space, the hatch on its 
underbelly opens, sending a trail of junk behind it.  Hidden among the 
refuse, the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> tumbles away.  In the next moment, the Avenger roars 
off into hyperspace.  The <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>'s engines are ignited, and it races 
off into the distance.  Amidst the slowly drifting junk, Boba Fett's 
ship appears and moves after the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>.</sd>

<setting>EXT. DAGOBAH - BOG - CLEARING - DAY</setting>

<sd>In the clearing behind Yoda's house, Luke again stands upside-down, but 
his face shows less strain and more concentration than before.  Yoda 
sits on the ground below the young warrior.  On the other side of the 
clearing, two equipment cases slowly rise into the air.  Nearby <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> 
watches, humming to himself, when suddenly he, too, rises into the air.  
His little legs kick desperately and his head turns frantically, 
looking for help.</sd>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		Concentrate... feel the <name type="ORG">Force</name> 
		flow.  Yes.  Good.  Calm, yes.  
		Through the <name type="ORG">Force</name>, things you 
		will see.  Other places.  The 
		future... the past.  Old friends 
		long gone.</sp>

<sd>Luke suddenly becomes distressed.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		<name type="NORP">Han</name>!  Leia!</sp>

<sd>The two packing boxes and <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> fall to the ground with a crash, then 
Luke himself tumbles over.</sd>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
			(shaking his head)
		Hmm.  Control, control.  You must 
		learn control.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		I saw... I saw a city in the 
		clouds.</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		Mmm.  Friends you have there.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		They were in pain.</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
It is the future you see.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Future?  Will they die?</sp>

<sd>Yoda closes his eyes and lowers his head.</sd>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		Difficult to see.  Always in 
		motion is the future.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		I've got to go to them.</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		Decide you must how to serve 
		them best.  If you leave now, 
		help them you could.  But you 
		would destroy all for which they 
		have fought and suffered.</sp>

<sd>Luke is stopped cold by Yoda's words.  Gloom shrouds him as he nods his 
head sadly.</sd>

<setting>EXT. BESPIN SYSTEM - MILLENNIUM FALCON - DAWN</setting>

<sd>The powerful pirate starship blasts through space as it heads toward 
the soft pink planet of Bespin.</sd>

<setting>EXT. BESPIN SURFACE - MILLENNIUM FALCON</setting>

<sd>It is down on the gaseous planet.  Huge billowing clouds form a canyon 
as the ship banks around them, heading toward the system's Cloud City.</sd>

<sd>Suddenly, two twin-pod cloud cars appear and move toward the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>.  
The cloud cars draw up alongside the starship.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>One of the cloud cars opens fire on the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>, its flak rocking the 
ship.  Chewie barks his concern.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(into transmitter)
		No, I don't have a landing 
		permit.  I'm trying to reach 
		<name type="GPE">Lando</name> Calrissian.</sp>

<sd>More flak bursts outside the cockpit window and rattles the ship's 
interior.  Leia looks worried.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(into transmitter)
		Whoa!  Wait a minute!  Let me 
		explain.</sp>

				<setting>INTERCOM VOICE</setting>
		You will not deviate from your 
		present course.

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Rather touchy, aren't they?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		I thought you knew this person.</sp>

<sd>Chewie barks and growls at his boss.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(to Chewie)
		Well, that was a long time ago.
		I'm sure he's forgotten about 
		that.</sp>

				<setting>INTERCOM VOICE</setting>
		Permission granted to land on 
		Platform Three-two-seven.

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(into transmitter)
		Thank you.</sp>

<sd>Angry, <name type="NORP">Han</name> snaps off the intercom.  Chewie looks at him and grunts.  
<name type="NORP">Han</name> turns to the worried princess and her droid.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		There's nothing to worry about.
		We go way back, <name type="GPE">Lando</name> and me.</sp>

<sd>Leia doesn't look convinced.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Who's worried?</sp>

<setting>EXT. CLOUD CITY - MILLENNIUM FALCON - CLOUD CARS</setting>

<sd>The clouds part to reveal a full view of the city as it bobs in and out 
of the cloud surface.  The cloud cars and the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> head for the 
gleaming white metropolis.</sd>

<setting>EXT. CLOUD CITY - LANDING PLATFORM - MILLENNIUM FALCON</setting>

<sd>With the cloud cars still guarding it, the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> lands on one of the 
Cloud City's platforms.</sd>

<setting>EXT. LANDING PLATFORM - DOOR OF MILLENNIUM FALCON</setting>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> and Leia stand at the open door, armed.  Behind them, Chewie, also 
armed, surveys the scene warily.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Oh.  No one to meet us.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		I don't like this.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Well, what would you like?</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Well, they did let us land.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Look, don't worry.  Everything's 
		going to be fine.  Trust me.</sp>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - CORRIDOR - DAY</setting>

<sd><name type="GPE">Lando</name> Calrissian, a suave, dashing black man in his thirties, leads a 
group of aides and some Cloud City guard rapidly toward the landing 
platform.</sd>

<sd>The group, like the other citizens of the city, is a motley collection 
of aliens, droids, and humans of all descriptions.  <name type="GPE">Lando</name> has a grim 
expression on his face as he moves onto the landing platform.</sd>

<setting>EXT. LANDING PLATFORM - DOOR OF MILLENNIUM FALCON</setting>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		See?  My friend.
			(to Chewie)
		Keep your eyes open, okay?</sp>

<sd>Chewie growls as <name type="NORP">Han</name> walks down the ramp.  <name type="GPE">Lando</name> and his men head 
across the bridge to meet the space pirate.</sd>

<setting>EXT. CLOUD CITY - LANDING PLATFORM</setting>

<sd><name type="GPE">Lando</name> stops ten feet from <name type="NORP">Han</name>.  The two men eye each other carefully.  
<name type="GPE">Lando</name> shakes his head.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		Why, you slimy, double-crossing, 
		no-good swindler!  You've got a 
		lot of guts coming here, after 
		what you pulled.</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> points to himself innocently, mouthing, "Me?"</sd>

<sd><name type="GPE">Lando</name> moves threateningly toward <name type="NORP">Han</name>.  Suddenly, he throws his arms 
around his startled, long-lost friend and embraces him.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
			(laughs)
		How you doing, you old pirate? 
		So good to see you!  I never thought 
		I'd catch up with you again.  Where 
		you been?</sp>

<sd>The two old friends embrace, laughing and chuckling.</sd>

<setting>EXT. LANDING PLATFORM - DOOR OF MILLENNIUM FALCON.</setting>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
Well, he seems very friendly.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
			(wary)
		Yes... very friendly.</sp>

<setting>EXT. CLOUD CITY - LANDING PLATFORM</setting>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		What are you doing here?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(gestures toward 
			 the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>)
		Ahh... repairs.  I thought you 
		could help me out.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
			(in mock panic)
		What have you done to my ship?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Your ship?  Hey, remember, you 
		lost her to me fair and square.</sp>

<sd>Chewie growls a reserved greeting.  <name type="GPE">Lando</name> suddenly notices the princess 
and smiles.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		Hello.  What have we here?  
		Welcome.  I'm <name type="GPE">Lando</name> Calrissian.
		I'm the administrator of this 
		facility.  And who might you be?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Leia.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		Welcome, Leia.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Lando</name> bows before Leia and kisses her hand.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		All right, all right, you old 
		smoothie.</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> takes Leia by the hand and steers her away from <name type="GPE">Lando</name>.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Hello, sir.  I am See-<name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, 
		human-cyborg relations.  My 
		facilities are at your...</sp>

<sd>Before <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> can finish his self-introduction, <name type="GPE">Lando</name> has turned to 
follow <name type="NORP">Han</name> and Leia, who are walking toward the city.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Well, really!</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Lando</name>, his aide, Lobot, and <name type="NORP">Han</name> lead the way across the bridge, 
followed by <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, Chewie and Leia.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		What's wrong with the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Hyperdrive.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		I'll get my people to work on it.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Good.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Lando</name> turns to Leia.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		You know, that ship saved my life 
		quite a few times.  She's the 
		fastest hunk of junk in the galaxy.</sp>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - CORRIDOR</setting>

<sd>The group has crossed the narrow bridge and entered the city.  They 
walk down the lovely Art Deco passageway, rounding several corners and 
passing many small plazas as they go.  <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> lags a bit behind.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		How's the gas mine?  Is it 
		paying off for you?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		Oh, not as well as I'd like.
		We're a small outpost and not 
		very self-sufficient.  And I've 
		had supply problems of every kind.
		I've had labor difficulties...
			(catches <name type="NORP">Han</name> 
			 grinning at him)
		What's so funny?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		You.  Listen to you - you sound 
		like a businessman, a responsible 
		leader.  Who'd have thought that, 
		huh?</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Lando</name> is reflective.  He looks at <name type="NORP">Han</name> a moment.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		You know, seeing you sure 
		brings back a few things.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Yeah.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
			(shakes his head)
		Yeah.  I'm responsible these days.
		It's the price you pay for being 
		successful.</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> and <name type="GPE">Lando</name> laugh together, and the group moves on through the 
corridor.</sd>

<sd>The lagging <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> passes a <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>-type silver droid who is coming 
out of a door.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Oh!  Nice to see a familiar face.</sp>

<sp><speaker>SECOND THREEPIO</speaker>
			(mumbles)
		E chu ta!</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		How rude!</sp>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> stops, watching the silver droid move away.  Then he hears the 
muffled beeping and whistling of an R2 unit coming from within the 
room.</sd>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - ANTEROOM</setting>

<sd>Curious, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> enters the room.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		That sounds like an R2 unit in 
		there.  I wonder if...</sp>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> walks through the doorway to the main room.  He looks in.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Hello?  How interesting.  Oh, my.</sp>

<sp><speaker>MAN'S VOICE</speaker>
			(from within)
		Who are you?</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Oh, I'm terribly sorry.  I... I 
		didn't mean to intrude.  No, no, 
		please don't get up.  No!</sp>

<sd>A laser bolt to <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>'s chest sends him flying in twenty directions.  
Smoldering mechanical arms and legs bounce off the walls as the door 
whooshes closed behind him.</sd>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - CORRIDOR</setting>

<sd><name type="GPE">Lando</name>, <name type="NORP">Han</name>, and Leia continue down the corridor unaware of <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>'s 
dreadful accident.  Chewbacca glances around, sniffs the air, but 
shrugs his shoulders and follows the group.</sd>

<setting>EXT. DAGOBAH - BOG - DUSK</setting>

<sd>In the bright lights of the fighter, Luke loads a heavy case into the 
belly of the ship.  <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> sits on top of the X-wing, settling down into 
his cubbyhole.  Yoda stands nearby on a log.</sd>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		Luke!  You must complete the 
		training.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		I can't keep the vision out of my 
		head.  They're my friends.  I've 
		got to help them.</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		You must not go!</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		But <name type="NORP">Han</name> and Leia will die if I 
		don't.</sp>

<sp><speaker>BEN'S VOICE</speaker>
		You don't know that.</sp>

<sd>Luke looks toward the voice in amazement.  Ben has materialized as a 
real, slightly shimmering image near Yoda.  The power of his presence 
stops Luke.</sd>

<sp><speaker>BEN</speaker>
		Even Yoda cannot see their fate.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		But I can help them!  I feel 
		the <name type="ORG">Force</name>!</sp>

<sp><speaker>BEN</speaker>
		But you cannot control it.  This 
		is a dangerous time for you, 
		when you will be tempted by the 
		dark side of the <name type="ORG">Force</name>.</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		Yes, yes.  To Obi-Wan you listen.
		The cave.  Remember your failure 
		at the cave!</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		But I've learned so much since 
		then.  Master Yoda, I promise to 
		return and finish what I've begun. 
		You have my word.</sp>

<sp><speaker>BEN</speaker>
		It is you and your abilities the 
		Emperor wants.  that is why your 
		friends are made to suffer.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		And that is why I have to go.</sp>

<sp><speaker>BEN</speaker>
		Luke, I don't want to lose you to 
		the Emperor the way I lost Vader.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		You won't.</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		Stopped they must be.  On this 
		all depends.  Only a fully trained 
		<name type="ORG">Jedi</name> Knight with the <name type="ORG">Force</name> as his 
		ally will conquer Vader and his 
		Emperor.  If you end your training 
		now, if you choose the quick and 
		easy path, as Vader did, you will 
		become an agent of evil.</sp>

<sp><speaker>BEN</speaker>
		Patience.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		And sacrifice <name type="NORP">Han</name> and Leia?</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		If you honor what they fight for
		... yes!</sp>

<sd>Luke is in great anguish.  He struggles with the dilemma, a battle 
raging in his mind.</sd>

<sp><speaker>BEN</speaker>
		If you choose to face Vader, you 
		will do it alone.  I cannot 
		interfere.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		I understand.
			(he moves to his 
			 X-wing)
		<name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, fire up the converters.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> whistles a happy reply.</sd>

<sp><speaker>BEN</speaker>
		Luke, don't give in to hate - 
		that leads to the dark side.</sp>

<sd>Luke nods and climbs into his ship.</sd>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
		Strong is Vader.  Mind what you 
		have learned.  Save you it can.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		I will.  And I'll return.  I promise.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> closes the cockpit.  Ben and Yoda stand watching as the roar of 
the engines and the wind engulf them.</sd>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
			(sighs)
		Told you, I did.  Reckless is 
		he.  Now matters are worse.</sp>

<sp><speaker>BEN</speaker>
		That boy is our last hope.</sp>

<sp><speaker>YODA</speaker>
			(looks up)
		No.  There is another.</sp>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - PLANET DAGOBAH</setting>

<sd>Luke's tiny X-wing rockets away from the green planet of <name type="FAC">Dagobah</name> and 
off into space.</sd>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - LIVING QUARTERS - DAY</setting>

<sd>Within the quarters assigned her on Cloud City, Leia paces in 
agitation.  She has changed from her cold-weather pants and jacket to a 
lovely dress.  Her hair is down, tied back with ribbons.  She moves 
from a large, open window and turns to see <name type="NORP">Han</name> entering through the 
doorway.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		The ship is almost finished.
		Two or Three more things and 
		we're in great shape.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		The sooner the better.  Something's 
		wrong here.  No one has seen or 
		knows anything about <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>.
		He's been gone too long to have 
		gotten lost.</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> takes Leia by the shoulders and gently kisses her forehead.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Relax.  I'll talk to <name type="GPE">Lando</name> and 
		see what I can find out.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		I don't trust <name type="GPE">Lando</name>.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Well, I don't trust him, either.
		But he is my friend.  Besides, 
		we'll soon be gone.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		And then you're as good as gone, 
		aren't you?</sp>

<sd>Not speaking, <name type="NORP">Han</name> considers her words and gazes at her troubled face.</sd>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - JUNK ROOM</setting>

<sd>The room is piled high with broken and discarded machine parts.  Four 
Ugnaughts, small hoglike creatures, separate the junk and throw some 
pieces onto a conveyer belt which moves briskly toward a pit of molten 
metal.  Pieces of <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>'s golden body move down the belt.  Chewie 
enters the room and spots an Ugnaught picking up and inspecting 
<name type="ORG">Threepio</name>'s head.  The <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> barks a command, startling the Ugnaught, 
then reaches to grab the head.  But the Ugnaught tosses it away from 
him to another Ugnaught.  This game of keep-away goes on until 
<name type="ORG">Threepio</name>'s head falls from their grip and bounces with a clang onto the 
ground.</sd>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - LIVING QUARTERS - DAY</setting>

<sd>The door zaps open.  Chewbacca walks in, carrying a packing case of 
<name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, arms and legs hanging over the edge.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		What happened?</sp>

<sd>Chewie sets the case on a table, grunting and groaning an explanation.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Where?  Found him in a junk pile?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Oh, what a mess.  Chewie, do you 
		think you can repair him?</sp>

<sd>The giant <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> studies the array of robot parts.  He looks at the 
princess and shrugs sadly.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		<name type="GPE">Lando</name>'s got people who can fix 
		him.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		No, thanks.</sp>

<sd>There is a buzz and the door slides open, revealing <name type="GPE">Lando</name>.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		I'm sorry.  Am I interrupting 
		anything?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Not really.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		You look absolutely beautiful.
		You truly belong here with us 
		among the clouds.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
			(coolly)
		Thank you.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		Will you join me for a little 
		refreshment?</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> looks at <name type="GPE">Lando</name> suspiciously, but Chewie barks at the mention of 
food and licks his lips.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		Everyone's invited, of course.</sp>

<sd>Leia takes <name type="GPE">Lando</name>'s proffered arm, and the group turns to go.  <name type="GPE">Lando</name> 
spots <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>'s remains.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		Having trouble with you droid?</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> and Leia exchange a quick glance.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		No.  No problem.  Why?</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> and Leia move arm-in-arm through the door, followed by <name type="GPE">Lando</name> and 
Chewie.  The door slides closed behind them.</sd>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - CORRIDOR - DAY</setting>

<sd>Leia walks between <name type="NORP">Han</name> and <name type="GPE">Lando</name> as Chewie follows a short distance 
behind.  Long shafts of light pour across the corridor between tall, 
pure-white columns.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		So you see, since we're a small 
		operation, we don't fall into 
		the... uh... jurisdiction of the 
		<name type="GPE">Empire</name>.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		So you're part of the mining 
		guild then?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		No, not actually.  Our operation 
		is small enough not to be noticed... 
		which is advantageous for everybody 
		since our customers are anxious 
		to avoid attracting attention to 
		themselves.</sp>

<sd>The group walks into another corridor and heads for a huge doorway at 
the far end.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Aren't you afraid the <name type="GPE">Empire</name>'s 
		going to find out about this 
		little operation and shut you down?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		That's always been a danger looming 
		like a shadow over everything we've 
		built here.  But things have 
		developed that will insure security.
		I've just made a deal that will 
		keep the <name type="GPE">Empire</name> out of here forever.</sp>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - DINING ROOM</setting>

<sd>The mighty doors to the dining room slide open and the group enters the 
dining room.  At the far end of a huge banquet table sits Darth Vader.  
Standing at his side and slightly behind him is Boba Fett, the bounty 
hunter.</sd>

<sd>Faster than the wink of an eye, <name type="NORP">Han</name> draws his blaster and pops off a 
couple of shots directly at Vader.  The Dark Lord quickly raises his 
hand, deflecting the bolts into one of the side walls, where they 
explode harmlessly.  Just as quickly, <name type="NORP">Han</name>'s weapon zips into Vader's 
hand.  The evil presence calmly places the gun on the table in front of 
him.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		We would be honored if you would 
		join us.</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> gives <name type="GPE">Lando</name> a mean look.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		I had no choice.  They arrived 
right before you did.  I'm sorry.</sp>
		
<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		I'm sorry, too.</sp>

<setting>EXT.  LUKE'S X-WING - BESPIN SYSTEM</setting>

<sd>Luke's X-wing races through thick clouds toward Cloud City.</sd>

<setting>INT.  LUKE'S X-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke is grim-faced as he pilots his course toward Bespin's shining 
city.  <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>'s beeps and whistles are transmitted onto the scope.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		No, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>'s with them.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> whistles another worried inquiry.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		Just hang on.  We're almost there.</sp>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - LARGE CELL</setting>

<sd>Chewbacca is in a Cloud City prison cell.  The stark room is flooded 
with hot light.  To add to Chewie's misery, a high-pitched whistle 
screeches loudly.  Chewie is going mad.  He hits the wall with giant 
fists as he paces back and forth across the cell floor.  The upper 
lights go off abruptly.  The prisoner rubs his eyes and moves to a 
wall, where he listens for a moment.  Then, moaning to himself, he 
moves to a platform where the disassembled pieces of <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> lie.  He 
picks up the golden droid's head and meditates on it for a moment, 
barking a few philosophical remarks.  Chewie sticks the robot's head on 
its torso and starts adjusting wires and circuits.</sd>

<sd>Suddenly, the lights in <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>'s eyes spark to life as Chewie touches 
two connectors together.  <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> immediately begins to speak, but his 
voice is so slow and so low as to be nearly unintelligible.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		<name type="GPE">Mmmm</name>.  Oh, my.  Uh, I, uh - Take 
		this off!  I, uh, don't mean to 
		intrude here.  I, don't, no, no, 
		no... Please don't get up.  No!</sp>

<sd>Chewie looks at <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> in bewilderment, then scratches his furry 
head.  He gets an idea and adjusts some connections, whereupon <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> 
immediately begins speaking normally.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Stormtroopers?  Here?  We're in 
		danger.  I must tell the others.
		Oh, no!  I've been shot!</sp>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - PRISON ENTRY AREA</setting>

<sd>Darth Vader strides through the room as two stormtroopers prepare an 
elaborate torture mechanism.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> is strapped to a rack which tilts 
forward onto the torture device.  Vader activates the mechanism, 
creating two bursts of sparks, one of which strikes <name type="NORP">Han</name>'s face.</sd>

<sd>The door opens, and Vader leaves the torture room just as <name type="NORP">Han</name> screams a 
sharp, piercing cry of agony.  Darth Vader moves to the holding 
chamber, where <name type="GPE">Lando</name> and Boba Fett await him.</sd>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - HOLDING CHAMBER</setting>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		Lord Vader.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
			(to Fett)
		You may take Captain Solo to 
		Jabba the <name type="ORG">Hut</name> after I have 
		Skywalker.</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name>'s screams filter through the torture room door.</sd>

<sp><speaker>BOBA FETT</speaker>
		He's no good to me dead.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		He will not be permanently damaged.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		Lord Vader, what about Leia and 
		the <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name>?</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		They must never again leave this 
		city.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		That was never a condition of our 
		agreement, nor was giving <name type="NORP">Han</name> to 
		this bounty hunter!</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Perhaps you think you're being 
		treated unfairly.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		No.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Good.  It would be unfortunate if 
		I had to leave a garrison here.</sp>

<sd>Vader turns and sweeps into the elevator with Boba Fett.  <name type="GPE">Lando</name> walks 
swiftly down another corridor, muttering to himself.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		This deal's getting worse all 
		the time.</sp>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - LARGE CELL</setting>

<sd>Chewie now has a little more of <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> back together.  One arm is 
connected, but the legs are yet to be attached.  There is one small 
problem, however.  It seems the <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> has managed to put the droid's 
head on backwards.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Oh, yes, that's very good.  I like 
		that.  Oh!  Something's not right 
		because now I can't see.  Wait.  
		Wait!  Oh, my!  what have you done?  
		I'm backwards, you stupid furball.  
		Only an overgrown mophead like you 
		would be stupid enough...</sp>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> is cut off in mid-sentence as Chewie angrily deactivates a 
circuit and the droid shuts down.  The <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> smells something and 
sits up.  The door to the chamber slides open and a ragged <name type="NORP">Han</name> Solo is 
shoved into the room by two stormtroopers.  Barking his concern, the 
huge <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> gives <name type="NORP">Han</name> a big hug.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> is very pale, with dark circles 
under his eyes.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		I feel terrible.</sp>

<sd>Chewie helps <name type="NORP">Han</name> to a platform and then turns as the door slides open 
revealing Leia.  She, too, looks a little worse for wear.  The troopers 
push her into the cell, and the door slides closed.  She moves to <name type="NORP">Han</name>, 
who is lying on the platform, and kneels next to him, gently stroking 
his head.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Why are they doing this?</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		They never even asked me any 
		questions.</sp>

<sd>The cell door slides open.  <name type="GPE">Lando</name> and two of his guards enter.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		<name type="GPE">Lando</name>.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Get out of here, <name type="GPE">Lando</name>!</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		Shut up and listen!  Vader has 
		agreed to turn Leia and Chewie 
		over to me.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Over to you?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		They'll have to stay here, but at 
		least they'll be safe.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		What about <name type="NORP">Han</name>?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		Vader's giving him to the bounty 
		hunter.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Vader wants us all dead.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		He doesn't want you at all.  He's 
		after somebody called Skywalker.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Luke?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		Lord Vader has set a trap for him.</sp>

<sd>Leia's mind is racing.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		And we're the bait.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		Well, he's on his way.</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name>'s rage peaks.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Perfect.  You fixed us all pretty 
		good, didn't you?
			(spits it out)
		My friend!</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> hauls off and punches <name type="GPE">Lando</name>.  The two friends are instantly engaged 
in a frantic close-quarters fight.  The guards hit <name type="NORP">Han</name> with their rifle 
butts and he flies across the room.  Chewie growls and starts for the 
guards.  They point their laser weapons at the giant <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name>, but <name type="GPE">Lando</name> 
stops them.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		Stop!  I've done all I can.  I'm 
		sorry I couldn't do better, but 
		I have my own problems.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Yeah, you're a real hero.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Lando</name> and the guards leave.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> wipes the blood from his chin as Leia 
and Chewie help him up.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
			(dabs at his wound)
		You certainly have a way with 
		people.</sp>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - CARBON-FREEZING CHAMBER</setting>

<sd>Four armor-suited stormtroopers stand at the ready in the large 
chamber, which is filled with pipes and chemical tanks.  In the middle 
of the room is a round pit housing a hydraulic platform.  Darth Vader 
and <name type="GPE">Lando</name> stand near the platform.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		This facility is crude, but it 
		should be adequate to freeze 
		Skywalker for his journey to the 
		Emperor.</sp>

<sd>An <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> soldier appears.</sd>

<sp><speaker>IMPERIAL SOLDIER</speaker>
		Lord Vader, ship approaching.
		X-wing class.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Good.  Monitor Skywalker and allow 
		him to land.</sp>

<sd>The soldier bows and leaves the chamber.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		Lord Vader, we only use this 
		facility for carbon freezing.  If 
		you put him in there, it might 
		kill him.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		I do not want the Emperor's prize 
		damaged.  We will test it... on 
		Captain Solo.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Lando</name>'s face registers dismay.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - BESPIN SYSTEM -  LUKE'S X-WING</setting>

<sd>Luke's X-wing moves through the clouds as it nears the city.</sd>

<setting>INT.  LUKE'S X-WING - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Encountering no city guards, Luke scans the display panel with concern.</sd>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - CARBON-FREEZING CHAMBER</setting>

<sd>There is a great activity on the carbon-freezing platform.  Six 
Ugnaughts frantically prepare the chamber for use.  A special 
coffinlike container is put in place.  With Boba Fett in the lead, a 
squad of six stormtroopers brings in <name type="NORP">Han</name>, Leia and Chewie.  Strapped to 
Chewie's back, with only his head, torso, and one arm assembled, is 
<name type="ORG">Threepio</name>.  <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>'s head faces the opposite direction from Chewie's 
and the droid is constantly twisting around in a vain effort to see 
what is happening.  His one attached arm is animate and expressive, 
intermittently pointing, gesturing, and covering his eyes.  The 
remaining pieces of his body are randomly bundled to the <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name>'s back 
so that his legs and other arm stick out at odd angles from the pack.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		If only you had attached my legs, 
		I wouldn't be in this ridiculous 
		position.  Now, remember, Chewbacca, 
		you have a responsibility to me, 
		so don't do anything foolish.</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
			(to <name type="GPE">Lando</name>)
		What's going on... buddy?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		You're being put into carbon freeze.</sp>

<sd>Boba Fett moves away from the group to Darth Vader.</sd>

<sp><speaker>BOBA FETT</speaker>
		What if he doesn't survive?  He's 
		worth a lot to me.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		The <name type="GPE">Empire</name> will compensate you 
		if he dies.  Put him in!</sp>

<sd>Realizing what is about to happen, Chewie lets out a wild howl and 
attacks the stormtroopers surrounding <name type="NORP">Han</name>.  Within seconds, other 
<name type="ORG">Imperial</name> reinforcements join the scuffle, clubbing the giant <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> 
with their laser weapons.</sd>

<sd>From the instant of Chewie's first move, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> begins to scream in 
panic while he tries to protect himself with his one arm.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Oh, no!  No, no, no!  Stop, 
		Chewbacca, stop...!</sp>

<sd>The stormtroopers are about to bash Chewie in the face.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Stop, Chewie, stop!  Do you hear 
		me?  Stop!</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Yes, stop, please!  I'm not ready 
		to die.</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> breaks away from his captors.  Vader nods to the guards to let him 
go and the pirate breaks up the fight.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Chewie!  Chewie, this won't help 
		me.  Hey!</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> gives the <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> a stern look.</sd>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		Save your strength.  There'll be 
		another time.  The princess - you 
		have to take care of her.  You 
		hear me?</sp>

<sd><name type="NORP">Han</name> winks at the <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name>, who wails a doleful farewell.</sd>

<sd>In a flash the guards have slipped binders on Chewbacca, who is too 
distraught to protest.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> turns to Princess Leia.  They look 
sorrowfully at one another, then <name type="NORP">Han</name> moves toward her and gives her a 
final, passionate kiss.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		I love you!</sp>

<sp><speaker>HAN</speaker>
		I know.</sp>

<sd>Tears roll down Leia's face as she watches the dashing pirate walk to 
the hydraulic platform.  <name type="NORP">Han</name> looks one final time at his friends - and 
then, suddenly, the platform drops.  Chewie howls.  Leia turns away in 
agony.</sd>

<sd><name type="GPE">Lando</name> winces in sorrow; it makes a life-changing impression on him.</sd>

<sd>Instantly, fiery liquid begins to pour down in a shower of sparks and 
fluid as great as any steel furnace.  Holding Leia, Chewie half-turns 
away from the sight, giving <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> a view of the procedure.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		What... what's going on?  Turn 
		round, Chewbacca, I can't see.  
		Oh... they've encased him in 
		carbonite.  He should be quite 
		well-protected - if he survives 
		the freezing process, that is.</sp>

<sd>Chewie is in no mood for technical discussion; he gives the droid an 
angry glance and bark.</sd>

<sd>A huge mechanical tong lifts the steaming metal-encased space pirate 
out of the vat and stands him on the platform.  Some Ugnaughts rush 
over and push the block over onto the platform.  They slide the 
coffinlike structure to the block and lift the metal block, placing it 
inside.  They then attach an electronic box onto the structure and step 
away.  <name type="GPE">Lando</name> kneels and adjusts some knobs, measuring the heat.  He 
shakes his head in relief.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Well, Calrissian, did he survive?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		Yes, he's alive.  And in perfect 
		hibernation.</sp>

<sd>Vader turns to Boba Fett.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		He's all yours bounty hunter.
		Reset the chamber for Skywalker.</sp>

<sp><speaker>IMPERIAL OFFICER</speaker>
		Skywalker has just landed, my 
		lord.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Good.  See to it that he finds 
		his way here.  Calrissian, take 
		the princess and the <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> to 
		my ship.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		You said they'd be left in the 
		city under my supervision.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		I am altering the deal.  Pray I 
		don't alter it any further.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Lando</name>'s hand instinctively goes to his throat as he turns to Leia, 
Chewie, and <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>.</sd>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - CORRIDOR - DAY</setting>

<sd>As Luke and <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> move carefully down a deserted corridor, they hear a 
group of people coming down a side hallway.  <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> lets out an excited 
series of beeps and whistles.  Luke glares at the tiny droid, who stops 
in his tracks with a feeble squeak.</sd>

<sd>Boba Fett enters from a side hallway followed by two guards pushing the 
floating, encased body of <name type="NORP">Han</name> Solo.  Two stormtroopers, who follow, 
immediately spot Luke and open fire on him.  The youth draws his weapon 
and blasts the two troopers before they can get off a second shot.  The 
two guards whisk <name type="NORP">Han</name> into another hallway as Fett lowers his arm and 
fires a deadly laser at Luke, which explodes to one side and tears up a 
huge chunk of wall.</sd>

<sd>Luke rushes to a side hallway, but by the time he reaches it, Fett, 
<name type="NORP">Han</name>, and the guards are gone.  A think metal door blocks the passage.  
Luke turns to see Leia, Chewie, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, and <name type="GPE">Lando</name> being herded down a 
second hallway by several other stormtroopers.  Leia turns just in time 
to see Luke.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Luke!  Luke, don't - it's a 
		trap!  It's a trap!</sp>

<sd>Before she can finish, she is pulled through a doorway and disappears 
from sight.  Luke races after the group, leaving little <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> trailing 
behind.</sd>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - ANTEROOM</setting>

<sd>Luke runs into an anteroom and stops to get his bearings.  Leia and the 
others are nowhere to be seen.  Behind Luke, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> scoots down the 
corridor toward the anteroom when suddenly a giant metal door comes 
slamming down, cutting off Luke's exit.  Several more doors clang shut, 
echoing through the chamber.</sd>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - HALLWAY LEADING TO ANTEROOM</setting>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> stands with his nose pressed against the giant metal door.  He 
whistles a long sigh of relief and, a little dazed, wanders off in the 
other direction.</sd>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - CARBON-FREEZING CHAMBER - ANTEROOM</setting>

<sd>Luke cautiously walks forward among hissing pipes and steam.  Seeing an 
opening above him, he stops to look up.  As he does, the platform he 
stands on begins to move.</sd>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - CARBON-FREEZING CHAMBER</setting>

<sd>Luke rises into the chamber, borne by the platform.  The room is 
deathly quiet.  Very little steam escapes the pipes and no one else 
seems to be in the large room.  Warily, Luke walks toward the stairway.</sd>

<sd>Steam begins to build up in the chamber.  Looking up through the steam, 
Luke sees a dark figure standing on a walkway above him.  Luke holsters 
his gun and moves up the stairs to face Vader.  He feels confident, 
eager to engage his enemy.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		The <name type="ORG">Force</name> is with you, young 
		Skywalker.  But you are not a 
		<name type="ORG">Jedi</name> yet.</sp>

<sd>Luke ignites his sword in answer.  In an instant, Vader's own sword is 
lit.  Luke lunges, but Vader repels the blow.  Again Luke attacks, and 
the swords of the two combatants clash in battle.</sd>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - CORRIDOR</setting>

<sd>Leia, <name type="GPE">Lando</name>, and Chewie, with <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> on his back, march along, 
guarded by six stormtroopers.  The group reaches an intersection where 
Lobot and a dozen of <name type="GPE">Lando</name>'s guards stand at attention.</sd>

<sd>The guards immediately aim their weapons at the startled stormtroopers.  
Taking the stormtroopers' weapons from them, Lobot hands one to Leia 
and one to <name type="GPE">Lando</name>.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		Well done.  Hold them in the 
		security tower - and keep it 
		quiet.  Move.</sp>

<sd>As <name type="GPE">Lando</name>'s guards quickly march the stormtroopers away, <name type="GPE">Lando</name> begins to 
undo Chewie's binding.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		What do you think you're doing?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		We're getting out of here.</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		I knew all along it had to be a 
		mistake.</sp>

<sd>Chewie turns on <name type="GPE">Lando</name> and starts to choke him.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Do you think that after what you 
		did to <name type="NORP">Han</name> we're going to trust 
		you?</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Lando</name> tries to free himself from Chewie.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
			(choking)
		I had no choice...</sp>

<sd>Chewie barks ferociously.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
			(to Chewie)
		What are you doing?  Trust him, 
		trust him!</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Oh, so we understand, don't we, 
		Chewie?  He had no choice.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		I'm just trying to help...</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		We don't need any of your help.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
			(choking)
		H-a-a-a...</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		What?</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		It sounds like <name type="NORP">Han</name>.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		There's still a chance to save 
		<name type="NORP">Han</name>... I mean, at the East 
		Platform...</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Chewie.</sp>

<sd>Chewie finally releases <name type="GPE">Lando</name>, who fights to get his breath back.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
			(to <name type="GPE">Lando</name>)
		I'm terribly sorry about all this. 
		After all, he's only a <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name>.</sp>

<setting>EXT. CLOUD CITY - EAST LANDING PLATFORM - BOBA FETT'S SHIP</setting>

<sd>The two guards slide <name type="NORP">Han</name>'s encased body into an opening in the side of 
the bounty hunter's ship.  Boba Fett climb aboard on a ladder next to 
the cargo hold.</sd>

<sp><speaker>BOBA FETT</speaker>
		Put Captain Solo in the cargo 
		hold.</sp>

<sd>And with that, the door slams shut.</sd>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - CORRIDOR</setting>

<sd><name type="GPE">Lando</name>, Leia, and Chewie run down a Cloud City corridor when suddenly 
they spot <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> who rushes toward them, beeping wildly.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		<name type="GPE">Artoo</name>!  <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>!  Where have you 
		been?</sp>

<sd>Chewie turns around to see the stubby droid, causing <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> to be 
spun out of sight of his friend.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Turn around, you wooly...! 
			(to <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>)
		Hurry, hurry!  We're trying to 
		save <name type="NORP">Han</name> from the bounty hunter!</sp>

<sd>Whistling frantically to <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> scoots along with the racing 
group.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Well, at least your still in 
		one piece!  Look what happened to 
		me!</sp>

<setting>EXT. EAST LANDING PLATFORM - SIDE BAY</setting>

<sd>An elevator door slides open and <name type="GPE">Lando</name>, Leia, and Chewbacca race for a 
large bay overlooking the East Landing Platform.</sd>

<sd>Just as they arrive, Boba Fett's ship takes off against a cloudy sunset 
sky.  </sd>

<sd>In wild anguish, Chewie howls and starts firing at the ship.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Oh, no!  Chewie, they're behind 
		you!</sp>

<sd>A laser bolt explodes near the princess.  Everyone turns to see what 
<name type="ORG">Threepio</name> has already spotted coming from the other direction; a squad 
of stormtroopers running toward them.  <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> peeks out from the 
elevator.</sd>

<sd>Leia and Chewbacca start firing at the troopers as <name type="GPE">Lando</name> makes a break 
for the elevator.  Laser bolts continue to explode around the princess 
and the <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name>, but they refuse to budge.  <name type="GPE">Lando</name> sticks his head out 
of the elevator and motions for the pair to run, but they barely 
notice.  They seem possessed, transported, as all the frustration of 
captivity and anger of loss pour through their death-dealing weapons.</sd>

<sd>But after a few moments, they begin to move through the rain of laser 
fire toward the elevator.  Once they are inside, the door slams shut 
and the stormtroopers race forward.</sd>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - CARBON-FREEZING CHAMBER</setting>

<sd>Luke and Vader are locked in combat on the platform overlooking the 
chamber.  Their swords clash, the platform sways.  Luke aggressively 
drives Vader back, forcing Vader to use defensive tactics.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		You have learned much, young one.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		You'll find I'm full of surprises.</sp>

<sd>Vader makes two quick moves, hooking Luke's sword out of his hand and 
sending it flying.  Another lightning move at Luke's feet forces the 
youth to jump back to protect himself.  Losing his balance, Luke rolls 
down the stairs to the circular carbon-freezing platform.  There he 
sprawls on the floor, surprised and shaken.  Just in time he looks up 
to see Vader, like a giant black bird, flying right at him.  Luke rolls 
away as Vader lands.  Crouching, Luke keeps his gaze steadily on his 
enemy.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Your destiny lies with me, 
		Skywalker.  Obi-Wan knew this to 
		be true.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		No!</sp>

<sd>Behind Luke the hydraulic elevator cover has opened noiselessly.  All 
the while, Luke slowly, cautiously moves back, away from the Dark Lord.</sd>

<sd>Suddenly, Vader attacks so forcefully that Luke loses his balance and 
falls back into the opening.  There is a rumble, and in an instant 
freezing steam rises to obscure Vader's vision.   Vader turns aside and 
deactivates his sword.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		All to easy.  Perhaps you are not 
		as strong as the Emperor thought.</sp>

<sd>Through the steam behind Vader something blurs upward.  Liquid metal 
begins to pour into the pit.</sd>

<sd>Vader turns around - and then looks up.  He sees Luke, who has leaped 
fifteen feet straight up and who now hangs from some hoses on the 
carbonite outlet.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Impressive... most impressive.</sp>

<sd>Luke jumps down to the platform where he is separated from Vader by the 
steaming carbonite pit.  He raises his hand.  His sword, which had 
fallen on another part of the platform, swiftly jumps into his 
outstretched hand and is instantly ignited.  Vader immediately lights 
his sword as well.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Obi-Wan has taught you well.  You 
		have controlled your fear... now 
		release your anger.</sp>

<sd>Luke is more cautious, controlling his anger.  He begins to retreat as 
Vader goads him on.  As Luke takes a defensive position, he realizes he 
has been foolhardy.  A quick sword exchange and Luke forces Vader back.  
Another exchange and Vader retreats.  Luke presses forward.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Only your hatred can destroy me.</sp>

<sd>Breathing hard, Luke jumps in the air, turning a somersault over Vader.  
He lands on the floor and slashes at Vader as the room continues to 
fill up with steam.</sd>

<sd>Vader retreats before Luke's skillful sword.  Vader blocks the sword, 
but looses his balance and falls into the outer rim of pipes.  The 
energy Luke has used to stop Vader has brought him to the point of 
collapse.  Luke moves to the edge and looks down, but sees no sign of 
Vader.  He then deactivates his sword, hooks it on his belt, and lowers 
himself into the pit.</sd>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - TUNNEL AND REACTOR CONTROL ROOM</setting>

<sd>Moving through a tunnellike entrance, Luke cautiously approaches the 
reactor room.  He ignites his sword and moves into the room and toward 
a large window as Vader enters.</sd>

<sd>Luke raises his sword and moves forward to attack.</sd>

<sd>Behind Luke a large piece of machinery detaches itself from the wall 
and comes smashing forward toward his back.  Luke turns and cuts it in 
half just as another machine comes hurtling at him.  Using the <name type="ORG">Force</name>, 
Luke manages to deflect it and send it flying as if it had hit an 
invisible shield.</sd>

<sd>A large pipe detaches and comes flying at Luke.  He deflects it.  
Sparking wires pull out of the wall and begin to whip at the youth.  
Small tools and equipment come flying at him.  Bombardment from all 
sides, Luke does his best to deflect everything, but soon he is 
bloodied and bruised.  Finally, one machine glances off his and goes 
flying out the large window.  A fierce wind blows into the room, 
unmoving, stands the dark, rocklike figure of Vader.</sd>

<sd>A piece of machinery hits Luke and he is knocked out of the window.</sd>

<setting>INT. GANTRY - OUTSIDE CONTROL ROOM - REACTOR SHAFT</setting>

<sd>Luke falls onto the gantry, rolls, and hangs over the edge, holding his 
deactivated sword in hand.  He puts the sword on his belt and begins to 
scramble up.</sd>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - CORRIDOR LEADING TO LANDING PLATFORM</setting>

<sd>Leia, <name type="GPE">Lando</name>, Chewie and the droids come round a corner and head for the 
door to the landing platform.  They glimpse the Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> for a 
moment before the door slams shut.  The group ducks into an alcove as 
stormtroopers arrive at the end of the corridor.  The troopers send a 
rain of laser bolts at the group.  Chewie returns their fire as <name type="GPE">Lando</name> 
punches desperately at the door's control panel.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		The security codes has been changed!</sp>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		<name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, you can tell the computer 
		to override the security system.</sp>

<sd><name type="ORG">Threepio</name> points to a computer socket on the control panel.  <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps 
and scoots toward it.  <name type="GPE">Lando</name> meanwhile has connected up to the panel's 
intercom.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		Attention!  This is <name type="GPE">Lando</name>
		Calrissian.  The <name type="GPE">Empire</name> has takes 
		control of the city.  I advise 
		everyone to leave before more 
		<name type="ORG">Imperial</name> troops arrive.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> takes off a computer cover and sticks his computer arm into the 
socket.  Suddenly, a short beep turns into a wild scream.  <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>'s 
circuits light up, his head spins wildly, and smoke begins to seep out 
underneath him.  Quickly, Chewie pulls him away.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		This way.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Lando</name>, Leia, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, and Chewie flee down the corridor.  As he scoots 
along with them, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> sends some angry beeps <name type="ORG">Threepio</name>'s way.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Don't blame me.  I'm an interpreter. 
		I'm not supposed to know a power 
		socket from a computer terminal.</sp>

<setting>INT. CLOUD CITY - CORRIDOR</setting>

<sd>In a panic, Cloud City residents are trying to get out of the city.  
Some carry boxes, others packages.  They run, then change direction.  
Some are shooting at stormtroopers, others simply try to hide.</sd>

<sd>Other stormtroopers pursue <name type="GPE">Lando</name>, Leia, and Chewie who are firing back 
at them.  <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> works on another door to the landing platform while 
<name type="ORG">Threepio</name> berates him for his seeming ineptitude.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		What are you talking about?  We're 
		not interested in the hyperdrive 
		on the Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>.  It's 
		fixed!  Just open the door, you 
		stupid lump.</sp>

<sd>Chewie, Leia, and <name type="GPE">Lando</name> retreat along the corridor.  A triumphant beep 
from <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> - and the door snaps open.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
			(to <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>)
		I never doubted you for a second.
		Wonderful!</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> lays a cloud fog, obscuring everything, as the group dashes 
outside.</sd>

<setting>EXT. LANDING PLATFORM - CLOUD CITY - DUSK</setting>

<sd>They race for the Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> as a battalion of stormtroopers 
reaches the main door.  <name type="GPE">Lando</name> and Leia hold off the troops as the 
droids get on board with Chewie.  As Chewie bounds to the ship the 
<name type="ORG">Threepio</name> on his back, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> hits his head on the top of the ramp.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Ouch!  Oh!  Ah!  That hurt.  Bend 
		down, you thoughtless... Ow!</sp>

<sd>Chewie starts up the ship.  The giant engines begin to whine as <name type="GPE">Lando</name> 
and Leia race up the ramp under a hail of laser fire.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		Leia!  Go!</sp>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - CORRIDOR</setting>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> drags the partially assembled <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> down the corridor of the 
<name type="ORG">Falcon</name>.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		I thought that hairy beast would 
		be the end of me.  Of course, I've 
		looked better.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps understandingly.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Chewie works the controls as Leia sits in <name type="NORP">Han</name>'s seat and <name type="GPE">Lando</name> watches 
over their shoulders.  As Chewie pulls back on the throttle, the ship 
begins to move.</sd>

<setting>EXT. CLOUD CITY - LANDING PLATFORM - DUSK</setting>

<sd>The Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> lifts gracefully into the twilight sky and roars 
away from the city.  Troops fire after it and <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters take off in 
pursuit.</sd>

<setting>INT. GANTRY - OUTSIDE CONTROL ROOM - REACTOR SHAFT</setting>

<sd>Luke moves along the railing and up to the control room.</sd>

<sd>Vader lunges at him and Luke immediately raises his lit sword to meet 
Vader's.  Sparks fly as they duel, Vader gradually forcing Luke 
backward toward the gantry.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		You are beaten.  It is useless 
		to resist.  Don't let yourself 
		be destroyed as Obi-Wan did.</sp>

<sd>Luke answers by rolling sideways and thrusting his sword at Vader so 
viciously that he nicks Vader on the shoulder.  The black armor sparks 
and smokes and Vader seems to be hurt, but immediately recovers.</sd>

<sd>Luke backs off along the narrow end of the gantry as Vader comes at 
him, slashing at the young <name type="ORG">Jedi</name> with his sword.  Luke makes a quick 
move around the instrument complex attached to the end of the gantry.  
Vader's sword comes slashing down, cutting the complex loose; it begins 
to fall, then is caught by the rising wind and blown upward.</sd>

<sd>Luke glances at the instrument complex floating away.  At that instant, 
Vader's sword comes down across Luke's right forearm, cutting off his 
hand and sending his sword flying.  In great pain, Luke squeezes his 
forearm under his left armpit and moves back along the gantry to its 
extreme end.  Vader
follows.  The wind subsides.  Luke holds on.  There is nowhere else to 
go.  </sd>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		There is no escape.  Don't make 
		me destroy you.  You do not yet 
		realize your importance.  You 
		have only begun to discover your 
		power.  Join me and I will complete 
		your training.  With our combined 
		strength, we can end this destructive 
		conflict and bring order to the 
		galaxy.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		I'll never join you!</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		If you only knew the power of the 
		dark side.  Obi-Wan never told 
		you what happened to your father.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		He told me enough!  It was you 
		who killed him.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		No.  I am your father.</sp>

<sd>Shocked, Luke looks at Vader in utter disbelief.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		No.  No.  That's not true!  
		That's impossible!</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Search your feelings.  You know 
		it to be true.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		No!  No!  No!</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Luke.  You can destroy the Emperor.
		He has foreseen this.  It is your 
		destiny.  Join me, and together 
		we can rule the galaxy as father 
		and son.  Come with me.  It is the 
		only way.</sp>

<sd>Vader puts away his sword and holds his hand out to Luke.</sd>

<sd>A calm comes over Luke, and he makes a decision.  In the next instant 
he steps off the gantry platform into space.  The Dark Lord looks over 
the platform and sees Luke falling far below.  The wind begins to blow 
at Vader's cape and the torrent finally forces him back, away from the 
edge.  The wind soon fades and the wounded <name type="ORG">Jedi</name> begins to drop fast, 
unable to grab onto anything to break his fall.</sd>

<setting>INT. REACTOR SHAFT</setting>

<sd>Suddenly Luke is sucked into an exhaust pipe in the side of the shaft.  
When Vader sees this, he turns and hurries off the platform.</sd>

<setting>INT. EXHAUST PIPE</setting>

<sd>Luke tumbles through the exhaust pipe.</sd>

<sd>He slides to the end of the slickly polished pipe and stops as his feet 
hit a circular grill and knock it open.  Luke claws at the surface of 
the pipe, trying to keep from sliding out into space.</sd>

<setting>EXT. BOTTOM OF CLOUD CITY - WEATHER VANE - DUSK</setting>

<sd>Unable to hang onto the pipe, Luke tumbles out, emerging at the 
undermost part of Cloud City.  Reaching out desperately, he manages to 
grab onto on electronic weather vane.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Ben... Ben, please!</sp>

<sd>Luke tries to pull himself up on the weather vane but slips back down.  
He hooks one of his legs around the fragile instruments.  All the 
while, a powerful current of air rushes out at him from the exhaust 
pipe.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Ben.  Leia!</sp>

<sd>There is an ominous cracking sound from the base of the
weather vane and a piece breaks off, falling into the clouds far below.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Hear me!  Leia!</sp>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Leia seems to be lost in a fog, her expression troubled.  Chewie is 
busy operating the ship.  <name type="GPE">Lando</name> stands next to the <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name>, watching a 
readout on the control panel.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Luke... We've got to go back.</sp>

<sd>Chewie growls in surprise.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		What?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		I know where Luke is.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		But what about those fighter?</sp>

<sd>Chewie barks in agreement with <name type="GPE">Lando</name>.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Chewie, just do it.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		But what about Vader?</sp>

<sd>Chewie turns on <name type="GPE">Lando</name>, the newcomer, with an ominous growl.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		All right, all right, all right.</sp>

<setting>EXT. CLOUD CITY - MILLENNIUM FALCON - DUSK</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> makes a graceful banking turn back toward Cloud City.</sd>

<setting>EXT. CLOUD CITY - LANDING PLATFORM</setting>

<sd>Vader enters the landing platform and watches as the speck that is the 
<name type="ORG">Falcon</name> disappears.  The wind blows at his cape.</sd>

<sd>He turns to two aides who are standing near the entrance to the landing 
platform.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Bring my shuttle.</sp>

<setting>EXT. BOTTOM OF CLOUD CITY - WEATHER VANE</setting>

<sd>Nearly unconscious, Luke hangs upside-down on the weather vane as his 
body shifts in the wind.</sd>

<setting>EXT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - BOTTOM OF CLOUD CITY</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> dives to the underside of the floating city.  Three <name type="ORG">TIE</name> 
fighter close in on the starship.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON</setting>

<sd>Leia tries to remain calm.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
			(pointing out the 
			 cockpit window)
		Look, someone's up there.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		It's Luke.  Chewie, slow down.
		Slow down and we'll get under him.
		<name type="GPE">Lando</name>, open the top hatch.</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Lando</name> rushes out of the cockpit.</sd>

<setting>EXT. BOTTOM OF CLOUD CITY - WEATHER VANE</setting>

<sd>Luke hangs by one arm from the crossbar of the weather vane.  He slips 
from the bar and grabs onto the pole of the vane as the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> banks 
toward him.  The <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> positions itself under Luke as <name type="GPE">Lando</name> moves up 
through the opening of the hatch.  Luke begins to slide and finally 
falls from the vane into space.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Out the cockpit window, Leia sees Luke falling from the bottom of the 
city.  The ship gains on him.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		Okay.  Easy, Chewie.</sp>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> closes in on Luke.</sd>

<setting>EXT. BOTTOM OF CLOUD CITY</setting>

<sd>Three <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters race toward the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>, firing away.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - HATCH</setting>

<sd>The hatch pops open with a hiss of pressure.  <name type="GPE">Lando</name> reaches out to help 
the battered warrior inside the ship.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Flak bursts all around it as the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> banks away from the city.  Leia 
and Chewie struggle with the controls.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
			(into intercom)
		<name type="GPE">Lando</name>?</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
			(over intercom)
		Okay, let's go.</sp>

<setting>EXT. BOTTOM OF CLOUD CITY</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> races away.  It is closely followed by three <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters, 
all of which keep up a heavy laser assault on the fleeing starship.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Explosions erupt all around the cockpit, buffeting the ship wildly.  
Chewie howls as he frantically tries to control the ship.</sd>

<sd>Leia and Chewie turns to see Luke, bloody and battered, enter the 
cockpit supported by <name type="GPE">Lando</name>.  Leia jumps up and hugs him while Chewie 
barks in joyous relief.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Oh, Leia.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		All right, Chewie.  Let's go.</sp>

<sd>Leia helps Luke from the cockpit as another huge blast rocks the ship.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - CLOUD CITY - DAY</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>, still followed by the three <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters, races away from 
the cloud-covered city.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - SLEEPING QUARTERS</setting>

<sd>Luke rests on a cot, his injured arm wrapped in a protective cuff.  
Leia gently wipes his face.  The ship lurches again.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		I'll be back.</sp>

<sd>She kisses him, then leaves the quarters.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>All over the ship muted alarm buzzers sound.  <name type="GPE">Lando</name> anxiously watches 
the flashing lights on the control panel and hurriedly adjusts some 
switches.  Seated next to him, Chewie points out a new blip appearing 
on the panel.  Leia, watching over their shoulders, recognizes the 
shape.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		<name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name>.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		All right, Chewie.  Ready for 
		light-speed.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		If your people fixed the 
		hyperdrive.</sp>

<sd>Another explosion rocks the ship.  Leia notices as a green light on the 
panel next to her flashes on.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LEIA</speaker>
		All the coordinates are set.
		It's now or never.</sp>

<sd>Chewie barks in agreement.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		Punch it!</sp>

<sd>The <name type="NORP">Wookiee</name> shrugs and pulls back on the light-speed throttle.  The 
sound of the ion engine changes...it is winding up.  Faces are tense, 
expectant.  But nothing happens, and the engine goes off.  Chewie lets 
out a frustrated howl.  The flak still violently rocks the ship.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
		They told me they fixed it.  I 
		trusted them to fix it.  It's not 
		my fault!</sp>

<sd>Chewie gets up from his chair and starts out of the cockpit.  He gives 
<name type="GPE">Lando</name> and angry shove as he storms past him.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>In the distance the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters continue their chase, still shooting 
lasers.  Vader's <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name> moves behind them, determinedly 
following the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>.</sd>

<setting>INT. VADER'S STAR DESTROYER - BRIDGE</setting>

<sd>Vader stands on the bridge looking out the window as Admiral Piett 
approaches him.</sd>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		They'll be in range of our 
		tractor beam in moments, my lord.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Did your men deactivate the 
		hyperdrive on the Millennium 
		<name type="ORG">Falcon</name>?</sp>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		Yes, my lord.</sp>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Good.  Prepare the boarding party 
		and set your weapons for stun.</sp>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		Yes, my lord.</sp>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON</setting>

<sd>Beeping while he works, <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> is busy connecting some wires to <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> 
who now has one leg attached. </sd>

<sd>Chewie enters through the doorway, grunting to himself.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Noisy brute.  Why don't we just 
		go into light-speed?</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> beeps in response.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		We can't?  How would you know the 
		hyperdrive is deactivated?</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> whistles knowingly.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		The city's central computer told 
		you?  <name type="GPE">Artoo</name>-Detoo, you know better 
		than to trust a strange computer.
		Ouch!  Pay attention to what 
		you're doing!</sp>

<sd>Chewie is in the pit.  He is trying to loosen something with an 
enormous wrench.  Frustrated, he uses the wrench like a club and hits 
the panel...</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Leia and <name type="GPE">Lando</name>, seated in front of the control panel, are suddenly 
sprayed by a shower of sparks.</sd>

<setting>INT. VADER'S STAR DESTROYER - BRIDGE</setting>

<sd>Vader stands on the bridge, watching as the Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> is chased 
by the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> fighters.  As his Destroyer draws nearer, Vader's breathing 
gets slightly faster.</sd>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Luke.</sp>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - SLEEPING QUARTERS</setting>

<sd>Luke realizes that Vader's ship is very near.  He feels resigned to his 
fate.  He senses that he is beaten, more emotionally than physically.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Father.</sp>

<setting>INT. VADER'S STAR DESTROYER - BRIDGE</setting>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Son, come with me.</sp>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - SLEEPING QUARTERS</setting>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(moaning)
		Ben, why didn't you tell me?</sp>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="GPE">Lando</name> and Leia are at the controls of the <name type="ORG">Falcon</name>.  Meanwhile, in the 
ship's hold, Chewie continues to work frantically on the hyperdrive 
mechanism.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
			(into intercom)
		Chewie!</sp>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> races through space followed very closely by the <name type="ORG">TIE</name> 
fighters and the huge <name type="ORG">Imperial</name> <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name>.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Luke enters the cockpit and looks out the window.  He is almost 
unconscious with pain and depression.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		It's Vader.</sp>

<setting>INT. VADER'S STAR DESTROYER - BRIDGE</setting>

<sp><speaker>VADER</speaker>
		Luke... it is your destiny.</sp>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Ben, why didn't you tell me?</sp>

<setting>INT. VADER'S STAR DESTROYER - BRIDGE</setting>

<sp><speaker>PIETT</speaker>
		Alert all commands.  Ready for 
		the tractor beam.</sp>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - HOLD</setting>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> races to a control panel and starts working on a circuit board.  
Furious, <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> stands on one leg, yelling.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		<name type="GPE">Artoo</name>, come back at once!  You 
		haven't finished with me yet!
		You don't know how to fix the 
		hyperdrive.  Chewbacca can do 
		it.  I'm standing here in pieces, 
		and you're having delusions of 
		grandeur!</sp>

<sd><name type="GPE">Artoo</name> moves a circuit on a control panel.  Suddenly, the control panel 
lights up.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd>Leia and <name type="GPE">Lando</name> are thrown into their seats as the Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> 
unexpectedly shoot into hyperspace.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - HOLD</setting>

<sd>The ship tilts up and <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> topples into the pit on top of Chewie.</sd>

<sp><speaker>THREEPIO</speaker>
		Oh, you did it!</sp>

<setting>EXT. SPACE</setting>

<sd>The <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> soars into infinity and away from the huge <name type="ORG">Star Destroyer</name> 
which seems, by contrast, to stand still.</sd>

<setting>INT. VADER'S STAR DESTROYER - BRIDGE</setting>

<sd>Admiral Piett and another captain glance at Vader in terror.  Vader 
turns slowly and walks off the bridge, his hands held behind his back 
in a contemplative gesture.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - REBEL CRUISER</setting>

<sd>The Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> is attached to a huge Rebel cruiser by a docking 
tube.  Rebel fighters move about the giant cruiser, and a Rebel 
transport ship hovers near the fleet.</sd>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sd><name type="GPE">Lando</name> sits in the pilot's seat as he talks into the comlink.  Chewie 
busily throws a variety of switches in preparation for takeoff.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		Luke, we're ready for takeoff.</sp>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(over comlink)
		Good luck, <name type="GPE">Lando</name></sp>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		When we find Jabba the <name type="ORG">Hut</name> and 
		that bounty hunter, we'll contact 
		you.</sp>

<setting>INT. STAR CRUISER - MEDICAL CENTER</setting>

<sd>Luke speaking into the comlink as a medical droid works on his hand.  
Leia stands near him while <name type="ORG">Threepio</name> and <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> look out the window.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		I'll meet you at the rendezvous 
		point on Tatooine.</sp>

<setting>INT. MILLENNIUM FALCON - COCKPIT</setting>

<sp><speaker>LANDO</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		Princess, we'll find <name type="NORP">Han</name>.  I 
		promise.</sp>

<setting>INT. STAR CRUISER - MEDICAL CENTER</setting>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		Chewie, I'll be waiting for your 
		signal.</sp>

<sd>Chewie's wail comes over the comlink.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
			(into comlink)
		Take care, you two.  May the 
		<name type="ORG">Force</name> be with you.</sp>

<sd>Luke looks down at his hand.  A metalized type of bandage has been 
wrapped around his wrist.  The medical droid makes some adjustments in 
a tiny electronic unit, then pricks each one of Luke's fingers.</sd>

<sp><speaker>LUKE</speaker>
		Ow!</sp>

<sd>Luke wriggles his fingers, makes a fist, and relaxes it.  His hand is 
completely functional.</sd>

<sd>He gets up and walks over to Leia.  There is a new bond between them, a 
new understanding.  Leia is thinking about <name type="NORP">Han</name>; Luke is thinking about 
his uncertain and newly complicated future.  Together they stand at the 
large window of the medical center looking out on the Rebel Star 
Cruiser and a dense, luminous galaxy swirling in space.</sd>

<sd>Luke puts his arm around Leia.  The droids stand next to them, and 
<name type="ORG">Threepio</name> moves closer to <name type="GPE">Artoo</name> putting his arm on him.  The group 
watches as the Millennium <name type="ORG">Falcon</name> moves into view, makes a turn, and 
zooms away into space.</sd>

<setting>EXT. SPACE - REBEL STAR CRUISER</setting>

<sd>While Luke, Leia, and the droids stand, looking out the window of the 
star cruiser, two escort fighters join the large ship.  Slowly, the 
cruiser turns and moves away into space.
DISSOLVE TO </sd>

<setting>EXT. GALAXY - SPACE</setting>

<sd>END CREDITS FADE IN AND OUT OVER BACKGROUND</sd>

<sd>THE END</sd>

</script>
</root>