<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!--I'm typing text above the root document-->
<!--Shift + Ctrl + Comma-->
<xml>
    <title>Country Loaf (Pain de Campagne)</title>

    <Publisher>Deb Lindsey for The Washington Post</Publisher>

    <date int="date">SEP 10, 2014</date>
    <intro p="1">
        <author name="First-Last"> Washington author Sam Fromartz</author>
        <para>has been making sourdough variations of this yeast bread for years. Here, he adds
            fermented cider for flavor. <Sub>A mild beer may be substituted;</Sub>
            <exception>an IPA would be too bitter</exception>. The loaf is sized to last a few days.
                <p>The optional tablespoon of water is to compensate for the variable absorption of
                the rye and whole-wheat flours.</p>
            <p>You'll need a colander, a pastry cloth or clean dish towel and a covered cast-iron or
                enameled cast-iron pot.</p>
            <p>Make Ahead: <time t="80min">The dough needs four 20-minute rests</time>, plus an
                    <time t-="480-1440min">8-to-24-hour stay in the refrigerator</time> and a final
                    <time t="90min">1 1/2-hour rise.</time></p>
            <p>Storage Notes: Store the cooled loaf in a paper bag for a day,</p>
            <time t="1440-2880+min">and store in a plastic bag for a few days after that.</time>
            <notice>Do not refrigerate.</notice>
        </para>
    </intro>
    <subTitle>SERVINGS:</subTitle>
    <Measurement>
        <subHeading>Tested</subHeading>
        <Size>size: 10-12</Size>
        <p>servings; makes one </p>
        <unit m="11">11-ounce </unit>
        <Slices count="10-12">loaf 10 to 12 slices</Slices>
    </Measurement>

    <subTitle>INGREDIENTS</subTitle>
    <IngedList>
        <li Ingred="1">
            <quant int="1.25">1 1/4 cups <unit m="g">(160 grams)</unit></quant>
            <p>white bread flour, plus more for dusting</p>
        </li>
        <li Ingred="2">
            <quant int=".25">1/4 cup <unit m="g">(38 grams)</unit></quant>
            <Wheat type="Stone-Ground whole-wheat flour"> stone-ground whole-wheat flour</Wheat>
        </li>
        <li Ingred="3">
            <quant int=".25">1/4 cup <unit m="g">(32 grams)</unit></quant>
            <p>stone-ground whole rye flour</p>
        </li>
        <li Ingred="4">
            <quant int=".50">1/2 teaspoon </quant>
            <p>instant yeast or bread machine yeast</p>
        </li>
        <li Ingred="5">
            <quant int="1">1 teaspoon</quant>
            <p>table salt</p>
        </li>
        <li Ingred="6">
            <quant int=".25">1/4 cup <unit m="g">(55 grams)</unit></quant>
            <p>dry fermented cider</p>
            <substitute>(may substitute Pilsener beer; see headnote)</substitute>
        </li>
        <li Ingred="7">
            <quant int=".50">1/2 cup <unit m="g">(120 grams)</unit></quant>
            <Temp t="80^f">lukewarm water <unit m="f">(80 degrees)</unit></Temp>, <OpStep>plus an
                optional 1 tablespoon</OpStep></li>
    </IngedList>
    <subTitle>DIRECTIONS</subTitle>
    <StepList>
        <li step="1">Whisk together the flours, yeast and salt in a mixing bowl. Combine the cider
            and water in a liquid measuring cup.</li>

        <li step="2">Add the liquid to the flour mixture; use a spatula or bench scraper or your
            hand moistened with water to blend them <time t="1min">for about a minute.</time> The
            dough should be shaggy yet cohesive. Cover the bowl with a towel; let the dough rest for
            20 minutes.</li>

        <li step="3">Moisten your kneading hand. If the dough seems stiff, add the optional
            tablespoon of water. Stretch one edge of the dough (still in the bowl), then press it
            into the center of the bowl. Repeat this about a dozen times, moving clockwise to catch
            all sides of the dough. (This should take 1 or 2 minutes.)</li>

        <li step="4">Turn the dough over so the seams are on the bottom. Cover and <time t="20min"
                >let rest for 20 minutes</time>. Repeat the clockwise stretching and folding two
            more times, with 20-minute rests after each. Cover and refrigerate at least 8 hours and
            up to 24 hours. The dough should have doubled. If it hasn't, leave it on the counter
            until it does.</li>

        <li step="5">Lightly flour a work surface. Use a pastry cloth or clean dish towel to line a
            round colander. Dust the cloth with flour.</li>

        <li step="6">Transfer the dough to the floured work surface. Fold the edges toward the
            center to create a round shape, turning it over so the seams are on the bottom. Let it
            rest for 5 minutes, then transfer to the colander, seam side up. Cover with a towel and
            let the dough rise for 1 1/2 hours.</li>

        <li step="7"><time t="30min">Thirty minutes before baking,</time> place a cast-iron Dutch
            oven (lid on) or enameled cast-iron pot with a lid (on) in the oven; preheat to 475
            degrees.</li>

        <li step="8">Carefully remove the hot pot from the oven.</li>

        <li step="9">Turn the dough out onto the counter so the seams are on the bottom. Use kitchen
            scissors to make 8 snips on the top of the dough in an evenly spaced spoke pattern, each
            about 1/4-inch deep. Lift the dough and carefully drop it into the hot pot. Immediately
            cover with the hot lid. Bake for 30 minutes, then reduce the heat to 450 degrees.
            Uncover and bake for 8 to 10 minutes or until the crust is dark brown. Try to minimize
            the amount of time the oven door is open.</li>

        <li step="10">The bread is done when its internal temperature registers 205 degrees on an
            instant-read thermometer and the loaf sounds hollow when knocked on the underside.</li>

        <li step="11">Transfer the loaf to a wire rack to cool for at least 1 hour before
            cutting.</li>
    </StepList>
</xml>
