<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
    <menuname>Beef Wellington</menuname> by <author>DELISH EDITORS</author>
    <publishtime>JAN 18, 2022</publishtime>
    <title>This Beef Wellington Will Wow Your Dinner Guests</title>
    <paragraph num="1">So, you've decided to make Beef Wellington. Congratulations! You are about to
        make your dinner guests extremely happy. While the origins of this famous dish are unknown,
        we do know it's a holiday showstopper that it is not for the faint of heart. Below, we break
        down all the elements of a classic Beef Wellington from the inside out, so you can
        fearlessly make the best Wellington you can. We believe in you!</paragraph>
    <importantstuff num="1">The Meat</importantstuff>
    <paragraph num="2">We're starting with one of the most tender cuts of beef ever—the tenderloin!
        Beef tenderloin is super delicious, but without bones or much marbling, it's not the most
        flavorful cut of beef in the world. That is why we season liberally. (Read: about 1 teaspoon
        kosher salt per pound.) That is also why we sear the meat before anything else. Browning the
        meat on all sides, including the ends, does SO MUCH for the flavor of the Wellington as a
        whole.</paragraph>
    <importantstuff num="2">The Mustard</importantstuff>
    <paragraph num="3">To add another layer of complexity to the finished product, brush the seared
        tenderloin with mustard. Feel free to use your favorite type—we love a variety with some
        heat like dijon or spicy brown mustard. </paragraph>
    <importantstuff num="3">The Mushrooms</importantstuff>
    <paragraph num="4">AKA the duxelle, this mixture of mushrooms, shallots, and thyme is SUPER
        savory. As if beef tenderloin wasn't bringing enough umami, this mixture takes it to the
        next level. Word to the wise: don't try to speed up the cooking process on this one, you
        realllllly want to cook out as much of the moisture as possible. If you don't, the mushrooms
        will continue to lose moisture when you're baking the Wellington, which could lead to a
        soggy bottom.</paragraph>
    <importantstuff num="4">The Prosciutto</importantstuff>
    <paragraph num="5">Speaking of soggy bottoms (or more specifically, how to avoid them) meet your
        new bestie: prosciutto! Wrapping your tenderloin in prosciutto is a little extra insurance.
        It provides a barrier for moisture, and on top of that it adds even more delicious meaty
        flavor. By shingling a layer of prosciutto onto a layer of plastic wrap, you can easily
        spread your duxelle in an even layer and wrap your tenderloin evenly. It's a
        win/win!</paragraph>
    <imoportantstuff num="5">The Pastry</imoportantstuff>
    <paragraph num="6">Some people like to make their own puff pastry for their Beef Wellington.
        Those people are crazy. Well, maybe not crazy, but definitely overachievers. We've found
        that, not only is store bought puff pastry much more convenient, but it's also incredibly
        delicious. We're particularly fond of this brand, and honestly don't think we could make a
        better version if we tried. If you DO want to attempt making your own, check out this step
        by step guide from our friends over at the Kitchn.</paragraph>
    <servings>YIELDS: <howmany>6</howmany> SERVINGS</servings>
    <preptime>PREP TIME: <times>0 HOURS 15 MINS</times></preptime>
    <totaltime>TOTAL TIME: <times>2 HOURS 30 MINS</times></totaltime>
    <ingredients><title>INGREDIENTS</title>
        <ingredients num="1"><weight>1 (2 lb.)</weight> center-cut beef tenderloin,
            trimmed</ingredients>
        <ingredients num="2">kosher salt</ingredients>
        <ingredients num="3">freshly ground black pepper</ingredients>
        <ingredients num="4">extra-virgin olive oil, for greasing</ingredients>
        <ingredients num="5"><howmany>2 <unint>tbsp.</unint></howmany> Dijon mustard</ingredients>
        <ingredients num="6"><howmany>1 1/2 lb.</howmany> mixed mushrooms, roughly
            chopped</ingredients>
        <ingredients num="7">1 shallot, roughly chopped</ingredients>
        <ingredients num="8">Leaves from 1 thyme sprig</ingredients>
        <ingredients num="9"><howmany>2 <unint>tbsp.</unint></howmany> unsalted butter</ingredients>
        <ingredients num="10">12 thin slices prosciutto</ingredients>
        <ingredients num="11">all-purpose flour, for dusting</ingredients>
        <ingredients num="12"><howmany>14 <unint>oz.</unint></howmany> frozen puff pastry,
            thawed</ingredients>
        <ingredients num="13">1 large egg, beaten</ingredients>
        <ingredients num="14">flaky salt, for sprinkling</ingredients></ingredients>
    <directions>DIRECTIONS</directions>
    <step num="1">Using kitchen twine, tie tenderloin in 4 places. Season generously with salt and
        pepper.</step>
    <step num="2">Over high heat, coat bottom of a heavy skillet with olive oil. Once pan is nearly
        smoking, sear tenderloin until well-browned on all sides, including the ends, about 2
        minutes per side (12 minutes total). Transfer to a plate. When cool enough to handle, snip
        off twine and coat all sides with mustard. Let cool in fridge.</step>
    <step num="4">Meanwhile, make duxelles: In a food processor, pulse mushrooms, shallots, and
        thyme until finely chopped.</step>
    <step num="5">To skillet, add butter and melt over medium heat. Add mushroom mixture and cook
        until liquid has evaporated, about 25 minutes. Season with salt and pepper, then let cool in
        fridge.</step>
    <step num="6">Place plastic wrap down on a work surface, overlapping so that it’s twice the
        length and width of the tenderloin. Shingle the prosciutto on the plastic wrap into a
        rectangle that’s big enough to cover the whole tenderloin. Spread the duxelles evenly and
        thinly over the prosciutto.</step>
    <step num="7">Season tenderloin, then place it at the bottom of the prosciutto. Roll meat into
        prosciutto-mushroom mixture, using plastic wrap to roll tightly. Tuck ends of prosciutto as
        you roll, then twist ends of plastic wrap tightly into a log and transfer to fridge to chill
        (this helps it maintain its shape).</step>
    <step num="8">Heat oven to 425°. Lightly flour your work surface, then spread out puff pastry
        and roll it into a rectangle that will cover the tenderloin (just a little bigger than the
        prosciutto rectangle you just made!). Remove tenderloin from plastic wrap and place on
        bottom of puff pastry. Brush the other three edges of the pastry with egg wash, then tightly
        roll beef into pastry.</step>
    <step num="9">Once the log is fully covered in puff pastry, trim any extra pastry, then crimp
        edges with a fork to seal well. Wrap roll in plastic wrap to get a really tight cylinder,
        then chill for 20 minutes.</step>
    <step num="10">Remove plastic wrap, then transfer roll to a foil-lined baking sheet. Brush with
        egg wash and sprinkle with flaky salt.</step>
    <step num="11">Bake until pastry is golden and the center registers 120°F for medium-rare, about
        40 to 45 minutes. Let rest 10 minutes before carving and serving.</step>
</root>
