<xml>
<title>A Fond Farewell</title>
<line speaker="Layton">...Well then, my boy. Why don't you get some tea ready for our guests?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right away, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Man, that was one wild and crazy ride.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Definitely. Everyone back in Labyrinthia seemed as plucky as ever.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Well, Mr Wright... that's all thanks to everyone's efforts. For the longest time, our town was shrouded behind a thick veil of secrecy. But now? It's absolutely thriving! And I, too...am thriving. For the first time ever, I truly feel like myself.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I believe I speak for all of us when I say it is most reassuring to hear that, Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Saying that... doesn't it feel like one heck of a long adventure?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. In fact, the development of this very game seems to have been quite the long adventure in and of itself.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The game's...development, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Merging together two such distinct series as Professor Layton and Ace Attorney... It must have taken a considerable degree of thought and planning to get such a project off the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, hey. Clearly they were able to get the ball rolling pretty easily, or else we wouldn't be standing here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's right! I bet it was smooth sailing getting the idea through!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Quite right, Luke. Level-5 and Capcom both certainly saw the potential success of such a combination. However... it was not quite a walk in the park to begin with. In fact, things were a bit... uncomfortable at the start.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I-is that right, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come to think of it... Things didn't exactly hit the ground running, huh? Professor, remember when they had us stand side-by-side for the first time?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. I must say, there was quite the bit of...incongruity between the two of us, wasn't there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Definitely. And I'm pretty sure everyone MORE than noticed it, too... I mean, all anyone has to do is take one good look at the two of us side-by-side... Our character designs are pretty different.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yeah, that's true, Mr Wright. You and Maya both look a little more, um..."real" than we do.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Not to mention, Nick and I were, what... two or three heads taller than you guys?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Three heads taller is overkill, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">But I never noticed any sort of strange discrepancies between you all...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They must have gone through all sorts of adjustments before the game, right?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Adjustments...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This is just an aside, but there is something rather odd that I became aware of. I felt as if...I were gradually growing taller throughout the game's development.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Of course! You were getting more and more stylish by the day, huh, Professor? Y'know, I was playing the professor's latest game just the other day... and I totally thought to myself: "Is the 3D getting weird, or does the professor look shorter in this game?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...But you know, the professor and Luke weren't the only ones that needed a little bit of adjustment.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">WHAAAAAT?! Seriously?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I do believe Mr Wright and yourself needed a bit of a height reduction for the sake of balance, Miss Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww, man... You mean to tell me Nick and I were both cut down to size? The developers never tell me anything...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's a bit scary when you think about it. Having to get used to being changed over and over...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I have to say, though... the final showdown between Mr Wright and the professor was really very impressive.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You said it! That final trial sure was something else! And, Professor, you were quite the sly fox, too!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Excuse me, Miss Fey? A sly fox...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, how you told us "I'm off to go fetch some evidence for the trial, old bean!" and left us to the trial totally unprepared. But then! You kicked down the door to the courtroom, like BOOM, and completely took over the inquisitor's bench! I was actually hoping I could've stepped in as inquisitor. "Milord, Inquisitor Fey sentences that burger to my stomach!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, do you even listen to yourself when you speak...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Now, now...I was just giving the players what they came to see, Miss Fey. After all... "vs" is in the game's title, is it not?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's right! Nothing says "vs" like a dramatic courtroom battle, eh, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Don't forget about the team puzzle. It proved to be quite popular, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... You're talking about that puzzle for opening the huge door down in the underground ruins, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, yeah...the puzzle that Nick moaned on and ON about until he ended up trial-and-erroring it, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Resisting the urge to object. Hey, I'd say that's sorta got a "vs" kind of vibe. Us versus the puzzles, right?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would seem our dear developers had quite a few different ideas on how to implement the "vs" of the title.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh, yeah...that reminds me! Remember in the initial storyboard... there was even a scene where the professor and Mr Wright face off against each other in a fencing match!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Fencing...? Oh yeah! I totally saw that too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I have to admit, I was pretty surprised to see that in the storyboard. I mean...pointing my finger at people is one thing, but a sword? That's a whole other ball game.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It didn't make it into the final game in the end though, did it?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">No. Unfortunately not, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah... But at least... the professor got to hack 'n' slash those HUGE walking tin cans the Storyteller called knights!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That, I assure you, was a special case, Miss Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By the way, I've gotta say, Maya. You surprised me. You're not usually the kind of person that literally leaps into action, like you did when you saved Espella back in court... But...you're definitely the kinda person that would get trapped in a steel cage of death and dropped into a raging pit of fire.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Well yeah- HOLD IT! Whaddya mean I don't leap into action?! I can leap! Who said I can't?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">At any rate... there are a number of fun and interesting ways for the developers to play on the "vs" theme of the game.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You said it. But honestly...it sounds like making this game was really tough.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Speaking of which, know what else was tough? The developers' offices! I bet they had more than their share of...disagreements.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. This is just a rumour, but... I heard development on this game was SO ridiculously tense, the developers ended up fighting, just like in those other "vs" games!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So much for cooperation...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mind you, that said... all of us have been able to get along quite amicably despite coming from two different games. On the other hand... the developers seemed to use this opportunity to develop, let's say, a strong rivalry with one another.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, that's right. Couldn't have said it any better myself, Professor. Both were in the versus spirit, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. Whether contesting as fierce rivals or helping one another, it was all in the versus spirit. The important thing is that everyone did their utmost. Whether friendly or competitive.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick, if someone were crazy enough to put you in a fight against someone, what would be your finishing catchphrase?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, I'd have to go with something like... "It's time to pay for your crimes!"</line>
<line speaker="Layton">While the methods and thinking may differ, the end goal is the same. Both paths will lead us to the right answer. That's right... I speak of puzzle solving.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Puzzles...Professor? Ah, right. I think I get what you're saying.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, then... it appears our time together is coming to an end.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh...it is? Cor, that was fast, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Yeah, tell me about it.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Are you ready, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Absolutely, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Let us combine our efforts one last time. And put this one final puzzle to rest.</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Adventures filled with mysteries and excitement will always be around. You never know where they may take you. I am sure our paths will cross again, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I guess this is farewell until then, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um... You two will be sure to come and visit us, won't you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Duh! Of course we will. You take care of yourself, Espella. Don't go near any bells or towers. We want to be able to see you again, y'know...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Hee. I can't wait, Maya. Oh, yes... We can't forget to thank YOU all for playing our game. You have our utmost gratitude. It was thanks to you that true peace has come to our town. Even if it's just a fleeting visit, please do come back and see us in Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What Espella is trying to say is: don't be a stranger and DEFINITELY come back and see us all!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I know I'll be giving the game another go very, very soon!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, at any rate... This final special episode seems to have come to a close.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You really stuck it out with us through it all. Thank you for all of your support. I'm sure we're bound to meet again soon!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Remember! Our adventures aren't over yet!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I hope you all had as much fun as we did! ...From everyone in the Layton and Ace Attorney universe: SEE YOU LATER!</line>
</xml>