<xml>
<title>A Taste of Despair</title>
<line speaker="Luke">What do we do now? We made it out of the courtroom but... everyone's in an uproar. So, um...where do we go from here?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I...I'm truly...truly sorry! It's my fault that Maya... This all happened because of me!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Th-that's not true at all! It's not your fault, Espella! I-isn't that right, Mr Wright?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Uh...um...Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Uh... Oh! Luke, did you say something?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Y-yeah... That's right! Espella, it's not your fault! You shouldn't blame yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Um, Mr Wright, I just said that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, really?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well anyway, at least we managed to save you, Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, but...because of that, now Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya believed in you. That's why she wanted to protect you.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">He's right! So we can't let ourselves get captured now!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Luke...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That settles that then... Okay, let's get moving! We're bound to get caught if we stick around here any longer.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But, where should we go? Everyone's looking for us now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I was thinking maybe we could go to Patty's shop...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">But the knights are certain to be waiting for us there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh yeah... That's true...</line>
<line speaker="???">...My, you certainly managed to get yourselves into quite the predicament.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Th-that voice! Inquisitor Barnham!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Please wait, Inquisitor Barnham! A-arrest me, lock me up, I don't care! But... these two have nothing to do with this! Take me! I'm the one you want!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">No way, Espella! None of us are at fault here! We're not the ones who did anything wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Luke...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You are accomplices to the Great Witch Bezella and have assisted in her escape. In a manner of speaking, you have been branded an enemy to all of Labyrinthia. ...There is nowhere you can hide.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But... But why?! Espella isn't the Great Witch! Why can't you understand that?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Then, I must ask you... why do you continue to deny the clear allegation that this girl is Bezella?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's easy! Because we believe in her. I know back in the courtroom...I said I didn't believe in Maya but... Deep down, I believed in her... We all did and we all still do!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Luke...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's why I'm going to stand strong. I'm going to stick by Espella's side no matter what!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ ...Is that so? By the way...Sir Blue Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The loss of Maya Fey is...unfortunate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You...have my deepest sympathies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Really? Your..."deepest sympathies"?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">While such bedlam was indeed unexpected, we should have done something more to prevent it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Inquisitor Barnham. I proved Maya's innocence...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I admit, indeed you did.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And yet, last I saw she was being dropped into a pit of fire. Tell me, Inquisitor... Does that seem like "justice" to you?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All witches are to be cast into the flames... That's the law of the land around here, right? But... Maya WASN'T a witch! How do you explain that, Inquisitor Barnham?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...It is truly regrettable. What occurs in the courtroom... is my responsibility and mine alone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Responsibility"? ...Fine! Then take some "responsibility" right now! Magic exists here, right? Well then...use some magic and bring Maya back! Cast whatever spell you need to cast... and BRING HER BACK!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ There exists no such magic. I cannot undo her death.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ ...'Tis my blame to bear. If it would bring you solace, then take this sword and strike me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just stop it! You knights are always ready to get rid of those different from yourselves... Just...get out of my sight. ...I said GO!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">M-Mr Wright! Those voices are getting closer! At this rate, we're...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ Exit through the main gate and head east through the forest. You should be able to escape along the small path there.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">On the outskirts of the city, you will find Rouge's tavern... You should be safe there.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wh-why are you helping...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Go! Now! You will be caught if you stay here... and this will be all for naught!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Luke! Mr Wright! L-let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Y-yeah, right! U-um...Mr Wright? Are you coming?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ ...Okay. Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Rouge's tavern is just through that forest. Now go! It is the only haven you have right now. You should be well hidden there. Go. Quickly.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What are you doing?! Be gone with you! Hurry and get to Rouge's tavern. It is just through the forest path!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I've got a bad feeling about this. Not that I'm scared, of course. My legs are shaking from the cold wind.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I...I think someone's staring at us in the darkness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you hear that? Hmm, I think it was just the wind...hopefully...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Everyone leaving the courthouse has to pass through here. Let's hurry!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's so bright here, making everything else seem jet black.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are houses in that direction, too.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Let's go the other way, away from the town!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">The place Sir Barnham told us to go to is some distance away from the shopping district.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks like we made it through the forest... I can't see those knights anywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I think we'll be safe here for a little while.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ I'm sorry for all of this, Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If we'd just headed for safety right away, we wouldn't be in this situation.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I need to apologise to you too, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've been trying your best this whole time. Just to get Espella out of here safely. It's my fault those knights are on our tail and are probably going to find us.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But...I wouldn't say all's lost just yet! I mean...there's got to be a way to bring Maya back... I'm sure we can find a way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>C'mon Phoenix... You have to keep it together here! These two need you now more than ever!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well then... How about we make our way to that tavern Inquisitor Barnham mentioned?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Yes, that would be Rouge's tavern. I can show you the way.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? Hey, Espella...you know that place?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, yes... It looks a little bit scary, so I've never been inside before, though. But...I come to this side of town often to do my shopping, so I've passed it a few times. ...Um, I think Ms Mary's goat farm is around here as well.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I-is that right...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Okay. It's just this way... Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right then. Let's get going, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, yeah... Hey, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yes? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I just wanted to thank you for earlier. You really helped me out.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wh-what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...See, I get it now. I'm...not the only one who's just lost someone important to them.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">......... I believe in the professor. He would never be beaten by something like "magic". ...That witch just cast a spell on him, that's all. So...all we have to do is find a way to undo that spell, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... You know, you're right, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The professor will come back, I'm sure of it! That's why...all I can do for now is keep moving forward. It's what any true gentleman in training would do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...I get it. Okay then, let's go.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">What's wrong, you two? It's over this way! Hurry up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, sorry about that! We're coming!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Luke, check this out. It looks like there's a puzzle hidden here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm on it, Mr Wright! Make way for the ace apprentice!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hold on, Luke. I think I'd like to try this one.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Really, Mr Wright? Okay! Good luck! I'll be here if you need me!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">35</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A wide assortment of edibles is laid out on the food stand.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's something like a black market. People sell whatever they can get their hands on.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Guys, we need to hurry. You can come enjoy the sights later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Never before did house lights look so warm and welcoming.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I miss Aunt Patty...and Eve... What are they doing right now?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's time for dinner... You can't help feeling hungry even when you're depressed.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's a tool shop.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anything useful here? ...Nope.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The shopkeeper's not here. Let's come back tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Whoooooa!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Luke, what's wrong?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">S-sorry about that, Espella. I just tripped a little, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Hm? Is this...a potato?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Let's see if we can put this back into the basket. Wouldn't want anyone else to trip over it. Crikey, this place really looks like it's seen better days...</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey, hey, hey! What's with all this racket?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">S-someone's coming!</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">This ain't no place fer kids! Why don't you tykes run off and find somewhere else to play, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh! It's you!</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">...Hm? Ho ho! You're that lad from yesterday, ain't you?!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Is he an acquaintance of yours, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">Not JUST an acquaintance! This lad and the bloke in the dark hat. They... They're my saviours! Them two really saved my hide yesterday! These two pulled my fat outta the fryer right when I needed it most!</line>
<line speaker="Luke"><thought>I guess that's one way of putting it...</thought> It's all right, Espella. This man is really a good person.</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">Ho ho! That's right, lass! Ol' Cutter has a face you can trust! Hang on... Where is the bloke with the dark hat, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh... Um, well you see...the professor... He... .........</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">...Somethin' mighty unpleasant must've happened from the looks of it. How abouts we take the conversation inside, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">When you say inside...that wouldn't happen to be Rouge's tavern, would it?</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">Ho ho! Hey now! Didn't think you'd know about a place like that! I betcha you must be quite the heartbreaker with the lasses!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's not it at all! We just have a bit of business to take care of there, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">All right, all right. Just pullin' yer leg, lad. Well, if you're lookin' for Rouge's tavern, yer standin' right in front of it! It's the brightest house on this road. Y'can't miss it! No worries, though. I'll head there with you guys.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Thank you very much!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, what's that there?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright! That's a hidden puzzle! Not to worry! Just leave it to me!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">40</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">Rouge's tavern is just up ahead. It's the one beaming with light. Can't miss it!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mind your feet, everybody! The ground is littered with sharp-looking objects.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ouch! I hurt my foot...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">What a cheerful, lively place!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Somehow, that's the only brightly lit area.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The lights are off...The gloom is a little unsettling.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I miss the comfort of light, too. Darkness makes me uneasy...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow... It sure is lively in here!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It certainly is. Even more so than I thought. It's so cheerful, and everyone seems to be having a good time.</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">See, it ain't just the shadiest of the shady that hang about here. Well, y'do get the occasional rabble-rouser every now and then... But for the most part, everyone here's good people. You'll find the head honcho herself over behind the counter. Why not go introduce yourselves?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't you usually use DARTS on a dartboard? Ah, what's the use?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Knives as darts... It really does seem like something out of a fantasy book, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">The atmosphere in here is so different from the town square... I wonder if we'll be all right here?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">D-did it just sway, Mr Wright? ...I sure hope this doesn't get loose and fall.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">How pretty! It's not every day you see a chandelier like that around here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If Maya were here, I bet she'd be trying to jump up and take one of those candles...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow, look at all those bottles. I wonder if that's a whole day's worth of juice...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's a bit funny imagining Inquisitor Barnham sitting here with a tall glass of tomato juice, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It'd be funny just watching him try to sit in one of these chairs with that armour of his.</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">Ho ho! Boss Lady! I come bearing customers for ya!</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Turn the volume down, before you scare away all my other customers. Use your indoor voice, remember? ..."Customers", you say?</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">Now, I sorta sprung this on you and I know they're just a bunch of kids, but that lad there is my saviour! Hand to heart! So do me a favour and get the lad a juice. It's on me! Just put it on my tab!</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">I don't care about that! Did you take a look at that girl? What the heck were you thinking?!</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">...Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Do you have a loaf of bread for a brain or something! [sic] You fool!</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">Huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">That girl...is suspected of being the Great Witch Bezella!</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">B-B-B-B-Bezella?! Are you joking?! I didn't know that!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Now, see here! Espella is NOT Bezella!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...We were the ones that proved her innocence and cleared her of the charges.</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">S-see, Boss Lady?! The lad agrees she's not Bezella! And besides, I knew the girl was innocent from the moment I laid eyes on her!</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">...Cutter, your judgement is about as reliable as paper shoes in the rain. What I'd like to know is who told you three to come here in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It was...Inquisitor Barnham.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">...! Really now...? So, it was him, was it? You guys... Listen, don't say a word of this to anyone else, you hear me? It could make life very difficult for our dear inquisitor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... R-right. Got it...</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">I don't know what he expects me to do with you guys, but... Fine. I'll lend you a hand. You can stay here for the night. There's an empty room you can use upstairs. We don't exactly get the cleanliest types staying here, so forgive the mess. Should be good enough to sleep in, though.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Thank you very much!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...We really appreciate it.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Um... Thank you so much.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Don't get the wrong idea, kiddos. This place ain't a charity. I expect you to return the favour some day!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Phew, I'm sure glad Rouge turned out to be such a nice person!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes. Mr Cutter and Miss Rouge are both very kind.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks like we can rest easy for now! Right, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup. And I guess we can take this time to do a little sleuthing too, if we want to. But we should probably rest while we can. Tomorrow is going to be a pretty hectic day.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Now that's an idea I can get behind!</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">This place is where folks like me can come and be ourselves. Boss Lady is always helpin' out anyone that's in trouble. I know she seems a little rough at first, but I always knew she'd end up helpin' you lot in the end.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Everyone here really trusts Rouge, don't they?</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">No doubt about it, lad! And, you know? A gal like that sure demands attention, if you catch my drift.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I-I, umm... I don't really think I fully understand what you mean...</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">Gah, ha ha ha! Still a bit too green fer that, eh, lad? Oh! Would you look at the time? Best get ready for bed! Your room is upstairs. It's a bit messy, though. Hope you don't mind! Anyway, just enjoy your stay and relax! If you get sleepy, just head on upstairs!</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">Your room is upstairs. Don't mind the mess. Just enjoy and relax!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Do you and Inquisitor Barnham know each other?</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Hm, I guess you could say that.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Is...that right? It's just a bit surprising, I guess... I mean, Inquisitor Barnham is head of the Knights, and you're...</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Some ne'er-do-well tavern owner, right? Well, can't fault you for stating facts, kid!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...You may both be different, but I get the feeling you really trust one another.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Zack is...well, different from all the other knights in Labyrinthia. To any other knight, we're nothing more than a bunch of filthy no-good scum. We're the first ones to blame whenever a crime or anything happens out in the town.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's true. Mr Cutter didn't do anything wrong when the professor and I gave him a hand.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Yup. Society judges us very harshly, y'see. But Zack...he's fair. He doesn't judge anyone based on how "innocent" or "shady" they may look or what sort of job they've got. He's only interested in protecting the town with fair and sound judgement. That's why he always helps us out.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Interesting... Like I thought, he really is a good person...</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Hm? Did you say something?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah, no... It's nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Well, I think that's my cue. You take it easy and rest up, okay? If Zack told you to hide out here, then I really doubt the knights will come snooping around. And even if they did come here, we sure as heck wouldn't turn you over to the likes of them.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's good to know! Thank you again, Miss Rouge! You're really too kind.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Heh, for such a little guy you sure do know how to keep a level head in a tough spot. Your friend over there, on the other hand... I haven't heard a peep from him this whole time.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's fine. I'm sure he'll be right as rain tomorrow...</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Hm...</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">What's up? You look a little thirsty. How about I pour you a glass of fresh juice?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh wow! That'd be great!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This must be it... So this is the room Rouge was talking about, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh my... It is...quite unique, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is that...a statue in the corner? How very...err, "avant garde".</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">That statue really looks a lot like Mr Cutter, doesn't it...? ...Hey, I wonder if he made this himself.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Not only is Mr Cutter very nice, it seems he's quite artistic as well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I dunno if I'd call this "art", per se.</thought> Anyway, it's just nice to have a safe place to rest for a while.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Uh-huh! We did so much running about today. I'm totally exhausted.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think we can plan out our next step in the morning. Let's try and get some rest.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Just great. I should be ready to pass out right now. ...But I just can't fall asleep. I'm a little thirsty... Maybe I should go grab some water.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like the party is over. Everyone must have gone home by now... I'll just grab some water and head back to the room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't you usually use DARTS on a dartboard? Ah, what's the use?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If Maya were here, I bet she'd be trying to jump up and take one of those candles...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*knock* *knock* ...Sounds like it's all tapped out. People here sure do love their tomato juice...</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">What's up? Can't get to sleep?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah. I'm absolutely beat, but I just can't keep my eyes shut.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Hm...you don't say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like you've got your work cut out for you cleaning up this place. Do you need a hand?</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Nah, it's fine. The house rule is: "you [sic] make a mess, you clean it". But those dummies couldn't keep their eyes open. I'll make 'em clean up in the morning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh? So, hasn't everyone gone home?</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">I couldn't exactly let them go home in that state, so I shoved them all upstairs for the night. This is both their home and shelter. I mean, don't tell me you can't hear their loud snoring from down here...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...And here I thought that was my stomach growling this whole time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rouge">...So? You must have come down here for something, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh yeah...that's right. I came down for a glass of water.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Hm... All right. But, you'll have to earn it first. You win at my game and I'll get you any drink you want. On the house.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you say...game? Um...what kind of a game?</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">...SILENCE!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoa, now that...was totally unexpected...</thought> U-um...I'm really sorry... If I said something wrong...</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Now, don't you go getting the wrong idea. I only drew this knife... to use in this puzzle I've made for you!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">No penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Heh. Not too shabby, tiger. Well, a promise is a promise. You can have any drink you want, no charge. Refills included. Just say the word.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you... I think I'll take you up on that offer...</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">You earned it, y'know. Never saw anyone around these parts take down a puzzle like that so fast.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha. It was pure luck, trust me. If you want a puzzle expert, Luke is the one to talk to.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Oh? You mean that sharp-looking kid, right? You know, for someone so young, he's got a good head on his shoulders, that one. It looks like he's been through a lot...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...he sure has. He seems to be in good spirits, but... deep inside he must be hurting really bad. He just lost someone very dear to him... But he's trying so hard to hide it.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then there's Espella... She had a new accusation thrown at her and is again at risk of being burned alive. And...Maya. I can't stop thinking how her death was completely my fault... That's why I need to be stronger... But I can't. I just feel so...hopeless. I'm the only one who can protect Luke and Espella. ...But I'm scared. I'm scared that what happened to Maya will happen again...</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">...Maya, huh? I caught wind of what happened today in court. She seemed...very important to you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I'm...all right. I'm just...not sure I can protect those two. More than that... I just don't want them to think I might fail them.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">............ You want to protect them...and don't want them to think you'll fail...huh? That all sounds well and good. ...But you want to know what I think? I think you're just telling yourself what you want to hear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">I think the words coming out of your mouth right now are downright selfish.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-hey, what are you...</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Have you taken a second to step back from your wallowing and think how worried they must be about you right now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">So it's hopeless, huh? Do you think those kids are hopeless too? Pssh, don't make me laugh! You wanna see hopeless? That's easy. Just take a look in the mirror.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">How do you expect to protect those two if you can't even manage to get a hold of yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I...</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">...It's okay. I get it. You had some really...really rough stuff happen to you today. Unimaginably sad, emotionally trying stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">That's why the first thing you need to do... is just accept it. Accept it all. The sadness, the remorse...everything. Honestly, I don't blame you for expressing just how hard this whole situation has been on you. Who could?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... ...I... I can never forgive myself for letting this happen... I couldn't do anything...not a single thing! I did nothing to help Maya at all... Maya... She gave her own life to save Espella! If only I'd been quicker... If only I could've done something... Maya would still be... ...She'd still be here by my side... ...... It's all my fault... ......</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">......</line>
<line speaker="Luke">......</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Oh, Luke. What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah...Espella. What are you doing up at this time?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I couldn't sleep. I thought I'd just get a glass of water... Huh? Who's that over there? Is that... Miss Rouge and Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Uh... Hey, we should head back to bed, Espella! We have an early start tomorrow, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mmm. You're right.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...... Mr Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">U-um... Rouge, I just wanted to thank you... You know, for hearing me out.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Pfft, no need for formalities. We did just share a puzzle, after all. Anyways, go on and get some rest. Something tells me you'll need it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay. I'll do just that. ...Good night, Rouge.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Hm... Night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm no sword expert, but even I can tell the difference between these and something like Barnham's.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like this statue is still a work-in-progress. Makes a great hammock support, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm guessing it's supposed to be a person. Something tells me they won't be finishing any time soon.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh...sorry, Luke, did I wake you up? ...Is Espella still asleep?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yup. She's out like a light. She must have been really tired.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um...Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Starting tomorrow... I'm going to give 110...no, 210 per cent!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-whoa! Where'd that come from all of a sudden?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I...just want to help you stay focused, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Luke...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm sure with Espella and me on your side, we can take on anything that comes our way! There's no puzzle out there tough enough to stop the likes of us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha. No puzzle too tough, huh? That sure sounds like the Luke I know.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah ha... I guess it does, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Luke...you've really helped me get back on my feet. I can definitely see why you're the professor's apprentice.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That I am!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's give it our best, Luke. As an ace attorney and an ace apprentice.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, so...what do you say we get some rest, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...I'm all for that! Good night, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good night, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">...The next parade is the most crucial one yet.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Yes, Milord. I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I leave the rest in your hands. Please take care of Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">You have had to endure much thus far... but understand that the end is near.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Hmph... Oh, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Is that a hint of contempt I see in you, Inquisitor Darklaw...? Urk-!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">...I must rest.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...What a foolish man. You...will know soon enough. Soon you will see the advent of a new story. And you will pay for all of your mistakes...</line>
<line speaker="???">Huh? ...The advent of a new story?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I wonder... What could she be planning?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good morning, Luke, Espella. Did you guys sleep all right?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, thank you. I slept very well.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Me too! I'm recharged and ready to get started, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like someone got plenty of rest last night.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's right! A lack of sleep leads to a weary mind, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, guys. Let's decide on where we should investigate first.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, it would probably be safer if we avoid going into the town centre for now...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That's right. Inquisitor Barnham did say there was "nowhere we could hide"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right then, let's just stick to this area and see what information we can find. That Great Witch Bezella has to be a pretty important part of Labyrinthia's history.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are! I mean, she is called the "legendary" Great Witch... I'm confident someone can tell us something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... There's bound to be a clue out there somewhere that can shed some light on this thing.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I think you're right. Detective Accidenti mentioned some things about Labyrinthia in his letter to the professor, too... He wrote that this town is shrouded in secrecy. And where there are secrets, you can bet there are clues.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...We should investigate this area first. There are no knights patrolling around here. I guess they really do avoid this part of town, huh? I'm sure we can get a lot of information from the townsfolk.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Now that you mention it, isn't this near where Espella had that run-in with those two guys?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, it is. It's about halfway from the marketplace.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Then in that case, I think there's a possibility we'll find someone with a connection to what's happened. And that means more information on the witches for us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You got it, Luke. We've got two weeks to gather as much information as possible.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">O-oh nooooo. That's right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's wrong, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I didn't mean to startle anyone. I...just forgot to mention... The next parade...isn't actually in two weeks...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...? I-it's not...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That no-good Storyteller changed the date of the parade by writing in his book! He just changed it right there in front of us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He rewrote the Story? Then... when exactly...is the next parade?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Weeeeeell...it's... it's sort of...actually today, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wha... WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?! D-did you just say..."today"? <thought>N-no way! Man, talk about time slipping away...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">I think they've already started preparing for the festival! It looks like...it might start this evening.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">J-just our luck...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">M-Mr Wright...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Okay, this gives us all the more reason to start investigating right away.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see what kind of clues we can find today while there's still time. I'm sure we can find something on the Great Witch Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Y-yes, you're right!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Okay! Let's do our best to find some clues!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright, look! There's a puzzle over there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow, a puzzle there of all places? You can find these puzzles just about anywhere, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Let's solve it, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">60</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Can be solved in ten moves</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Espella">A sword and a hatchet? Hmm... Not very surprising to find something like that in a place like this, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm no sword expert, but even I can tell the difference between these and something like Barnham's.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I can't imagine why you'd ever need a sword this...aggressive, can you, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">This statue looks an awful lot like Mr Cutter, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like this statue is still a work-in-progress. Makes a great hammock support, though.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I have a sneaking suspicion the sculptor greatly exaggerated whoever this is supposed to be.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Someone must be working on another statue... They must've just started it recently.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I think so too, Luke. I can't even tell what this is supposed to be.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm guessing it's supposed to be a person. Something tells me they won't be finishing any time soon.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Espella. Hold on a second.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">H-huh...? M-me?</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Think you could give me a hand around the place? Things have got a bit busier around here, and I'm a bit short-staffed at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">But I have to...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Miss Rouge, we really have to get going...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually...that might be a good idea. What do you think, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Umm... Well...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You'd definitely be a lot safer here. Just leave the investigation to us.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Okay. If you think that's best. Just...both of you be careful out there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course. We'll be back soon with lots of info!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Is it really okay to just leave Espella here, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think Rouge really needed any help. I think she's actually looking out for Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? She is?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella has just been accused of being Bezella... Who knows what would happen if she set foot outside in the town?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella's already been through so much. I don't think angry villagers and knights with sharp swords are gonna help her. Looks like this investigation is on us, Luke. Let's get out there and find ourselves some clues.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The ace attorney and ace apprentice are on the case!</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">You can let me take care of Espella. It's best you two focus on your investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks a lot, Rouge.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Heh... Well now, someone looks happier than a kid in a candy shop.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-ah ha ha... Well, I have you to thank for that.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hm? What do you mean, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-it's nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...?</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">That reminds me, I have another cunningly crafted puzzle for you to try. Think you've got what it takes to solve it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...well, Luke would be better suited for it. He's the puzzle master here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Puzzle? Did you say puzzle?! Just leave it to me, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There. You see, Rouge?</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">I hate to disappoint you, kiddo. But this puzzle is best left to us grown-ups. Now, go on and show the boy what you've got. Let's get started!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">60</line>
<line speaker="Notes">No penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Nicely done yet again. You know, that's freshly squeezed tomato juice in that chalice. You can drink it, if you want.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tomato juice, huh? Thanks for the offer, but I'm more of a grape juice guy, myself...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But wait, if that's tomato juice, why can only grown-ups try solving this puzzle?</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Them's the rules. There's a tale that says the one who can successfully slide the red glass and solve the puzzle... will fall in love with their soulmate.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Whoa, really? Mr Wright, you and Rouge have become fast friends, haven't you? Do you think you'll both find your soulmates?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...No, Luke. I can say with certainty, I don't think so.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...?</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Espella's fine. Just let me take care of her. You boys have things you need to take care of, don't you? Now go on, get to it.</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">B-Bardly? What are you doing in a place like this? Oh, I know! I bet you perform here, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">Yes, indeed... My tantalisingly tasteful tunes reach even the most dubious parts of Labyrinthia. This tavern is home to a variety of musical palettes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Say, you're not the only bard in town, are you? There's that other guy...Birdly, right?</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">Good sir! The mere mention of that fowl-loving fellow fiddler wounds me greatly! ............ And now, a song.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Rival"...? Sheesh... Never would've thought being a bard would be so hard♪</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bardly">And just overnight, a star did he become. The town was abuzz... He gets all the fun♪</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I see. So you're saying that Birdly stole the stage from you, is that it?</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">Yes! Quite! Can you see how terribly tragic... How tragically terrible his magic?!♪</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So, you think you need a parrot too?</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">If I could get my musical minstrel mitts on TWO parrots...</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There we are, Bardly! You've got lots of parrots to choose from. Now you won't have to perform by yourself any more.</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">...Too...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Too...?</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">Too many parrooooooooots!!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">There are simply too many adorable parrots to choose from. I cannot decide which I want!♪ I want them all to sing with meeeeeeee!♪</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now that IS something I would pay to see.</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">There is but one thing which I do not doubt. A parrotly pair will turn my luck about!♪</line>
<line speaker="Espella">......</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What's wrong, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, no... Nothing's wrong. I was just reminiscing about the old days.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The old days?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes. You know, about the bakery and how we used to bake bread... I think I'd like to bake some sweet, lovely bread for all of the sweet, lovely people here at the tavern... If they let me, of course. I learned everything about baking from Aunt Patty. I used to always watch her making delicious bread and pastries. But out of everything we baked, the sweet banana bread was my specialty.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Aww. It's too bad we didn't get a chance to try any of your baking, Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Am I the only one having a hard time picturing these guys munching on "sweet, lovely" banana bread?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Good luck on the investigation, you two.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Thanks! We'll let you know if we find out anything!</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">Hello there, lads! I take it you slept like rocks last night?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Definitely. Thanks a lot. But I, uhh...have to say the room was definitely..."unique". I mean, especially that statue...</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">Ha ha! So you noticed! Why, that's where I keep all of my artistic works-in-progress! Betcha you lot must've felt mighty safe sleeping under my stone brother's watchful eye, eh?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If by "safe" you mean "kind of creeped out", then yes...never felt "safer".</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey, Mr Cutter, do you happen to be a sculptor?</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">Ho ho! Sharp as a whip, you are, lad! That's right! I'm the best sculptor in all of Labyrinthia! 'Least I think so... Thing is, there's a rumour goin' around that modelling for my sculptures ain't none too good for yer health, if you catch my drift.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I think so... That, uhh...sounds kind of ominous.</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">So not many people wanna be models. That's why I've got no choice but to rely on the ol' noggin here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow! You mean you sculpt from memory? You must be incredibly gifted, Mr Cutter!</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">Hah! Allow me to demonstrate, lad! HAAAAA!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Th-that was amazing! You sculpted that statue in no time! You didn't stop once!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By the way, who is this supposed to be? <thought>I feel like I've seen him somewhere before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cutter">This bloke? He's an old friend o' mine. Well, WAS an old friend o' mine. Gone now.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I-I see...</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">Aye! So, whaddya say? How about a complimentary sculpture from yours truly?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Ahh...I think we'll pass.</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">Next time I'll do a sculpture of you lads! All from memory, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow! Someone managed to get a bullseye!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Call me crazy, but throwing knives across a room full of people is just asking for trouble...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The candles are lit even during the day. I guess it's always dark in here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's hanging on just one chain... won't it fall?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*knock* *knock* ...Sounds like it's all tapped out. People here sure do love their tomato juice...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Too bad it isn't grape juice, huh, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm no sword expert, but even I can tell the difference between these and something like Barnham's.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I can't imagine why you'd ever need a sword this...aggressive, can you, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like this statue is still a work-in-progress. Makes a great hammock support, though.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I have a sneaking suspicion the sculptor greatly exaggerated whoever this is supposed to be.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Someone must be working on another statue... They must've just started it recently.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm guessing it's supposed to be a person. Something tells me they won't be finishing any time soon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What the... Check out that barrel. It looks like something's moving inside.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright, it looks like something might be stuck in there. Do you think we should pull it out?</line>
<line speaker="???">...Rrrrrrr...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="???">Rrrrrrrrrrrrr...</line>
<line speaker="Cooper">RRRAAAAAAAAAAAAWRRR!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Aaaaahhh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">T-tell me a KID didn't just pop out of that barrel!</line>
<line speaker="Cooper">You! Why touch home?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Now, wait a second! We didn't touch your barrel! We only SPOKE about touching it!</line>
<line speaker="Cooper">You touch! I saw! No touchy-touch! You throw rubbish!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We did NOT!</line>
<line speaker="Cooper">People walk! Think barrel for rubbish! Or think barrel for leaning!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well...it IS a barrel, kid. Did you ever stop and think that maybe, just maybe, you should get out of that barrel once in a while?</line>
<line speaker="Cooper">Barrel home! Cooper and barrel same! Plus! All stuffs inside barrel! Very much stuffs! Look! Stuffs!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh, I get it! It's sort of like a storage box!</line>
<line speaker="Cooper">Not box! BARREL! You want box?! Solve puzzle! Many box! Tricky-tricky box! That why Cooper only roll with barrel!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">40</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Cooper">You found tricky-tricky box! Must tell how find!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's simple really. Every puzzle has a solution, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But really...boxes and barrels are both really similar. I mean, they both hold stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Cooper">! No! Box and barrel different! FACT! Like sun and moon! Like potato and tomato! DIFFERENT!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I don't think I fully understand what he means, Mr Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trust me, Luke... The only fact here is that this kid really loves barrels...</line>
<line speaker="Cooper">Boy no understand why barrel great? Next time, join Cooper inside barrel. Cooper barrel full of fun.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">No, thank you. I don't think we'll both fit in there.</line>
<line speaker="Cooper">Too bad. So sad.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hmm... What a strange boy.</line>
<line speaker="Cooper">Never forgive when throw rubbish at Cooper barrel! Fling Cooper apple at head. SPLAT!</line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">Oh my. How ever were you fine gentle sirs able to notice me way up here on the balcony?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A-apologies, miss. We didn't mean to disturb you... Wow, what a fancy dress. I didn't think we would find royalty living on this side of town! Right, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, it's fancy...in the absolute loosest sense of the word...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">Please, oh gentle sir... Do not think ill of me simply because of these makeshift rags I am forced to wear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Me?! No, no! Don't be ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">Now that I look at you, gentle sir...I am ever so certain we are kindred spirits, you and I.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">"Kindred"...?</line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">Oh, indeed, gentle sir. Could it be that you, too, have fled from whence you called home? No doubt you have noticed the state of my attire. It is ever so much in need of good cleaning and repair... But truly, I hail from an ever so noble family... I dare say you did not think yourself to be in the presence of royalty, did you? Hee hee.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Look around you... Do you really want to be saying that "ever so" loudly in a place like this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">Pray...allow me to tell you of how I spent my nights within the nobility. Oh, the nightly balls were ever so lovely.</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">25</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">Just imagine it in your mind right this very moment... Ahh...is it not the ever so loveliest ball you have ever seen? Sadly, there is little desire for such things here, what with this talk of witches... Oh, to have my Prince Charming come and whisk me away from here...</line>
<line speaker="???">Cindy! Outside again, are you?! Get AWAY from that balcony, girl! You're as much a princess as I am queen of Labyrinthia! Now "whisk yourself" back into this house, NOW! I mean it, young lady! Don't make your mum go out there!</line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............ Um...I think your mother is calling for you.</line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">Whatever do you mean, gentle sir? That was but the sweet, gentle chirping of the robins... Oh, make haste, my prince. You must one day come whisk me away!</line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">To be of such noble blood, yet... destined to hide away in a place such as this. My life is a tale ever so tragic.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There's food on one of the crates. Someone was having a meal here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The atmosphere in this alley is so different from the rest of the town. It feels so...seedy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That roof looks like a health hazard. I hope the ceiling isn't going to cave in.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It seems to be all right even with this many people in. It's more durable than it looks.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh, someone was looking at us from that window!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm glad Espella stayed in the tavern. I wouldn't want her to be out here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? Miss Mystere? What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Actually, I was hoping I'd run into you. I have a puzzle I'd like to introduce you to. And speaking of which... How fares the hunt? I hope you're coming across a copious amount of puzzles? I have taken the liberty of gathering all your undiscovered and unsolved puzzles into one place. Now then, which puzzle would you like to tackle today?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">I have taken the liberty of gathering all your undiscovered and unsolved puzzles into one place. Now then, which puzzle would you like to tackle today?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This place is so different during the day. It's absolutely bustling! Vegetable vendors, tailor shops, bazaars... There are lots of different shops all over the place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like this must be the marketplace.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A marketplace...? That sounds like fun.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How about we take a look around while we check for clues?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Umm...but, Mr Wright... We have to make sure we focus on the investigation as well, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow. Luke is super serious...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Huh? Hey, Mr Wright... Look! Isn't that...Mr Knightle and Miss Mary standing over there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh yeah... Now that you mention it, Espella did say that Ms Mary's farm is somewhere around here, didn't she? <thought>I don't see any knights around anywhere... I wonder what Knightle is doing here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mary">Fresh milk! Fresh milk of Labyrinthia! You won't find a baaaaaaaargain like this anywhere else. Oh? We meet again. Are you here to purchase some of my fine milk?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I'm afraid not...sorry. We'll be sure to pick some up next time. Anyway...you didn't happen to see any knights come by here, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Knights? No, not today. Speaking of which... I heard there was a BIG to-do over at the witch trial last night. You...wouldn't have something to do with that, now would you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no, no! Ha ha! We didn't do a thing, did we, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Th-that's right! We didn't do anything, honest!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Well, okay. That's a relief. We wouldn't want Mummy's little milk muffin getting all spooked because of your antics, now would we?</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, ma'am...we'll, uhh...be careful not to spook your little "milk muffin".</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Mary has a little goat whose milk is white as snow and ten times more delicious! Come and get your fresh milk here! Have a look! I've got a specially made bottle just for you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Err... Do I wanna know what makes this... "special"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um...Mr Knightle, is that you?</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you doing around here?</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">...Is it not obvious? I am selling potatoes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I see...</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">I shall never forget that fateful day. That...fateful witch trial... Truth is, the following morning... I...I had my entrance exam to join the order of knights.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I-is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">But...the night of THAT trial... What happened in THAT courtroom... THAT was also the night you made me a complete laughing stock! And not only that! Because you dragged that trial so late into the night, I overslept!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So, you must have ended up being late to your exam, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's totally not my fault.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Umm, well... Good luck on the next exam, Mr Knightle.</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">I have abandoned such a title!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">I live, eat and breathe potatoes now. Potatoes are...my life. The journey of a potato seller is a long and arduous one... You may now address me as...Spudley!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ All right, Spudley. I'll take two potatoes, please.</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">You have my thanks, Sir Blue Knight!</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">What a spectacular failure I am... I heard even an elderly gentleman four times my age managed to pass with flying colours! Perhaps such was the destiny... the noble Storyteller has seen fit for me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The sight of this delicious food is helping me snap out of my depression.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Looky here! Juicy-looking fruits! How about we buy some? Maybe Espella can bake bread with them!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">In other parts of Labyrinthia, flags flutter in the wind. Here it's people's laundry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">People who live here seem more laid back than those in the shopping district.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These shops deal in some suspicious stuff that you can't get in the shopping district.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Some of this stuff looks like rubbish. Where did it come from?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess not. I'd really like to stick around and see what other information we can find around here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But the only other people around here look a little...shady, if you ask me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All the more reason we should ask. I'm sure they've heard all sorts of rumblings out here. Espella must be a nervous wreck waiting for us to get back with some information. We can't go back empty-handed, right?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You're right! Well then! Let's get back on the case! How about we try looking over there, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">W-was that an explosion...? Wh-what could've exploded like that?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urgh... Luke, are you all right?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Y-yeah, I'm fine. How about you, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...I-I think I'm okay...considering.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Whew! That's a relief!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What could've caused that explosion? And of all places... Why the middle of the marketplace?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright, do you think... Could a witch have done this? We know they can summon fire and turn people into gold... There's no doubt about it! This has to be the work of magic!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I agree. At least, it sure seems likely.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We should investigate the area of the blast. Let's go, Mr Wright! I'm sure we'll find something that'll give us a lead regarding the witches.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. And if we come across anyone injured, let's give them a hand, all right?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">In that case, how about we split up? ...I'll go and check that side over there!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Oh dear! Why do all the strangest things always happen on THIS side of town?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">..."Always happen"? Ms Mary, did something else happen here?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Isn't it obvious? This area was perfectly peaceful before you started trying to defend every witch out there! You do remember the incident with Robbs and Muggs, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh yeah.... That happened right around here, didn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Yes. Right on the footpath that leads to the courthouse through the forest. ............ You know...I've just remembered something rather strange.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Just before the blast, I saw a bright spark on the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A bright spark?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Truth be told, I noticed the same thing back when those flames erupted, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you saw...a spark of light on the ground?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Yes, yes! I definitely saw it. I definitely saw a spark on the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-and you say this was before the explosion? Could it have something to do with magic?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">I'm afraid I couldn't say. Snowy and I will be staying far, far, FAR away from this mess! We're not getting dragged into any trials! N-now I have to get back to the farm! I have to go and protect my precious little lovelies!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh boy... I see the crazy goat lady is still as crazy as ever...</line>
<line speaker="Mary">I'd think about getting out of here if I were you! Snowy and I aren't getting wrapped up in any more of that courtroom drama!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Hmm, I see. There's nothing left anywhere around the area of the blast. Huh? Is something wrong, Mr Wright? Don't worry about this side. The ace apprentice has it all under control!</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Why?! Why?! Whhhhhhhhhhyyyyyyy?! Why must the fates conspire against me?! ...I failed to become a knight! ...And now, just look at my potatoes! They're all baked! Every last one of them! Who would ever buy a baked potato?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-whoa, whoa whoa! Calm down, Knigh- err, Spudley!</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Knightle is dead... Spudley is no more... Oh, cruel fate! Oh, Storyteller! Please... Tell me what... WHAT-OH-WHAT should I do now?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey now, c'mon, Spudley. Your potatoes are just a little baked. They're still good!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Here's an idea! Why don't you just give yourself a temporary name until you decide what you should do!</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Why, that's it! After all, WHAT is a man? ...Ah ha! Henceforth, I shall be known as the ever-pondering...Sir Whatley!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Identity crisis averted. Let's get going, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Okay!</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Behold! Whatley is born! I shall make it my life's mission to find out...my life's mission!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this? It kinda looks like a bell? <thought>I can't describe it, but something's weird about this bell...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-hey, you... Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Who's that?! Wait...just a moment!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Luke! Are you okay? I-it's you!</line>
<line speaker="???">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wait a second. Haven't we seen her somewhere before...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no way! I-I don't get it. There's no way you should be alive...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...What? Oh! I remember where we saw her! It was at the other trial! You're... Weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Kira!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You're right. It IS Miss Kira...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah. She was supposed to have been dropped into the flames. We saw it with our own eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ I...I must go.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a minute, Ms Kira! I just wanna ask you a few questions!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I must go...quickly. If I fail my task...I cannot return.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">T-task...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell us, Ms Kira! How is it...that you're still alive?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...I must go.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wh-whoa! Did you see that? She...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She just...vanished.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Was that...the spell "Dimere"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think so... Remember, to cast magic, you need to be carrying a Talea Magica... And we didn't hear her say any sort of incantation, so... <thought>But I did see her ring that small bell...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">That bell...what do you think it's for?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um...Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ms Kira should've died when she was dropped into the fire, but she looked alive to me just now. If that's the case, then maybe... ...Maya! ............ Hey, Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Y-yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's head back to Rouge's place! I just thought of one more place we need to search!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Eh? But why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no time to explain. We have to get back. Espella will want to hear this, too.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Okay, got it!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Ooooooh. There, there... Shhh... Shhh... It's okay, it's all over now.</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...Ms Mary?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">What is it? Can't you see I'm a little busy right now? My precious Snowy is so stressed. Isn't that right, snowflake of my eye?</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hmm, Snowy says what's stressing him out most right now is the headlock you've got him in...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Talking to animals... That has to be a first for any assistant I've ever had...</thought> Ms Mary, you didn't happen to see a girl run by here by any chance, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">I don't think so. I don't think I've seen a single person come by, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? You didn't see her at all? She was wearing a black robe! And what's more, that girl was actually Miss Kira!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Hmm?! Did you say Kira? What are you blabbing about? Kira was sent to the flames, don't you remember?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But it really was Kira! We saw her!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">S-stop pulling my leg! Snowy and I want nothing to do with this! We won't hear another word about all these "witches" and "magic"! We saw nothing, you hear me? Nothing! Now just leave me and Snowy in peace!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">That explosion's really put a damper on things around here, hasn't it? But I'm thankful my little snowball made it out safe and sound.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh...Mr Wright, Luke! I heard a loud bang coming from the town... Did something happen there?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There was a HUGE explosion! Thankfully no one was hurt...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">An explosion?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We don't know for certain...but I suspect magic was involved.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">M-magic, you say...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh yeah! Th-that reminds me! You're not going to believe who we just ran into! ...Miss Kira!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">K-Kira...? B-but that can't be right! I mean, she...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a minute, guys. Can I just say something?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I still can't believe it myself, but...Luke and I definitely saw Kira in town today.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Th-that...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um...couldn't she have...been brought back with magic somehow?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I don't think so. Remember, Inquisitor Barnham said that no such magic exists.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh yeah...that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Regardless, the reality is Kira should have been burned after the trial but is somehow now alive again... That means, as crazy as it sounds... there's still hope!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...! Y-you mean... There's a chance Maya is still alive!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Maya is still alive... A-are you absolutely certain, Mr Wright?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think so. I mean, if magic isn't the reason for Kira's sudden reappearance... then there's only one place we really need to investigate.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I think I know! The fire cage back at the courtroom, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Exactly. I have a hunch there's more to that cage than meets the eye. I bet if we search that place inside and out, we're bound to uncover some kind of huge secret!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">We should hurry then!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. There's just...one small problem. We've got the entire knighthood looking for us... How can we sneak back in there without getting caught?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah ha...! I've got it! Don't worry, Mr Wright! Just leave it to me! Eve told me about a hidden entrance behind the courtroom. It's the same secret entrance I used to help Espella escape from the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Huh...? E-Eve told you?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Uh... Ha ha... A-anyway... We should get going, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">What's with all the commotion? Did I hear someone say there was an explosion in town?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's right, Miss Rouge. No one was hurt, but a few stalls were destroyed...</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Huh. Is that so...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Um...Ms Rouge? What do you think will happen to the street stall owners now that their stalls are gone? They probably won't be able to open their stalls for a while...</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">I say we oughta look on the bright side. At least no one was hurt, right? With the townsfolk and my little group of good-fer-nothings here helping out, everything will be rebuilt in no time. A little hard work wouldn't hurt the lazy bums, trust me. Don't you worry about the townsfolk. Just leave them to me. You have your own things to be thinking about. Well? Are you headed out, or what?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Y-yes, if that's all right. I'm terribly sorry for leaving in the middle of helping you, Ms Rouge...</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">It's fine. Don't you worry your pretty little head over it, Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Thank you so much, Miss Rouge... for everything.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">...All right, all right. Don't get all mushy on me. Just get out there and get it done.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Leave the townsfolk to me. Go on, get going.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh, someone was looking at us from that window!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was an explosion! What's going on?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">What was Kira doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Quick, we need to investigate this incident!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thankfully, no one was hurt in the explosion.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">If you want to go to the courthouse, better hurry up before the knights come!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Was that explosion...caused by Miss Kira with magic?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">The explosion has prompted shopkeepers to close their shops early today and go home.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Everyone's nervously looking around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It'll be a while before it's business as usual here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright, I understand you want some time to enjoy the scenery, but we really need to go!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Let's hurry, before the knights take notice of the commotion and find us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Witches' Court lies further ahead. I hope we don't run into anyone on the way there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it looks like the knights haven't tried searching for us out here, huh? So where do we go now?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We take the hidden passage into the courtroom, of course! Espella, you remember it, right?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">You mean...the passage we used to escape yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's right!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Luke, how is it you know about this secret passage, anyway? I had no idea such a thing could exist here in the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, it was hidden within a puzzle. Answering it correctly unlocks the door. But I closed the door, just to be on the safe side. All I have to do is solve the puzzle again to open the way!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. It's in your capable hands then, Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right! The entrance is right over there!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There! It's open! Now we can head inside!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A job well done, ace apprentice! Now, let's hurry in!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmph... It's really cramped in here...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We're almost there, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you all right, Espella? Not long now!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Uh-huh...yes, I'm fine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Man, I hate these dark, narrow spaces. I guess I'm a little bit claustrophobic...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Oh! I can see light!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Woah!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Waaah!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Ahhh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ouch...that smarts. ...A secret entrance in the ceiling, huh... What are the odds?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It doesn't look like we can go out the way we came in, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Let's not focus on how we'll go back for the time being.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, you're right. But where did we end up, exactly? ...It looks like one of the cells underneath the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">H-huh? Uh-oh! I'm so sorry... I must have taken a wrong turn somewhere. But we should get to the courtroom if we continue straight from here...</line>
<line speaker="???">Wh-what are you...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Ms Greyerl?!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Miss Greyerl... You're okay!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">M-Miss Cantabella! Are you unharmed?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank goodness... We were all so worried about you. So it looks like...they didn't feed you to the flames after all.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...It's all due to your brilliant defence work.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">To argue that, even if I was a witch, I still did not commit the crime... Your words...seemed to have a profound effect on the judge and somehow changed his mind. I'm...currently awaiting my new sentence instead of being sent to the flames. I am truly, truly...thankful to you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-it was nothing... I'm just glad I was able to help you.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">And yet... I must also apologise to you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">For what happened to Miss Fey... It was truly tragic... and I was the cause of it all... Simply thinking back on it is difficult.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Miss Greyerl! There's something you really should know!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">What...? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Earlier today, in town... we saw someone who we thought had been sent to the flames! We saw Miss Kira!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Wh-what did you just say?! B-but...if I remember correctly, there is no magic that can bring the dead back to life!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yup. That's right. And I imagine... There isn't anything in alchemy that can do that either, is there?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ Master Belduke always used to say: "Alchemy is logical. Its very existence is tied to the natural order of the world." To break that rule is to try and swim against the tide of Mother Nature herself. ...Therefore, the dead cannot be returned to the world of the living. That is the natural order of the world.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I-I...see.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">There's...one more thing. Bringing the dead back to life violates all logic... Yet, if what you say is true and you did in fact see Miss Kira today... then I imagine you believe there has to be some manner of trickery present that can supposedly "bring back" the dead.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That means the reason you have all put yourselves in great danger coming here... is so you can find out the true nature of this "trickery", specifically the fire cage.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Th-that's incredible, Miss Greyerl! That's exactly why we're here! We're going to inspect that fire cage inside and out to see if there's anything strange about it!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">The Chamber of Fire is located just past the waiting area... however, there may be guards stationed there at the moment. Getting past them undetected is going to be rather difficult.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Th-that would be my fault! I accidentally led us down the wrong path...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Taking that wrong path is how we ended up meeting Ms Greyerl, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">He's right, Luke. We were able to meet her thanks to you!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I agree. I'm glad we all managed to meet again.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">R-really? Ah, ha ha...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, anyway... We've got to think about how we can get past those guards.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ If it pleases you, I ask that you leave those guards to me, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I'll draw their attention. Then, while they're distracted, you sneak past them into the Chamber of Fire.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-but, Ms Greyerl...we wouldn't want to get you into any more trouble...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Not at all. Nothing I can do will ever repay you for what you've done for me. ...Please allow me the honour of assisting you this once.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ All right. We won't forget this, Ms Greyerl!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">AHHHHHHHHH! Guards! Guards! Please! It's most urgent!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Wh-what? What's going on in there?!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">It's coming from the Deathknell Dungeon! Hurry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like she did it! They're gone.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It would seem all of the guards bolted off in the direction of the cells when they heard her voice.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Let's head inside before they come back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. C'mon, let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright, let's go inside!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We've got to hurry! Or the guards will come back and catch us!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So, here we are again...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry, Luke. It's different this time. Last time there was nothing but despair... but this time there's a glimmer of hope.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Let's try and find some clues now that there isn't anyone inside this contraption.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Espella's right! Let's finally get to the bottom of this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, let's get started. How about we start by checking out the area around the contraption?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not really much of a railing here... One good trip and it's a one-way trip down... *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Maybe there's something hidden at the bottom?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow... Even without the fire, this pit still looks quite terrifying, doesn't it, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">The cage has been hoisted up into the air. I still remember how terrifying it was to be trapped in there...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hmm... I wonder if there's some sort of trick we don't know about inside that cage?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not too sure, Luke. It's hard to tell looking at it from down here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright, look! It's dark, but you can just make out where the audience sits during the trials.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Just yesterday this was bursting with people...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's really eerie when it's all dark and quiet like this. ...We should hurry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I remember seeing a knight pull this lever here last time.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Maybe we should give it a pull. That way we'll be able to see from here if anything changes or moves.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Good idea, Espella! Let's give it a shot!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">H-hnnnnnnnggggggh! I-it won't budge!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Luke, do you need me to give it a shot?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hhhnnnnnngggggh... It's not that...hnnngh! It just keeps... getting stuck...hnnngh! Halfway... Hhhnnnnnngggggh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It stops...halfway?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">U-um, perhaps... Maybe it doesn't move unless someone is inside the cage...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... That's a possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But...who in their right mind would be crazy enough to go inside?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'll go inside, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella, no way am I letting you get inside that thing. We've been trying to keep you OUT of the fire, remember? I'll do it. Granted, I'm not a big fan of heights, but... there has to be some sort of trick to this whole thing... I don't think there's anything to worry about.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm? What's up, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I-I'll get inside! Please, let me go inside and try it out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">L-Luke...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">it's just like Mr Wright said. There's a hidden trick behind this device. I think so too, and I believe in Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, but...you really shouldn't be putting yourself in harm's way!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's no problem for ace apprentice and gentleman in training Luke Triton! There's more to this fire pit than meets the eye, and it's up to us to get to the bottom of it! The parade is going to start before we know it! Let's hurry, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Okay, fine. But promise me you'll get out of there at the first sign of danger, all right?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I promise!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, Luke, are you ready?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ready whenever you are!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Luke, be careful...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Don't worry, Espella! Remember what Miss Greyerl said earlier. It's impossible to bring people back from the dead. So that means this whole thing must be fake!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes. Yes, you're right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, here we go... ............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Whenever you're ready, Mr Wright! Don't hesitate, just pull it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no... It's not that. It's this lever... It looks like it's actually a puzzle, if you can believe that...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wh-what?!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh no! Luuuuuuuuuke!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Luke! Are you all right?!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Th-there's no fire, but... falling like that was a bit scary!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey, guuuuuuys! Can you hear me...?!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright! Did you hear that? It's Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We hear you loud and clear, Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm all right! Why not try jumping down here yourselves?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, thank goodness...you're okay! Should we go see what's down there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just like we thought... There's definitely something fishy behind this contraption. Which means Maya must be...</thought> All right, let's go, Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Okay!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Wh-whoa!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Aaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Aaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urgh!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ow, ow ow...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm so sorry! Are you okay, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...I'm fine, Espella. I'm pretty used to breaking people's falls. ...I wonder where we ended up?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Uh-oh! Mr Wright, look! I think someone's coming!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is bad... There's nowhere we can hide!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Hey, there's a wagon. Maybe we can hide inside...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?! Well, I guess, but...it looks like kind of a tight fit for all three of us, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hmm... The wagon's cargo is all over the place...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh no! They're getting closer!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">No problem! The professor's apprentice is on the job!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">50</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Quitting the puzzle immediately leads back into the puzzle</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Wagon Driver">...... ...Oh, what's this? I don't remember there being this much cargo. Hee hee... Oh well. These old eyes must be playing tricks on me again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whew... Looks like we're in the clear.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey, I've seen that old lady before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, really? When?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">When I first arrived in Labyrinthia. The professor and I woke up right here in this wagon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you mean...this driver is...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yeah. She's the same old lady that was driving the wagon last time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In that case, do you think this wagon might be able to take us outside of the town?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Maybe the witches that were burned alive were transported somewhere in this wagon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Hmm, you could be right.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Then Maya could be...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm afraid I have to intervene. You see... protecting a young lady in distress, is the duty of every gentleman.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huuh...Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Are you all right, Miss Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">P-Professor! What are you doing here...?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We shall speak later. It's best we make our way out of here. Now then, which one of you is first?</line>
<line speaker="???">......</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? They're not doing anything... You think maybe your impressive swor- err, stick work scared them stiff?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Either way, now is our chance. Come, let's head into the forest. We should be able to lose them there.</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">45</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Quitting the puzzle immediately leads back into the puzzle</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... That's a relief. I don't see anyone following us.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Not quite, Miss Fey. I'm afraid we cannot be so sure just yet. It will be safer if we continue on ahead. Now then, follow my lead.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-you got it, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Much of this area looks the same. It would be easy to get lost, so stay close, Miss Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Wait... I recognise that tree. Weren't we just here? Or was it that tree? ...Stupid identical trees!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There are an awful lot of twisted trees in this forest. ...I don't trust 'em, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">They certainly are bunched together, aren't they, Miss Fey? It seems they can block out most of the sun, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Fun fact: Professor, did you know not all mushrooms are edible? Mystic Maya's Fun Fact of the Day!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ha, ha. Right you are, Miss Fey. The colour of these mushrooms does not seem...safe.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ We should be safe here. Miss Fey, are you hurt?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nope! I'm right as rain! Um...thank you for saving me back there. You look like you're all back to normal, Professor! Not as shiny and way more talkative.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...What do you mean by "back to normal"?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You were turned into gold, Professor. Someone cast a magic spell on you!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A-a magic spell...on me, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let me refresh your memory. You remember the witch that appeared when we were in Mr Belduke's house, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. So you're saying that was when... a magic spell was cast on me?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's right! You were SUPER golden and SUPER shiny!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">"Super" shiny and golden... Most fascinating.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you...not remember any of that?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Sadly, I do not... ...To tell you the truth, I have no recollection of what happened to me then. It seems I lost consciousness immediately after the witch appeared... and when I regained consciousness, I was already in this forest.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh... So, then...do you think maybe they carried you here after the trial?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...A-after the trial? Then that must mean...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup. You were the unfortunate victim of witchcraft in that trial, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">H-how extraordinary... Miss Fey, could you please bring me up to date on everything that happened after my disappearance? What about Luke and Mr Wright? Are they okay? I recall Luke and I heading to Sir Belduke's house. We thought you and Mr Wright were in danger.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-yeah... I think they're all right. So much has happened... Where do I even start?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Did I hear you correctly? You say that one of my arms broke off?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup! The right arm! Snap-o!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And so, Miss Fey, you were charged with using magic...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup! That's right! And then, Luke cried his little eyes out! And THEN, the parrot on Luke's head testified its little beak off!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That must have been quite the sight. ...But I must say, this situation has certainly piqued my interest. Hmm, I see... My apologies, Miss Fey. Had I had the strength at the time, I could have been of more help.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No way, Professor! You saved me just a moment ago!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And quite the close call it was. By the way, Miss Fey, why are you in this forest?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That...is a very good question. Nick managed to prove my innocence, but... I still ended up being thrown into the fire.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You were found innocent, yet still sent to the fire?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, anyways! So much weird stuff has happened since then!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...It would seem so, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...But it's strange. There must have been more to that cage I was trapped in. Like, a trick or something...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A trick...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. The cage dropped down through the chamber and then came to a stop just above a wagon... That wagon was how I ended up here.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would seem there is more that fire chamber than I originally thought...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then when I saw those...things, I tried to get away. But as you saw back there, they found me. I thought I was a goner...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And that is when I appeared, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup! That's right! ............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Is something the matter, Miss Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's Nick... He must be worried sick. I mean, I was thrown into the fire right before his eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Yes. I'm also concerned about Luke. However, I believe Luke and Mr Wright... are certain to sense something is amiss and solve this mystery. We're sure to all meet up again soon.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-yeah! You're right, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">For the time being, let's investigate this place as much as possible.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Investigate...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. This forest appears to be full of secrets... First, I was turned into gold and awoke to find myself here... And then you, Miss Fey, were transported here from the courtroom, under the illusion of having been put to the fire. Perhaps this forest...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">......Uh-oh! How'd they manage to find us so fast?! What should we do, Professor?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... It appears they were lying in ambush. I'm afraid an altercation here is unavoidable.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Th-these guys look like they've been hitting the gym. They're a lot bigger than the others...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. Leave this to me. Now...please step back, Miss Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Knock 'em into next week, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="???">...Now, just what is all the commotion? You were given a task to carry out, were you not...? So what exactly do you think you're doing? Answer me.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Forgive us... Oh Great Witch...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-WHAAAAAAT?! Th-that's the witch from last time! What's she doing here?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...!</line>
<line speaker="???">...Now, isn't this a strange sight? Two visitors from the witch trials... A victim and an accused? Strange, indeed...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">C-come again...? It was YOUR fault we were a part of those trials in the first place, you...you witch!</line>
<line speaker="???">My, this one has some fight in her. Relax. I do not plan to harm you two.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...... This marks the third time we have now met. Tell me...what exactly are you planning?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?! Professor... You two have met three times?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes. I first met her in London. Prior to arriving in Labyrinthia, of course.</line>
<line speaker="???">Heh heh... That's right. Now, enough. Stand down. These two are considered guests. You are not to lay a finger on them, is that clear? Make sure the rest of the Shades get that message.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Shades? Are they those creepy people in the weird robes?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Yes, mistress. As you command, oh Great Witch...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">"Great Witch"...?</line>
<line speaker="The Great Witch">There is no need to be alarmed. You may relax.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm afraid I cannot oblige. Not as long as you are here. Tell me. What are you?</line>
<line speaker="The Great Witch">...You know, from what I hear, you're a big fan of solving puzzles and mysteries, are you not?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...!</line>
<line speaker="The Great Witch">Then, by all means, go ahead. You are free to investigate the Eldwitch Woods to your heart's content.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The Eldwitch Woods...</line>
<line speaker="The Great Witch">The answers to your questions are here. ...You're free to seek them.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Then you do not plan on having us captured?</line>
<line speaker="The Great Witch">You'll have to excuse the Shades' earlier behaviour. They can be a bit...overzealous at times. They were simply doing what was requested of them. Their "task", as they call it. Anyone lost in these woods is to be made a member of the Shade "family", as it were.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A-a member of the Shades? What does that mean?</line>
<line speaker="The Great Witch">Like I said, you should seek out the answers for yourselves. ...Now, if you'll excuse me. I have another engagement with a visitor of mine.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...A visitor?</line>
<line speaker="The Great Witch">Until next time...Professor Hershel Layton.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sh-she disappeared...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">......</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um... So, Professor... The "Great Witch" they mentioned... They must be referring to her, right? She has to be Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The Great Witch Bezella... If that woman were here... then that would make Eldwitch Woods the home of all witches.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm...this just keeps getting curiouser and curiouser! So then that means the "Shades", or whatever, are...witches?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That is what we must find out. I believe there may be a very important clue or two hidden within this forest. There must be some reason why this forest has been kept a secret from the citizens of Labyrinthia. I also must wonder why this "Great Witch" is simply allowing us to do as we wish... It is slightly concerning.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, there's no point looking a gift horse in the mouth! I say we take her offer and check this place out! That way we'll rack up a TON of clues by the time we reunite with Nick. And since we'll be working together, I'll act as your temporary Luke! "Right you are, Professor!"</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ha ha... Well done. Thank you very much, Miss Fey. Now then, let us begin our investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yessir! Let's go, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Shade">......</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, excuse me. We wanted to ask you a question real quick... What exactly do you do in this forest?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">We live to serve the mistress and carry out her orders...our tasks... The mistress speaks...we obey...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Tasks"? Is that, like, your job?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Yes... My task...is to assist all newly initiated Shades...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Assist...newly initiated Shades?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That must have something to do with what the Great Witch said earlier: Anyone lost in these woods is to be made a member of the Shade "family"...</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Although...my task is made much more difficult when they run away... Why do they always run away...? But we will not chase after you again. It is the mistress' orders...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I see. So you do everything the Great Witch commands?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, I bet you guys are always fighting over the good "tasks", huh? Who'd want to get stuck doing the Great Witch's laundry? Seriously, though... You guys were really close to turning me into a Shade earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm SERIOUSLY glad the professor came along when he did!</line>
<line speaker="Shade">My task...is to assist all newly initiated Shades... I must continue with my task...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y'know, Professor, I was thinking. You said you woke up in the forest, right? The Shades were on me the minute I set foot here... but they never went after you. Why is that?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That is true... I seem to recall waking up inside a cell, of sorts.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">D-did you just say a cell?! How did you manage to escape?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Fortunately, it was not a cell of the metallic variety, Miss Fey. Take a look over there... Do you see that entrance covered in vines?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oooh I get it... So you must have hack 'n' slashed your way to freedom.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, I wouldn't say I "hacked" or "slashed" anything, as such. All it took was a single cut to unravel my way to freedom. Allow me to demonstrate.</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">25</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoooooa! You sure showed that vine who's boss, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A single, precise cut is far more efficient than swinging around haphazardly. After I freed myself, I began to investigate the forest. Not long after that, I heard someone cry out.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah...yeah. You mean me?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Right you are, Miss Fey. I'm glad you were okay.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh-huh. And "okay" I was, good sir. So I guess you're still in the middle of that forest investigation, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would seem so. Shall we press on then?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! It's on now! I'm gonna cut these puzzles down to size with the power of my mind!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, now that you cut the vines off here... This doesn't look like much of a "cell". More like a storage closet or something...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...there do seem to be a variety of vases and ornaments littered inside. I wonder what they're all used for...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Check out the one that looks like a cat! I bet Espella and Luke would LOVE this! Let's take it back for them. It'll be like their own little piece of the Eldwitch Woods, since they weren't able to come.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... I have a sneaking suspicion the Shades would likely chase after us if we did...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Check out the branches on that tree. It kinda reminds me of a stadium dome! ...Minus the stadium.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. And it would appear this arrangement of branches is natural. Simply remarkable.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">In reality, this tree is really two trees grown together. Its twisted structure is simply fascinating.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's the trunk... No, no wait! That's a branch...? Hmm...a root?! This tree's a jerk, let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Could these pots have been used in some sort of ceremony? There's no mistake, these are certainly very old.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I bet you're just dying to check out these relics, huh, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you think...this is where the Shades live? It looks kinda like a village.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would appear so. They seem to lead a very simple lifestyle.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But they look so magical and fantastical. I figured they'd live somewhere way more... well, magical and fantastical.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ Now that you mention it, they don't appear capable of using magic, do they?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess if they did they'd only end up back at the witch trials.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Remember...that may be the law within Labyrinthia... but the Great Witch rules this forest. It is doubtful that such a law would exist here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...that's true. You think we should tell them to just let loose? I bet they have some really flashy spells.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Let us focus our efforts on looking around this village first. There appears to be a path leading out on the other side, too...</line>
<line speaker="Shade">All I can do is carry out my tasks the best I can...in hope that one day I may be allowed to return to the town.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Return? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">I am not too sure myself... It is something I was told when I arrived. The Great Witch keeps a record of all the tasks we successfully complete. Then...when our accomplishments outnumber our failures... She will consider returning us to the town. That is what I believe, and that is why I continue to toil away at my tasks.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Hm? So, does this mean these guys aren't witches?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">From the sound of his voice, it would seem this particular Shade is male. However, according to what you told me earlier...all witches here are female.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmmm... So then, who exactly are these Shades? Say, um...who are you?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...My, how very direct.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">A Shade is a Shade. Nothing more, nothing less.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Yeah, that wasn't really helpful.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps you can tell us what your particular task is?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">............ That I cannot tell you. Most Shades' tasks are closely guarded secrets.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">All I can do is carry out my tasks in hope that I may one day return to town. The details of our tasks...are strictly secret.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">So, how's the task going? Working hard?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Oh...t-task? Well, duh! Of course we are! Speaking of which, what's your task?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">My task is to prepare food for everyone. I'm actually trying to come up with the menu for today... I wouldn't exactly call my cooking "appetising" or "edible", but I must do what our mistress commands...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm...remind us NOT to stop by for dinner.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">...Did you say something?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Me? Nope! Not a thing! Hey, good luck! Try not to blow up the kitchen!</line>
<line speaker="Shade">What should I put on today's menu...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It looks like he's still struggling with what to put on the menu.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Compared to the houses found in Labyrinthia, the Shades' dwellings appear much more primitive.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Primitive? It doesn't look like they have indoor plumbing, Professor. That's WORSE than primitive!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Professor, I'm happy to report that the Shades have mastered well-making technology!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. This well reminds me of the features of Labyrinthia. Perhaps they share the same source.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">They've built a house up on a tree. How inventive. They must use a series of ladders to reach the top.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I knew you were smart, Professor! You do NOT want to hear Nick's thoughts on ladders, trust me.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This small path looks as if it leads away from the Shades' village.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup. It's a path. For walking.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Fascinating. I would like nothing more than to examine that shrine, but I'm afraid we must hurry on.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wonder who built that thing? Y'think it was the Shades' great-great-great-great-GREAT-grandparents?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder if Wordsmith is still in the market for a new napping spot...? This tree is totally napping material!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Under better circumstances, this tree would be most ideal for enjoying a nice cup of tea under its shade.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">I'm terrible at my task. The. Worst. I'm even more terrible at following orders... One small misstep and it'll be my fault we have a serious situation on our hands. I feel sick just thinking about it...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A "serious situation"...? What kind of task do you have, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">I can't say... The only thing I can say is that I'm terrible at it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm...why are you so nervous, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">It's because she's watching...always watching... She sits up there in her mansion and just keeps on watching...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mansion? You mean, the Great Witch lives nearby?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">On the other side of the river... It's quite far, but she can see our every move.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">So it's across the river, then?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Professor...we're sure to run into her again there. It's where she lives, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The best course of action may be to try and make our way there. There are still many questions to be answered.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! Then we'll finally see if she's the real deal or not, right, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's right, Miss Fey. Let us make our way across the river.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">I'm terrible at my task. The. Worst. I'm even more terrible at following orders... But you know who's REALLY the worst? The Great Witch, for making me go through so much stress, that's who...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whooooooa. Check out the beautiful scenery, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This is quite an open space, isn't it? Looking across the river...the Great Witch's mansion is slightly visible.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, you can just about make out the roof from here. Hey, do you think the wall behind it... could be Labyrinthia's outer wall?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That is quite possible. Which would mean...these Eldwitch Woods must be located directly outside Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? But isn't that kinda strange? The people in Labyrinthia said that nothing exists outside of the town, didn't they?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Yes, quite. I, too, have heard the townsfolk make such assertions. In fact, the very gate we used to enter Labyrinthia disappeared as soon as we passed it. ...I believe there must be some kind of a trick behind it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It looks like we've quite a lot to discuss with Little Miss Great Witch, don't we?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That we do. Let us continue, Miss Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Unfortunately, we cannot cross the bridge in its current state. Let us see what we can come up with.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I know, Professor! How about we try talking to that Shade over there?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Say, I think we're entitled to a few flowers, don't you think? We ARE the Great Witch's guests, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">These flowers certainly have a most unique scent. ...Miss Fey, please refrain from picking the flowers.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-is that a mansion over there on the other side? Do you think that's the Great Witch's evil secret lair?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm, could that be...? Let us find a way across and examine that side ourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That must be Labyrinthia... It would seem this forest is just outside of the town.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick and the others must still be inside there somewhere, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh no! The bridge is out!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm, it's been completely destroyed... All that remains are a few bits of debris and a small boat floating across the shore.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Are you two looking for a way to cross the river?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, that's right. Is there no other way across?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">If there's a way across, I sure wish I knew what it was. I'm sort of having a mini crisis here. Why did I have to get stuck with the task of reporting the daily task progress to the Great Witch? Granted, I get to bask in the presence of the mistress and take in her gorgeous visage... Which is actually pretty amazing. But being unable to cross the river, I can't even carry out my task now...let alone adore her unparalleled beauty.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh well. You know what they say: you either sink or swim... Hope you brought your bathing suits. We're swimming across!</line>
<line speaker="Shade">I...can't swim.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Hmm. We'll have to find another way.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Wait a sec. Professor, can you not swim? It's okay. I bet you could flip your hat over and ride it like a boat. It looks like it could float on water reeeeeeaaaal good!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Swimming has nothing to do with it... And I do not think using my hat as a boat would be the best idea, Miss Fey. I'll go across and fetch that small boat. I should be able to jump across rather easily using the bits of debris on the water. I'll then be able to use the boat to create a path all the way across. Rest assured, Miss Fey...this is my speciality.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, that's not a bad idea! You don't miss a beat, do you, Professor? Good luck!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">40</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Yes! Now I can give my mistress today's report! Thank you so much. I don't know how to repay you.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It was no trouble. A broken bridge would be inconvenient to everyone, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">By the way, what kind of tasks did the Great Witch give you two? I'm itching to know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? What's our task...? Umm... Let's see... Oh! That's it! We're puzzle solvers! Yup, that's right!</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Puzzle solvers... Ah, of course. That makes sense. Well, you have both performed your task magnificently. Please excuse me, I must report to the mistress. Now I can go back to truly enjoying my task! Farewell!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa, he's really booking it. Man, we did something really good, huh, Professor?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That we did, Miss Fey. Now, let us press on with our task.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Oh, mistress! Mistress!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Has something happened to the Great Witch?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">I went up to her room but...there was no answer. Oh, mistress... Most venerable Great Witch!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe she's just not in the mood to talk... Everyone has their days.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">No, never. She would never do that. The mistress always answers us.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow. I've gotta say I'm surprised. It sounds like she's really faithful to you guys. ...Um. Maybe she just stepped out?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">If she stepped out, we would know! Oh, what could have happened to you, mistress...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That reminds me. She mentioned there was a visitor waiting for her, or words to that effect.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then that "visitor" must still be waiting around for her, right?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">No, no. They are both inside the room.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...A-ha! I've got it! Zvarri! The supposed "visitor" is really some shady ex-knight looking for revenge!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Miss Fey, please refrain from putting any terrible scenarios into his head. Regardless, we must continue inside. It seems something rather serious is afoot.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Oh, venerable mistress... Should some harm have befallen you, I-I don't know what I shall do!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The horses have plenty of food and water... I must say, they seem quite content.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Horses! Okay, okay... What do I have to do to get Nick on one of these? Money is no object!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The fog is very dense here. It gives this area a most unearthly feel...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's really hard to see around here... Who needs a security system when you've got fog, right, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">These are sure [sic] some pretty flowers. And they're everywhere! Quick! Put some under your hat, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Now, Miss Fey... It is not a gentleman's place to take what does not belong to him.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Mistress! Mistress! Please answer! Something...anything! If something were to happen to you, I... WAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-whoa... Everyone's really freaking out. Hey, maybe I should pretend to Bezella. I can be all, like: "SILENCE, MINIONS!"</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed... I wonder what could have happened here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe she turned her visitor into a gold statue... Hopefully this one doesn't lose an arm.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">My task...is quite an important one...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's a ridiculously huge pot. I wonder what they're cooking in there...</line>
<line speaker="Shade">...! You! Stop! Do NOT interfere with my task!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">AHH! I-I'm sorry, I won't...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There appear to be two pots, each with a different substance being cooked.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa... Check that out, Professor! The colour changed. ...How'd they do that?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">While I agree the change in colour is rather peculiar...I'm more interested in its smell. I have a strange feeling I've smelled this very same odour somewhere before.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, now that you mention it...it does seem kinda familiar, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Quickly, quickly...very quickly... Mix, mix...must mix quickly...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What, may I ask, are you making in this pot?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">No clue. Just know it's important. Very important. MOST important...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Most important, huh? Are we talking like "Making soup for lunch" kind of important, or what?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">......</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Red flower... Mix in... Stir... Red flower... Mix in... Stir... Red flower... WHAT?! I'm out! No more stirring! No more mixing!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Are those not red flowers in that basket over there?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Red flowers... YES! I'm restocked! Back to mixing! Back to stirring!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This flower...blooms just off the shore of the lake, does it not? It would seem your task is to mix these red flowers into the pot, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Red flower... Mix in... Stir... Red flower... Mix in... Stir...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Boy, he's seriously concentrating so hard he can't even afford to have a conversation. ............ Wonderful weather today, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Red flower... Mix in... Stir... Red flower... Mix in... Stir...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ever the social butterfly, Miss Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Red flower... Mix in... Stir... Red flower... Mix in... Stir...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's really at it. It doesn't look like he can afford to talk.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">I...stir...the red liquid... Next to me they make...the blue liquid... The Shade over there...she has been trying to mix the two for some time...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You mean, mix the two liquids together?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder if we can give this a try. Let's look around and see, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Oh, mistress, please answer... What could have happened?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Excuse me, but...could you perhaps tell us what is going on here?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">We heard a loud noise from the mistress' room just a moment ago. We called out to her, but there was no answer. There was nothing. No answer at all. This isn't like her...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A "loud noise", huh? Maybe that was the sound of the Great Witch being attacked.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">No! To harm one as beautiful as her... What BARBARIAN would do such a thing?! But if she was attacked... then that means the attacker is still... Eeeeeeek! Just thinking about it is making me shake in my robe!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All right, guys! First things first! We've gotta get this door open!</line>
<line speaker="Shade">You are welcome to try, but we have already exhausted our options. You see, only the mistress has the key to this door. However, if something has happened, we had better hurry...</line>
<line speaker="Shade">H-how terrifying... I mean, please help us! B-but how utterly terrifying...</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Open the door... We must open the door... We must...help our mistress... We must...help the Great Witch...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They really cranked up the heat on this pot. Look at that blue liquid bubble!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Such a myriad of instruments. Creating these liquids must need the most precise measurements.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder which liquid has the most bubbles when it boils? Red or blue?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That is quite the sizeable pot. It must take quite a bit of time to bring that amount to a boil.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... These appear to be the flowers that grow in the vicinity of the mansion.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">More flowers! I bet Espella would love these. Seriously, Professor, put some under your hat!</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Mix equal measures of...blue and red... ...Ughh. I can't do it.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm, this Shade's task is proving to be quite challenging for her.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Isn't her task... to mix the red and blue liquids together?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Yes... They must be combined in equal measures. But no matter how many times I try, I cannot get it... Please... Can you help me...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-huh? You want us to help...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Hmm. I must admit, I am quite fascinated by the mixing process at work here. Very well. Let us give her a helping hand.</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">40</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Shade">You did it... You actually did it...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I knew you could do it, Professor! Our Shade friend here looks pretty pleased.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This liquid... It has a most mysterious glow. I wonder what type of dye they used? And yet, this scent... It smells oddly familiar... Perhaps I smelled it when arriving in this town... Hmm, no, I believe I smelled this scent before that, even...</line>
<line speaker="Shade">M-miiiiiistreeeeeeeeeess! WAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-what the...? What's wrong...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There's quite a bit of commotion coming from the entrance to that room... I believe something may have happened. Quickly, Miss Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">R-right!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um...excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Waah!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ahh!</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Wh-what gives? Could you please not scare me like that...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Our apologies. There seems to be a great many of you gathered here. Has something happened inside?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Something did happen... Oh! I can't even THINK about it, it's just so horrible!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">S-so what is this "horrible" thing that happened?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">The mistress...the Great Witch, she's... She's GONE!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaaaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">..."Gone"?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Oh, mistress! I knew something was destined to happen! I felt a premonition most disturbing...</line>
<line speaker="Shade">How? How did this happen? I saw no one enter or leave this room!</line>
<line speaker="Shade">The entrance to the room was sealed shut... Where could she have gone...?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">......</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The curtain hanging from this wall appears to have suffered a single tear down the middle.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait, Professor! Let me just check... All right, it's clear! No one's hiding behind the curtain.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This place definitely screams "something serious just went down", doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It certainly seems so, Miss Fey. Unfortunately, the culprit seems to have disappeared...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This red liquid managed to get sprayed throughout quite a bit of the room.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">From the looks of this place, the Great Witch definitely had her hands full...but what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-whoa...no kidding, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would seem the Shades made quite the mess searching for the Great Witch. Let us enquire with everyone in the room to get a better understanding of the situation at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right! How about we start with that Shade over there?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A good suggestion, Miss Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, excuse me? Do you think we could ask you a couple of questions?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Sure...what is it? Hmph... It's not like I'm busy or anything.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Could you perhaps describe to us what you saw when you entered the room?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Yes... We all heard what sounded like a fight happening on the other side of the door. No matter how many times we called out to the mistress, there was no reply... We thought something might have happened to the mistress, so we forced the door open. But when we got inside, she was nowhere to be found...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You say she was "nowhere to be found"... And was the door closed the whole time?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Yes... It was most certainly closed. But somehow, the mistress managed to disappear...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So let me get this straight: she disappeared from a sealed room, and then the room was found in a big mess... Professor! You know what this means? This means magic must be behind it!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This is quite the peculiar situation. The Great Witch mentioned having to meet with a visitor. Do you happen to know if that person was in this room?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">A visitor... I faintly remember a visitor. I do remember hearing another voice... To be honest... I-I didn't actually see them...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And there are no other exits present in this room, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Correct... This main door is the only one.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, so... The Great Witch and her "visitor" both disappeared from the room. And even with all of these Shades around, no one saw a single person enter or leave the room...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Or perhaps, Miss Fey... this "visitor" simply managed to stay incognito during the ensuing commotion... That is one possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? What do you mean, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">No one had seen the visitor prior to the incident, so even if that person was seen in this room... clearly no one would have realised it was them.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But...wouldn't an outsider stick out like a sore thumb here? All of the Shades are dressed the same.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, any "outsider" would certainly stand out. I imagine the Shades would be quick to apprehend them. However, what if this person were to disguise themselves as a Shade?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...oh! You could be right! Maybe they disguised themselves as a Shade right before the others came into the room...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Precisely. The rather dishevelled appearance of this room would immediately draw one's attention. Thus providing the perfect distraction for the culprit to hide.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, okay, so... Where's this visitor now?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">No one has left this room since we entered. Therefore...he or she must still be in this very room.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All right then...let's hurry up and catch 'em!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">In order to do that, we must question everyone currently present in the room and gather some information.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">U-umm...what do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">My apologies for troubling you once again. Could you please gather together everyone who entered the room?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Y-yes... Right away...!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Although only the Shade who entered first is relevant to the plot, all Shades must be placed in the correct order for the answer to be deemed correct</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would appear you are not quite the same as the other Shades present in this room.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Hmph...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The one who was in this room with the Great Witch... was you, was it not?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">............ Hmph. Impressive work, Sir Top Hat.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaaaaaaat?! Wh-what are YOU doing here...?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The Great Witch's visitor was in fact you... ...Inquisitor Barnham.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I have to say...that "logic" of yours is still as keen as ever, Sir Top Hat.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Logic, coupled with careful, precise thinking, can topple any mystery. So tell us...what exactly are you doing here in this place?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I might ask the same of the two of you. How can it be... that both of you are still alive? You were turned into a gold statue... and was she not sent to the flames as a witch?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey... I. Am. Not. A. Witch!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">This must be the Great Witch's handiwork as well!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?! No way... Inquisitor Barnham?! You didn't... Did you KILL the Great Witch...?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...What on earth are you talking about? I remember doing no such thing.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">You...you wretched liar! What have you done with the mistress?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Spare me. The condition of this unkempt room is but the result of its equally unkempt master.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Insolence! None shall speak ill of the mistress!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Please, stay calm. Inquisitor Barnham, please, tell us the state in which you found this room. Tell us, what happened here?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ Hmph. It would seem the presence of an inquisitor has fouled the atmosphere with the stench of distrust. Very well. I will tell you what I know.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...I did not think the situation would devolve to such a state. I only came seeking the one that could cast some light on the doubts that plague my mind...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And just who is this mysterious "one"?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...You cannot say. Very well. Please continue, Inquisitor.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I followed them and was led here to this strange forest. That is why I was here... I was aiming to put a stop to whatever plan the Great Witch was attempting to concoct.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">So you disguised yourself in their robes and made your way here to this room in hopes of foiling her plans...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">All those who doubt the Storyteller and speak ill of his word are a threat to all of Labyrinthia and its citizens. Of course, the witch refused to speak with me...and as I reached for my sword... I lost consciousness. Perhaps it was one of her detestable magic spells.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Magic?! Lies! Your words are nothing but lies!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I am true to my word! That was what happened before you forced open the door! That is why I lost sight of the Great Witch and was left stranded in this room. I attempted to make my escape a quick one, in order to avoid any unnecessary confrontations.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If you lost consciousness, then you did not see the Great Witch disappear, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Regrettably so.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Liar! You did it! Because of you, the Great Witch is...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">How many times must you accuse me?! A Court Knight is always true to his word!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait, wait, WAIT! Then how do you explain all this blood everywhere?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Actually...I do not believe this is blood.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...I did not draw my sword. No blood should have been spilt.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well then...what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It could be that strange liquid we saw the Shades brewing earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! I think you're right! It sure smells like it...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps one of these jars containing the liquid was knocked over during the struggle. The liquid must have splattered into the middle of the room, thus creating the scene we now see before us.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see... Now that you mention it, it does look like there's a broken jar on the floor over there...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...But can there really have been no other way for the Great Witch to have escaped?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">According to the Shades, there is not.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Then is the answer not clear? ...She must have used magic to disappear.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Not quite. Magic is not the only method through which one can exit a locked room.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey...are you saying this whole thing is like one giant puzzle, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">She managed to disappear out of a locked room with no other apparent exits. What other method could there be...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Regardless, we must search the room thoroughly for any clues.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You got it, Professor! I'm positive there's a clue or two lying around here somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, Miss Fey. Shall we begin?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Inquisitor Barnham was most helpful. Let us not squander this chance, and explore the room while we can.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Oh? What could this be...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Did you find something, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Miss Fey, please come and take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's a throne...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This throne does not appear to have any of the red liquid on it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sure looks that way.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">However, if we just move this to the side...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! It must have gotten shoved here during Inquisitor Barnham's mad struggle!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">......</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But what does this mean?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This throne does not have a single drop of the red liquid on it, yet the wall behind it does... Why do you think that is?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well...because the throne was in a different spot when Inquisitor Barnham was having the fight of his life?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Very sound reasoning, Miss Fey. And who do you think could have moved it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well... It must have been Inquisitor Barnham, when he was battling it out tooth and nail.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...'Twas not a battle fought with either teeth or [sic] nails. And I have no recollection of moving this throne at any stage.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">In other words, the only one who could have moved this throne was the Great Witch herself. And I believe moving this throne is in some way connected to what she did next.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"What she did next"...? Oh! You mean her little disappearing act!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Hmph... Wielding that "logic" you love so much? But remember, this is the Great Witch we are discussing. She could have easily used a magic spell to disappear.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Lies! The mistress' disappearance is your doing! You will return her at once!</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Please...bring her back to us...</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Grr! You detestable knight! We...we won't forget this!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-hold on a second! Wh-whoa! Wh-where did you guys get those weapons?!</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Tell us what really happened here... Tell us! There is nowhere for you to run!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">......</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh-oh... This is NOT good! Inquisitor Barnham looks about ready to rip them to shreds...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">HAAAAA!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">AHHHHH!</line>
<line speaker="Shade">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Listen well, servants of the Great Witch. If you seek the truth, you must find it yourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">G-gah...</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Urgh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa... No wonder Inquisitor Barnham is so famous around town! He truly is an incredible knight!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I cannot waste any more time here. I must make haste and return to protect the Storyteller. Sir Top Hat... ...'Twas a pleasure crossing swords with you once again.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...An honour, Inquisitor Barnham.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Ms Fey. </line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-yeah...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Your courageous acts of bravery are worthy of my respect and admiration.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">C-courageous acts of bravery...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Hmph... That is all for now. Until next time...farewell!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...He's gone.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps the good inquisitor has anticipated the Great Witch making another appearance. He must have thought it's more important to work out her next move, rather than dwell on how she disappeared... Inquisitor Barnham is set on ensuring the Storyteller's safety and continuing the fight against the witches... He is quite determined to stay true to his responsibility as an inquisitor. Miss Fey, let us have one more good look around the room.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right! Let's find us some clues!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We are certain to find something that can solve the mystery of how the Great Witch managed to seemingly disappear. Let's continue our investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey...Professor! Take a look at the wall where the chair was! Doesn't it look like that wall could be a door leading to a secret passage?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...As I suspected. It would seem the Great Witch did not really disappear into thin air. Although it is still unknown by what method she was able to make Inquisitor Barnham lose consciousness... we can assume she took advantage of the situation and escaped through this secret passage.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But, Professor, even if we go after her now...do you think we'd catch her? What should we do?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I believe she intended for us to discover this secret passage. It would seem she has us right in the palm of her hand. However... if we are to discover the truth, we must continue to move forward.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You said it! All right! Let's get going, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...*gulp*... That wasn't an ordinary puzzle... It was some sort of monster puzzle...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Don't worry, Mr Wright! You can always try it again! How about we have another go when you're ready?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, I'm good to go and ready to make a comeback.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Good luck, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hmm... That's odd. I should have been able to solve that one...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't sweat it, Luke. You can always try again later.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This looks like a hidden puzzle! Not to worry! I'll take care of it!</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Heh, what's wrong? Got cold feet? C'mon, give it another try.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Wanna give it another shot? Now that's the spirit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-whoa...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This puzzle is one tough cookie...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll say. How about we take a breather and regroup?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Let's try tackling this puzzle one more time!</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">What's the matter? Was my puzzle too much for you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well, duh! I told you I'm no good at these things...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Don't worry, Mr Wright. You can do it! Like the professor always says, "every [sic] puzzle has an answer"!</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Aww, what's wrong? Running away already? Now c'mon!</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">I must find a pair of parrots! But it must be a pair! One parrot simply will not do!♪</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">If I could find a brace of parrots, To help me when I sing, my popularity would surely soar, like a bird that's on the wing!♪</line>
<line speaker="Cooper">No try? Cooper knew. Box tricky-tricky. Not like barrel. Barrel full of fun!</line>
<line speaker="Cooper">Box tricky-tricky. Never know what inside. Barrel better. Cooper always inside barrel.</line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">Why, whatever is the matter, gentle sir? I hope you did not find my story ever so boring.</line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">In those days, nary a night went by on which we were not dancing the night away at one of our balls.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Are there any other puzzles you wish to take on?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">...Most impressive. Puzzles really are nourishment for the mind.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Come again if you wish to test your mettle against any one of my puzzles.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? That's weird... It opened up last time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Easy there, Luke. Take your time. Those knights won't find us any time soon.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">You can do it, Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey! Mr Wright, why did you stop?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Just thought we could use a little break. That and I think this puzzle just turned my brain to mush...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">But shouldn't we solve this puzzle before the knights get back...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Give it another go, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'll hop back inside! Good luck, Mr Wright! I know you'll be able to solve that puzzle! Just take it one step at a time and think carefully!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right, got it. Good luck in there, Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I knew it. There isn't enough space for the three of us.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">No, it's okay! All we have to do is rearrange all of the cargo and we'll all fit easily!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Guys... The light is getting closer and closer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Luke! You're up!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Just leave this to the professor's apprentice!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's no good, Professor! They're on us like glue! They'll catch us at this rate.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Shall we give it another go? Let's try and lose them in the forest.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww... C'mon, Professor! I really wanna know how you got out of that jam!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">All in good time, Miss Fey. I just need a moment to remember.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You really can't remember? Just like Nick... He'd forget his attorney's badge if he didn't love showing it off so much.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I awoke to find myself trapped in a vine-covered cell, of sorts. Allow me to show you just how I managed to escape.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I knew it. We're gonna have to swim across. I hope no one ate in the last hour!</line>
<line speaker="Shade">I told you, that won't work... I can't swim.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, how about you try the "maybe next time" strategy?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">That won't work...I have to complete my task.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I recommend we think of another possible way across. One that doesn't involve swimming, preferably.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, guys! After me! I'm going in! One... Two...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Wait a second, Miss Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah ha! I knew it! You can't swim, can you, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That is not the case at all. I merely believe it would be too hasty to resort to swimming. I think I have an idea. Just leave it to me.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">You couldn't do it... I knew it... This task...is just too difficult...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It is pretty tough...but just leave it to the professor! He'll have this solved faster than you can say "hail to the Great Witch"!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Of course. Every puzzle has an answer. Or should I say, every task.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">I just can't do it... Please, I beg you...give me a hand...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A puzzle about mixing liquids... Or should I say, a task about mixing liquids. Let us assist her in this task, Miss Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Professor! What are you doing? If you don't hurry, they're gonna get away!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Not to worry, Miss Fey. It never hurts to pace oneself and take a break when necessary. Let us try again when ready.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Now then, let us try one more time. Only upon solving this puzzle will we find the Great Witch's assailant.</line>
</xml>