<xml>
<title>Another Visit</title>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Here we are again, in downtown Labyrinthia!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This takes me back... It looks just the way we left it.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Sure does! Seems like it's life as usual around here.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, that's right. The townsfolk had become accustomed to their old way of life here. They felt more comfortable keeping their lives as unchanged as possible.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, I wish them continued happiness in doing so.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Thank you. But something is a bit odd...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...? What do you mean, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Well, actually... Eve was supposed to meet you all here too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, really? Eve was coming here?</line>
<line speaker="???">...Heh heh heh heh heh... ...Those led by the Story... ...Welcome to Labyrinthia...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Th-that voice!</line>
<line speaker="???">...There is nothing to fear here... ...For the time being, enjoy your nostalgia... ...That's right... ...For the time being...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey, it's Eve! You know, I just love that costume!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's good to see you, Eve. How have you been?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...that was a rather dramatic entrance. It's a pleasure to see you again, Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A bewitching performance, as always! You never fail to give me goosebumps when you talk like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">........................ Umm...Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">What is it, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is Eve...feeling okay?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, well... She's just... I'm afraid Eve often feels a little nervous around groups of people...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nervous...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Well, yes... Meeting you all without a bit of drama would make her feel too embarrassed.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh...? N-no way!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'd have thought this would be a great opportunity to remove the mask and talk together in a more relaxed manner.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I think so too... Come on, Eve. Say hello to everybody!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">De-fin-ite-ly! C'mon, Eve! You can do this! For us...? Pretty please? No need to be bashful!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">........................ ...Um...I... I'm...Darklaw...and as you all now know... I am also Eve. Thank you for coming here today... It's good to see you all again.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You don't have to be nervous with us, Eve! We've already talked, like, a million times in the main game, haven't we?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's right! It's not like you to be so nervous!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Well, it's not that... It's just... I've heard this is some sort of... Special Episode, or something.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, that's what we've been told.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's right! Players who've completed the game can get this as extra content.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">So you mean...people all over the world are unlocking this and playing it? As in...five million people...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">........................ Say WHAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Five million people...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Excuse me, Mr Wright... Has this game been quite such a big hit, as far as you're aware?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... I'm not really sure...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm? What is it, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y'know, Eve is pretty cute and all... But I'm starting to think she's actually kind of a drama queen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Oh, brother.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And with unwavering confidence, the Great Witch makes her exit...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Ah...it would appear that you have arrived.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh! ...Whoa! Everyone, it's the Storyteller!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Allow me to warmly welcome you all back to Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Phew...thank goodness. At least the Storyteller is his normal self!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I see Eve has taken her leave. Please excuse her, she's just a little shy, you understand.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...But the second she puts on that Great Witch's mask, she loses that shyness very, very quickly. And that's when the threatening words just start flowing from her mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, I remember that quote!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Don't expect me to do an "award statue" impersonation again...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's okay, Professor! You're already worth your weight in gold! By the way, Mr Cantabella...how's your health these days? Are you fully recovered?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, that's right...weren't you going to have an operation?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Yes, indeed. Thankfully, I have been able to make a full recovery. My dear Espella here, along with Eve, kindly aided me through my convalescence.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm glad to hear that, Mr Cantabella. We were all rather concerned.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Along with the reconstruction of this town, I have also been reconstructing my life, so to speak.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Hee hee... Dad, why do you always have to be so...melodramatic?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you mean, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Before the operation, let's just say that Dad became a bit...scared of having to go to the hospital.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It was quite the challenge getting him to go there...let alone actually allowing the doctors to do their job and help him.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Harrumph! Espella... There's no need to tell them all that!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Dad hates not being in control so much that he even tried to write a Story while he was there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean...like Labyrinthia's "Story"?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That's right! He's always used to having his Stories become a reality, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... I guess he ended up getting a reality check...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Hey, Eve. You don't happen to have that "Story" with you here, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey...it's the Historia Labyrinthia! Read it, Espella! Read it!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Now this is a chapter I'd like to hear! Wouldn't you, Professor?!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Please... Spare me this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What the heck is this?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It comes across as rather more of a wish list than a Story.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's practically a whole chapter about hospital food!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Great... Look what you've done! Now I'm just dying to eat some tiramisu!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">And do you know what the worst part is? They didn't even serve tiramisu. Not once...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Writing a Story like that seems a little pointless now, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Indeed...it is as you say. However, the comfort of routine can be a powerful ally. Writing that Story is what gave me the strength to face the future.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That, in itself, is an intriguing footnote. Perhaps you could say that stories... are rather like maps guiding us towards our dreams.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's deep...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">As long as we maintain a clear image of our dreams... then we can realise them simply by collecting and assembling the pieces. In fact, it's just like in this puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I believe stories often give us courage... Whether they become a reality or not is often incidental.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I gotta say, Professor... You summed that up pretty well.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Ah! What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">What's the matter, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">After what the Storyteller wrote in hospital... On the next page... there's a story in a different handwriting!</line>
<line speaker="The Great Witch">Uh-oh... Th-that must be...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? What's the matter, Eve?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Deathly magic"? "Under no circumstances"? C'mon, Luke! Let's read this bad boy!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">A story written by Eve...? This does sound interesting!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, if you insist...or even if you don't!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What the heck is this?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">"Handheld gaming's latest star eclipses all her rivals. Professor who? Phoenix what?" ...This particular dream is a little far-fetched.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know what, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm? What is it, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eve is pretty cute and all...but now I'm super sure... She's totally a drama queen.</line>
</xml>