<xml>
<title>At Naruhodo's Legal Consultancy</title>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm...um... Hello! I'm, um...I'm back!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, hello, Mr Naruhodo. Did you have a good outing?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hi, Runo! ...Hm? What's the matter? Your eyes are as big as dinner plates.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haha, Iris... I, I wasn't expecting to see you here!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I've just made some tea, Mr Naruhodo. Would you like a cup?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A cup or two! Yes! Um...definite-tea! Haha!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">......... Alright Runo, what's going on? You're acting extremely strangely.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? Me? No! Not at all! I'm as normal as normal can be! Normali-tea itself, see? Haha. Ha...ha...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Haah... Not again, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Sorry? Not what again? What do you mean, Susie?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Whenever he goes out on his own lately, he always seems to come back with a peculiar new purchase.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Peculiar? Peculiar? What's peculiar about the things I've bought?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You seem to think that anything British is a curio you simply must have. You keep buying items of bric-a-brac even though you don't know what they are.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, there are rather a lot of bric-a-brac shops and pawnbrokeries and the like around here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...It's when I've been to Lord Stronghart's to give my weekly report. I'm always so nervous beforehand. On the way home, I just find myself in those shops and... Yes, alright, I can't deny it! I've bought something!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You're right, you can't deny it. Because your eyes are wider than ever.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You really ought to put up a warning sign about them. They're bigger than some potholes around here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...It's hard to resist things in the bric-a-brac shop. It's all so cheap. Mr Sholmes has given me lots of useful advice about how to pick out the real bargains.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You must remember, Runo, that Hurley likes to have fun with you. Take his advice with a big pinch of salt.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, that's true. That thing he told me was a pot stand wasn't a pot stand at all. But I'd never have guessed it was a collapsible top hat!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, and I'd never have guessed that you could fill up this once empty room so quickly. Honestly, it's overflowing with things we don't need now. I mean, look at those scales. Not once have you weighed something on them.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know, but ever since I first stood at the defence's bench in court, I don't know why, but... ...I've just really wanted my own little set of scales.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Let's see it then, Mr Naruhodo. What have you come home with today?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Well, um...it's, erm...one of these!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It looks all dry and shrivelled up in a ball.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Really, Mr Naruhodo, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...It's a sea anemone.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">An, an anemone?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. I mean, I know it doesn't look like it at the moment. It's all shrivelled up, like you said.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Aren't sea anemones living creatures? The ones that dance about on the seabed?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, exactly! The ones that dance about on the seabed!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Oh. They sell sea anemones in bric-a-brac shops here in Britain?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't know whether they normally do or not, but I do know that I bought one today!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But why, Runo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, um...yes! For the aquarium, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Aquar...ium? I don't know that word.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, according to the shopkeeper... ...keeping sea creatures in tanks was hugely popular here in London before.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh yes, some people have some beautiful fish in seawater tanks, it's true. Having an aquarium became popular because the old glass tax was abolished.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">There it is again, rearing its ugly head. The subject of taxation...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It was a real craze for a while. Everyone in London had one!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">For a while?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, it didn't last long. People's enthusiasm soon waned. It's just far too much work to be changing the seawater regularly in a city like London.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Never a truer word said, I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You'd think people might have realised that from the start really, wouldn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Anyway, that was long before I was born. So now everyone jokes that there's an unloved aquarium covered in dust in every attic in the capital.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And it's true! There's one in this attic, too. When I told the man in the bric-a-brac shop about it, he had these words of wisdom: 'That's why this is the age of the sea anemone!' ...And that made a lot of sense to me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It...made sense to you, did it?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But Runo, this anemone is completely dried up.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'You just need to soak it in water overnight, and it'll be as good as new!' ...That's what the man said.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm not sure that it works in the same way as dried wakame seaweed, Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Once I've saved some money, I'm going to buy some prawns to keep this little fellow company!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, how exciting! Your office will be teeming with life!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Will it really...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Britain is a funny country, though. I mean, a sea anemone craze?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well... They say 'people in glass houses' about comments like that here, Mr Naruhodo. Don't forget that there was a very curious rabbit craze in our own country not so very long ago.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A mortifying chapter that people will try to erase from the history books a hundred years from now, I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You know, there was another craze as well before the aquarium one. Have you heard of Wardian cases?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wardy...what? No, I've definitely never heard of them.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...They were little glazed cases for growing plants indoors, I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, I see. For plant-lovers to raise their favourite tropical plants.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's right. Like different types of ferns.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ferns?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Do you mean those rather dull plants with lots of fronds for leaves?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">They're not dull at all! Ferns are lovely plants. I think people wanted to recreate the exotic foliage of the tropics in their own homes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So they grew ferns? I mean, ferns...sea anemones... Londoners certainly have a knack for the obscure.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well...thinking about it... ...my grandfather loved the moss on his bonsai. He looked after it better than the trees.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It seems like the more obscure something is, the more it interests people.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Maybe! Anyway, the Wardian case craze didn't last very long. Now most of those little glass cases are just gathering dust, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But haven't I seen one in your room, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ooh, very observant of you, Susie! Yes, that's right. Mine's certainly not gathering dust. I grow tropical herbs in it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Well, Mr Naruhodo... ...I really must ask you to stop all this frivolous buying of strange things.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes, alright. Sorry. It's just that, well... Think about Mr Sholmes's room! He has all sorts of peculiar trinkets lying around.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...well yes, that's true. And they seem to be growing in number. Recently I've noted a blowpipe, a few beryl crystals set in a twisted piece of gold, a gold-rimmed pince-nez...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I spotted a small gramophone record in there the other day, so I slipped it onto the gramophone. But it was just a whispering voice saying 'Norbury' and nothing more! What could it possibly be about?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Those are all mementoes of cases that Hurley's solved over the years.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Exactly! That's what I want to create in here! Just that sort of atmosphere.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, a room full of meaningful trinkets, each with their own unique history, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes! Yes, that! I knew you'd understand, Miss Susato!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But, Mr Naruhodo...none of the things you've bought for the room have any connection with any of our cases.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh. Don't they?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, for example, take that splendid, but rather weather-beaten top hat. That wasn't used as evidence in any of the cases we've worked on, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, so you have two top hats if you count the collapsible one as well?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, the collapsible one is a pot stand. ...As far as I'm concerned, anyway. But the other day when we were in court, they were everywhere, weren't they? Top hats, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, here in Britain of course, they're the mark of a true gentleman, so that's hardly surprising. If a man isn't wearing a top hat when he ventures out of doors, he'll be looked down upon.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gosh, it has very strict rules, doesn't it? The English gentleman's code.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I've been wondering how I'd look in a top hat recently. After all, my university uniform is black as well, so I think it could be very in keeping.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, what a good idea! Go on then, Runo, try it on!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The lesson here, I suppose, is that the juxtaposition of student and gentleman is just so strange and...wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Well I'd rather it didn't suit me anyway! I mean, these hats are ridiculous! I'd be willing to bet every foreigner who sees one of these for the first time thinks exactly the same thing: 'Why is that man wearing a chimney on his head?'</line>
<line speaker="Iris">People in glass houses, remember, Runo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, what about Japanese chonmage topknots? Those haircuts are the height of ridiculousness!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...true.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">At least you can take a hat off. Once you have a chonmage, it's 'chon' your head for good!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'd be willing to bet every foreigner who sees a chonmage for the first time thinks exactly the same thing: 'Why is that man wearing a cannon on his head?'</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...I suppose that's what it means to have different cultures, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">On the subject of hats... ...the one Mr Sholmes always wears is really very strange, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I, I, I beg your pardon, Mr Naruhodo? What a thing to say! That hat is the very essence of Mr Sholmes! Yes, without his deerstalker, the great detective would be unrecognisable!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's called a deerstalker? That's a surprisingly swanky name.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's the hat of a hunter, just like the flat cap. I made up my mind long ago to visit Regent Street and buy one for myself!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'm not sure it's going to fit over your hair.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well I think it's perfect for a great detective who stalks his criminal quarry!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What do you think is strange about it anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well you've seen it! It has two brims, one at the front and one at the back. Why do you need two brims on a hat? Surely one at the front is enough, no? </line>
<line speaker="Susato">Hmph! One moment, please...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you ask me, it's just Mr Sholmes's madcap personality coming through. I bet it's so that he doesn't have to think about which way round to put it on or something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes does not have a madcap personality! He always has a clear head!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Deerstalkers were made for hunters who had to hide in thickets when they were stalking their prey. The brim at the back was designed to stop the stalks of plants scratching the backs of their necks.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, so that's the reason! Thank you, Iris, for educating us.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes doesn't spend a lot of time in thickets though, does he?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well no...that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm telling you, it's just his impetuous personality. That's my theory, and I'm sticking to it. Firmly!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, here you all are!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, good afternoon, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I've not long since made some tea, Mr Sholmes. Would you like a cup?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I see I've come at a good time, Miss Susato. Thank you. Now...I have something I should like you all to see. I've designed myself a brand new great detective's hat!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wh-What the...? There's a brim...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...At the front and at the back...and at both sides! Four brims in total!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Your observation is quite correct, my dear madam. I'm a busy man, you see. But with this hat, whichever way I put it on, I shall always have it pointing the correct way!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">With my previous hat, I could, in an impetuous moment, wear it erroneously with the brims on either side.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's...impressively clumsy, I would say.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...And I must regretfully say, I think your madcap theory was correct, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But really, Mr Sholmes, with brims on all four sides like that, wouldn't it just be better... ...to wear a top hat instead?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh yes! Then however you put it on, you'd have a brim all around.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What?! So true, so true! How could I have been so blinkered to this fact until now?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well fortunately, I happen to have two top hats here. If you'd just lift the pot off it, you're welcome to try that one there.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed I shall, my good fellow. Much obliged.'</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh dear, Hurley, it looks terrible! More terrible than I could possibly have imagined!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, that's not good. Maybe it's because of your long face. Paired with the tall hat, it just...doesn't work.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well I think it's very nice, Mr Sholmes. ...Even if it will have the whole world in fits of laughter.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">AAAAAAARGH! I should never have meddled with it! Give me a deerstalker for evermore!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And give me my regulation university hat for evermore!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...There's still hope that you'll graduate one day, Mr Naruhodo. Don't give up!</line>
</xml>