<xml>
<title>At the British Supreme Court</title>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...here we are again...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Every time we visit here, the atmosphere in this place seems to get more and more overbearing.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just think, we could be at home with Mr Sholmes and Iris having a nice, cosy breakfast.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But we have a duty to report the outcome of the case. Especially since we're guests here in Britain. So I'm afraid this visit couldn't have been avoided.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I suppose not. But is there even anyone here? You could hear a pin drop in this place. It's too solemn for its own good.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It is very quiet, isn't it? The only sound is the ticking of the great clock as it keeps perfect time.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... What was that, I wonder? The usual comforting sound of the clock seems to have been joined by a less comforting shuffling sound today.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're right. Something's disturbing the rhythmical ticking. It sounds rather like an unfit middle-aged man running from pillar to post. Clumsily.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Who are you callin' unfit?! Hahh...hahh...hahh...hahh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Inspector Gregson! What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">What am I...?! Hahh...hahh... Isn't it flamin' obvious?! Hahh...hahh...hahh...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...Fifty-eight seconds remaining, Inspector.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">AAAAAARRRGH! We'll have to talk later, sunshine!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Um...good morning, Lord Stronghart!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Wow, he's really looking fiercely at his pocket watch today!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">And good morning to you. ...Business so early in the day?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Um...yes! Well, I mean, erm... It's about the other day... Um...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We are to deliver our report, Lord Stronghart. As our dealings with Mr Natsume are now over.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Ah yes, the little Japanese man. I've already cast my eyes over van Zieks's report.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I must say the outcome surprised me. ...I thank you for a job well done.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You are too kind, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">It's not here! It's not there! ...And it's not over there, either!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, I hope you don't mind me asking, but...what exactly is the inspector doing? He's been haring around between the bookshelves, looking beside himself with worry.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">He's looking for a particular work: 'The Lion's Pride'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Now there's an all-too familiar title.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I'd heard it was a popular tale, so I obtained a copy from the rental library. However, it wasn't able to maintain my interest, so I soon cast it aside. I happened to notice a vacant spot on one of my shelves at the time... ...so I duly stowed the book there. Unfortunately, I no longer remember where that was.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Nope! Not there! ...Not here, either! Come on! Where are you lions hidin'?!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">The book is due back today, so I've asked Gregson to locate it for me with his investigative prowess... ...inside five minutes!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I must say I've never seen anyone working so hard to find something. He's like a man possessed.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Ah yes. That's because his month's salary is staked upon the outcome.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>At whose instigation? ...Let me guess: this stony-faced lord.</thought> And...the five-minute time limit? What's the significance of that?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">There is none. Just my vulgar mischievous spirit showing itself, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh. By your own admission...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">GAAAAAAAAARGH! I, I can't... Hahh... My feet...hahh...are killin' me.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Five seconds. Four...three...two...one... Time's up, Inspector.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">GAAAAAAAAAAAAAAARGH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Which means that next month you will work unpaid and have no days off.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">No...no days off...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There really are just so many books here. It's overwhelming.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">For some, perhaps. I've purchased every book, new or old, on the subject of law from all over the globe.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Wouldn't have believe it a few short decades ago. A place like this couldn't have existed.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What do you mean, Inspector?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">When I was a kid, no one ever dreamed of buyin' books.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, I see. Western books are such luxury items, I suppose, with their leather covers and fancy bindings.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">No, that's not it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">There was a tax on paper, see?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, on paper?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yeah. I mean, it was abolished about thirty years back now, but it used to be the case. There was tax levied on any kind of paper. So obviously that meant most folk couldn't afford to buy any books at all.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, so is that why places like the rental library you mentioned before came into existence, Lord Stronghart?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Indeed. Vestiges of the paper tax system, you could say. The general public consider books as items for hire. London is home to a vast lending library of some three and a half million books.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...You couldn't hope to read all of that even if you were reincarnated ten thousand times.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Even I would choose to rent a book rather than purchase it, if I knew I would read it infrequently.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The subject of tax has actually surprised us already in the last few days. It came up in Mr Natsume's trial. It seems that the window in his room was filled in due to some kind of window tax.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">That would be true. Fortunately the window tax was abolished here some forty years ago. Sadly, in the East End in particular, many windowless houses remain.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Britain's always had a bit of a thing for taxin' stuff. Whatever they can tax, they tax! Sugar, salt, tea, coffee... you name it. Candles...beards...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait, sorry? What was that last one? Did you say 'beards'?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yup. The beard tax. Never heard of it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Never! Why should people have to pay money just because they let their facial hair grow?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">You may well ask. I suppose it's because it makes them look self-important.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...the Naruhodos will have a strict family policy of no facial hair, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">You can relax. The beard tax was confined to the annals of history long ago.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Even so, it's clearly something the British really love. Paying taxes, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Payin' 'em? You've got that back-to-front, sunshine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But you can't deny you've had a lot of funny taxes over the years. You'd never find anything like that in Japan. ...Would you, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... In actual fact...I'm afraid to say that you would, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? No... You don't mean...? Surely there's never been a window tax in Japan?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, but there have been similarly obscure taxes. For example, in the Edo period, there was a frontage tax.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What was that?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was a tax not on windows, but on the entrance to properties. The larger a property's entrance was, the greater the tax that was levied on it. Even today, some mansions survive with extremely narrow entrances due to that old form of taxation.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I had no idea...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Hmph. So you Japanese are as twisted as us Brits.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but we never had a beard tax! I mean that's really going a step too far!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well no, that's true. I'm not aware of any taxes for beards at least.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean 'at least'?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, rather than tax them, the shogunate did once prohibit them outright.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The ruling class...prohibited beards?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was called the Great Beard Prohibition. It was an Edo period edict.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But why did the powers that be want to ban beards?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Because it makes people look self-important? ...Just an idea.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It would seem that rulers in the East and the West have had very similar ideas over the years. There have been other unusual taxes in our history. Even in our current Meiji period.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There have?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">For example, though it was before either of us were born...there was a rabbit tax.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Th-There was a tax on those adorable, fluffy creatures - like the one who makes mochi sweets on the moon?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes. And it was an extremely large tax, too. The government demanded extraordinary sums of money.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This just gets stranger and stranger. What was the reason for that bizarre tax then?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, after Japan opened its doors to the world, there was an unprecedented rabbit boom in the Meiji capital.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A boom?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes. Keeping rabbits became hugely popular, and new species were traded at exorbitant prices. People were even swindled out of all their money for exotically coloured rabbits.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Like coloured chicks, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Hard to imagine, though. Rabbits are so timid and quiet. Wouldn't have thought one could bankrupt you.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So in response to this worrying social vogue, the government imposed a rabbit tax.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I suppose they couldn't just ignore the problem.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And it worked, because the rabbit boom came to an abrupt end. Six years later, the tax was abolished.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I hate to say it about my own country, but...Japan is strange.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But there's more: after the rabbit tax was abolished then, of course... ...society reacted by launching straight into a second rabbit boom.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh dear. The government didn't think that one through, did they?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Your ideas about the world are very much altered by the position you hold in society. If you are responsible for the running of the country, you will feel the need to raise revenue keenly.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Without a stable taxation system, the whole country would go down the drain.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, yes, I suppose so. But some of these taxes...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">That's precisely why ministers of state use their wiles to invent new and novel ways of taxing the public.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Novel ways?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Tell me, Mr Naruhodo. If you were one of my country's statesmen...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Me? A, a British statesman?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Yes. What novel tax would you impose? Pray, give us something truly original... ...inside five seconds.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! Oh, um...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Think of something that everyone uses, Mr Naruhodo! And really squeeze every penny out of the population!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...That's quite the intense stare! I'm very glad Susato-san isn't in charge.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Your time is up. So, what's your answer?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um... Well......... Air, maybe? Yes! How about air?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Hm... An air tax, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh well done, Mr Naruhodo! A truly novel and fiendish idea!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well everyone has to breathe. So while the population is inhaling air, my government is inhaling money!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Blimey. You're a tyrant at heart, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">A somewhat radical solution to a country's revenue problems, but sadly not an original one.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No! You, you mean to say...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Surely not... You mean a tax on air has been imposed in the past?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">It was last century. The finance minister of our neighbour France proposed it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">WHAT?! <thought>If I ever go for a visit, I'm holding my breath.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Unsurprisingly, it was strongly opposed by the public and soon scrapped. The minister didn't last long, either.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... Although clearly that would have been an untenable situation.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The public at large are a force to be reckoned with.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Don't I know it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">How about you, Inspector? What new tax would you impose?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Hm, let me see... My first thought is a tax on objections.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Been hearin' far too many of them recently in court. There's a particular lawyer I have in mind, as it happens. So I think an objection tax could be very handy.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Good to see you don't allow your personal feuds to influence your work in public office.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Hmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I reckon fivepence for every objection raised would be about right.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">A most amusing proposal, Gregson.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...A most unamusing proposal, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Well then, I think it's your turn now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry, my turn for what?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Why, what else? To locate my missing copy of 'The Lion's Pride'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">It's on one of the shelves in this room. Of that I am certain. Now...I shall give you ten minutes. And let's stake your student stipend on it, hm? Fail to find the book, and you forfeit next month's payment.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ob-<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Your time starts...now. ...Oh, and one more thing. I believe you just said the word 'objection'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Kindly leave your fivepence over there before you begin combing the shelves.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...This tax is going to be the death of me.</line>
</xml>