<xml>
<title>Awkward Moments</title>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa, check it out... The Witches' Court. If nostalgia were pennies, I'd be rich right now.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I heard the entire courtroom was converted into a large theatre.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, really? You mean, they managed to inject some fun into this creepy old place? I guess I can sorta feel the creepiness melting away, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Nope. Still kinda creepy to me.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey, then that means the Inquisitors' Hall must be somewhere over there!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, Luke. Although it has since been converted into the main headquarters for the Labyrinthia reconstruction effort.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That reminds me! Eve should have finished work by now. Come on, everyone, let's go and say "hi"!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, there she is!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would appear Mr Barnham has joined her, as well. And I do believe he's wearing his armour again today.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wh-why do they look like they're both ready to fight it out in a court? And, umm...what's with the scowling and the awkward silence?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I agree, it's a little strange... The two of them should have been finished with work by now.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Well, Zacharias? What is this matter of "great importance" that you needed to discuss with me? ...You've done nothing but stand there with your eyes closed for over an hour now.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">N-no...no, ahem... 'Tis not really a matter of such "great importance", as such...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Hmm? Espella, when did you get here? And...you brought everyone along with you.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That's right, Eve. I'm sorry if this is a bad time. I see you're still busy.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...No, it's fine. Believe me. Work is over for the day, so I'm free to speak with you all. Is there something you needed?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">U-um, hey, Eve? Today is your birthday, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh don't play coy, Eve! It's your BIRTHDAY! We all thought we'd come down and give you your presents personally!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Presents...? F-for me?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Ngh!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Well, I guess I'll go first. ...Here you go, Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Th-this picture!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Dad and I wrote you a little message on the back, too.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Thank you, Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooooh, me next! Wait for it... ZVARRI! A Mega Burger meal deal!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Mega...burger...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I didn't have enough to get you the killer large meal, but just throw another burger patty on it and you'll be full for days!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Um...okay, I think I get it. Thank you very much, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, ha ha. I guess I'm up next...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Well, out with it, defender. NOW.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uuuuuuhhh...what the heck?! Why do I get the "I'm gonna kill you, Wright" face...?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Oh! F-forgive me! I just... Upon seeing your face, I couldn't help myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That doesn't make me feel any better...</thought> Umm, anyway... This is from me. I followed Espella's recipe. It's been a while since I made one, so I hope it's good...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Is this...banana bread?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, yeah. I did work at Patty's bakery, after all. Barnham didn't call me "Sir Apprentice Baker" for nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I brought you something too, Miss Eve!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I went out and picked some red flowers down by the lake in the Eldwitch Woods. I used them to make you a necklace!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The craftsmanship is excellent, Luke. Thank you so much. And thank you all for such lovely presents.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...But wait! There's more! Oooooh, Baaaaaarnhaaaaaam. Did you give Eve your present yet?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wha... WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...? Holy cow...overreact much?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Er, no...I...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">W-wait...Mr Barnham... Have you still not given Eve her birthday present yet?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">You mean...you've been standing here for a whole hour trying to give your present to Eve? Why, Sir Barnham, I'm surprised.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Z-Zacharias... D-do you really call yourself a man?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">A-a-a-absolutely! Without question! Who exactly do you take me for?! It's just... Ms Primstone...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ms Primstone...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I cannot help but recall Ms Primstone's words...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Poor Mr Barnham. His schooling seems like it was quite strict... and a little depressing.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Barnham... Although I would normally advise otherwise, perhaps you should set aside your teacher's words just this once.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The professor's right! That was the past... so bury it already!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Ahem... Err, yes...well... Lady Dark- ...Miss Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Wh-what is it, Zacharias?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">In recent days, I have taken to working part time at the local bakery... My objective: to efficiently craft a deliciously decadent pastry in your image, as tribute to the day of your birth!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">T-to do what...? I, umm...I'm a bit confused...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Wow, Barnham... You, uh...kinda sorta did it. He was all, "Milady! I hath baketh you a treat most sweet in thou image fair" ...or something kinda like that. Say, I wonder if Barnham spent all day in front of the mirror practising that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'm gonna go out on a limb and say no.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">S-such was my intent. Lady Dark- ...Miss Eve! H-h-happy day of your birth! I give you...your present!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Th-thank you, Zacharias............. ........................ What? Is this an éclair?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">This éclair looks like no other éclair I've ever seen. Wh-what's this? I-is this... a lump?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">W-well, you see... I, err...I was unable to obtain the required amount of skill to bake you a proper pastry in the allotted time. Hence why... I focused all my efforts on choosing one of the remaining éclairs, left over from yesterday's sale at the bakery... Of all the éclairs that remained, 'twas THIS that most captured your essence, Miss Eve!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ I...don't quite know how I should feel about this. Should I be...flattered? ...Or completely and utterly NOT?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Stick a fork in 'im. He's done...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...You know what? I think you tried your best, Zacharias. ...And for that, I thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Urk! N-no! Miss Eve, 't-twas nothing! Your thanks is unnecessary! The smile on your face is reward enough! ...I owe this mission's success to my trusty armour!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What? Did that armour give him "birthday gift-giving" powers or something?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey... Barnham said he was "working" a part-time job, but he never actually got paid for any of it, did he?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hmm...you're right. It must be because he's still an apprentice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh yeah. Speaking of éclairs... didn't Constantine also give Eve, err... Cat Eve, a present just the other day?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Really? Constantine did? You know, on the subject of that mutt... I never would have imagined you, of all people, would end up owning a dog. ...You surprise me, Zacharias.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Y-yes, well...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...? If you'll permit my asking, whatever do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Let's just say Zacharias had a bit of a run-in with a dog some time ago. After that, he swore he'd "never set foot near any one of these wretched beasts" ever again...let alone own one.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, I think I remember that... Are you talking about the "Barnham's Wild Ride" incident?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is that some kind of roller coaster? Anyway, sounds too interesting not to hear! Give us the goods!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">It all started...during one of the Storyteller's famous parades. Zacharias always took point during these parades, riding in front, on his horse. That's when... A large dog suddenly came shooting out from one of the side alleys and jumped right in front of the procession.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...I shall never forget it. The beast's tail looked as if it were singed by the Legendary Fire itself. It was black and white, with a notable scar above its left eye.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The dog's sudden appearance sent Zacharias' horse into a frenzy. It bolted off, with him still hanging off by the saddle...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">'Twas indeed a great blunder. When my steed flung me from its back, my ankle became caught in the reins.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">And so...he couldn't get free of the horse. The thing must have dragged him around all of Labyrinthia for hours... Since then, the incident was charmingly dubbed "Barnham's Wild Ride".</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I remember that. The children used to tie their dolls to the knights' horses and call it "bouncing Barnham".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...That's brutal.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">And yet...now Zacharias has ended up owning a cute little puppy... It's funny how life turns out, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...I believe that is enough reminiscing for one day. Now, I have a question for you, Sir Top Hat.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Certainly. What is it, Mr Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Have you, too, come bearing a gift for Miss Eve? I believe you are the only one left to present her with anything.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A typically astute observation, Mr Barnham. And so, without further ado, Miss Eve, allow me to give you your birthday present. ...A present that I'm sure many of you out there were eagerly anticipating. Miss Eve, your birthday...reminds me of a puzzle!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There's nothing like a good puzzle to celebrate a birthday, wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Professor... I don't think you're supposed to, umm...solve the puzzle before giving it to her.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">W-well that puzzle did seem extra tricky, didn't it, Eve?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">To tell you the truth... I had actually already solved it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">WHAT?! Eve! You should've said something! Well, since you managed to solve it... Maybe you should give that thing a try.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">"That thing"...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">C'mon, you know! Like, how after you solve a puzzle you're all "tick, tick, tick...CHING"! And then..."insert catchphrase here".</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...I-I couldn't possibly perform a victory pose like that... Not in front of all these people watching us.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">C'mon, Eve, you've got to at least give it a shot. Like they say, you won't know until you try.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She's right, Eve. I think it'd be a really nice way to commemorate your birthday.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Yes, but... I'm simply far too embarrassed.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I have to admit, it's really quite strange seeing you so...reserved like this, Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet if you were wearing your Great Witch costume, you'd be singing a different tune right now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pretty please, Eve? I'll be your second best friend in town if you doooo!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Miss Eve, it would be a great honour to see Labyrinthia's former High Inquisitor pose gallantly at this time of celebration.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...*sigh* You all aren't going to give up until I try this, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. Now then, Miss Eve...you may begin any time you like.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">.......................... Yup. Knew it. Super flashy.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">You know, I think I might have seen that pose somewhere before, Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I must confess, even I have ever gone to quite that extreme after solving a puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Such an inspiring pose... Mark my words, that accursed dough will find itself baked at the hands of Zacharias Barnham!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...What I wouldn't do to be thrown into the flames myself right about now...</line>
</xml>