<xml>
<title>Bridge to the Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm still up at this hour, reading through the trial record of a certain case. It's the first case my mentor, Mia, had ever handled in a court of law. The horrifying truth that I refuse to accept is holding me hostage here within its pages. Dahlia Hawthorne... What I have read, I don't want to believe. What is written here... This wasn't the Dahlia I knew. After falling into the Eagle River, I was somehow miraculously saved... But I ended up catching a cold that seemed to knock me around the world and back. I feel dizzy, my ears are ringing, my throat burns, and my head is on fire. But I will recover! I have to recover by this afternoon... I have to meet with the most ill-tempered witness imaginable. But I know that he will be able to help me... somehow!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright... Are you sure you're well enough to be doing this? You still look a little green in the face.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Or maybe "viridian", in artist-speak.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, my fever has gone down quite a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">How's your temperature now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Only 102.2 degrees... Nothing to worry about. *cough* *cough* *cough* *cough* Anyway... I read today's trial record. You weren't bad, Edgeworth... Pretty impressive despite the circumstances.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We're not in the clear yet. The main point of contention tomorrow is going to be the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In the end, the Shichishito did not deliver the deadly blow. Which means there must be another sword hiding out there that we don't know about...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Another sword, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't you worry about anything, pal! I'll dig up the murder weapon myself, or I'll eat my coat!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Thanks again, Edgeworth. I'll handle things from here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh... That is probably for the best. Actually, I was thinking about paying the old precinct a little visit. There's something I want to look into...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that is...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Our client's background, naturally.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You mean Iris, sir...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have the feeling that we've met before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">All I want is confirmation, one way or the other. And since I probably won't be getting that from you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I bid you adieu, Wright. ...Take care.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Guess I should get moving, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why? Do you need to be somewhere?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, I've gotta get to work on this bridge, pal. I'm rigging something up so we can get across to the other side.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ack! That's right! Maya is still stuck over at the Inner Temple...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But don't you worry, pal! As soon as it's all set, you'll be the first to know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-Thank you, Gumshoe! *cough* *cough* *cough* *cough* *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No problem, pal. Just try not to give me that cough of yours, OK? Alright, I'm off!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hang in there, Maya. We'll get you out. I promise. But in the meantime... I've got to continue collecting evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like it's about 20 yards to that cliff over there. But I can't see the Inner Temple from here. I really hope Maya's OK...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a narrow path going off in a different direction than that of the Main Hall. Looks like someone's taken the effort to write "To Heavenly Hall" on the signpost.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That thing looks like it's ready to collapse... At least more than it did before. According to Bikini, Eagle Mountain is very prone to earthquakes. Which reminds me... If my memory serves me correctly, Edgeworth isn't exactly a fan of earthquakes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now it really is more of a "Dusty Bridge" than a "Dusky Bridge". That kidnapping incident happened here 11 years ago, so maybe it's cursed, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hazakura Temple doesn't have a single private phone line... ...and there aren't any houses in the area, so I guess Bikini is the only one who uses this. ...I really wish I had brought my cell phone with me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Looks like no one's here...</thought> Larryyy! ... Lauriiice! ... <thought>I was sure he'd be hiding here... Guess I'll try again later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the famous Eagle River. I got to try out its rough rapids the other night. They say it has a really strong current. And they weren't kidding. It's both powerful and fast-flowing. ... I was dead lucky... I mean lucky not to be dead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's Dusky Bridge up there. It's amazing how clearly you can see it from so far away. Larry supposedly saw everything through the shack's window. Not much light gets down here, so it must be pitch black at night... But this area was probably illuminated that night because of the burning bridge above.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These steps lead up to the foot of Dusky Bridge. Coming down is a cinch, but going back up doesn't look like a walk in the park. I'm starting to understand why rivers always want to flow downstream, not up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That stuff is really ruining the beautiful atmosphere around here. It's so inappropriate. Like Sister Bikini in a bikini! *shudder* ...I've gotta think of the kittens...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at this graffiti, scrawled right on the front of the shack. At least he managed to get a pretty good likeness. When I really think about it, I guess art kind of suits him. I mean, his very existence is an art... of sorts.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The snow is really piled up on the straw roof. It's otherworldly... Like something out of a fairy tale. ...Well, the roof part anyway. The sign says, "Heavenly Hall". I guess it's pretty fitting. If you spent a night in this little freezing shack... ...you'd probably find yourself at the pearly gates by morning.</line>
<line speaker="???">Come on! Pleeease! It's for art's sake! I swear!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's only one guy I know who could be this persistent and high-strung...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">I'm talking about the heroine here! The heroine in my book. It'll make you famous. Aaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eh...? Wait a second... I-I know you... You're... Um... Oww!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>My brain's frying like a sunny-side up and you want to grill me over a name!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Franzy! You can't do that! Even as we speak, Nick's on the brink of death! ...Or so I'm told.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, it's not! And I'm not on the brink of anything.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Come on, Nick. Tell her, would you? She must model for my picture book, "Franzy's Whip Lash Splash: Simple &amp; Magnificent"! Gaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And before that, you'll have to learn how to live a semi-coherent life, Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... I don't care what anyone says! I'm telling the truth! I saw what I saw! She flew, I'm telling you! Whooosh! Just like that dude with the red underwear! Don't think I'm gonna forgive you guys when you come crawling back to apologize!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sigh* Off he goes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is one impressive gate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks really idyllic with all that snow on it, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Don't make things up just because you think I'll never get to see it for myself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can see the Main Hall from here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, wow. Is that an inkling of human kindness I sense? Oww!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's nothing compared to the pain you cause with that leathery whip of yours...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a quaint, little bell tower. I never would've thought that something this horrible was about to happen... ...when Iris rang the lights out bell that night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd love to know what that thing was used for on the night of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry to burst your bubble, but I don't recall ever losing to you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like she mentally blocked out my victories over her from her memory...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you been in Germany all this time?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, joy. Sounds like she hasn't changed a bit. Has it really been a year since we first met...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Franziska was born and raised in Germany, and became a prosecutor at the age of 13. Her father was the legendary prosecutor, Manfred von Karma. He had a perfect win record for 40 long years... But now, he is gone from this world...</thought> Don't tell me you still hold a grudge against me... ...because of what happened to your father...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes, crystal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Edgeworth... Come to think of it... ...Edgeworth was pulled into being a prosecutor by Manfred von Karma as well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because it does.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>It's probably the fever, but... She's so openly hostile that it's almost kinda cute.</thought> Oww!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No whipping the sick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Edgeworth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It's not like I thought you were here to bring me some Coldkiller X, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You read the whole thing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No. The only thought in my mind was, "I have to get across."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gumshoe said he'd let me know once the bridge was repaired. Maya... She's got to be OK. I just know it. Plus, I need to ask her about what really happened at the Inner Temple that night...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, about this... Yeow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should've known better than to try...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Hmmmaaaaaaaaaaaaah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...That was one long sigh!</thought> Umm... Sister Bikini?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">My my my! I didn't know you were here! How are you doing? Wa ha. Wa ha ha ha ha ha ha! Hmmmaaaaaaaaaaaaah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, you don't have to pretend to be in a good mood for my sake...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I... I suppose I've made a terrible mess of things, haven't I? I let Mystic Elise die, and then there's Iris as well...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Mystic Elise"...? Now that I think about it... Hmm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">There's an acolyte stuck at the Inner Temple... ...and that poor little girl has gone missing, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That little girl...? Y-You don't mean Pearls... do you?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Yes, I'm afraid I do! She hasn't been seen since the morning after the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls? She's missing!? <thought>Why didn't someone tell me about this earlier!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've only seen a layout like this when I saw this really old Japanese movie on TV. Wow! This hibachi brazier really puts out a lot of heat! Just thinking about how happy we were, sitting here eating pot roast and gravy... *sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I must be getting old... I think I've seriously lost faith in myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you talking about your performance at the trial today?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">You believe me, don't you? I'm not a liar! I would never lie! I know what I saw! I saw Iris pull that sword from Mystic Elise's body that night... I'm certain of it! At least, I was until this morning...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't see any Psyche-Locks, so she must be telling the truth.</thought> Um... So why are you so unsure of yourself all of a sudden?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">You know that artist who testified after me?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I saw Iris flying! Her white hood fluttering! I felt like I might start flying myself.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">When I saw that man testify so fervently about something so impossible... ...I started to wonder if I had acted just like him when I was on the witness stand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wouldn't take that guy too seriously. He's an artist, but all he draws is trouble... and nothing else. <thought>If both Bikini and Larry are telling the truth... ...that can only mean one thing. They both didn't see what they think they saw.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the night of the incident, you met Iris at the Inner Temple. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">That's right. I'm sure it was Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But Iris claims she was in her room in Hazakura Temple.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I knew I shouldn't have come back here that night...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But because you did, Maya is stuck at the Inner Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Nngh... I am so sorry. The drafts in that place are nothing to shake a stick at. Winter is especially bad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll bet. The Training Hall looks like it's about to fall down any second.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Eagle Mountain has always been prone to earthquakes, just so you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Earthquakes...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Yes. I wouldn't be surprised if the next big one levels the Training Hall.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We've got to get Maya out of there... fast!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">But still. There's really no need to worry... That area on the other side of Dusky Bridge is isolated like an island.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's like an island? How so?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well, the only thing on that side of the bridge is the Inner Temple. No one lives out there, and it's surrounded on all sides by the river or the forest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I see...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">So a criminal would be trapped should they choose to flee in that direction. And as long as the bridge is out of commission, he or she will have to stay there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... That means Maya could be stuck out there with a murderer and no way to escape either!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh dear! Yes, I suppose it does!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nngh... Please, Gumshoe! Get that bridge up faster!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'm curious about a few things, if you don't mind answering some questions.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh? Do you need to know my measurements for your investigation or something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, no! I want to know a little more about the victim, Ms. Elise Deauxnim.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">... I'm afraid I don't know her waist size. Or her bust size for that matter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no. I'm wondering why she came to stay in a place like this to begin with. I mean, she told us herself that she wasn't here for spiritual training.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">My my my... You make it sound like this place is some sort of dump, Mr. Wright. Mystic Elise was here to soak up the natural beauty of Eagle Mountain, if you must know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There. You did it again... Sister Bikini... I noticed you always refer to Ms. Deauxnim as "Mystic Elise".</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...Oh!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. Now, why is that? After all, she's not here as an acolyte...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">W-We address all our visitors as "Mystic". It makes their experience feel authentic. A-And anyway... She's older than me. You must respect your elders, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How do you know that? How can you say for sure that she's older than you?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... It seems Ms. Elise Deauxnim was no ordinary visitor after all... And there's Pearls... She was with Ms. Deauxnim on the evening of the murder, and now she's vanished. It's all got to be connected somehow...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me, Sister Bikini... What kind of person was Ms. Deauxnim? I mean, you call her "Mystic Elise" even though she wasn't here for training.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Does she have some special connection with Hazakura Temple that I'm not aware of?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I'm terribly sorry, but... I just can't talk about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Hmm... There's a nasty feeling building in the pit of my stomach... Looks like I'm going to have to break this Psyche-Lock and find out the truth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-Why did Pearls have to get mixed up in this mess!?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Please, Mr. Wright! I know you're worried, but try to keep it together!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, man... My head's throbbing so bad, it's killing me!</thought> Pearls... She was with Ms. Deauxnim on the night of the murder, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Yes, but... I have a temple to run, you know. I was busy preparing for the training... I didn't see the little darling even once after we'd finished eating dinner.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The murder... It didn't take place right in front of her innocent eyes, did it...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">According to the detective, she hasn't turned up at her home, either.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come on! Keep calm! There's one place left where Pearls could be! She just has to be there! Gumshoe... I'm counting on you to check it out for me, so please hurry the repairs up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, about this picture...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh, that old thing! I always turned those reporter-types away in the past. But Iris was so insistent this time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh, yes! Iris loves to be the center of attention, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Really? I find that kinda hard to believe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Huh... Ahh! Well, well, well... Look what you've found! That's the Master of the Kurain Channeling Technique, Mystic Misty Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So this woman is Maya's mother, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">It's been nearly 20 years since Mystic Misty disappeared. Apparently, she intended to pass the torch on to her daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Her daughter? Don't you know who her daughter is?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well, I myself am part of a branch family of the Fey clan. But even I am not privy to that kind of information when it concerns the main family...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, Bikini doesn't seem to know Maya's standing within the Fey family...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well, well, well! That's a Demon-Warding Hood! Acolytes are highly susceptible to possession by evil spirits, you know. That's why we always wear these for protection.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Iris gave this to me on the night of the murder. But then I went and fell into the river and got this nasty fever... I thought maybe if I were to wear this hood, it'd make my fever go down faster!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">... I don't think so. Colds and spirit power have nothing to do with each other.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Way to crush a man's hope.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Maybe my eyes were playing tricks on me. I mean, Iris could never do such a wicked thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But they proved it in court today, didn't they? That this sword wasn't the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">That's what they were saying, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The problem is, I saw it, too... I'm sure that what I saw was this blade stabbed into Ms. Deauxnim's body.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Ah, it's Mystic Elise's staff. Hmm... The crystal sphere really is missing from it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the sphere was found near Dusky Bridge, right?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Yes. Even though I'm sure Mystic Elise was in Hazakura Temple that entire evening.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About this photograph...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh, yes. Those are our snowmobile's tracks, alright. I'd know them anywhere!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But there's only one set... Which means... ...the rider went out while it was still snowing, and came back after it had stopped. That's really the only logical explanation, I suppose.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Honestly! It's like the end of the world.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not a good thing, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">To think people have the gall to call this kind of scribbling by the name of art!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">If that's the sort of standard you need for the arts these days, I could be a pop diva!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, sure. But what about the contents of the picture? What do you make of that?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">... It's definitely the end of the world.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">This crystal sphere... It's not from a Demon-Warding Hood, but I would guess it serves a similar purpose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If it's not from a hood, then I guess it really is from Ms. Deauxnim's staff.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Look at the blood on it. Oh, poor Mystic Elise...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">She's a very important visitor, you know! An honored acolyte!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She is? Do you know her or something?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">The Fey name is synonymous with the Kurain Channeling Technique. Therefore, she must be a spirit medium of great power indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like Bikini is in the dark. She doesn't seem to know that Maya is the daughter of the Master of Kurain.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh dear. I wonder where on Earth this little girl has wandered off to? She's nowhere near the Main Hall. That's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>First I lost Maya, and now Pearls... How much more pain is this case going to cause me!? Urgh... Not to mention this fever is giving me a killer migraine...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">It's all my fault, isn't it? It's all my achy back's fault. Now Mystic Elise is dead, and an acolyte is trapped inside the Inner Temple... ...and that poor little girl has gone missing, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Missing"...? I hope that's all it is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh dear, oh dear. I've got to train to withstand more pain, don't I...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">How... How can I ever make up for this...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Make up for what?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">For allowing harm to come to such an important person!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So I was right... Ms. Deauxnim wasn't just any ol' visitor here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Please, tell me! What's going to happen to poor Iris!? If she was to be found guilty, I'd... Well, I wouldn't accept it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But your testimony, Sister Bikini...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">... I can't help my testimony! I saw what I saw! It's up to a pro lawyer like you to deal with problems like that!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">What a disgraceful young man!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've finally seen through him, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">How could he sit there and claim he really saw what he drew in that picture? Although, the portrait he did of me was rather flattering, I must say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Still... It's not like Larry to make something up that might get a woman he likes in trouble. There's more to that sketch of his than meets the eye. I'm sure of it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">You certainly have some unusual friends, don't you, Mr. Wright! Ho ho ho!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">F-Friends...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">That fancy-pansy painter is one thing, but whipping the judge is just bad form.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... Um... Do you think you could go drill that into her head for me...? Please?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">You must be very happy to have such a fine mentor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mentor...? No, he's just a friend...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh, you naughty devil! Always the joker, aren't you? Ho ho ho ho! Ah, he seemed like a lovely young man... Like the kind you can always count on.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah... <thought>It's kinda depressing how much faith she has in him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was wondering about this...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Hmm... Let me see... Well, as you may know... In order to see reality for what it truly is... ...we strive to break our attachments to much of the transient, material realm. I guess you could call me an "immaterial girl"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm guessing she makes an exception for fine dining...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is where Sister Bikini witnessed the incident. It's hard to imagine she was lying on the stand, so... ...maybe there are some clues that have yet to be found.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are a few of these stone lanterns scattered around in this courtyard. Without the city glare to compete with, I imagine they would seem a lot brighter. I guess Sister Bikini must light them now, since Iris can't be here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Deauxnim's staff... I definitely remember there being a crystal sphere attached to the staff. I guess Larry eventually found the sphere near the foot of Dusky Bridge, but... ...what was it doing all the way out there...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Shichishito. It's there in Mystic Ami's right hand. But it was proven in court today that it wasn't the murder weapon. Given the design, it must've been used for some pretty gruesome things in the past...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Main Gate's on the other side of that stone wall. The difference in elevation is almost 10 feet. That's how steep this hillside is! And that's also the height the body fell from, according to the autopsy. Is it possible that Ms. Deauxnim was pushed from the top of the wall...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That building up there is the Main Hall. It was where we were staying. It sits kind of funny because it was built on a very steep slope. If you enter from the Main Gate side, these rooms above me are on the ground floor. Apparently, Ms. Deauxnim was staying in the corner room. I guess that's where she was pushed from that night...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They get quite a bit of snow up here on Eagle Mountain. Around here, skis aren't just for fun. They're tools for getting around. But the sled... Now that's gotta be for Bikini's own personal entertainment!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Wh-What was that jarring, inconsiderately loud yell...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So this is where you've been! Keeping nice and warm, I see!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective! H-Have you finished repair--</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The bridge!? Yeah, I did! I told you I'd let you know!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well well well! Then I'll come along with you and...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry, ma'am! No unauthorized entry. Access is restricted to people involved in the case.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">What was that!? I'm involved, aren't I? You couldn't get much more involved than me!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well yeah, but that's not what I mea-- Aaah!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-You're...! Ms. v-v-v-v-v-v-Von Karmaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">My my my. Well, you certainly seem to have everything under control!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...As you work to pin the guilt on Iris.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OWW! That hurts, you know! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...She's not seriously going to follow me around, is she...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Things have certainly become a lot livelier than before.</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh! ...Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Th-That voice...</thought> Pearls!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Mr. Nick... Mr. Niiick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you were here... ever since that night...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I was so lonely, I thought I was going to die! When I woke up in the morning and saw that Dusky Bridge was gone... I... I realized I was all alone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She was all alone...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah! You're...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You're the prosecutor who was so mean to Mystic Maya last year.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... I don't like you. You're nothing but a little girl without your whip!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mystic Maya didn't do anything wrong, but you were so mean! I'll never forgive you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looks like Pearls's words are getting under her skin...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeowwww! Why are you whipping me!? I didn't even say anything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Anyway... Pearls...? Weren't you with Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah! ... I'm sorry! It's... It's all my fault!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!? What are you talking about, Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... I... Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaah! Mystic Mayaaaaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, wait! Pearls! <thought>She just ran off!</thought> Oww!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What was that all about? Pearls acting like that... It's giving me the creeps. I guess I'd better take another look around since I've finally got a chance! Especially since something about this place seems different from two days ago.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can see Dusky Bridge from here. It's an unusually long bridge, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess the gorge is too wide to cross with a piece of rope or wire, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!? And would you stop calling me by my full name like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A port...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, that. That's an anchor for one of the wires that used to hold up the bridge. I think the wire that was tied to this one probably snapped when the bridge burned down. <thought>I mean, there's no way there was ever a port all the way up here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I didn't say anything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at all the Buddha statues lined up along this path.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Why don't you ask her the next time you see her?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And she'll probably slap you for prying into her private affairs.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's a weird smell coming from that incinerator. The door is also open, almost like it's begging me to look inside...</thought> Well, well. Let's see what stunning clue is concealed in here, shall we?  ... Huh? It's empty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But it's a bit strange, don't you think? ...Franziska von Karma? <thought>I seem to remember... ...there was snow on this incinerator the first time I saw it. In other words, someone's been using it to burn something recently...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was only copying you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a little gate that leads into the garden. It says "No Entry" on the sign, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But it says, "No Entry".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's got nothing to do with anything! <thought>And who told you that!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The sign says "Inner Temple".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, I can't read it either.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She looks really happy to have finally caught me on something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. There's a solitary room there called the Training Hall.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... YEOWWW!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nngh... I don't know how much more of this woman I can take!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya... She was supposed to be in here training.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>What's that...? That strange lock...? It wasn't there two days ago. This whole room is really giving off some strange vibes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's an antique dresser.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now I know how Maya feels when I tell her not to touch things...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I thought we weren't opening it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, you can do anything... Except stand up to a 9 year old girl.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at those wafer-thin mattresses!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, you know. Thin like a wafer. In other words uncomfortable. That's how we describe things like these mattresses. I guess you must say, "wafer-thick" or something back in Germany?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... This door... When I was here two days ago, that weird lock wasn't on it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have. I've seen locks and chains just like this before. They look just like the ones that guard a person's secrets during a Psyche-Lock. I wonder if this lock is guarding something, too. Dark secrets in a dark cavern...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a scroll, not a poster. It's a picture of a woman who's actually... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's a different atmosphere in this room since the last time I was here. No... It's not a different atmosphere, it's a different smell!</thought> It's gravy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This scroll... It's been completely covered in gravy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No! No one does that! For starters, it stinks! <thought>This must be the gravy that we had with the roast on the night of the incident. But why would anyone do this? Why this scroll?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This scroll shows a picture of Misty Fey, Master of the Kurain Channeling Technique. But why would anyone cover it in gravy?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Artists? Um, yeah...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Prosecutor Godot! I didn't know you were here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How come you didn't show up at the trial today?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! I could ask you the exact same question.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? But I was... I had a cold, so...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I had something slightly more important than a common cold to deal with. The importance of which is something you have no hope of ever understanding.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">... Who's the wild mare, Trite?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is Ms. von Karma. She was the acting prosecutor in your absence today.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Well, I guess I owe you one then. But you can go now, princess. It's time for the big boys to take the reins.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Hey, Filly. Know your role, and shut your mouth. I can't stand women like you. I'm only going to say this once, Lady von Whippingberg. Go home!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What are you hitting me for!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! You deserve more cracks of the whip than that, Trite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You still don't get it, do you? You don't realize that you've set something in motion that you'll never be able to undo.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's something different about Godot today... I'm getting such a strong sense of... something from behind that mask of his. Is it anger? Or... Is it... sorrow?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You had some important business and that's why you weren't in court, huh? So what was it?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">... I've told you once before, but perhaps you don't remember.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I've returned from the depths of Hell... To do battle with you.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You see, Trite... I've experienced something most have not. Death.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You... died?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Of course, being extradited from Hell is a tedious affair. The meticulous regeneration and adjustment of all your internal organs is... Well... Let's just say modern medicine allows us all to live to a ripe old age. Even someone like me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... you mean... That mask you wear is...?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">This ugly device? I promise it's not a fashion statement, my unenlightened friend. Without this, I can't see your frequently dumbfounded face.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I didn't know...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">My eyesight is pretty messed up. Even with these huge goggles on my head, I still can't see everything. Still, I keep this worn-out piece of junk of a body going with regular servicing.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">... Why don't you ask him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? M-Me!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Yeah, Trite. You. You should know all about it. You know when my life ended... And who ended it for me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I don't know what he's talking about... <thought>Although... To be honest... I do feel a little tug at the corner of my memory... I think I do know about how Godot was "killed"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">It will all become clear in due time. Isn't that right, Trite?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Earlier, you said I've done something I can never undo. What did you mean by that exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">... The Inner Temple here on this side of Dusky Bridge is an isolated island.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's what Sister Bikini said, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">And I wonder, Trite... Do you know what the police are doing here today?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">They're searching... Searching for any trace of an acolyte who went missing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Missing?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">As leader of the search party, I can tell you this with absolute certainty... Maya Fey is not on this side of Dusky Bridge.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? B-But that's impossible! She came here that night and...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I won't say it again. The chances of her being here are nil. Excluding of course, one very unique place...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>One? Where is that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">The Sacred Cavern, the entrance of which we are standing at right now. This is the only place that the search party has yet to explore.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So they haven't searched that cavern yet, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Be aware, though, that the temperature inside frequently falls below freezing. Even if she was in there... ...the chances of her being found alive are slim at best.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Which means, Trite, that you sent Maya Fey to her death!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You must have blinders on, my equestrian angel. Don't you see the big lock and chains? It's a trick lock. I'm making preparations to open it as we speak. Well, Trite? Once again, a woman dies because of you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Once again"!? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Don't tell me you've forgotten...? It was only two years ago, after all... ...when the last unfortunate woman died because of you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Because of me...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">And do you know who that was? It was Maya Fey's sister! That's right! Mia Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mia!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You killed her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, that's not how it was!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">It was two years ago... Mia Fey was pursuing someone. A man. But she bit off more than she could chew. She made a very dangerous enemy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, that's one case I'll never forget.</thought> But... I got that guy! Personally!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Sure. Ms. Fey's murderer was caught. But that won't bring her back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well, no... but...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You were with her at the time. You and no one else. It was your responsibility! You should have protected her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I...!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You say Mia Fey was your teacher! Well then, I'd say you've learned nothing, Trite! You robbed her of her life. And now... ...you've let her sister suffer the same fate!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I... I haven't sentenced Maya to death...! No...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">I'm afraid we can't do that. This area has always been prone to earthquakes. The repeated tremors have weakened the foundations of the Training Hall. Any excessive force used to break the lock open would... Well, let's just say the Inner Temple and the Sacred Cavern would be a thing of the past.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Sure. Just show me where the keyhole is on this trick lock.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-There's no keyhole!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">That's right. An interesting puzzle, huh? The person who set this lock is the only one who can open it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then who was it!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Simple. The accused.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">When an acolyte undergoes training inside the Sacred Cavern... ...the attending sister is responsible for locking the entrance. Obviously, the night of the murder was no exception. Maya Fey was to train in there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sister Bikini did mention it a number of times, now that I think about it. She said that Iris was left in charge of supervising the early stages of the training.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">So Iris, the accused, is the only one who can open this lock. I've arranged for her to be brought here now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Iris is the only person who can open this lock...? I hope she gets here soon! ...Hang on in there, Maya. We'll get you out!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Godot... Would you mind taking a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! My eyes have a date with the horizon. They're flirting with the gulls. I don't have any intention of aiding a defense attorney like you, Trite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Look who's talking!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, Godot! How sure about Maya are you?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">... There's no doubt in my mind. She's in the Sacred Cavern somewhere. It's the only place she could be.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You'd better start praying. You'd better pray that friend of yours brings the accused back here soon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Edgeworth?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Listen up, Trite. There's only one thing I want to say to you before I go. I'll never accept you. Never.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what everyone says. <thought>It looks like I don't have much of a choice... I guess I'll just have to do what I can for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">... I dunno... Should I... Or shouldn't I...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sound like someone's talking to himself, but where's that coming from?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. I guess I better wash that off. That's what I'll do. No, but I can't do that. I'm a detective... ...Argh! My brain! This is driving me nuts! Aaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">P-Please don't whip me like that all of a sudden, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what's up, Gumshoe? Is something on your mind?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-H-How did you know, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-H-How did you know, sir!? Oh! Yeah! I nearly forgot. You can't go through that little gate there, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... You mean the one that says "No Entry" on it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... I... um... kinda already snuck in there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is he trying to be clever or something...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? A kind of... garden-like garden.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A garden?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. Anyway, it's under investigation right now, so keep out! I'm not telling you, I'm asking you, pal! You got me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Isn't it normally the other way around?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, see you later!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Of course! What else would we do? I really want to know what Gumshoe was thinking of washing off!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Strange feeling? Forget about that! What's that strange writing on the stone lantern?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aaah! What are you doing here, sir!? I thought I said you can't come in here!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">B-But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A little lantern, a little statue...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, I know this one! It's... um... It's a ...water bowl, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's true... <thought>I wonder if this has any impact on the case...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm... Well... I, uh... I doused my face earlier with the water in this. I was getting kinda sleepy... Gaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a charm or something poking out from the snow. <thought>It looks pretty old. There's a leather cord tied to it, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Apparently, it belonged to the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. There was a broken leather cord around the lady's neck. The ends of the cords found on both the victim and on this charm match exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This means that this charm definitely belonged to Ms. Deauxnim. This could be a really vital piece of evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are a couple of torches here. I guess you need all the light you can get up here in the mountains.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. I was looking at those things, pal. It looks like they've been lit pretty recently.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">As recent as the night of the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya was training here on the night of the murder... It's not unreasonable to think these things were lit up at the time, I guess.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well, this is odd. There's no snow on the ground here. And it's an almost perfect rectangle. It couldn't have happened naturally.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? No, it wasn't me, sir! It was already like that when my men and I got here to start the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If it wasn't the police, then who did it...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, yeah. There's something I need to tell you. Just between the three of us, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's top secret. You can't tell anyone, got it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, when I was a kid, I got knocked out of the local wrestling contest, you see. I was so disappointed, I just picked up my mouth guard and cried all the way home. Man, I got in so much trouble when I left it on the couch!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's it. Gaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoever cleared the snow away must have had a reason... Although I can't even begin to imagine what that reason could be.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What the heck is that!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Uh-oh... You spotted it, huh, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you kidding me!? It couldn't be more obvious!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. And before you ask, it's written in blood...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So how's the Inner Temple investigation going...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We have the best scientific forensic team in the world working the place!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nothing! Scientifically speaking, the place is as clean as a whistle.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Uh-oh... Well, there were a couple of things that bothered me when I first got here, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">They looked kinda fishy to me. You know, scientifically speaking. So I got the lab boys to look them over. The results were... It's kinda hard to say, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I better look into them myself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, about Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh... Um... Did Mr. Godot tell you yet?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes, we heard.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He's got a search party out looking for her. But there's nowhere else she could have disappeared to on this side of Dusky Bridge. All we can do is wait for Mr. Edgeworth to get here, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He's escorting Iris, the defendant, over here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! I think Mr. Edgeworth wants to talk to you about something too, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh? I wonder what it is...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Just don't be expecting any good news when you talk to him. When I spoke to him, Mr. Edgeworth sounded so down, I felt like I was drowning...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds... pleasant...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Maya"... So these letters are written in blood?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah... What's worse is it's the victim's blood.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!? This is Ms. Deauxnim's blood?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We haven't done a detailed analysis yet, but... it's looking that way, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You know what, that was really bothering me, too. But I just came up with the answer. The result of my own special Gumshoe Investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, on the night of the murder... ...that stone lantern was upside-down!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You must be joking! <thought>That's impossible!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">From the writing in the victim's blood and the other clues left behind... ...it seems pretty likely that this garden was the scene of Ms. Elise Deauxnim's murder. At least, that's our current theory on how the events took place, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So Ms. Deauxnim was killed here...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">However you wanna look at it, that's what people are saying now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then... what Sister Bikini saw in the courtyard at the main temple was... Well, what was it!? If that wasn't the scene of the crime, what did she see?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... What do you think, Ms. von Karmaaaaa!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But wait a sec. The bloody writing and all the other clues here... Someone could've easily set all that up after the murder had taken place, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry, but that's not an option, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why not!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I was overseeing repairs to the bridge the whole time. No one came over here before me and my men. Which means no one could've planted all this stuff here, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh...! <thought>I-I can't think of a counterargument to that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I knew it... I should've washed the blood off the lantern as soon as I got here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If this really was the scene of the crime... ...then I need to figure out exactly what it was that Bikini actually saw!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, look. It's my attorney's badge.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ha ha. Good one, pal. You're always good for a laugh with your little badge. But a real man... A real man has a police badge.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, that looks good. Is it a cough drop? I tell you, pal. I've had a sore throat all day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! No! That's my Magatama! You can't eat it!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>At least he doesn't just put stuff in his mouth first and ask questions later anymore.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know anything about this scroll, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Well, I know it smells great! Yeah, this is just the kind of weather for some steaming mashed potatoes and gravy. I really love that stuff. I eat it so much that my coat even smel-- Aaah!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... N-Not really.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Let's leave it at that, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She sure was a mysterious person. Her real name, her past... It's all a complete mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You know what probably happened? I bet she didn't know her books were gonna be such a success. That's what I think.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I didn't follow the ins and outs of it, but... ...it turned out that this wasn't the murder weapon, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If what Sister Bikini saw is right, then no, it's not. She said the murder weapon was thrust into the victim up to the hilt. But the blood stains on this aren't consistent with her story.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't worry, pal! I'll uncover the real murder weapon. If I haven't turned it up by Spring, you can take my badge!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The case will be long over by then, Gumshoe!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That staff belonged to the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, and apart from the crystal missing from the top, there's nothing wrong with it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, I just remembered something important! This is just between us, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, no. But it's really...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you make of this photo of the crime scene...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's really gruesome... All I gotta say is that the killer is messed up in the head. But it turns out that Shichishito thing wasn't even the murder weapon. So then, why would someone stab it in the victim like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's the mystery we're here to solve...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It was like a circus today in court. All thanks to this little sketch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK, I know Larry's a bit out there... ...but he genuinely wants to help Iris. I'm sure of that. He wouldn't have produced this for no good reason.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This was found close to Dusky Bridge, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's what that artist guy said, yeah. Right after the defendant flew over the burning bridge! According to his testimony, she dropped it when she landed on the other side.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But this crystal didn't belong to Iris.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And there are traces of blood on it, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The real question is what was it doing near the foot of Dusky Bridge...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That thing must've been worn by the victim. There's no other way of looking at it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean, because of the matching leather cord found around the victim's neck?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. I bet it was one of those things she always wore. I've got this safe driving charm I've been wearing for over a year now. If I ever get into an accident, it guarantees it'll be the other guy's fault.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Isn't it supposed to stop you from having an accident in the first place?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The situation hasn't changed. We still don't know anything about Maya's whereabouts. She's gotta be in the Sacred Cavern, though. That's the only place left. I heard it's real cold in there. We've gotta get her out fast, or it could be bad, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't there anything you can do, Detective!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What are you talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We're already on it! You couldn't get a faster response from a computer. Mr. Godot put everything in place right away. That guy doesn't mess around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">G-Godot?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. The coffee-drinking mystery man who didn't show in court. I gotta say. He's totally made me rethink my perception of him, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She cross-examined me once, you know. Yeah. That was us. The big guns locking horns. Witness versus lawyer! It was a battle of cunning tactics and tricks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But the witness isn't supposed to play any tricks...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't believe she's gone...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Apparently, the girl was trapped over here since the night of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did she say anything to you about Maya? She wouldn't tell me...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She's not gonna tell me something if she wouldn't even speak to you, pal. She was real upset. She wouldn't stop crying.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I will... Trust me, I will...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I know. Trust me I already know.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't believe he skipped the trial like that, without even getting permission. He'd have been fired for sure if he worked for a normal company.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Never would've expected the Prosecutor's Office to be so lax...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Of course, being extradited from Hell is a tedious affair. The meticulous regeneration and adjustment of all your internal organs is... Well... Let's just say modern medicine allows us all to live to a ripe old age. Even someone like me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. Why is he hiding that from everyone?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah. Why did he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, you wanna hear something, pal? Come on, I know you do! Maggey says she's gonna buy me a new coat!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? That's great!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. I think it's to say thanks for helping her out during that last case! Which means... I can finally chuck out this stinky, sweat-soaked rag!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Ah, well, I'll be sure to take good care of it once it's retired, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She's a sweet old lady. She doesn't look like the lying type to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But there was a problem with her testimony, wasn't there?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, but I don't think it was her fault. She was just trying to say the right thing, and it came out wrong, that's all. I know what it's like. Happens to me all the time!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I dunno. I'm not so sure anymore. The clues we found today have turned this case all topsy-turvy. I can't see how Iris could've done it now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why does every prosecutor want to burn me at the stake so badly...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He was Ms. Elise Deauxnim's apprentice, or so I heard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well, I suppose you could call him that.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The guy drew a portrait of me, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, lucky you, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, but I had to pay him 50 cents for it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's pretty awful.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... You aren't really enthused about this guy either, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... he made a mockery of the court today. <thought>And I'm almost sure he did it on purpose, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">............ Wow! What a beauty, huh? Gaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">............ That's a real nice broach she's got, too. Gaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gumshoe needs to learn how to give compliments faster than Franziska gives lashes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I haven't seen Mr. Edgeworth for about a year. Talk about a long time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know why he moved overseas?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't know. Probably to look cool.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's a lot of weight attached to doing research overseas, you know. Once I've done my stint in Paris, you'll have to call me Monsieur Gumchaussure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... People really don't get Edgeworth, do they?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about this, Detective Gumshoe? Any thoughts?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah... Well... It's pretty chilly today, huh? My brain doesn't work properly in the cold.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, no. My brain doesn't work properly in the heat. I'm kinda weak in the head.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There are some things you shouldn't advertise, Gumshoe. Especially in front of her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Iris! I'm really glad to see you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Godot managed to mobilize the police by claiming a state of emergency.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Never mind him! We've gotta hurry and unlock the Sacred Cavern...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I'm sorry, Mr. Wright! It's my fault someone so important to you is locked in there... Mr. Edgeworth. Can we finish our conversation later?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Alright. Let's hurry to the Inner Temple then. ...I'll see you later, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, Edgeworth! I'm coming with you guys!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Sorry, Wright. I can't allow you to come with us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I hate to be the one to break it to you, but... ...Maya Fey is in a rather... delicate position.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean by a delicate position...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... This isn't simply a rescue operation, Wright. It's also an investigation. That being the case... we can't allow members of the public to interfere.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">C-Come on, Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If anything happens, you'll be the first to know. ...Please understand, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But it's Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Mr. Wright! All that matters is that Mystic Maya is rescued, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">From now on, consider anything beyond Dusky Bridge to be off limits. We'll be going now... Excuse us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Aaack!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>She's right...</thought> ...Thanks. For reminding me.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sister Bikini looks like she's shrunk some since I last saw her...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">My my my! Hello, you two! How are you doing? Wa ha. Wa ha ha ha ha ha ha! Hmmmaaaaaaaaaaaaah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>From the sound of that sigh, I guess she's still pretty down.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Iris was just here, you know. She was accompanied by that handsome, crimson-clad prince!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is she talking about Edgeworth?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">It was just a courtesy call. I wasn't allowed to talk with her at all. Oh dear. It's all my fault that this has happened. Poor Iris. She was worried about my back, would you believe? What have I done to her...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">... Well, I don't hear anyone else saying that. ... ...... Mr. Blue-Suits doesn't seem to share your opinion, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Me? ...Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh, yes! You did great, Sister Bikini. ...Absolutely spectacular!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">*sniffle* You two are the only ones who've said that to meeee!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't shake the feeling that I just became a shill to a shrew.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sure, she was brave to testify so truthfully like that. But I know she's still hiding something. Guess it's time to break that Psyche-Lock of hers...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, would you mind taking a look at this, Sister Bikini?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Aaaah! Our scroll! Our precious scroll! What on earth have you done to it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no! It wasn't m--</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">You there, Ms. von Karma! Time to take out that whip of yours and teach him a lesson!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Aaaaah!! Someone... Anyone... ...h...e...l...p...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Sister Bikini. Would you mind taking a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Aaaaah! What are you doing with that!? Give it back at once!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't! This is evidence. <thought>This really must be one very important item...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sister Bikini. The truth is becoming increasingly clear to me. I'm convinced that Ms. Elise Deauxnim had a special significance to this temple. As to why she had a special significance, I believe it has to do with her true identity.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">What on Earth are you talking about? She... She was... M-Mystic Elise was an author. Just an author... of picture books.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To be honest... I had my suspicions almost immediately after I met her.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">S-Suspicions?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. But I didn't have any evidence to support my theory, though. But now I do. This piece of evidence proves Ms. Deauxnim's true identity!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Sister Bikini!? What do you have to say to that?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Of course! I don't know why it didn't hit me before. Your heart. It's impure! It's riddled with wickedness and fallacies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">That's why you keep coming up with these funny ideas. I recommend Mystic Elise's book, "The Magic Bottle", for a man in your condition.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"The Magic Bottle"...? I hope it doesn't have a child-proof cap on it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">She was a wonderful author and illustrator... That's all! I swear!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Deauxnim had this charm with her at all times.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Kaaargh! Where did you...!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This isn't some cheap good luck charm, either.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Th-Then... What do you think it is, Mr. Wright? Wh-What could a talisman like that possibly mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a "talisman", is it? Interesting...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oops!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This thing speaks volumes about who Ms. Deauxnim really was. This talisman and one other item unequivocally prove Ms. Deauxnim's true identity!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well!?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">You really ought to think about buying one of the charms we sell here, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Otherwise... You just might find yourself jumped on by a little old lady on a dark mountain path!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What am I doing!? The piece of evidence I need to show Bikini is obvious!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">That's... That's just a plain old good luck charm. So please, just give it back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, no! I don't think so!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The painting is obscured by this gravy stain at the moment...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But this scroll shows the Master of the Kurain Channeling Technique. The crest at the top is a sign of that honorable title. The very same crest that adorns the talisman the victim carried with her!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Aaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This crest is reserved for the Master of Kurain.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Who on Earth told you that nonsense!? I-I've got no idea what you're talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The new Master, Maya Fey, told me!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Wh... WHAT!? Y-You mean that acolyte... is Misty Fey's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Daughter? Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">... Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. In fact, since her first daughter passed away, Maya is Misty Fey's sole successor.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">... ...M... Mystic Mistyyyyyyy!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Mystic Elise graced us with her presence about a week ago. When she showed me the talisman with that mark on it... Well! I nearly fainted! No one had seen her in 17 years. That's when she disappeared.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">The Kurain Talisman? It's the symbol of the Master of Kurain. The bearer must carry it with them always until their death.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So Elise Deauxnim was really Maya's mother, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">... She was Misty Fey, the Master of the Kurain Channeling Technique.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...The truth comes out at last. It looks like we're making some headway here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Because something happened that called her out of hiding.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...W-What happened?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I-It can't be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">E-Earthquake!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh my goodness! The Inner Temple! This kind of tremor might...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">The Sacred Cavern in the Training Hall! It might very well cave in!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WH-WHAT!? MAYA!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, we can't just stand here and do nothing! Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To the Inner Temple, of course! Where else!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sister Bikini! We'll finish this later, alright!?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Of course. You run along now! People may have been hurt. I must get some first aid kits ready.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-Thank you... <thought>Right at that moment, I had the worst feeling in my gut. We just had an earthquake... I wonder if he's alright...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Come on. Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We've gotta hurry to the Inner Temple and...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aah! Wh-What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gurgh... H-How could I have...? ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeooowww! Hey! Why am I the one getting whipped!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sh-She's gone...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>N-No...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The defendant... Iris... She's... gone...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">She fled... She escaped!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... it was just now... during the...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's easy to see Edgeworth's one and only weakness. His fear of earthquakes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I should've known better than to escort the defendant alone! As soon as the ground started shaking, everything went dark before my eyes and... ...I stupidly passed out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That incident... haunts you to this day, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... That's no excuse for letting the suspect get away... I can't believe I let it happen. Wright, the Inner Temple area is a dead end, so she only could've escaped to this side.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then we need to get a manhunt underway now, and search Eagle Mountain from top to bottom!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, Edgeworth. Have you thoroughly checked the Inner Temple yet?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't be ridiculous! Why would I? The Inner Temple is like an island. There's no way to escape but to cross...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, that's not it... Iris isn't the type of person to run away, Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sister Bikini mentioned something when we were with her. She said that the Sacred Cavern might've caved in because of the quake.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Listen, Edgeworth. I'm sure she's at the Inner Temple. A manhunt is not necessary.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's not waste any more time. We need to get to the Training Hall's Sacred Cavern now!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Alright. Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Fortunately, the Sacred Cavern didn't cave in. But... What we found... ...was something none of us would've ever expected.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-How can there be...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-What is the meaning of this...!?</thought> Iris!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Iris! Please tell me! What the hell is going on!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright, is this what Godot was talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah. The trick locks.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, Iris. Please remove these at once.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Umm... Mr. Edgeworth... I'm afraid I can't... It-It's not possible for me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>During the earthquake, when the cavern was in danger of caving in, Iris escaped. And I know that there was only one lock when I last came here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If only I was stronger...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth, how are you feeling? You look a little pale in the face.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Like you're one to talk with your face all green.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't be ridiculous! I'm perfectly finngh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...... ... Understood. I'll handle the investigation in the garden... You take care of things here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Edgeworth...</thought> He's got so much pride that he's probably off crying in a corner of the garden...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I see. Well, thanks for your help. Now then... Do you mind if I ask you a few things, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">No, not at all...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's an antique dresser.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now I know how Maya feels when I tell her not to touch things...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I thought we weren't opening it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, you can do anything... Except stand up to a 9 year old girl.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... This door... When I was here earlier, there was only one lock, but now there's five of them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have. I've seen locks and chains just like these before. They look just like the ones that guard a person's secrets during a Psyche-Lock. I wonder if these locks are guarding something, too. Dark secrets in a dark cavern...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did you make a run for it, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I... I'm sorry. I heard the Inner Temple had been severely shaken by the strong earthquake we had. I... I was so worried. I just had to come and see.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I can't tell you how relieved I was when I saw the Sacred Cavern was alright, but...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Then I saw these chains here. I saw all these extra locks that someone had put on the Sacred Cavern's door, and...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Who in the world would've done something like this?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">These trick locks are a sacred treasure of the Kurain Tradition. There are hundreds of ways to set them. That's why only the person who set the lock can open it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think it's that simple, Franziska von Karma. When we were here the first time, there was only one lock. But now, somehow, there's five of them...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">What does that mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It means that someone wanted to secure the place even more... And they wanted to secure it before you got here, Iris. Presumably because they wanted to make sure Maya couldn't get out. This means that Iris can only open one of these locks. The first one.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... Yes... That's correct.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Iris! Try to think, please! Isn't there any way around this?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... Well, like I said, there are hundreds of different ways to set these locks. I suppose if I went through every combination with each one, I could remove them. But...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes. About a day, if I had to guess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A whole day!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Sure. I'll do whatever I can.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We've got to wait another day? Hang in there, Maya. You're going to have to call on your inner strength now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know what, Iris... There's still one thing I don't quite get.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think it's obvious. Iris, on the night of the murder, where were you?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please, Iris! Don't give me that look! You told us that you were in your room at Hazakura Temple at the time of the incident. But you were seen that same evening at the Inner Temple. And then, you were spotted at the scene of the crime in Hazakura Temple, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Iris? I think it's about time you told us the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I knew it. There's something going on here that we don't know about.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the night of the murder, you were spotted in two very different locations: In Hazakura Temple's courtyard, and in the Training Hall at the Inner Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And yet you claim that you were in your room the entire time. I'm sorry, Iris, but I don't buy your story. It's time you told me the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... I'm sorry, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Truthfully, there's one other thing that's been bothering me. If I can just break this Psyche-Lock... ...I might be able to answer that question as well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you take a look at this for me, Iris? Yeow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's right... I'm going to have to hold off on asking her about things for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">I'm sorry, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The cops are still combing the place. They look pretty nervous... I'd be nervous, too. It's got to be a tough job. Especially with someone giving you the evil eye the whole time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*mutter, mutter* How could I have done that...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow. I can't believe it's still bothering him.</thought> Edgeworth...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aaaah! ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Hey! Don't you dare run away!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...What do you want, Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do I want?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you came here to laugh at me, then get on with it. Go on! Laugh away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sigh* I was ready to hug it out with him, but he's just the same, prideful Edgeworth.</thought> You went back to the Criminal Affairs Department, right? You said you wanted to look into something concerning Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-Yes... ...And thanks to what I found, I was reminded of something terrible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A little lantern, a little statue... It's small, but the whole place is incredibly well-kept.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's just one thing that's troubling me. Everything else is covered in snow or frozen over... ...but the ice in this bowl has been broken by someone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Maybe one of the detectives washed their face in it or something?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't be ridiculous, Wright! No detective would be that careless at a crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's really angry... I'd better not say it was Gumshoe or his salary's gonna pay...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a charm or something poking out from the snow. <thought>It looks pretty old. There's a leather cord tied to it, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It belonged to the victim. We're sure of that now. It's going in the evidence room once the investigation is over, so hands off, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't need to tell me that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, our dear friend Larry just tried to steal it when no one was looking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He probably just wanted something to remember his esteemed teacher by...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are torches of the naked flame variety. I guess you need all the light you can get up here in the mountains.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Accordingly to Detective Gumshoe, they were lit on the night of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Maya was training up here, so there's nothing strange about that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Except... Apparently, they don't light these torches for training sessions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I heard that too much light isn't conducive to spiritual training.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh... I didn't know that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why's this the only area with no snow?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Someone must have cleared it away. What other explanation is there? Of course, I played the "What If?" game as well... But when I asked our trusty bungler, Detective Gumshoe, he said it wasn't him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I suppose Edgeworth has a point... Whoever cleared the snow away must've had a reason to do so. I just can't imagine what that reason could be.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose you've noticed that Maya's name is written on this lantern.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's pretty hard to miss, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's written in Ms. Deauxnim's blood. She was probably forced up against the lantern by the killer. Then with her back against the lantern, she wrote that name with her finger. That's why it's written upside-down.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You think the victim wrote this herself?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Isn't that the obvious conclusion?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But why would she write Maya's name?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I don't think that's something I want to discuss with you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You guys are putting a lot of effort into the investigation of the garden here, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's a high chance this is the actual scene of the crime. That's why.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean because of the writing in blood and the talisman in the snow?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Exactly. As you know, those things couldn't have been planted here after the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But surely... you don't suspect... ...Maya, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... We have to treat everyone as a suspect - Maya, as well as Iris. It's our job, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... I guess you still haven't gotten over your fear of earthquakes...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No... Thankfully, my nightmares have stopped. But still, if the ground gives even the slightest tremor, I find myself short of breath.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...17 years ago... when we were little school kids at the same elementary school... Edgeworth found himself in the middle of a murder...</thought> It all started with that big quake that hit the courthouse...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. I was stuck in the elevator with my father, who was a defense lawyer. We were deprived of oxygen and we passed out. That's when it happened. That single gunshot... shattered my whole life... I lost everything that day... All because of that earthquake. My dreams, my family... and myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... It's been more than 17 years now... And that case was finally resolved 3 years ago, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You think I don't know that!? I was there! But... It was such a shock. I never imagined I could be so wrong about myself and my life... I'm sorry, Wright... There's nothing else I can say. Not after you chose to become a lawyer for my sake... And not after you saved me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Edgeworth... You're stronger than you think, so no more of this self-pity, OK...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There was something that bothered me about her from the moment we met. I felt like I'd seen her somewhere before. No... Wait... Not "somewhere"... I felt like I'd seen her in court before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you went back to the Criminal Affairs Department to look for her file?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. I checked over every case file I've ever worked on. And I was right. I had seen her face before, six years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Six years ago...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was my first appearance in court, and as cases go, it was my worse [sic] nightmare.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So!? Who is she...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I'm sorry, Wright. I can't give that information away to a member of the general public.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!? Why not? It might be the crucial piece of the puzzle that solves this case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The woman I knew was the daughter of a jewelry store owner. She had nothing to do with Iris and Hazakura Temple. And neither did the case. No, that woman is completely unrelated to this murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Unrelated?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. I can say that with complete confidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You're wrong, Edgeworth! She's totally related to this case! I need to fill Edgeworth in. I need to explain the connection between Iris and the woman Edgeworth knew.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is that your attorney's badge? Interesting. I never imagined I'd ever see you wearing one of these, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's because of you that I became one, Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not that I have any regrets. I really don't.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If you're trying to say "thanks", you can start by saying it a bit louder...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Another victim we know nothing about. Same as always. I hope you'll tell me if you know something about our mystery woman, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I know that Elise Deauxnim was no ordinary visitor to the temple. But her true identity could be a useful weapon for the defense. And I can't give that away just like that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Iris gave that to you, didn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, and it really works! It helped my fever go down quicker. I'm sure of it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you say! But your face is as white as a sheet, and sweat is running down your cheek! Anyway, it seems to me like there's something going on between the two of you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Actually... I don't know exactly why, but there's something about Iris that just tugs at me. I can't figure out whether I feel like I know her, or don't know her at all. It's really weird.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Get that piece of filth out of my face!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're still mad, huh, Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I know a thing or two about Larry Butz, just like you. We both know he likes to act up, but this? Even he couldn't make something like this up. If this is what he drew, then... this is what he saw. As unbelievable as it may seem...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know. That's what I think, too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Every time! Every single time I see that guy, he's in it up to his neck!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I knew it. Edgeworth's still mad as a hornet at Larry.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't know Maya Fey very well. But it seems to me that the girl is always landing herself in trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seems to me that you know her better than you think!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I do sincerely hope she's going to be alright...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">One of the biggest names in the world of law, as I'm sure you'll agree. For better or for worse, we were only destined to meet once in the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I know. I read all about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was the first time for the both of us. Two novices, head to head. I can still remember how downhearted I felt after that trial ended the way it did...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if Mia felt the same way, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems Pearl was trapped on this side of the river on the night of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did she tell you anything?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Listen, Wright... She's just a kid. I can't force things out of her. You'll have to be the one to find out what she knows.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He's something of a legend, I hear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't say it like you don't know anything about him! Tell me what you know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a bit strange, actually. If he really was anything special, I should have heard about him by now. I'm always well-informed about the rookies coming into the Prosecutor's Office, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then you mean... ...he isn't anything special?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. You should already know the answer to that. Although, there is one other possibility...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He could have come into the profession from a different channel.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What different channel?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's more than one way to become a prosecutor, Wright. Perhaps he started off as a defense attorney, but decided it wasn't for him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A defense attorney...? <thought>I didn't even know you could switch sides like that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was just with Detective Gumshoe. I treated him to some pasta.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You owe him that much! After all, it's your fault his salary is so low!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">H-How's it my fault?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And look, if you're going to buy the guy lunch, at least get him something decent, OK? Gumshoe practically lives on pasta and noodles already.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well I did order some extra parmesan cheese on top. He was crying tears of joy as he dug into it. It was quite moving.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...All you have to do is give the poor guy a raise...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's crossed my mind once or twice that her testimony might be a bunch of lies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There certainly are a lot of problems with it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The thing is... ...as far as I can tell, she has no reason to deceive us. I believe she did meet the defendant at the Inner Temple, and witnessed the murder, too. The one in the Hazakura Temple courtyard, in any case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Apparently, Iris was taken in by the sisters here at the temple when she was a child. However, we still don't know much about her past, so we're looking into it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This reminds me... Edgeworth went back to the Criminal Affairs Department to look up some stuff on her... I should ask him what he found.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Apparently he had become something of an apprentice to Elise Deauxnim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. Something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He did this portrait for me earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's great...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Let's just leave it at that about Larry, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like someone's still mad at the Butz for his performance in court today.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's been more than a year since I last saw Franziska myself. But it seems that she's been dying to see you again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She really said that...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe she wants to eat you for breakfast! Or to put it another way, whip you silly. Literally and metaphorically.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Go on, let her have her way! It would make for a great anecdote about my trip!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Forget it, Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you want to know how to run the perfect trial, there's a lot to study and learn.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, is that what you're studying about right now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've sat at the prosecutor's bench for trials in five different countries now. The first thing you must do is gain complete mastery of the language. It's quite a task.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd never get anywhere then! It's taken me a lifetime to sort of master one language!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think about this, Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry, Wright... You're a defense attorney, and I'm a prosecutor. It wouldn't be right for us to discuss things so intimately.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But you were acting for the defense in the trial today!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm finally getting to the bottom of this case. I can count on Iris to break those locks, so I should try to gather more clues. From Sister Bikini, Edgeworth, Gumshoe... ...and Pearls...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can see Dusky Bridge from here, and it feels like an unusually long bridge to me. I guess the gorge is too wide to cross with a piece of rope or wire. In other words, no one has crossed it in either direction since the night of the murder. Which means that scene in the Inner Temple's garden couldn't have been set up by someone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's an anchor for one of the wires that used to hold up the bridge. I guess it must have snapped during the fire.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at all the Buddha statues lined up along this path. Looks like one of the cakes someone left as an offering is missing, though. I guess Gumshoe couldn't resist, the poor guy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's something strange about this incinerator. I'm sure there was snow on it the first time I saw it. That, and the door's open. Someone's been burning something, that's for sure. It's a shame there isn't a trace of what it was left inside.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the other side of that little gate is the garden. Edgeworth is probably still in there, crying softly to himself. I guess we better hug it out and talk about what he's uncovered so far.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't read it very well, but I think that sign says, "Inner Temple" on it. Or maybe it says, "Training Hall". No. Maybe it's not that at all. Maybe it says, "The Bridge of Dawn". ... ...I really should get back to work!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya has got to be inside the Sacred Cavern. She's just got to be. I hate feeling so useless. It's driving me nuts. But I need to look for clues so that I'm ready when we finally get her out of there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's weird that there's no one around all of a sudden. It sure gets quiet up here in the mountains when you're all on your own. Speaking of alone... I guess I should go check out the shack just down this path... Maybe I'll find Larry there sulking again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That thing looks like it's ready to collapse... At least more than it did before. According to Bikini, Eagle Mountain is very prone to earthquakes. I had a feeling something bad was going to happen, and sure enough, it did. Yup. Edgeworth definitely couldn't live up here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder if Sister Bikini has gone back to the Main Hall already. I haven't seen Gumshoe around for a while, either. Maybe they're having a cup of tea together somewhere. I bet Gumshoe is Sister Bikini's type.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is one impressive gate. It's pretty grand for something that belongs to a branch family of the clan. I bet they make an exorbitant amount of money here. I mean, that whole Special Course thing has got to be good business! ... Ack! Noooo!! I'm starting to think like Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can see the Main Hall from here. Sister Bikini should be back by now. We were interrupted earlier by the earthquake. I think I should go pick up our conversation where we left off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a quaint, little bell tower. I never would've thought that something this horrible was about to happen... ...when Iris rang the lights out bell that night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder what this thing was used for on the night of the murder... There is only one key to this snowmobile, and Iris is the one who had it. So I have to wonder if it was her... ...But she says she never left Hazakura Temple that night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like Sister Bikini is not here. She must be sorting things out after the quake. Must be hard on her with her bad back. There are a few things I really need to discuss with her. Guess I'll drop by again later and see if she's around.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls! What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">N-Nothing... What about Mystic Maya!? Is she alright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Well... We don't know yet.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey! What do you think you're doing here, Nick!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">This is the losers' shack, where losers get together to lose themselves!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the what...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey, we find comfort in each other's failures, OK? You got a problem with that?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Look, Mr. Nick. Mr. Laurice did a picture of me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's, um... great, Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">We're going to gather firewood now. We'll be cooking some half-rotten potatoes over a miserable little camp fire. So stay out of our way!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't believe this... Why can't he try getting fired up over becoming a better man?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">No one believes a word I say anymore. Listen to me, Pearl. You don't wanna trust this kind of guy, OK? He'll only let you down!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... Oh, Mystic Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry, is there something you want to tell me about this picture?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Heh! I've got nothing to say to you, Nick! My life's here now, with Pearl. Two losers cooking potatoes together forevermore!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What am I going to do with him...?</thought> Alright then. What do you think about this picture, Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... I think it's really well drawn! I can't draw at all, so I think it's really amazing.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">See! Someone appreciates it! It's tough getting the flames to look like that, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It's supposed to be Sister Iris flying through the air, isn't it? I love it! It's like a dream. A wonderful fantasy.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">No, no, no! It wasn't a dream! She really flew! I'm telling you, Iris really flew that night.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But Mr. Laurice...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">*sigh* Not you too... Please don't look at me like that, Pearl... Don't look at me like I'm some kind of nutcase. I beg of you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess this picture really is a representation of what Larry thinks he saw...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">OK, so I was half asleep when I was here that night. But I was wide awake after the lightning struck! And I saw what I saw! It was exactly like I drew in the picture.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And it looks like I don't have any choice but to take this sketch at face value...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey! What's with the look of doubt on your face!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm, Pearls...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Y-Yes, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've been meaning to ask you about the night of the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Where were you, and what exactly were you doing when it all happened?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I, um... I... I was just... Well... I'm just a kid, you know. I-I'm sure it doesn't really matter wh-what I was doing, d-d-does it, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, Pearls... But yes, it does. On the night of the murder... ...you were supposed to be in Ms. Deauxnim's room, reading a book together. But... Ms. Deauxnim was murdered, and you, Pearls, were at the Inner Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just what exactly happened that night, Pearls...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... I'm really sorry, Mr. Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... I've been a bad girl. I know I'll be punished.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you talking about, Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">My spiritual power... It has disappeared.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What? Her powers have disappeared...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come on, Pearls. You can tell me. What happened to you on the night of the murder? Why were you found taking refuge at the Inner Temple today?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... I...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow. It must be a really big secret she's hiding.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean your power has disappeared, Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... It's... It's all over for me. A spirit medium who can't channel spirits is... like a painter who can't paint.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey! What are you looking at me for!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls. Did you try to channel someone's spirit right here at Hazakura Temple? Tried but failed, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah... Waaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Way to go, Nick! You made her cry! That's... That was really c-cruel of you... Waaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just as I thought... I'm going to have to break her Psyche-Lock to get the truth out of her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Pearls...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...It's no good. She's in no condition to look at anything for me right now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well!? What's the damage!? How is the Sacred Cavern!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like it survived. But we have a bigger problem now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I told Sister Bikini all about it... About the five locks that were stopping us from getting inside the Sacred Cavern.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">... But who... who could've done that...? The only people who know how to set those trick locks are those of the Kurain Tradition.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We have Iris at the Sacred Cavern, trying her best to open them for us right now. Actually, there's something I've been meaning to talk with you about, Sister Bikini.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh, yes. We were in the middle of a chat, weren't we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. You were telling me how the Master of Kurain disappeared 17 years ago. I want to know why Misty Fey suddenly appeared at this temple.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">It was about a week ago when Mystic Elise... No, I mean Mystic Misty, arrived. After she showed me the talisman that proved she was the Master, she said... "Someone is trying to destroy the Kurain Tradition's main family line. I am here to put a stop to them."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Someone was trying to destroy the main family line?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">There is only one heir to the title of "Master" at any time, and it's usually the eldest. That child becomes the new Master of Kurain, and her daughters, the main family. All other mediums become branch family members, with no hope of controlling the clan. That's why nothing has changed throughout the history of the clan... Branch families always have and always will plot to erase those of the main family line.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>Is the power of the Master worth this much bloodshed...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, would you mind taking a look at this, Sister Bikini?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Aaaah! Our scroll! Our precious scroll! What on earth have you done to it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no! It wasn't me! I swear! <thought>But who did this, and why would anyone want to cover this thing in gravy? More importantly, does this have anything to do with the case...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">So... This young lady is the new Master...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. Maya Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh dear, oh dear... If I'd known who she was... I would've prepared a feast, not a boring old pot roast and some gravy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Once we get her out, you can give her all the feasts you want.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Of course! You just make sure you get her out, alright? She's the Master! You just have to rescue her!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Ah... This poor little girl...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>First I lost Maya, and now Pearls... How much more pain is this case going to cause me!? Urgh... Not to mention this fever is giving me a killer migraine...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">How... How can I ever make up for this...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Make up for what?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">For allowing harm to come to such an important person!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sister Bikini must feel really responsible for what happened... Ms. Deauxnim was the Master after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">When I think about it, I do kind of feel sorry for Mystic Morgan. It wasn't her fault that her sister was a more powerful spirit medium. Mystic Morgan just couldn't compete with her sister. It must have been really tough on her...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even so... That doesn't excuse all the things she did.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">... No... Of course not.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Iris had a twin sister... That's really all I know about her. That and the fact that she was taken away from her mother by her jeweler father. I don't have any idea where she is or what she's doing now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I could tell her... But she'd probably have a coronary and a half...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">You believe in the Technique, don't you Mr. Wright? You know its power is real...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... I do...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's been three years since I first met Maya. In that time, I've seen her channel the spirits of the dead plenty of times. During the MaskDeMasque case, and during Maggey Byrde's trial, too. Thanks to Maya, Mia's always on hand to help me out when I need her the most.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">The Kurain Technique has made a huge difference to the world, you know. I mean, the ability to commune with the dead... That's true psychic power, you know. Members of the Tradition have always been there, behind every important leader. Who wouldn't respect such a tremendous skill?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I suppose so, but... With all that power and influence, I kind of expected you'd be really rich by now...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Are you saying we're poor, Mr. Wright? Ho ho ho! You're very direct, aren't you? People don't believe in it anymore, you see. All because of one little mistake...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A mistake? What mistake?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">It was 17 years ago. That's when everything came crashing down. All because of that incident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"That incident"? Is she talking about what I think she is...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I'm sure the records still exist if you're interested. Locked up, of course. It was called the "DL-6 Incident". That's the name of the file.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The DL-6 Incident, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The DL-6 Incident... ...I know it well. I handled a related case just three years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...! Ah! That's right... So it was you who was the defense attorney on that case...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A murder that took place 17 years ago...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">It was the first time in the country's history the police ever used a spirit medium. The idea was to channel the victim's spirit to learn the identity of the murderer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And the medium who performed the channeling was Misty Fey, Maya's mother.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Through Mystic Misty's channeling, the name of a certain man surfaced. Armed with that as evidence, the investigators were spurred into action...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that man... He was found not guilty, wasn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...That's right. He was. And the case remained a mystery... In other words, we failed. It was the first case the world had ever seen the Kurain Tradition openly involved in. It was all over the media. The public, the judiciary, the people of Kurain Village... Everyone judged her. Everyone said Mystic Misty's powers were a sham. And then she just disappeared; vanished, while everyone still thought of her as a fraud.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I know the truth! Misty Fey's spirit channeling wasn't a sham at all!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Of course it wasn't... And since you managed to reveal the truth, we're finally making a comeback. The Kurain Tradition is starting to recover at last. But with a new Master wielding the power of the clan...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Does she mean Maya!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">The spiritual power of the Kurain Channeling Technique is in the blood.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya's told me the exact same thing before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">We, the women of the Fey family, have always been spirit mediums. It's because the power to communicate with spirits flows strongly through us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>According to Maya, only the women in the family can inherit that power.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">The main family's bloodline stems directly from Mystic Ami. But with each new generation, only one daughter becomes the new Master.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the ones who don't become branch families, right?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">That's right. And it's always the cause of tragedy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... You know, Maya had a sister, too. An older sister named Mia...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh yes. I've heard of her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!? You know about Mia!?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Of course. She became a lawyer in the hopes of discovering what happened to her mother.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And lost her life as a result...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Do you know what Mystic Mia is rumored to have said? She said it wasn't only because of her mother that she became a lawyer... She also didn't want to fight with her sister over the leadership of the Tradition.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really...!?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well, she saw what happened to her own mother, Mystic Misty, as she grew up. I guess Mystic Mia got tired of seeing all the rivalry between her mom and her aunt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's right. Misty Fey had an elder sister, too. And Misty, having superior powers, managed to usurp the Master's seat from her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Mystic Misty's sister is Mystic Morgan, as you probably know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Morgan? There's a name I know well. It was a year ago now, at Maya's home, Kurain Village. What she did was terrible. It was all so she could make her own daughter the next Master.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I suppose if you know about Mystic Morgan's daughter... ...then you must've already realized that Iris...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Iris...? <thought>What's Iris got to do with any of this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">That Iris is Mystic Morgan's daughter...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh... IRIS IS WHAT!? <thought>Is she kidding me!? Iris is Morgan Fey's daughter!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you just say that Iris is Morgan Fey's daughter?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oops! I thought you already knew! It sounded like you'd met one of Mystic Morgan's daughters already.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I have. I know her very well.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. Pearls. Pearl Fey. But I always thought she was an only child.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">... You jest! That child... She's Mystic Morgan's... ............ I had no idea... ............ ...Mystic Morgan... But she's in prison now, isn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. Ever since she was found to be a co-conspirator in a murder case last year. It was all done to set Pearls up as the next Master.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I see. So I've been wrong all this time. Mystic Morgan had three daughters, not two.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaa!? ...Th-Three?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Yes. Iris, her twin sister, and Mystic Pearl.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAT!? Tw-Twin sister?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh, didn't you know? It all happened twenty years ago... After the clan leadership was taken from her by her sister, Mystic Morgan's life crumbled. It wasn't many years later that Kurain's reputation hit an all-time low. When Mystic Morgan's husband realized his wife would never become the Master... ...he left her and the village, taking their twin daughters with him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How awful...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">He was a jeweler, you know. In the end he remarried, and that's when it happened. He decided to give one of his girls up, to be looked after by us here at the temple. That was Iris, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's unbelievable! If Iris has a twin sister... Could it be...?</thought> Um, could you tell me one more thing, Sister Bikini? What was the name of Iris's sister?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">............ I'm sorry, Mr. Wright. I just can't remember. All I can recall is that her father was a jeweler.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, that's a clue, I guess. Hmm... A jeweler...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Yes, that's right... No doubt it was all because of Mystic Morgan's anger towards the main family...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anger? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Her twin daughters were taken from her by her jeweler husband. But even that couldn't destroy her dream that a child of hers would one day lead the clan.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's why she had Pearls?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">It seems that the incident here was a result of Mystic Morgan's anger. It was able to break free of the bars that confine her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So Iris has a twin sister... The plot thickens... But this information will be useless unless I can flesh it out a bit. I need to ask more questions, and get some more info!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... I was expecting Larry and Pearls to be here. I guess they must've gone to collect firewood. I suppose I'll have to check back later.</line>
<line speaker="???">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like someone's happy. What tune is that they're humming...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No motive, no crime. No motive, no crime. Sing it with me - No motive, no crime! ...I remember, when we use to search... in the Channeling Room in Kurain... Whoop! I love my job! Who cares if the clues I find are no good? That's not what investigating's all about! The investigator investigates for the love of investigating! It's a passion! Good cases we have, good cases we've lost... Along the way...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I would have never guessed that Gumshoe was into reggae.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Every case is gonna be air tight... Every case is gonna be air tight... Hey, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Who, me?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">How long have you been there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I just got here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Oh, OK.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what are you up to, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm investigating, pal. I made a promise to Mr. Edgeworth. I promised I would find the real murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The real murder weapon...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That barbed sword thing turned out to be a false lead, right? I'm giving it my best shot here, but I still haven't turned up any clues. I just found these weird scraps of paper. It looks like a letter or something. It doesn't seem to have anything to do with the case, though...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A letter?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So how's the investigation going, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't know if I should be telling you, pal. But I guess it can't hurt. Looks like the murder took place in the Inner Temple garden. And they're taking that bloody writing on the lantern pretty seriously back at HQ.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!? You mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't have the details, pal. All I know is, if you don't find Maya down in that Sacred Cavern... ...we're gonna be faced with one ugly situation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What kind of ugly situation are we looking at here...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... You got me! I don't know. They're not my words, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then who said it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Godot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Godot!? <thought>What did he mean by that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About that letter you found...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't remind me, pal! I'm busting a gut here trying to find the murder weapon... ...and all I find is some burnt up old letter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Burnt up old letter?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. It was in that incinerator right outside the Inner Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The incinerator!? <thought>I knew it! I knew I wasn't imagining it! There was snow on the incinerator when I first saw it. But after the incident, the snow had melted away. Which means someone used the incinerator on the night of the murder.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What's up with you, pal? I've got it right here if you wanna take a look.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">C-Can I...? Do you mind?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure, go nuts! I don't want it, pal. You can have it. It's all spirit mediums and Masters and stuff. I bet it's got no relation to the case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Spirit mediums!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's got to be important if it mentions spirit mediums and Masters. I'd better give it a good looking over and some serious thought...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Make sure you chuck it in the trash when you're done. Littering's a crime, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what do you know about the real murder weapon so far?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well it wasn't the Shichishito that was found impaled in the victim's body. Mr. Edgeworth proved that in court today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">In which case, it must've been another blade.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's what you're running around like a headless chicken looking for now, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. And man, is it tiring work! But let me tell you something, pal... I'm no chicken. We've got the feather of forensics in our cap these days. We're using the department's secret weapon on this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Secret weapon...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this secret weapon of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You wanna know? You've gotta think scientifically, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The murder weapon was a sword. Swords are, scientifically speaking, made of metal, right? Any questions so far?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No. <thought>I know what he's gonna say, but I'll let him look smart.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So what's the perfect tool for the job!? Ta-da! A metal detector!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Raise your hand if you didn't see this coming from a mile away...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well? You wanna give scientific investigation a go?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? M-Me?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I've been using this thing for hours now. It gets pretty boring after a while. Why don't you give it a try?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't know... Should I help Detective Gumshoe out, or not?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Come on, pal. It's good fun, I'm telling you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No. I, um... I've actually gotta be someplace...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, really? That's too bad. I'll just take a break by myself for a while, then. I'm gonna get you to do this somehow, pal! You'll see!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I thought you liked doing field work! Isn't that what you were just singing about!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know anything about this scroll, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Well, I know it smells great! Yeah, this is just the kind of weather for some steaming mashed potatoes and gravy. Oh! And weenies! Mashed potatoes with gravy and weenies! Potatoes and weenies are the two greatest foods invented by man. A dream combination! Although, I can't afford to try them together yet. It's an unfulfilled dream...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... I was hoping you'd have more to say about the scroll and less about the gravy...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, sorry. Nah, I can't tell you much about that scroll, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Why do I bother anymore?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She sure was a mysterious person. Her real name, her past... It's all a complete mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not quite. She was Maya's mother. But Gumshoe doesn't know that yet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Just like every other case, huh? Always a mystery!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That staff belonged to the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, and apart from the crystal missing from the top, there's nothing wrong with it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, I just remembered something important! This is just between us, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-OK... What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I've never told anyone this before... It's a secret. I... I actually wanted to be a wizard when I was a kid.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, that's it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... How did the crystal sphere get separated from the staff? And what was it doing near the foot of Dusky Bridge...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It was like a circus today in court. All thanks to this little sketch. You want my advice? You should ignore it, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, I know Larry's a bit out there. But he wouldn't just draw something like this as a joke.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Then I guess I should start getting hyped for tomorrow's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Seeing you trying to explain that thing... I wouldn't miss it for the world, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Maybe he's right. Maybe I should just ignore this useless piece of graffiti.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This was found close to Dusky Bridge, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's what that artist guy said, yeah. Right after the defendant flew over the burning bridge! According to his testimony, she dropped it when she landed on the other side.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But this crystal didn't belong to Iris.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There are traces of blood on it too, you know, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The real question is what was it doing near the foot of Dusky Bridge...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The girl was trapped over at the Inner Temple since the night of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did she say anything to you about Maya? She wouldn't tell me...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She's not gonna tell me something if she wouldn't even speak to you, pal. She was real upset. She wouldn't stop crying.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That guy's got more mysteries than a Choose Your Own Escapade book, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I know. Trust me.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't believe he skipped the trial like that, without even getting permission. He'd have been fired for sure if he worked for a normal company.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know where he is now?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nah. But I bet he's walking around somewhere with a mug of coffee in one hand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, I should've figured... It looks like Gumshoe doesn't know about Godot's physical condition...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Of course, being extradited from Hell is a tedious affair. The meticulous regeneration and adjustment of all your internal organs is... Well... Let's just say modern medicine allows us all to live to a ripe old age. Even someone like me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He had a good reason for missing the trial. So why didn't he tell anyone about it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, you wanna hear something, pal? Come on, I know you do! Maggey says she's gonna buy me a new coat!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? That's great!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. I think it's to say thanks for helping her out during that last case! Which means... I can finally chuck out this stinky, sweat-soaked rag!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She's a sweet old lady. She doesn't look like the lying type to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But there was a problem with her testimony, wasn't there?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, but I don't think it was her fault. She was just trying to say the right thing, and it came out wrong, that's all. I know what it's like. Happens to me all the time!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I dunno. I'm not so sure anymore. The clues we found today have turned this case all topsy-turvy. I can't see how Iris could've done it now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What clues are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I dunno if I should be telling you, pal. But I guess I can let you in on it. The fact that the Inner Temple Garden was the crime scene. And... that bloody writing. However you look at it, Maya Fey's the only person who... ... Hey! Quit giving me that evil stare, would you? You look just like Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It wasn't Maya! There is no way it could've been her!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I knew I shouldn't have said anything.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, speaking of Ms. von Karma, what's she up to...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She's keeping an eye on Iris at the Inner Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, really!? Phew! I can relax at last; now that you've lost her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She has a real thing for hitting you with that whip of hers, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, but I'm kinda getting used to it... which scares me a lot. Oh! So this one time, she forgot her whip at home or something...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And...? Tell me you were able to have a violence-free day.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nah. She slapped me instead. I prefer the whip. Getting slapped all day makes you look like such a loser.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And being whipped doesn't?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I haven't seen Mr. Edgeworth for about a year. Talk about a long time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know why he moved overseas?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't know. Probably to look cool.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's a lot of weight attached to doing research overseas, you know. Once I've done my stint in Paris, you'll have to call me Monsieur Gumchaussure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>People really don't get Edgeworth, do they?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I've seen this lady someplace before. ............ Isn't she that jaw-droppingly large strawberry desert woman? Oh, yeah! She's Pearl Fey's mother, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She was involved in that incident in Kurain Village last year, wasn't she? ... Hey! She was the one who did it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why doesn't he think his whole thought through BEFORE opening his mouth!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, that was one ugly case, huh, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Was"? I don't know... The more we look at this case, the more I feel like that one never ended...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She's locked up safe in solitary confinement at the detention center, though... At least we can rule her out of this case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about this, Detective Gumshoe? Any thoughts?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah... Well... It's pretty chilly today, huh? My brain doesn't work properly in the cold.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Perhaps we'll just have to wait until Summer when it's warmer?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, no. My brain doesn't work properly in the heat. I'm kinda weak in the head.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There are some things you're better off not advertising, Gumshoe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Come on, pal. It's good fun, I'm telling you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright, then... I guess I'll give it a go...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Like I said, this is the department's most advanced gadget. The absolute best! It's so sensitive, you could make it cry! It's so hi-tech, you could sky dive off it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, bother.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So, now I'm gonna tell you how to use it. It's possible the real murder weapon is around here somewhere, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure. That's what we're trying to find out.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Right. So first, let's turn the detector on. That's the sound of the metal detector's signal bouncing off of something metallic. Next, touch the detector and take a real good look around this courtyard with it, pal. Once you've hit something metallic, the CHECK gauge will flash. And when that happens, touch the gauge to really give the area a good, hard stare. This thing picks up metallic objects that are hidden from sight, too... Take a good look at anything and everything that seems suspicious, OK pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is there something up on the eaves?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't tell from here, pal. ...Meh, just forget about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But it's right under Elise Deauxnim's window! And it's the perfect spot for hiding something long and thin like a sword!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... I'll go take a look. Ah, it was nothing, thank goodness. Someone just dropped a spoon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why are you so happy about that...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, imagine if the murder weapon had turned up there... It'd make me look pretty dumb, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...At least he recognizes that much.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's just a pair of skis. Nothing useful for our case here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm actually pretty good on skis you know, pal. I just love to fly down the slopes with my coat fluttering in the wind!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? I had no idea. How good are you, then?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well... I'm better on skis than I am on skates. But not as good as when I'm on a snowboard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's a pretty detailed answer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! But you know what I'm best at? Making mashed potatoes and gravy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>The guy's losing it. Must be the altitude. We'd better get back to the investigation...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's odd. This sled's made of plastic...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It says, "Bikini #1" on the side...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe there's something under it...</thought> Hey, what's this? A-A badge...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah-haaaaaa! I've been hunting high and low for that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-It's yours, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That thing's priceless to a guy like me, pal. A cop can't be a cop without his badge! I'm sure glad I put that dime in there now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How did you manage to drop your badge here, of all places!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I know! I bet it happened this morning. I was playing around with the sled and...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Stop right there. I don't need to hear any more.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Look, a ladder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a "step"-ladder.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What's the difference? Looks like a normal ladder to me, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Surely everyone knows the difference... I mean, they're pretty ordinary objects...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I've met plenty of guys like you, always picking on the smallest details. The vegetable store guy near my place does it all the time. He even corrects me when I ask for a head of lettuce. "That's a cabbage," he says. I'm telling you, they're the exact same thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No they're not! They're completely different!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You have to plant both of them firmly in the ground before they can grow, don't you? Listen. You gotta take a step back and look at the bigger picture sometimes. Otherwise you could miss a really important clue. That's advice from a pro, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...The last person I need advice from is this guy in front of me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be an old pan handle or something.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-How do you know that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh, what?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That was my nickname in junior high.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What, "pan handle"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I didn't have much money back then, pal. I used to bum stuff off the other kids sometimes, so they called me "Panhandler".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... "Panhandler", huh? I can see that.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Thinking back, it's actually kind of a nice memory now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This looks like... a wallet?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah-haaaa! That's where it's been!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is it yours, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm always dropping it, so I put a bell on it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you still dropped it anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, but now I found it again, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Your wallet is completely empty.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I drop it all the time, so I don't put money in it anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Then how come the metal detector picked it up...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Must be because of the bell, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, I found a dollar coin.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? M-Money!? If you find money, you have to turn it in to the police. Or a detective. If the owner doesn't come forward within six months, you get to keep 10 percent! The other ninety percent goes to m... I mean, to the Police Department.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Don't get so close to me, Detective. Give me some space, will you!? Here's the coin. Happy?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... I definitely made the right decision becoming a detective.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yikes... Talk about a serious case of denial...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this...? A pen?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! I've been looking all over for that, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? It's yours?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. My old man gave it to me when I qualified as a detective. He told me it'd be good for sticking in suspects' faces.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That makes you detectives sound really nasty.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's my dream to stick it in your face one day, Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Then don't go losing it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That Shichishito next to the golden statue wasn't the real murder weapon, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I know. I just thought I'd check it again anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, yeah! That reminds me! Do you know about that sword? It's supposed to represent the multiple branches that life can take, all ending as one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. I heard something about that.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You know what I think about sometimes? What kind of life I'd be leading had I not joined the Homicide Division.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You think about that kind of stuff, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course I do. I think about it a lot. Me as a traffic cop. Me as a detention officer. Me as the Blue Badger...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...There's something to be said about the humor value of Gumshoe as the Blue Badger.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like there's something round buried in the ground here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't touch that, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's a trap! People set them out to catch us detectives. They're real nasty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A trap... for detectives? You mean like those fierce traps with sharp teeth that are supposed to snag your leg?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah! Those! I got my finger caught in one of those once.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Your finger?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There was this bit of cheese, and it looked so tasty. I reached out, and then... bam!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I'm not sure I know how to respond to a story as stupidly pitiful as that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is Ms. Deauxnim's staff, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Scientifically speaking, they're usually made of wood.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the detector is reacting to it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, but however you look at it, the thing's made of wood, alright? I don't bother investigating anything unless it looks like it might be metallic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Isn't the whole point of a metal detector to find metal where you can't see it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's weird that this thing is causing a racket...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here, let me take a look at it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! Hands off! Examining evidence is a job for the...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! The top is coming off!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Look what you've done! You've damaged a really important piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Th-That's a...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A... A sword...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Inside the staff...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is this... Could it be...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...The murder weapon!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... It doesn't look like there's anything here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal! You've gotta watch the CHECK gauge and wait for it to flash, OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Alright, already... I'm not exactly a wiz at machinery, you know...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd never have guessed there'd be a sword concealed in the victim's staff.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">They call this kind of thing a sword-cane, pal. This one's a real gem... The workmanship is really something else! Thank goodness it wasn't a cane-sword, or else the victim would've stabbed her own foot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I officially give up on trying to figure out how Gumshoe's mind works. If the real scene of the crime was the Inner Temple Garden... Then why was the sword used to kill the victim found in the Main Hall Courtyard?</thought> Hey, Gumshoe... Who knows about the hidden sword?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No one. Even the police didn't know about this until I discovered it just now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, as they say, there's no "Team" in "Gumshoe".</thought> It doesn't look like there are any traces of blood on it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Then I guess this isn't the murder weapon, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, no! I'm sure someone just wiped it off after the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Yeah, of course! This thing's definitely the murder weapon! Great job, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's about the same length as the Shichishito, too. This must be the murder weapon!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait up, Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? What is it, pal? I'm a pretty busy guy right now, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're going to get that staff analyzed, right? Would you mind holding off for just a while?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? What are you talking about, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please! Just until we find Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Maya? What's this got to do with her?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know, but I'm starting to get a really bad feeling in the pit of my stomach.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh? How so?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, Maya's trapped inside the Sacred Cavern right now and... Well, we don't even know if she's OK or not... The more evidence and testimony I hear, the more uneasy I feel.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-You don't think...? Maya's been murd--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please, Detective! Let's just wait until we can get inside the Sacred Cavern.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You're... looking kinda viridian there...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OK, OK. Just stop it with that face, pal. One thing, though... This staff's secret trick... Let's keep it between you and me, alright? If it gets out that we knew about it and didn't say anything, we're finished.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is just a regular, run-of-the-mill staff, you got it? ...OK, now you take good care of it, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Don't worry... She'll be fine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gumshoe...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You know, there's a place at the base of this mountain that has some really good pasta. How about I take you there when you find Maya, huh, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure... Thanks...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't help but wonder, though... What was Elise Deauxnim doing with a staff like this in the first place...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I still can't believe it, pal! I'd never have guessed there was a sword in that thing. Sure, there isn't any blood left on it, but... ...there's a good chance this is the murder weapon, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But this is Ms. Deauxnim's staff, right? That would mean she was killed with her own weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... I guess so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And there's something else that's bothering me, too.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh? What's that, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Deauxnim was an author and an illustrator, right? So what was she doing carrying a sword around with her?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... That's a good question. And there's gotta be a good answer to it, I guess. Good luck finding it, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I'm beginning to see why he receives the salary he does.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Edgeworth... Did you know that Iris had a twin sister...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">WHAT!? A-A twin...? You can't be serious!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sister Bikini told me. But... The problem is, she didn't know the name of this twin.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There was nothing about Iris having a sister in the files I checked.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Iris was taken in by the temple when she was really young. Apparently her sister was raised by her father. A jeweler, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A jeweler!? ... Wright, I... I might just know who this twin sister of hers is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I had a feeling you'd say that. Let me guess... Her name is Dahlia Hawthorne, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Yes, exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please tell me what you know about her, Edgeworth... Please.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was my first court case, six years ago. I was a greenhorn, and due to my inexperience, the defendant died.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're talking about Terry Fawles, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...! Y-You know about that case...!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're not the only one who noticed something about Iris and Dahlia Hawthorne. I checked one of Mia's old files from six years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, Dahlia was a key witness in that case. Dahlia and Terry Fawles conspired together to stage a fake kidnapping 11 years ago. They stole a jewel worth 2 million dollars from Dahlia's father, a jeweler. And five years after that... ...she murdered her own sister, Valerie Hawthorne, to keep her from talking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Her sister?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, her stepsister, actually. They weren't blood-related. Valerie was the only daughter of Dahlia's father's second wife.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... <thought>And this is when she entered my life... The woman who tried to kill me.</thought> So after Terry Fawles died, what happened to Dahlia? Did you check that out?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... There is no need. Like I said, Dahlia isn't connected with this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why are you so sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's simple. Dahlia Hawthorne is dead.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, her metabolic processes are a matter of interest only to historians, so to speak.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean by, "Dahlia Hawthorne is dead", Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I only just discovered this, Wright, but... I never knew about the murder case you were involved in during your college years.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Dahlia Hawthorne was found guilty... ...thanks to the persistence of Mia Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">... ...Grr... Nngghh... Hnnn... MIA FEY...! MIA... FEYYYY...!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>At the time... Dahlia... It's like she was possessed by a demon or something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's been six years since that guilty verdict was handed down... ...and her sentence was finally carried out. She was executed... last month.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Executed?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sure that's a bit of a shock for you, Wright. And for more reasons than one. But do you understand now? She can't possibly be connected with this case. She's dead, and once someone is dead, there is no way to revive them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>There's no way to revive the dead...? Hmm... I wonder...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what is that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's about Iris and Dahlia Hawthorne's mother.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's their mother got to do with any of this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She's Morgan Fey. A spirit medium from a branch family of the Kurain Channeling Technique.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Did you say, "Kurain Channeling Technique"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Do you know something about it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh, yes. I know it's connected with that fraudulent spirit medium!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Fraudulent...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was involved in another nightmare, 17 years ago. I was caught up in the middle of a murder investigation. The police didn't have any leads. They were stumped... And that's when they called her in. She was a very famous spirit medium and the "Master" of her channeling school. But you know what happened? As a result of her efforts, an innocent man was accused of murder! She and her powers! They were all fraudulent!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Go to the Police Records Room. It's all in there. All you have to do is check the DL-6 Incident case file and you'll know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Of course... How could I forget... Edgeworth was the victim in that case.</thought> Edgeworth... You'll understand someday... And then, you'll see that the Kurain Channeling Technique is real...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think it's time you told the truth about what you were doing on that night.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You said you were in your room at Hazakura Temple the entire time. Do you still claim that to be the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes... That's where I was.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Iris... I believe you're innocent. That's why I want to believe what you're telling me, too. But I can't. Because this person saw you somewhere else on the night of the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Iris!? I trust you, so you need to trust me.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But, Mr. Wright... I can't.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I can't trust such random nonsense! It doesn't make any sense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oops. Looks like I screwed up there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm talking about Sister Bikini, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Sister Bikini...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Her testimony in court today was very clear.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">That night I was helping an acolyte with her training in the Inner Temple. But... Well, as you can see, my back likes to act up. Violently. So, I left Iris to help the acolyte, and returned to Hazakura Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sister Bikini didn't just see you, she spoke with you. You two talked about Maya's training that night. So you see, Iris... ...you were there at the Inner Temple on the night of the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's... very impressive, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">The acolyte's actual training was due to start after 10 o'clock that night. I left the Main Hall early, so I wouldn't be late.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What time was that?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Let me see... It takes about 20 minutes to walk between the Main Hall and the Inner Temple. So, I would've left at about 9:40 PM, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I'm sorry, Iris, but lying just doesn't suit you.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, you say you left the Main Hall at 9:40 PM, but what you say doesn't add up with this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Iris">I'm sorry, Mr. Wright... But mistakes just don't suit you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I had hoped you would get at least this much correct. I hate seeing you mess up and getting all disappointed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nngh... I didn't know she could be so harsh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Iris, what are you trying to hide...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The more you lie about it, the more I know it's got to be something really important.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You yourself testified to the contrary, don't you remember? You said you rang the lights out bell at 10 o'clock that night.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Plus, only moments before you rang that bell... ...you were seen at the Main Hall by the most reliable witness I have.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Who's that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We even spoke a little that evening. That's when you gave me this. Surely you haven't forgotten?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... N-No... That's right. I remember...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that brings us to another puzzling fact, Iris. At 10 o'clock on the night of the murder... ...you were seen in two different places at the same time!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's time you told me exactly what's been going on, Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So far, I've managed to prove two things. First, on the night of the incident, you were at the Inner Temple. And second, at the exact same time, you were ringing the bell at Hazakura Temple! There's only one possible explanation for this apparent impossibility!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is only one of you, Iris. You couldn't possibly have been in two places at once. That being the case, you were probably really at...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's what I wanted to ask you. What was that "probably" you just came out with?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, umm... Well... The problem is, you spoke to witnesses at both the Main Hall and the Inner Temple. It's kind of hard to disprove either sighting, but...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's no position for a lawyer to find himself in, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No... <thought>She got me there!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">It seems to me like there just isn't a solution to this puzzle. It's probably best if you just forget the whole thing, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I'm sorry, Iris, but I can't do that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is only one of you, Iris. You couldn't possibly have been in two places at once. That being the case, you were probably really at...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's what I wanted to ask you. What was that "probably" you just came out with?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, umm... Well... The problem is, you spoke to witnesses at both the Main Hall and the Inner Temple. It's kind of hard to disprove either sighting, but...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's no position for a lawyer to find himself in, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No... <thought>She got me there!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">It seems to me like there just isn't a solution to this puzzle. It's probably best if you just forget the whole thing, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I'm sorry, Iris, but I can't do that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the night of the incident, you were seen in two different places at the same time. Which means, there must have been two of you. I can't think of any other explanation, Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">B-But that's crazy! How could that be!? There's only one of me! It's impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Impossible? I wonder... The way you're trembling certainly seems to suggest otherwise.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">*gulp* You're seriously trying to suggest there's more than one of me? Then show me the evidence! Show me something that proves there is more than one of me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Iris">... Err, Mr. Wright... When you said there was "another me"... ...I was kind of expecting someone who looked like me. You know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I guess so...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">In that case, are you saying that I look like this person?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I can't say with 100% certainty, but...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Can you show me something you are 100% certain about then...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I really need to get to the bottom of this. Iris is determined to hide something from me. I can't drag it out of her unless I can show her some irrefutable evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">I'm sorry, Mr. Wright. I don't mean to be uncooperative, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have a firm grasp of the situation now, Iris. You have a sister, don't you? A twin sister, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. Dahlia Hawthorne. A woman I know only too well.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... I had no idea you knew of her. Very impressive, Mr. Wright. But... She's no longer...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, I know. Her sentence was carried out recently, wasn't it...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no need to explain now, is there Iris? This "second you" who was here at the temple on the night of the murder... ...it was your twin sister, Dahlia Hawthorne!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">B-But you just said it yourself a second ago! My sister's dead! Have you forgotten that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you forgotten this, Iris? This is a channeling dojo, a training ground of the Kurain Channeling Technique.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That night... ...someone channeled Dahlia's spirit. And you knew about it! And that's the secret you've been trying to hide from me!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... Aaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I... I was in my room in the Main Hall that night. As soon as I heard that I'd been spotted at the Inner Temple, I knew. I knew it was my sister. Dahlia, the other half of me who... passed away last month.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just as I suspected. The "Iris" that Sister Bikini saw at the Inner Temple on the night of the murder... It was Dahlia Hawthorne!</thought> Why didn't you tell me this before!?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">B-Because... Because my sister always does the right thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And because I mustn't get in the way of what she's trying to do. I already betrayed her once before! I can't do it again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You betrayed her? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's why I... I have to accept I may be found guilty. It's the only way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is she talking about!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">You know about it, don't you, Mr. Wright? About the fake kidnapping that took place here on Eagle Mountain 11 years ago?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That was the start of it all. It twisted her entire destiny. She started to commit crime after crime, and in the end, she... she lost her life. I-It's all because I betrayed her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How did you betray her, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It was no coincidence that Eagle Mountain is where the exchange was to take place. After all, I... I helped plan the whole thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But I got scared, so I ran away.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you talking about!? Why would you help her!? Stealing 2 million dollars... from your own father! That's awful!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But I promised. I promised that I'd help. And... She didn't do it for the money.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It was revenge. On our father.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Revenge?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean by revenge...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">He was a hideous man. He threw our mother away, and then sent her to Hell...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Her mother? She must be talking about Morgan Fey...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Our mother was the eldest daughter of the main branch of the Fey family. The main family had a lot of influence in many business and political circles at the time. As the eldest daughter, our mother was set to inherit all of that as the next Master. That's the reason our father married our mother in the first place. For power. But his plan backfired. Because our mother's sister took it all from her. She took over as the Master of Kurain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That would be Misty Fey... Maya's mother.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">But before long, the credibility of the Kurain Tradition hit rock bottom. The new Master, Mystic Misty Fey, made a terrible mistake... It was during the investigation of the DL-6 Incident. After that happened... ...our father took me and my twin sister away, leaving our mother and our home behind. He hated the place. He said it was a hick dive, and that he had no reason to stay there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's when you came here to Hazakura Temple?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes. The woman my father took as his next wife already had a daughter... Valerie. I... I had no place in his new family, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And I haven't seen my mother once since then. Having the Master's seat stolen from her, and being rejected by her own family... I've heard she's been very battered, spiritually and emotionally.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's what it looks like. Iris... There's just one more thing I want you to tell me.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">What is it...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">During the incident in which your sister, Dahlia Hawthorne, poisoned a lawyer... ...she began relations with a certain college student in order to hide the evidence. That college student... Have you heard anything about him...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... Well... I did hear one thing... She said she hated his guts.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... ...I see. Thank you for your help.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You're welcome...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Leave these locks to me. I'll open them for you, I promise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you. <thought>I suppose I'd better continue my investigation. There's still one giant secret left to unlock... Pearls's Psyche-Lock...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Look at that! They really did make a fire, right in front of the shack...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hah! You're too late, Nick! If you came here for one of our potatoes, we've already polished them all off!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I've pretty much got all the evidence I need. Now I just need to find out what Pearls is hiding.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">After dinner on the night of the murder... ...you were supposed to be in Elise Deauxnim's room, reading a book together, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes! I was so happy when she invited me! But... I didn't go in the end.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You didn't go...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... No. There was somewhere else I had to go instead. I was so worried, I... I had to go. I didn't know what to do with myself. I was so nervous.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So Pearls never went to Ms. Deauxnim's room... Because she was too worried about something or someone else...</thought> ...Pearls. On the night of the murder, you went to this place, didn't you...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You went here, didn't you Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like she's still not going to open up to me.</thought> This is where you went because you were so worried, right? Then the next question is, "Who or what were you so worried about?" Now, I'm going to take a guess, and you can tell me if I'm right or wrong, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Y-You mean you know!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If I'm right, will you tell me the whole truth?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... O-OK...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You went to this place for one very simple reason, and that is this:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well Pearls? This is what you were worrying about, right?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... There's something I'm worrying about right now, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You, Mr. Nick. Your face has turned a really strange color.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You shouldn't work so hard, you know. You need to take a break once in a while.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Being chided by a 9 year old. How embarrassing... But there's really only one thing Pearls could have been worried about that night. She must have been worried about "her". There's no one else it could be.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'll go get some sheets to make up a bed for you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, it's OK! I'll die of pneumonia if I nap in a drafty little shack like this! <thought>I guess I'm going to have to think this through one more time from the very beginning.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's obvious what you were so worried about, Pearls. It was Maya, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You knew the training Maya was undertaking was dangerous. After all, it was the Special Course.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I signed up for your "Special Course"!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well, my, my, my. Quite brave of you considering how cold it is! Young people can be so reckless with their health! Don't blame me if you become one with those you channel. Wa ha ha! Ho ho ho!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sister Bikini scared you with what she said, didn't she? And because it was you who introduced Hazakura Temple to Maya in the first place... ...you felt responsible, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... Thinking about what could happen to Mystic Maya made me more and more worried... I couldn't sit still at all. That's why I decided to go and find out how she was doing at the Inner Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then we're clear now that you went to the Inner Temple that night, Pearls. What's not clear is what happened after that...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Unngh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About what time was it when you headed over to the Inner Temple?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... It was probably around 9:30 when I left the Main Hall. I heard the real training was supposed to start at 10. I wanted to get there before it started. But there was so much snow, so I didn't get there until after 10 o'clock.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Until after 10? How did you know what time it was?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Because I heard the bell ringing for lights out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She heard the lights out bell...?</thought> The Hazakura Temple bell's pretty small though, isn't it? You must have really good hearing.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... I was really trying to pick up the sound of that bell, that's all. I didn't want to miss it. That would be terrible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She was trying to hear the bell...?</thought> Tell me, Pearls... Why were you so worried about hearing that bell?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Huh!? Oh! I...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think I know why. The reason you were so worried about that bell was because of this:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... You know, Mr. Nick, I think you should take a break now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Even your hair's starting to look a bit tired. The spikes aren't looking so sharp.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like picking this piece of evidence wasn't so sharp of me, either.</thought> ...A-Anyway! You said you couldn't afford to miss the sound of the lights out bell...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were given some instructions to follow for that night, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I presume you recognize these pieces of paper?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Aaaaah! Wh-Where did you...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In the incinerator at the Inner Temple. Pearls... You were following the instructions in this letter that night, weren't you? That's why you couldn't afford to miss the sound of the lights out bell.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... I'm speechless, Mr. Nick! You're amazing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These instructions that were found in the incinerator... I believe they were written for you, Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">For me!? I... No...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As you can see, a large portion has been burnt... But the last section is still fairly legible. "As soon as you hear the lights out bell, you must channel her spirit."</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who was it, Pearls? Whose spirit were you supposed to be channeling?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Taking into account the author of the note, and their purpose for writing it... ...whose spirit would Pearls have been trying to channel? Don't over-think it, Phoenix! It's pretty obvious who Pearls was supposed to channel...</thought> The person you were trying to channel that night, Pearls, was...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Pearls? Am I right?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... I can't channel anyone anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">A spirit medium who can't channel spirits... is like a painter who can't paint.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor kid. It's really getting her down.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But... I have never channeled that person's spirit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should have all the evidence I need, so what am I not getting here...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was Dahlia Hawthorne, wasn't it? That was the name that was in the letter.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's just as I suspected... It wasn't Iris who Sister Bikini met at the Inner Temple that night... It was Dahlia Hawthorne!</thought> Do you know anything about her, Pearls? Do you know what kind of a woman Dahlia Hawthorne was?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Umm... no. I've never heard of anyone by that name before reading those instructions...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I thought so. Pearls doesn't have a clue. She doesn't know that Dahlia is her sister...</thought> About the instructions in the letter I found, Pearls... Who wrote them?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoever it was asked you to channel the spirit of someone you'd never heard of... You must have quite a lot of respect for them.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">After all, you followed their instructions without question. So here's my next question. Who wrote this set of instructions for you to follow...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the person who wrote the instructions, isn't it Pearls? You must have had a lot of faith in them to follow their instructions to a tee!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... I... I had a lot of faith... in you, Mr. Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh! Thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But... ...I don't think I can trust you anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ouch... Pearls sure can be blunt when she wants to be... Alright now, think! Someone who Pearls would trust, no questions asked... There can't be many candidates for that post.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls... I have to wonder about something... You didn't have any idea what these instructions meant, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...*ba-dump*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you followed them to the letter regardless. Why? Because it was your own mother who asked you. That's why.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">H-How did you...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I figured it out. The person who wrote you this letter was your own mother, Morgan Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Uh... Waaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright, Pearls! It's time you started telling me the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-M-Mr. N-Nick... I-I-I...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why's she holding back from me? I don't like this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">D-D-Don't underestimate m-me, j-just because I'm a ch-child!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">If you're trying to say I followed these instructions... I'd l-like to see some proof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Because... I... I d-don't think y-y-you have a-a-any!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nnnnnngh... <thought>She'd say anything rather than admit to carrying out those instructions... I guess I'll have to produce some more evidence, then. One more thing should do it.</thought> ...Alright, Pearls. We both know someone carried out these instructions on the night of the murder. But you're right. There's no evidence that proves it was you.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I-I-I knew it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However... I do know that whoever did it was a child.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Huh? H-How do you know that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It couldn't have been an adult... No adult would've made a simple mistake like that.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">A... simple mistake? What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure you thought you were carefully following the instructions you'd been given. But you misunderstood some of the words, and this is the evidence that proves it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This shows the mistake you made!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... Umm... I guess you know what I'm about to say, huh? I don't think it's me who made a mistake, Mr. Nick. It's you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But the person who read these instructions must have been a child. That's why they misunderstood the meaning of that word... It's the only explanation for how such a simple mistake could've been made!</thought> OK, Pearls. I'll go over it again. The person who read these instructions...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was you who splattered gravy on this hanging scroll, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah! Wh-What!? Wh-Why would I d-do something like...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you remember what was written in that letter? "Gravely roast the Master in the fires of Hades and bring our vengeance to fruition." But you didn't know how to read the words "gravely" and "roast" among others, right?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">H-How do you know that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Remember the conversation you had with Ms. Deauxnim on the night of the murder...?</line>
<line speaker="Elise">Perhaps we can read some books together.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">R-Really!? I'd love to! I, umm... I'm not very good at reading.</line>
<line speaker="Elise">Ha ha ha. Well then, would you like to practice reading with me?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, Ms. Elise? So, for example, how do you read this?</line>
<line speaker="Elise">It says, "gravely"... That's kind of a tough word.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, Ms. Deauxnim taught you how to read "gravely" and "roast". But what she didn't teach you... ...is what they meant!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">"Gravely" sounded like "gravy" to me, and the only "roast" I could think of was the food...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's why you did it... That's why you covered the picture of the Master in gravy from that night's pot roast.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... To be honest... I did think it was a bit strange. I guess I really did get the wrong idea...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just a tiny bit.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... I really am useless! I didn't even manage to burn the letter properly as my mother had asked of me... Such a simple thing... And I couldn't even do it right...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... After dinner that night, I did go to the Inner Temple. With a pot full of the leftover gravy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The gravy?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I saw the picture on the hanging scroll near the Sacred Cavern. I was sure it was the Master of Kurain, like it said in the letter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see. And then?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Well, it was already way past 10 when I got there because of all the snow. So I went to the Inner Temple guest area.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The guest area?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes. I thought I could wait there until the training was over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why didn't you just go to the Training Hall?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Because Mystic Maya's main training had already started, and I couldn't interrupt it! So I just stayed where I was and prayed for her to get through it. But then... I... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls, did you fall asleep?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm sorry! I didn't mean to! I just couldn't help it!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey, don't worry about it, Pearl! Who cares if you fell asleep? I fell asleep waiting for Iris, too. It happens.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anyway... Then you found yourself trapped at the Inner Temple?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes. When I woke up, it was morning. I tried not to cry, but... ...Dusky Bridge wasn't there anymore and there was no one in the Training Hall. I thought everyone had left me because I overslept! I threw the letter into the incinerator, then I heated up the leftover gravy, and...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And let off some steam by chucking the gravy on the scroll while you cried...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">It must've been pretty scary for you, Pearl. I know what it's like. Nick used to leave me behind when I fell asleep at school, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't equate something so trivial with her experience, Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It was written right in my mother's letter. It said, "As soon as you hear the lights out bell, you must channel her spirit." I was on my way over to the Inner Temple when I heard the bell ring.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you channeled Dahlia Hawthorne's spirit?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">No... I tried, but I couldn't do it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You couldn't do it...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I've never failed at channeling someone. This is the first time it's happened. I tried and I tried and I tried... Yesterday, this morning, the whole time! But I just couldn't do it...!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">D-Don't let it get you down, Pearl. It'll all work out. If you want, I'll come flying through the sky for you! Whooosh! Just like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So she never managed to channel the spirit...</thought> Is that why you think your spiritual powers are gone?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes. I... I don't know what to do...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't there any other explanation for why you couldn't channel a spirit?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... I suppose there's one other possibility. It's not very likely, though...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you please tell me what it is anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It could happen if someone else was already channeling the same spirit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Someone else? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Well there's only one of each spirit, right...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yup, it's like dating a girl, Nick. You can't see a hot chick if she's already taken!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Then that would mean on the night of the murder... ...someone else channeled her spirit before Pearls could. Someone else channeled the spirit of Dahlia Hawthorne!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm a failure. I couldn't even grant my mother's final wish...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Her "final wish"...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes. This letter. "This is my last wish," she said. "So make sure you follow the instructions carefully."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... This letter... I definitely need to find out more about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">My mother has gone to a place called a "penitentiary".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I know, Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I visit her every month... And last month, she told me...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">The time we've been waiting for has come, Pearl. There's something I need you to do for me. I hid a letter for you at our home before they brought me here. I want you to read it, and do exactly what it says. It's for the good of the Fey clan, my angel. You'll be doing a great thing. Now, listen carefully, and I'll tell you where the letter's hidden...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">My mother is always nice to me... I love her very much!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah. Moms will do anything for their kids, right?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">She said it was for the good of the Fey clan, so I knew I had to help her. I mean, Mystic Maya's part of the Fey clan, so it had to be good for her, too. That's right, isn't it, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I guess so, yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">There was a picture with her letter, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A picture?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Of Ms. Dahlia Hawthorne. Usually, a picture is enough to channel someone's spirit, but this time...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...Pretty weird, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Like Larry knows anything about this stuff!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">There's something else that was strange about my mother's letter... The seal on it was broken, as if someone had already opened it once before.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...That sure is pretty strange.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Someone had opened it already?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You're very welcome! My mother is watching over us! So I'm sure Mystic Maya will be alright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Look at that innocent smile on her face. What am I supposed to say to her?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Ha...!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Finally figured it out, have you, Trite? You've finally realized how terrible of a crime being painfully oblivious is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">G-Godot!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">The entrance to the Sacred Cavern looks like a freaking puzzle workshop.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess he's talking about Iris and the lock-breaking effort...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">...But it's all a waste of time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Why do you say that?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Because Maya Fey isn't coming back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? You don't know what you're talking about! How can you say something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">It was your job to protect her, Trite. Just like it was your job to protect Mia Fey... Two sisters, caught up in the worst circumstances.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I realize that, but...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">And you were the only one who was by their sides. You were the only one who could have saved them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I didn't know anything about what was going on!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! What did I just say, Trite? Being oblivious is a heinous crime in itself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Tomorrow... We'll settle everything in court tomorrow. ...Once and for all.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-Mr. Nick... Is... Is what that man just said true?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It'll be alright, Pearls. I'm sure Maya's alive. You'll see for yourself tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... Yeah! That's right! I know I can trust you, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">...My dear Pearl... ...You've done so well, my child. My Pearl... ...It's better that you don't know... ...I knew this day would come for you... ...The blood of the main family is no more... ...Now you... You are to take the place at the head of the Fey clan... ...My last, great wish... It seems I was just in time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think I have enough evidence yet... I should investigate and gather some more clues before I try again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nnrgh! I've made too many mistakes!</thought></line>
</xml>