<xml>
<title>Bridge to the Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh my... Mr. Laurice feels that way about... me...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Apparently... he isn't aware of your real secret at all.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... ......</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is no time to be embarrassed!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I-I'm sorry! I'm just... hardly accustomed to that sort of thing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Worry not... And in any case, whatever it was that he saw on the night of the incident... Mark my words, I will drag it out him!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Does that mean... Mr. Laurice is the witness today...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...No. I believe that nun... will be the first to take the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Sister Bikini...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">She claims to have seen the very instant in which you carried out the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I just want to ask you one last time. It really wasn't you who killed Ms. Elise Deauxnim, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... That is correct. It wasn't me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Very well then.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Um... Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You are a prosecutor... aren't you? Are you sure about this? If your true identity is revealed...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't worry. ...I've taken the necessary steps.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Y-You have...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Iris. It is a prosecutor's job to doubt people.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But right now... I am a defense attorney. A defense attorney's job is to believe in people, and to believe until the bitter end. That's what a friend of mine told me once.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You may pass judgment on me from the defendant's chair. You are the one to decide... ...whether or not I am able to do the task I have been entrusted.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... ...Very well, sir. I leave my defense in your capable hands.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Sister Iris of Hazakura Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...The defense does indeed appear to be ready... However, the same cannot be said for the prosecution in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm not sure I like such blatant waste of this court's time. An empty prosecutor's chair can only mean... ...that the prosecutor has no confidence in their ability to prove their case. It would seem this case is already over before it had a chance to begin. I am ready to announce my verdict at this time. This court finds the defendant...</line>
<line speaker="???">The prosecution... stands ready.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-And you are...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">V-Von Karma, you say...? Perchance, you wouldn't be of any relation to the legendary prosecutor Manfred von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-You did!? Then... you must be quite a big shot, eh! By the way, Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm almost certain that I've seen you somewhere before. Or am I just imagining things? You look very much like a prosecutor I met once...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I believe you are imagining things, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. von Karma? Do you have anything to say?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There... there isn't...? But I'm sure... once before, in this courtroom... Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What is that!? A whip!? I'm not sure I care for such a thing in my courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-Bailiff! Remove that whip, at...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I have no objection to the whip.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-You don't...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution can wield a whip or drink seventeen cups of coffee... But there is still only one truth. That is what I stand here to prove today!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I see you brought your flair for the histrionic.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Allow me to add to the things I'm not sure about... People acting bizarrely in my court! Uwa-hah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Ms. von Karma, please give an outline of this case. With as little whipping as possible!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The sword in this picture... is the weapon in question, correct...? ...Very well. The court accepts this photo of the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Please bring this witness to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>And so it begins... My first and my last trial... as a defense attorney!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">H-Hold on here! I'm not sure about being not sure if I care for this at all! Witness! Please stand up nice and straight!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If I recall correctly... ...there are a few milk crates in the defendant's lobby for witnesses with bad backs.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Fetch a crate for this poor lady, please!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Little old me? Well, I'm the head nun of Hazakura Temple on Eagle Mountain. My name is Bikini. You got it? Bikini. Nice to meet everyone.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... But you don't appear to be wearing a bikini right now... Uwah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-You want me to leave!?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">No need to get your bikinis in a twist! Let me tell you, I'm a sight to behold in summer! Wha ha ha! Ha ha ha! Ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In any case... Witness. I hear that you saw the crime take place on the night in question.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">That's right! I can still hardly believe it myself, to be honest. There's no way dear little Iris could do anything like that...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let us hear what you have to say then. First, tell us aboot your own movements that night, eh!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">That night I was helping an acolyte with her training in the Inner Temple. But...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So it was simply coincidence that you found yourself returning to Hazakura Temple?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...Yes, you could say that. If my back hadn't been in so much pain, I would have stayed at the Inner Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That sounds like a pretty important statement she just made...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth. ...Please begin your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">That night I was helping an acolyte with her training in the Inner Temple. But...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is this Inner Temple...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well, see, conversing with the spirits is what we train people to do, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We'll be the ones asking you the questions, madam.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...In order to do that, a place strong in spiritual power is required. There's a small temple across Dusky Bridge, called the Inner Temple.  Acolytes must spend an entire night there to undergo intense training.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And how exactly do you help with this process...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">It is all quite exacting. It can't be performed without a nun supervising.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A tutor with a whip, in your case.</thought> If that is the case... ...then why did you return to Hazakura Temple, where the murder took place?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well, as you can see, my back likes to act up. Violently.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Violently...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">That's right. It's no laughing matter, especially in winter! I can't hold anything heavier than a knife and fork during the cold months! Just being alive is like strict training! Wah ha ha! Wha ha! Wah ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">On the night of the murder, was this fabulous back of yours hurting again...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">That's right. Raging like a bull in a pigpen. I almost fainted once or twice! I just knew that unless I warmed it up, it was going to finally finish me off!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">So, I left Iris to help the acolyte, and returned to Hazakura Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You "left Iris to help"... With what?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">What do you think? The acolyte's training, of course. It was just past 10 PM, so we were starting to enter into the training exercises proper.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wasn't it your place to remain with the disciple?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well, the job is simply to watch over the acolyte so that they don't pass away.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just to confirm this point again, that night... ...you met Iris in the Inner Temple, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Yes, yes. She's a gentle, honest girl. She's never once failed to follow my directions.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Witnesses have to undergo their own trials, I'm afraid. The defendant's fate rests on their powers of observation and memory, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well, well, well. Don't worry! I'm more than up to the task! I'm a woman of faith, after all. The head honcho of Hazakura Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In that case, Ms. Honcho... I'd like you to explain something for me. The discrepancy between your testimony and that of the defendant, Iris. She claims that after ringing the lights out bell, she went back and stayed in her room. ...Which means! She did not go to the Inner Temple at all!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">N... No...! She said that...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But that is completely illogical. The murder was committed in the courtyard of Hazakura Temple. Claiming that she "went to the Inner Temple" would make for a much better alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">But that is odd... Whatever the reason... I can't believe that she would lie...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... she does indeed have honest eyes! Uwaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why am I the only one being whipped in here...!? Anyway! Neither the witness nor the defendant have any reason to lie! Which means... We must call your memory into question...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Dear, dear, dear. You're older than me and yet you want to play that game, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-Ah, well, that isn't exactly what I...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">My memory is perfect! Crystal clear! Especially in winter!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then... I suppose it's too early to end this cross-examination, eh. Mr. Edgeworth. If you are going to question the memory of this witness... ...you will need to show me a more decisive piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Understood, Your Honor. <thought>I was naïve to think that alone would do the trick.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then please add your comments aboot Iris to the testimony... And let us return to the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Iris came to the Inner Temple. She was dressed exactly as she had been at dinner.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you sure that you're not making a mistake...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...You, young man, need to get your estimation of me up from the floor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Iris always wears the same clothes. The smallest thing out of place would have stood out like a sore thumb to me! You're making a mistake, thinking I made a mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...An excellent finish there, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Still, I have to wonder...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">There's no bath at the Inner Temple, you see, and I needed a long, hot soak.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...So you returned to the Hazakura Temple in order to take a bath?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">My back is to blame for everything. It's a "do or be done in" kind of world, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How long were you in the bath for, if you don't mind me asking?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">... My my my, what a filthy little rogue you are! I know what's on your mind!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I bet your next question is going to be, "Where exactly did you wash?" Ah, THIS is why you have to watch the young ones...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-What are you going on about!? I was... Gwah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The lowest of the low.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is there some sort of "Kick Me" sign stuck to the defense's bench!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Anyway, I couldn't afford to be away from my post for too long, you understand, so...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">It was after I had finished, just as I was heading back... that's when I saw it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The crime took place in the courtyard, correct...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">When you go from my room to the Main Hall... ...you have to take a winding hallway from which you can see the courtyard.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That certainly seems to be true.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There is indeed only one problem with this testimony. If I can clearly point out what it is, then I can begin to quantify... ...just how good this witness's memory and observation skills are.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Witness. Let's get one thing straight. The defendant whom you claim to have met... ...she was wearing this "Demon-Warding Hood", correct?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Of course! That is a very important piece of clothing, I'll have you know! Wha ha ha! Wha ha ha! Ha ha... Wait a minute...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's the question of the day, now isn't it... Ms. von Karma? I'll have you know that this hood was given to someone as a gift that night. Before the lights out bell was rung.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You know where I'm going with this, don't you? If the witness had seen the defendant as she claims... ...the defendant couldn't have been wearing this very hood!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well well well!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's not a bad feeling at all, exposing contradictions like this... Now I understand that happy look on Wright's face every time he does it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court! Witness, your response... Wuahaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Spares... Well... I do tend to make too many of them.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... A stockpile. A surplus of hoods, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Each nun is only given one hood. This should be the only hood that Iris owned...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Then this is quite strange! Waaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'm sorry to break this to you, Ms. von Karma... but you won't get away that easily. Discrepancies such as this will sow seeds in any human heart. The seeds of doubt.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Witness. While I don't wish to call your testimony into doubt... ...you must give every detail with precision.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I-I'm not sure I'm comfortable going along with this...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Those seeds of doubt are sprouting in the Judge's heart. They just need a little more stimulation to bear fruit... Contradictory stimulation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I finished my bath around 11, and I thought I should return to the Inner Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You saw a truly terrible sight, didn't you...? If I was in your place... ...then it would be much like Ms. von Karma whipping Mr. Edgeworth in two in court! And me, seeing it all from this very chair! ...Er, well, something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This judge... His imagination is about as vivid and creative as Detective Gumshoe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Calling everyone by their full name... Can't you do something about that habit of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I finished my bath around 11, and I thought I should return to the Inner Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...How far is it from your room to the Inner Temple?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Let me think a moment... About twenty minutes, on these stumps of mine. It's about 15 minutes to Dusky Bridge from Hazakura Temple. The Inner Temple is just beyond the bridge.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">T-That's right... I was heading along the walkway toward the Main Hall...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">And as I was walking back... I heard a noise from the courtyard. I took a look and...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You say you heard a noise...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">"Thump"... Just like that.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">It's very quiet in the temple, you know. You can even hear the snow falling from the branches. "Thump"... Just like that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But then, couldn't this noise you heard have been snow falling to the ground?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">... I never thought of that. Wah ha ha. Wha ha ha. Ha ha...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hoh hoh. Hoh hoh. Hoh hoh... Uaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well. Whatever the source of the sound, I looked over at the courtyard and...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Iris was...! Oh, Mystic Elise! And with that sword, of all things!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...This is the second time that the witness has testified to seeing the defendant. But... some doubt remains in these claims.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Hey, just what does that mean!? Just because you're a good-looking young man doesn't give you the right to...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The murderer who stabbed the victim with the sword... Sister Bikini, try to recall exactly who it was you saw! As clearly as you can!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Hmm... Well. You're a handsome young man, so I'll forgive you. ... Oh! Now that you mention it... There was something awfully strange about her... Something that has been bugging me all this time!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Please, don't keep us in suspense.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Her hood!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">That's right! ...It's coming back to me... Iris... She wasn't wearing her hood! I thought something was out of place, but... It all makes sense now, doesn't it? After all, she'd given that hood away to someone, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you say, Mr. Edgeworth? Is this testimony important?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...This line of questioning is only going to tear the  wound open further.</thought> These statements are as useless as the investigations of a certain detective. ...There is no need to record them.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. ...Please, continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This may initially appear to put me at a disadvantage... But, I can't see any other leads at the moment...</thought> ...Your Honor. I would like these new statements to be added to the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness. Add that statement to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...No problem.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Now that you mention it... Iris didn't have her hood on.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You are sure about that...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Yes. After all, we always wear the same clothes. Ah! I don't mean because we're poor, you understand? It's our style. Yes, that's it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...There's absolutely no need to explain yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Anyway! She looked different from normal, so that really stuck out.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>At least then it might bite you and not someone else...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Iris didn't have her hood on. I'm sure of it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Now, please tell us aboot the victim, eh.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Mystic Elise was staying in the corner room, which faces out onto the courtyard.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The room the victim was staying in overlooked the courtyard, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Which means... the victim's room was on the second floor?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">No, no. Hazakura Temple is a single story building. But the mountain itself slopes downward... ...which elevates the Main Gate side of the temple and the guest rooms in the back... ...to about the height of a two story building.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... And the victim was staying in one of these elevated rooms, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Yes... I should know. I'm the one who carried her things to her room, after all...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">The stabbing I saw must have occurred after she was pushed out of her window.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What makes you so sure of all this...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">It's just like I told you earlier... "I heard a noise from the courtyard." OK? "Thump"... Just like that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It appears that the witness was not mistaken then.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Yep. Yep. I'm more than just a pretty face. Especially in winter! I'm a woman of faith, after all. The head honcho of Hazakura Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's only two of them working there...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...It doesn't feel like she is lying. This is very powerful testimony, too. She claims to have seen the instant in which the defendant stabbed the victim... There are only two things I can believe in right now... My client, Iris, and my own abilities as a defense attorney.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Impressive logic. That's what I'd like to say, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh please do! My brain is something else... especially in winter!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However... I think you are overlooking one thing. ...Ms. von Karma. Would you be so kind as to take another look at the autopsy report?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The victim did fall from a  height of 10 feet. ...However. This fall... was after she was killed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">T-That's right! It says "after death" right here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The scene the witness claims to have seen is contradictory! If the defendant stabbed and killed the victim there in the courtyard... ...how did the victim then go on to take a ten foot fall!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Order! Order! The victim was killed and then fell! If that is the case... ...then the victim must have been killed in her room... Don't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Were there any signs of a struggle in Ms. Deauxnim's room...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">She was stabbed with a sword! That would leave a blood stain, wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Well, Ms. von Karma? Was there any blood...? Waaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Your whip has just caused traces of blood to be found on my glorious playoff beard. However! If there was no blood in the room, then your claim that... Waaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">When it produces the most blood...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. With the weapon still in place... ...it acts like a lid on the wound.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's true... With the weapon still in the body, there wouldn't be much bleeding... A perfectly reasonable line of thinking!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! I must admit that this is a probable version of events!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'd expect no less from Franziska von Karma... She locates and takes control of every vital point!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems... ...that we need a clearer testimony from the witness. Remove all supposition on your part and tell us only the truth, please! Witness! Please! Remain standing on the crate!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Don't go selling me short now! The weight of winter snow has bent me out of shape! ...Especially my back and my mood!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...With the whip?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...Oh, boy. Alright, alright...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">When I looked across at the scene, the sword was already in place.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... This all confirms Ms. von Karma's theory...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>"Perfection" is an impossibility, Franziska von Karma... And I'm here to teach you just that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">When I looked across at the scene, the sword was already in place.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">At that time... was the victim bleeding?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well... I was very shocked to be seeing all this, of course... So I'm not entirely sure... But I don't think I saw any blood. Not then.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In any case... Let's be clear on one very important point. Did you actually see the instant in which the victim was stabbed!?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Thinking about it now, I didn't actually see her stab Mystic Elise.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Think carefully. This is very important.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">It's Iris we are talking about here! I'm thinking for all I'm worth! ... No, when I looked over, the sword was already in Mystic Elise's body.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It might not be  conclusive, but... ...this testimony supports her theory.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I saw the instant in which the blade, plunged in to the hilt, was smoothly drawn out.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Smoothly", you say... You're saying you saw the sword smoothly slide out?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">That's right...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">The whole thing happened right next to the gold statue of Mystic Ami. Mystic Elise was on the ground, and Iris was stooped over her. The sword was buried up to the hilt. When Iris stood up, the sword in her hand just slid out of Mystic Elise's body. It slid out from that gaping wound...! Aaaah...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It goes without saying... that if the sword was removed there would be bleeding.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is that really the case...? I can't help but feel that something about this testimony is very out of place... That something which couldn't possibly have happened... appears to have happened.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I've never seen so much blood before...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...So you're saying that you saw the victim's blood?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">T-That's right! Some of it had splattered onto Iris, too...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What!? <thought>Her clothes were blood-flecked as well...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... That seems quite conclusive to me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What should I do...? Press this point further?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't afford to make things look any worse for the defendant. I'll bide my time for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Witness. Please continue your testimony. From after you witnessed the victim bleeding!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Going back to your previous statement... ...you said that you saw little bleeding when the victim was stabbed. But now... you say you saw the victim bleeding...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well, well. I say that what I saw is what I saw.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-What did you see?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Maybe I didn't see the poor woman get stabbed... But I saw the girl pull the sword out of her, plain as day.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Pulling the sword out...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well, it wasn't exactly pulling... It was more like it "came out".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! You will add this statement to your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh... Was that important...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>More important than you can imagine...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Was the bleeding caused by the killer removing the sword...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">No mistaking it! I remember it all, clear as day!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Don't you think that's a bit odd?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why would the killer pull out the sword?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If all she wanted to do was place the weapon in the hand of the gold statue... ...then there was no reason to remove it from the body. All that would've accomplished is causing the victim to bleed unnecessarily. ...Your thoughts, Ms. von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed... It is strange, now that you mention it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'm going to need to find an answer to this mystery, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">That's when I fainted. You can't blame me, can you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, on to what the killer did next... You saw none of it? Correct?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well... I was unconscious...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I don't know... 10, maybe 20 minutes...? A young man with a very prickly looking head woke me up. ...By stepping on me, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I'm not sure I like that method of resuscitation!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well, I wasn't asking for mouth-to-mouth, or anything of the sort... ...but I would've welcomed a more gentle awakening right about then, let me tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I shall have words with the offender personally. What did you see upon awakening...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">And when I awoke... Mystic Ami was... stabbing Mystic Elise through the back!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">By "Mystic Ami", you are referring to the golden statue, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Just stabbing someone with the Shichishito, a sacred treasure, is terrible enough.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">But to then make Mystic Ami hold the blade...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is easy to despise something. Anyone can do it. However, there is something that cannot be done so easily...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Exactly why would the killer set up this gruesome scene? Can anyone explain the reasoning behind that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmm... No, I don't think I can.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">That's true, so true. In early spring, for example, I often find myself...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>"There isn't always"... That phrase might come in handy someday.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There are too many unnatural elements in this case... Why was it necessary to use the Shichishito from the Ami statue as a weapon? Why was the weapon finally placed back in the hand of the statue? If I can expose the flaws in this testimony, perhaps then I will begin to find the truth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sister Bikini. You are a reliable witness... At least, I'd like to think so. But there are too many contradictions here.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">W-What do you mean? You make it sound as though I'm a liar! But... You're a handsome young man, so I'll forgive you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In the scene that the witness claims to have seen... ...the weapon was thrust up to its hilt into the victim. Furthermore... the killer withdrew the weapon smoothly from the body. ...However! Both of these are complete impossibilities!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean...? Please, explain you... Uwaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To start with... Do you think it would be possible to stab someone to the hilt with this? No matter how I look at the defendant, she doesn't appear strong enough for that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The objection stands! I wept a little back there, I must admit.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That isn't the only issue here. If this sword was truly stabbed into the body up to the hilt... Well, just look at all the branches on it. It certainly wouldn't come out smoothly.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We also have the problem of the amount of bleeding. It's true that when a blade is left in a body, it acts as a "plug" of sorts. However! When the weapon is shaped like this, it's an entirely different story. The wound would be too large for the blade to completely stop from bleeding!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm not finished. There is still one more... conclusive contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-You've still got more!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...This one is simple. If this sword really was thrust in all the way to the hilt... ...why is there only blood on the tip of it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If this witness is telling the truth... Then there should be blood along the entire length of the sword!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Ord-- Whaaaaaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But what does this all mean!? You have proven contradictions regarding the murder weapon, but...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Having come this far, there can only be one answer.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The weapon used to kill the victim... ...was not the Shichishito!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Whaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's examine this again. What was it that made us think this sword was the murder weapon?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">W-Well... It's because Mystic Ami was holding it...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Exactly. However! If you reflect on this, that is the only basis we have to assume such a thing. The impression left by the scene was just too strong. That is what influenced us. It influenced us to believe that the Shichishito was the murder weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! Waaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmmm... That's true! Your response, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... If that is so... I would like the prosecution to answer the obvious question it raises.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The obvious... question?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes. Namely... Where did the real murder weapon disappear to?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It goes without saying that the police searched the Main Hall and the surrounding area. ...Perhaps the prosecution can enlighten us as to if a "sword-like object" was found.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Answer the question, Ms. von Karma!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmm... Another mystery to throw onto the pile! A trial without a murder weapon is a tricky beast!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Excuse me... Could I say something...? I just remembered something, actually...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I was just thinking... It's possible... ...that just maybe... what actually happened was... it was just over there...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... What exactly are you going on aboot here?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">The murder weapon, I mean! Maybe... I think I might know where the sword was disposed of!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You what!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Impossible...! What else... What else could this old woman have seen!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I saw the murder at around 11 PM...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmmm... Witness. Please, tell us everything you know right away next time.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well. I'm not in the best of shape. What with my back and my age, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A snowmobile, eh... I see. Well, it certainly is an interesting theory...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Did she really go to the river to dispose of the murder weapon...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth! ...Your cross-examination, please.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I saw the murder at around 11 PM...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You are sure about the time?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Yes... I was worried about it, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why was that?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Because I have a strong sense of responsibility. Especially at this time of year. The acolyte was being doused in freezing water at the time... I couldn't very well take it easy in the bath all night now, could I? So at 11, I decided to leave Hazakura Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Her estimation of the time seems reliable, at least.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">And after asking that it be reported, I went out to the Main Gate.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You asked Phoenix Wright to report the crime, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Right, right, the one who trampled me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It seems she is the type to hold a grudge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">There isn't a phone in the Main Hall, so I sent him to the bridge.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He had forgotten it at home, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Anyway, I was really scared... And it was taking him a while to get back... So I thought I'd go out by the Main Gate for a spell.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">And there... I saw tracks! Tracks that indicated the snowmobile had been used!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As I recall, there was a snowmobile outside the Main Gate when I visited.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">That's it. That's the only one we have. It'll run no matter how much snow falls!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, you're certain the snowmobile was there at the Main Gate when you arrived?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Yes, of course. It was parked in front of the gate.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I'm not sure if this is really relevant... What should I do...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I need answers to every possible doubt.</thought> The snowmobile in question... Was it still warm at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? What do you mean? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I'm playing to a slow crowd here.</thought> It goes without saying that using a snowmobile will heat its engine. If it was still warm, then it means it was recently used.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Ah! I see! I never thought of that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm, that's right! I overlooked that, too!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then answer the question please, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">... I don't often go around touching hot engines...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hmm.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">However... Now that you mention it... There wasn't any snow on it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Snow...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Yes. For some reason, only the snowmobile wasn't covered in snow...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There wasn't any snow on it!? Curses!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems highly likely that the killer did use the snowmobile then, eh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It looks very likely that the snowmobile is related to this case. I can't help but think that Iris used it... But for what...? I'd better hold off on this... for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Well then, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How long does it take to reach the bridge by snowmobile?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">It takes 15 minutes to walk to Dusky Bridge, but less than 5 using one of those!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In that case... why didn't you use it yourself? You could've spared yourself some walking.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Ah! There's a reason for that! Have we got a moment for me to explain?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think that's why the question was asked in the first place...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...It was about a month ago. I was driving my beloved little snowmobile, happy as can be. I'd fetched some water and was heading back when I went and crashed into a tree! The tree and my back both went crunch. Just like that. Crunch.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Crunch.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...I haven't been able to find the courage to ride anything since then...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Anyway, the killer must have used it!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Maybe they threw the weapon into Eagle River and came back while I was knocked out?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Refresh our memory. How long were you knocked out for...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Like I said, somewhere between 10 to 20 minutes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I have to concede that is more than enough time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...Iris could have done that. She can drive a snowmobile after all...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">While it would have been possible, time-wise... ...one element remains out of place here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh? And what would this mystery element be?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The killer's reasoning, Your Honor. "Why did the killer do all of this?" Why go to the Eagle River to dispose of the murder weapon when there are other methods?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Too many unanswered questions! Your response, Ms. von Karma? Waaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She's as over the top as always...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Another mystery to feed the fire... "Was there any reason to go and throw away the murder weapon"...? Luckily, there is surely a problem with this testimony. Now all I have to do is start poking holes in this flawed account...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I admit this photograph proves something. It proves that the snowmobile was used on the night of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However... If what the witness says is true, why is there only one set of tracks?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Iris left Hazakura Temple, threw the weapon into the river, and then returned. If this was the case, then naturally there should be two sets of tracks in the snow! Those from heading out to</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">... Ah...! You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see! While she was at the river, the snow stopped... ...leaving just the return tracks in the snow.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is there a flaw in her theory...? This idea that the snowfall covered one set of tracks...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...The tracks leading to the bridge were covered by the snow.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I do not have any evidence that can dispute this claim.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well... that would be...!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">......... It could only be Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-And the reason being...!?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">There is only one key for the snowmobile.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Whaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Now I don't feel like a clueless Puck Bunny! I understand everything! If the defendant did indeed use the snowmobile... ...which means that Iris is most definitely the murder--</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Your Honor! Please, wait a moment.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is one gaping hole in Ms. von Karma's claim!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm not sure if I care for your response, Mr. Edgeworth. Next time, bring up whatever issues you have earlier. Do you understand!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh... <thought>I should have noticed it sooner...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The tracks to the river were covered by snow... What a nice theory. However, Ms. von Karma... That is impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...No need. The evidence will do all of the talking for me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">On the night of the murder the killer went to, and returned from, Dusky Bridge... ...in order to dispose of the murder weapon. The outgoing tracks were erased by snow. ...Or so claims Ms. von Karma. Mr. Edgeworth! Present your evidence to the contrary, eh! Evidence that the outgoing tracks were not covered by snow!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Witness! Please tell us again what time it was when you witnessed the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Like I said! It was around 11.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Of course, this means that the weapon was thrown away after that time, correct? On that note... Please take a look at this data. It is the weather report for Eagle Mountain on the night of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The... weather report...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Snow started to fall at 7 PM... But it stopped at around 10:50.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Therefore! When the Sister witnessed the crime at 11 PM... ...the snow had already stopped falling! It is impossible for any tracks made after that time to have been covered up!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well then... It looks like Ms. von Karma's claim has been... snowed in. Waaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, no, no no... You've got it all wrong. This isn't a forecast... This is... actual data... Gyaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmm... It's true. We cannot be totally sure, eh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-What!? <thought>How did she pull that off!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">"It had stopped snowing at Hazakura Temple when the murder took place." ...You need to provide conclusive evidence of this.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I've come this far... There's no turning back now.</thought> ...Very well. I, too, cannot allow any doubt to remain concerning this testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well then... Mr. Edgeworth! Where is your evidence that it had already stopped snowing when the victim was killed!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Your response, Ms. von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And to think you just arrived after a long, tiring flight from Germany. That was poetry. Pure poetry.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This evidence is only going to freeze my case solid.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even if it is snowing in my heart... At the time of the murder... it had already stopped snowing at Hazakura Temple!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Here is the evidence! What do you have to say, Your Honor...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... ...This reminds me of when I was a little hockey goon in training... When I was a child, I hoped for school to be canceled due to heavy snowfall. Perhaps, Mr. Edgeworth, it would've been better for you had court been snowed in. ...That's all this evidence says to me, in any case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Nothing else...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Nothing else.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>According to the witness's testimony, the incident occurred after 11 PM... In which case... ...there has to be evidence that can undeniably prove something doesn't match up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ultimately, it all comes down to one point. That being... Whether or not it was snowing in that courtyard when the victim was stabbed...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Incredibly easy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If we want to know whether it was snowing or not, this photo will tell us everything. Of course, I am referring to the photo of the crime scene. As you can see... everything is covered with snow. ...With just one exception.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The victim herself, Ms. Elise Deauxnim! Why is there no snow on top of her...? The answer is simple! It had stopped snowing when she was killed, that's why!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In other words! If the killer really did go to the Eagle River to dispose of the murder weapon... ...then in this photograph, there should be two sets of tracks!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Just what are you... Gyahaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>To be honest... I am not entirely sure myself. But...</thought> This is simply what all of the facts point to. That night... someone used the snowmobile to leave Hazakura Temple. From the tracks left, it can be understood that they were heading for Dusky Bridge. At that time... it was still snowing. </line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then when this person returned to Hazakura Temple... ...the snow had stopped. Thus, the return tracks remained.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Can I say something? This all sounds a bit fishy to me...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">There is only one key for the snowmobile.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...Which can only mean, that night... Iris used the snowmobile to go to the Inner Temple...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>But... Iris said that she never went there... I should probably press on this point some more when I get the chance...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">The snowmobile can't cross the suspension bridge... So, she must have left it on the Hazakura side of the bridge and crossed on foot.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...That sounds right.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">But... What's odd is, when I left Iris and returned to Hazakura Temple... I didn't see anything near Dusky Bridge.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Maybe... But when I made it back to Hazakura Temple... ...it was there, by the Main Gate... The snowmobile, I mean. I know what I saw. It was covered in snow, too...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">B-But that... isn't possible!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order in the court! ...What does this all mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So then what was the snowmobile used for...? It wasn't taken by the defendant when she went to the Inner Temple. If it had been, then the witness couldn't possibly have seen it by the gate. Furthermore... it wasn't used by the killer to dispose of the murder weapon. If that was the case, there should be two sets of tracks in this photo. All we know is this... After it stopped snowing... someone used the snowmobile to return to Hazakura Temple!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I never thought a simple snowmobile could cause so much trouble...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I think we've arrived at this point due to the witness...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Yes, yes. I've nothing more to add. I've told you everything, everything that I know.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then... That still leaves us with the same problem. If only there was someone... A witness who could testify to having seen the snowmobile!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A witness, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Was there no one out, walking perhaps, near Dusky Bridge on that night?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">... I don't think that's likely. It was cold enough to freeze your ears off. Only an idiot would go out wandering in that. ...Unless they had something really important to do.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmm... That's a shame.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hold on... Something is coming to me... An idiot may well have gone wandering out on that sub-arctic night!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Your Honor! I actually have an idea... There may be one individual able to help us.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">R-Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't know for sure if he saw it or not... But there are two things about him that do come to mind.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Which are...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">First... that he saw "something incredible" on the night of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This individual that I am thinking of went wandering outside on that cold night... In other words, he is our kind of idiot.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth! Who is this idiot you're talking aboot!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Just what is the meaning of this, Mr. Edgeworth...? Are you saying that... this is the person who was near Dusky Bridge that night?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I did think so, however... Aaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Cool off before you try to take me on again! Ungh...! <thought>What was I thinking!? This is the perfect chance to drag him onto the stand!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmm... Mr. Edgeworth. This individual... Did they really see the snowmobile that night?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This guy must be a product of "Jean-Luc de Laduc's Guide To Obnoxious French Painting"...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is Larry Butz... The student of the victim, Elise Deauxnim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Her student...? Interesting. Why was he wandering on the night of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">T-That's... <thought>I could tell them all about his designs for Iris... But it may cost us his credibility as a witness... Before I even call him.</thought> He is, after all, an artist. He was, perhaps, searching for something in the snowy scenery that would move him. ...Although I cannot guarantee that this is the reason.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I intend to extract that from him, right here in this courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Summon this youth as a witness immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe he is in the gallery for this trial. It will not take long to summon him.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Larry... You may have escaped me yesterday... But today I'm going to get everything out of you!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...The court will now adjourn for a 20 minute break. Ms. von Karma, please see to preparing the next witness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good... Well then! Court is now in recess!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Excuse me... Mr. Edgeworth? I'm not really sure what to say...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Iris. We only have 20 minutes. There are two things which I need to ask you before we reconvene.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...Alright. I'll help</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">First, about that night. You really didn't go to the Inner Temple, correct? The last witness claims to have met and talked with you in the Training Hall. Either you or Sister Bikini... ...is lying.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... Mr. Edgeworth. It is just as I said yesterday. Until the incident occurred... I was in my own room, in Hazakura Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Very well. The second thing, then. That night, the temple snowmobile was used in between the time Sister Bikini... ...returned to the Main Hall and when she bore witness to the murder. Sometime between 10:30 and 11 PM that night. Were you the one who used the snowmobile?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... There is only one key for the snowmobile. The only person who could have used it... was me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So it was you...! But... why? ...What made you go out to Dusky Bridge?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... I'm sorry, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Iris...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I can't... tell you about that... yet.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Yet"...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Not until her safety is confirmed...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Her?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">The safety of the acolyte...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The "acolyte", huh... She's must be talking about Maya...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Iris. Look me in the eye and tell me the truth. Did you kill Elise Deauxnim?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... No matter who or what may come... I could never take a life.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... <thought>As I thought... no Psycholock...</thought> ...Very well. It is my job to get to the truth. You'll discover this for yourself soon enough.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Court will now reconvene. Ms. von Karma. Where is the witness...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Suspicious behavior...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Dare I ask what the witness was sketching when he was detained?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I can only presume that his intention was to capture you-- ...Aaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It would seem that whip is going to see plenty more use today...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Ouch!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">H-Hey! I was just artistically rendering... Ou-Ouch!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">L-Look! I'm nothing but a fledgling artist, training out in the mountains! I'm only down here in the city because I ran out of green paint. Well, to use the technical term for the color, "viridian".</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Larry... This isn't an art store, now is it...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I know! I graduated junior high, OK!? Look. Art is all about working in the fields, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Working in the fields...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I presume he wanted to say "field work"... I hope.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Th-That's it! Thanks, buddy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's kind of sad that I was able to understand his mangled train wreck of a sentence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">I just happened to stop in here and found a wonderful new model!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">So see!? I've got nothing to do with this trial! At all! I expect all of your faces to be red when you realize this mistake! Bright red! Or, to use the technical term, "crimson lake". ...Ou-Ou-Ouch! Ou-Ou-Ou-Ouch! Ouch!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ou-Ou-Ou-Ouch! Ouch! Ou-Ouch!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Refrain from whipping me, Ms. von Karma! Cross-whipping is as bad as cross-checking. Witness! That was all your fault! Testify, now!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Waaaah... This is almost too much for me...!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I was at that lodge out in the mountains, looking up at the stars that night.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! Please refrain from talking directly to the lawyers during your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I-I'm just a nobody! Nothing but a small, worthless man, aren't I!? And why wasn't I asked for my name and occupation... or anything else...!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Mr. Edgeworth. This man seems to have quite a severe inferiority complex.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...He's recently been the cause of numerous incidents. I think he's finally realized for himself... ...just how much of a nuisance he has been to other people!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah, that's right! I'm behind everything, every case! Watch out, OK! Just touching me will make you eternally unhappy!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Well then, let us proceed with the cross-examination. With no touching, thank you. We can delve into other details at a later time.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I was at that lodge out in the mountains, looking up at the stars that night.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What ever is the matter, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This one single statement is so full of contradictions... For a moment there, I thought I was going to collapse.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">OK, give me a minute... Well, it was snowing that night so I couldn't possibly have seen the stars. That run-down shack is hardly a "lodge", is it...? And even if the stars could be seen, it isn't like I was there to look at them, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Heh heh heh... Ou-Ou-Ou-Ouch!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I walked to the bridge a number of times, but...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"A number of times"...? How many?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Maybe... five times? I went once every twenty minutes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Which means... ...you spent almost two hours at Heavenly Hall that night?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">You bet! Real love is about waiting with your heart in your hands!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Love, you say...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was this man's intention to summon the defendant to the small shack. ...Using this blackmail letter.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-Blackmail...!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">No, no! That was simply a product of overflowing love... A-Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So... what did you see? I hope for your sake you saw a snowmobile... You huffy, puffy, loosey-goosey excuse for a whimpering whining wuss of a witness, eh!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Um... well... You see...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Being called those names doesn't seem to bother him at all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">I didn't see a s-snowmobile!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Larry! You really didn't see it?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">H-H-Hey! No need to hit your desk! I can hear you! ...I didn't see it! I didn't see a s-s-snowmobile!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Larry. Say "snowmobile" for me, please?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">S-S-S-Snowmobile.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you truly have nothing to hide... ...then why are you stammering like you just flew over a cuckoo's nest!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Sh-Shut up! W-W-What is this!? I don't know! Don't ask me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It seems that I'll need to start from a more obvious contradiction. I'm going to strike the blow that will finally get him to spill the beans!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">I didn't meet anyone at the bridge that night!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You didn't meet anyone?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's right. Because I've got nothing to do with this! And I'm just here to buy some viridian paint, OK!? Come on, I expect to see those crimson lake faces! Now!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... It would appear that simply pressing him isn't going to be enough, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It seems that he's going to claim to have nothing to do with this to the end. I don't want this guy to cost us any more time... I need to slice through his obvious contradictions and keep things moving along...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Larry Butz... I can understand why you might want to throw your old life away. You're pretty pathetic, and you cause all sorts of trouble...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I'm sorry...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But... Having realized just how much of a nuisance you have been... ...that could be considered a step in the right direction.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Edgey! Are you... trying to console me?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It certainly doesn't sound that way to me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However... I cannot forgive you for simply turning away from the incidents you create!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Waaah... You're totally pinning this on me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Now then. Let us talk about the night of the murder. Sister Bikini, after seeing the murder take place, asked Phoenix Wright to report it. Thus, he headed for the public phone by the bridge... There, he happened across a certain nefarious individual! You, Larry Butz!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... That's right. Me, in the flesh.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Listen carefully, witness. It doesn't matter if you change your name. So long as you remain pretty pathetic, you will continue to cause these incidents! That reality will not change!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">B-But...! What do you want me to do, then!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Larry. What you need to change is your inner self. "What you saw that night"... Testify truthfully! That is all you can do for now.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... Edgey... I... I think... I've finally woken up! ... Well. I guess I could still be sleeping... But anyway! I'll do it! I'll testify! ... Well. I'm not sure this'll go especially well...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'll ask again, then, witness. What did you see on the night of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I went to the shack at around 9, so it would have been about 10:30 PM...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmm... You certainly saw quite a lot, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">It was like me after a three day stint chasing a girl... It totally burnt out. Like, almost totally gone. ...I mean, trying to cross the burning remains was what caused Nick to fall.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh, don't worry... nothing life-threatening. He just caught a cold.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, Mr. Edgeworth! Please commence your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I went to the shack at around 9, so it would have been about 10:30 PM...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What did you do out there in the cold for an hour and a half?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, if you really must know... I was busy being excited. I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmm... "Excited"? Dare I even ask...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I set the meeting time as 10:00 PM, right? But I couldn't wait. And I thought she might come early, too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Well, it appears she didn't come at all, in the end.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Shut up! Don't go picking my fond memories apart! Anyway, I was getting a little worried. I thought maybe Iris had lost her way. So every twenty minutes or so, I went out to the bridge. But I didn't see anything particularly suspicious... I didn't have anything else to do, so I went back to the shack to wait for her.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I was lying under my bedding when a white flash almost blinded me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This "light" was, of course...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Lightning. Like... KERPOW! Like a slap from Naomi, honestly! A big bada-boom! Hagaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Waaah! That's more like a punch from Miranda!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, did you actually see the lightning hit the bridge?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, I was a bit startled by the flash of light, so...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I looked out the window... and Dusky Bridge was on fire!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Seeing that, what did you do?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What do you think!? I was burning up as well! From the fire in my heart!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well. To be honest... It was freezing cold, so at first I thought, "Forget it. I'm not leaving my covers." But it had pretty much stopped snowing... So, I dunno, I changed my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmmm. I'm not sure I care for the "forget it" attitude you had at first, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">There was still some thunder, but I went right away to check it out.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You said "right away"... But exactly how long after the strike was that?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hmm... The lightning fell, and then the bridge caught on fire... Maybe around five minutes? I mean. I suddenly thought, "Gotta go check this out!"</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hold on... Well, it had pretty much stopped snowing... I guess about a five-minute walk?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And how did Dusky Bridge look when you got there?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Like I had recovered a piece of my childhood. I mean, not even the bonfires kids make during school camping trips can compare!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Well? Should I press him for a little more info?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I don't think we can expect any more relevant information... Probably best to turn to other leads.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Witness. Please continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Larry. Let me ask you one thing.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What is it, Edgey? What's with the serious face?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why didn't you call anyone?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Eh? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Normally... when faced with a "towering inferno", one would try and tell someone. There is a public phone right by Dusky Bridge, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... Well, of course I thought of doing that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So then... let's hear why you didn't!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">H-Huh? Yeah, OK. A reason... My reason... It isn't that I didn't try to tell anyone... I just didn't have time to, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you suddenly thought to "check out" the bridge...? Does this mean that you initially had no intention of doing so?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">W-Well... Yeah, I guess it does... It was really cold... I didn't really want to go out there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that's the case... Why did you change your mind? I would like to hear your reasoning.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In which case... please give testimony to that effect, witness!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">M-My reasoning... OK... Reasoning, is it...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's when I ran into Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How did Phoenix Wright look when you met him?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hmm... He looked like a beaten up mule. He was dead tired. I mean, he had run all the way from Hazakura Temple. He simply stood, staring at me, breathing hard for a moment.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">On his legs... a 15 minute run, I'd say.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...And that's when the murder was reported?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's right! And then he took a fall from the bridge!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I arrived at the bridge, and Nick showed up less than a minute later.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You claim to have arrived at the bridge at the same time as Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Y-Yeah! I thought, "I'd better tell someone about this." But then Nick came up yelling about murder! It totally made me forget about the bridge. The fire was pretty much out by then, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What's this feeling...? I suddenly have a terrible case of unease...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah. That's pretty much it. More or less.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Butz">I thought I'd never get another chance to see something so big burning!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...So you decided to go and see what was happening?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's right! We're talking about a massive suspension bridge burning to high heaven! That's not something you see every day. A real spec... specule... ... Like, really special?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Can we really trust a witness who is unable to pronounce "spectacle"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Life seems to love hitting this poor witness below the belt...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, my motto is to "hit life back as hard as I can." A-Agah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...He told me about the burning bridge yesterday. But there's still something that doesn't quite fit... It looks like... ...despite his change of heart, Larry still isn't telling us the whole truth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your very existence being a contradiction, I'm not sure if you can grasp this or not...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What the hey, Edgey!? You make me sound like some sort of alien!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But your testimony is conclusively contradictory. The problem here... is time.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I've never been the best timekeeper, you know. "Three minutes after Billy leaves on foot, you follow him on your bicycle. How long does it take for you to catch up with him?" Terrible at those.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...This is much more simple. You saw the lightning strike Dusky Bridge... ...and immediately went to see what had happened. ...Is this correct?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah... Well, I wasted about five minutes first, but more or less.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I have the weather data from the night of the murder here. According to this, the lightning fell at 10:45 PM. You say it takes less than five minutes from the shack to Dusky Bridge. Meaning you probably got there at around 11 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...That all sounds about right, I guess. And then Nick showed up and did his falling act.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That is impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">11 PM is when the murder occurred in Hazakura Temple. Thus... Wright was still there, in the courtyard. There is no way that Larry could have encountered him at Dusky Bridge at that time!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Ah! Excuse me! I-I have an objection!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You do?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Edgey! How many times do I have to say this!? I'm not Larry! I'm Laurice Deauxnim! Gyaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Watch your footing there, Ms. Franziska von Karma. The slope ahead is slippery! For there is still no way that Wright could have been at Dusky Bridge at 11 PM!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is clearly written here in the weather data report. It took around 30 minutes for the bridge to burn out. Therefore! The bridge must have been burning until at least 11:15 PM!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Which means... what, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright did not see the bridge as it was burning that night. He did not arrive there until after the flames had died down! ...Larry! You arrived at the bridge at 11 PM. Wright did not make it there until at least 11:15... Are you still trying to hide something from us!? What happened during these missing 15 minutes!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Urk... I... I feel like I just woke up... I guess I was still sleeping after all! Ha ha ha! Pinch me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! Ordaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah! Not much of a problem at all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Really...? The bridge is burning before your eyes, and there is a phone right next to it. Why, then, did you not report the accident?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Did you simply... watch the bridge burn?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That is the problem here... Even after the bridge burnt out, he was still there! He simply stood there and didn't report anything.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This might be Larry we are talking about, but even he is incapable of being so stupid. There has to be a reason for his inaction!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... Edgey... I think it's about time I got serious with you, dude.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Just as I thought, you've been playing with us all this time.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Listen... I'm... I'm going to tell you everything! Are you sure you want to hear it all!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I may reeeeally say it this time! Everything! Kahaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well... I have a terribly bad feeling aboot this; however... ...let's have the witness finally give us the whole truth. Now... for this 15 minute gap, what where you doing, witness!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I'm a Deauxnim. I'm an artist! What do you think I was doing?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmm... I suppose artists can be strange folk...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's right! I'm willing to sacrifice everything in order to draw the perfect sketch!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Including the truth, from the sound of it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth. Has this removed the last of your doubts?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not at all, Your Honor. One very large doubt still remains.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is a surprisingly believable story, especially considering the source... So why did he think he needed to hide it from us until now? I intend to drag the reason out of him!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hah ha ha! You'll regret this, Edgey!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I'm a Deauxnim. I'm an artist! What do you think I was doing?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tell us, Larry...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">My name is Laurice! Get it right! Mistakes like that are what keep you from being popular with the ladies like I am!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Just who exactly are you!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I'm Laurice Deauxnim! Apprentice extraordinaire!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's what he calls himself, in any case.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Then you are... an artist?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Of course! I'm an artist, the real thing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yet again, that's what he calls himself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That is a very big issue, indeed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Sketching! In front of the bridge! I was whipped up into a frenzy of art!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">S-Sketching!? The burning bridge?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">The burning bridge and everything that came with it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... What? "Came with it"...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">You want to hear this from my lips, do you, Edgey!? Y-You'll regret this! That sketch of mine is... Gaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... W-W-W-What are you talking about? I don't know what you mean!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That does indeed appear to be the fastest solution. ...I'll leave it to you, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What should I do...? I've got a terrible feeling that the instant this sketch is revealed... ...the entire world may be changed by what is depicted there...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I cannot recommend looking at the sketch. His "works of art" are a force of nature best measured on the Richter scale.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's right! They'll shake your heart to pieces!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmm... This courtroom has yet to meet earthquake standards! I think we'd better pass! ...In which case, let us turn to other leads.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Larry. I wonder if you could show us your sketch. Please?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... Well, well... Even I couldn't have imagined it'd turn out like this.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Imagined what?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That Laurice Deauxnim's debut would take place here, today, like this! Ou-Ou-Ou-Ou-Ouch!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">OK... But steel yourselves! This... is the world of Laurice Deauxnim!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Ah. Um... Well... So this... this is Dusky Bridge, correct? Q-Quite a large bridge, isn't it? Your response, Ms. von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Isn't it? Isn't it? I struggled to reproduce those flames. I really did!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Yes, I'm sure you did. ...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">......</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh... This is going to get ugly... No one has the bravery to bring it up, it seems... This... mysterious flying object...</thought> ...Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The burning bridge is fine. But... What is that unfortunate looking figure...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Ah. You spotted that? I thought you might.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However much I might want to ignore it... I can't.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">It's Iris, of course! Iris! I wish she'd take better care of herself. We have to plan for our future, you know! What would've happened to her if she had injured herself flying like that...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Larry, please. Answer this next question honestly.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">OK.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you REALLY claiming to have seen this? Are you claiming to have seen the silhouette of the defendant... ...flying over a bridge that was engulfed in flames...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yep. That's what I saw. That's why I drew it! I'm an artist! A real artist!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">High! The girl... She's really high up in this picture!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uwaaah! What was that for!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please whip your own cheek from now on if you wish to test your wild theories! A-Anyway! No court of law will ever acknowledge... ...that p-p-people can f-f-fly!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">She was flying pretty high, my sweet Iris. She was about 30 feet above the bridge, at least! It was really something to see!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-This has to be some kind of m-m-mistake! ...Mr. Edgeworth, please bring the witness back down to earth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What? Me...!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This witness is your friend, is he not?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let us get back to the cross-examination! By force, if necessary! Mr. Edgeworth, I expect you to expose the obvious contradiction here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-Yes, Your Honor... <thought>Looks like I've got another reason to remember this moron...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">...Well, what did you think of my debut piece?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Get that thing away from me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, hurry up and cross-examine him!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Could the reason you were so excited be...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What do you think!? My girlfriend was flying through the sky! Almost 30 feet above the bridge! I felt like I might start flying myself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If only you'd be so kind as to fly out of all of our lives...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Anyway! I completely lost myself when I was drawing this scene!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I saw Iris flying! Her white hood fluttering!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just where did you see this sight from!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey! No need to shout... When I was lying in bed in that run-down shack... The crack of the lightning bolt made me realize that the bridge was burning. I just watched it for a while from there, thinking how nicely it was burning! Then after about five minutes, I saw it.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's right! That's when I decided to go to the bridge!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I see. That all makes sense. Aside from the sketch itself...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Yes... This sketch doesn't make any sense... I just need to convince the artist that his work is ludicrous.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Butz">The shock and awe that I was feeling... I transferred it all directly onto the page!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The burning bridge moved you that much, did it? ...I find that hard to believe.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">You moron, Edgey! You don't understand me at all! If I see an abandoned cat, I find myself passing by it with tears in my eyes! I am a man overflowing with irresponsible kindness! And I use my irresponsible kindness to fill the pages of my notebook!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">W-W-What has that got to do with anything!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm not sure if I care for an artist using a notebook for sketching. Proceed, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...Before I realized it, the flames had gone out and then he came running up.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You forgot the passage of time to that extent, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well... Once I get caught up in something, I tend to forget everything else...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's true... He's always  been that way. I guess he's not lying about that, at least.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aside from doubts of his humanity, eh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There is a big clue waiting for me in this cross-examination... This testimony does nothing less than mock the court... But I am sure that there is a vital kernel of truth hidden in it somewhere!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Larry. What did you really see that night...? Not that I particularly care.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">In your position, that's just being irresponsible! I... I drew exactly what I saw! I'll give you a whole dollar that it's the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that is truly the case... Then there is one thing that we can say for certain.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What might that be...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That the person who flew over the bridge... ...could not have been the defendant, Iris!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">W-W-What!? What do you mean? I don't understand!? Uwaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Tell us, Larry. According to this picture... ...the individual whom you say you saw was wearing a hood. Correct?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Of course she was! That run-down shack is quite a way from the bridge... The hood is what told me that this floating angel was my Iris! The hood is my darling Iris! And Iris is my darling hood! Waaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Larry, there's something you need to be made aware of. On the night of the murder... Iris wasn't wearing her hood. She had given it to Wright as a gift! Are you going to change your story now? Perhaps suggest it was Wright who took flight!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">W-What are you talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I think you understand what I mean just fine.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Why...? Why did Nick have Iris's hood!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eh...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Edgey! What's going on with Iris and Nick!? Why you, Niiiiiick! You dooooooog!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I do believe... ...that this unbelievably mysterious sketch... ...is destined to disappear, discredited and discarded. Straight into the garbage.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...Hah... Hah ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Hah ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Hagaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">It feels like... I've been waiting 25 years for this very day to come! Edgey! Today is the day I get to completely stupefy you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-What...!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is the meaning of your outburst, witness!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...I hate to have to do this, but I have some definitive evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Definitive"...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Iris did indeed come flying over the burning bridge! And I, Laurice Deauxnim... ...shall prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I didn't expect to ask this again... But we shall be needing your testimony once again. Tell us anything you know concerning the defendant as depicted in this sketch... And show us your evidence that this nightmare was actually a reality!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...OK. I hope you're ready, Edgey! Because I'm going to feed you a whopping serving of pain!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...You've been serving us a whopping serving of pain this whole time. Trust me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">When I reached Dusky Bridge she was already gone...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A c-crystal sphere...!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">This one. Pretty, isn't it? But finders keepers!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Let me see... Around here, somewhere? Looks about right.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And it was half-buried in the snow...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">It had pretty much stopped snowing by then... But there was still some falling as I walked to the bridge.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmm... The court accepts this crystal sphere!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...That's mine, OK!? I want it back afterward!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There's something on it, isn't there...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh my... It's a blood stain!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What!? A blood stain...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">You ready, Edgey!? By tomorrow morning, you'll be calling me "Master Larry"! Yeah, I like the sound of that! No one's going to push me around anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Didn't you want to be called "Laurice Deauxnim" only a few minutes ago!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">When I reached Dusky Bridge she was already gone...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...So, you went to the burning bridge?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's right! To meet Iris! She actually flew to get to me! The least I could do was meet her halfway!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... the defendant was not at the bridge when you got there, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I guess she went back to Hazakura Temple. She's a girl, after all. She must have wanted to look her best.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It must be lovely to live in the fantasyland of Larry's mind... Actually, it's so depressing that I can't even work up the energy to point...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So... what did you do next?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I was so worried! So I frantically searched all over for her!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you searched all over for her?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">She was flying pretty high, you know. I thought maybe she slipped on her landing and got hurt. Hey! It was more than possible! Also, when I headed out to the shack the first time, I was snacking on a banana. I was pretty sure I threw the peel away somewhere around there, so, you know...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... <thought>Can one guy really be this stupid?</thought> So, did you find any signs of her so-called "landing"?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hmm... I don't really remember. I kept on falling over myself, and kinda lost it for a while there.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You... fell over yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah. The snow was deep, and there was even a banana peel out there!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... <thought>Yup. There's stupid, and then there's Larry Butz.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The short of it is that you didn't find any signs of her "landing", correct? Then what happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That led to me finding a beautiful crystal sphere, half-buried in the snow!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Half-buried"...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">It was sitting in the snow, with a little gathered on top of it. It was very hard to spot, actually. I mean, it was dark out, too.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm impressed... You did well to find it!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">No matter what you may think when you look at me, I'm a pro. A genius security guard. I used a penlight I "borrowed" from my company to help in my search... And it sparkled really brightly, as if it was saying, "Here I am!" to me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It does indeed look very much like the crystal sphere on Iris's hood... But need I remind you that she was not wearing her hood that night?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Butz">I'm sure that Iris was simply wearing a spare hood.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Each nun is assigned their own hood! And they are assigned only one!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I don't know anything about that, OK! And Iris is special, alright dude!? Even if she did steal a spare hood... I'll forgive her!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This is getting us nowhere... Our destination for the day, it seems.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">However... this crystal sphere was found near the bridge. That is a fact. If it didn't come from a hood, where could it have come from?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That is the question I aim to answer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Butz">After all, no one else could have lost a crystal sphere that night.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let me confirm this one last time, Larry. The reasons you thought that this was "Iris"... ...are the hood and this crystal sphere, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's right! My gut is never wrong! I met that old Bikini the next morning... And her crystal sphere was still there, safe and sound!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed... She was wearing it in this very room, earlier today.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This case isn't going to end without a fight... Exposing the obvious contradictions in this testimony will be easy... But I fear that all that awaits us are further mysteries!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Larry. That night... There was someone. Someone who lost a crystal sphere.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Th-There was...? Who!? Who was this stupid idiot!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Elise Deauxnim! The mentor to a stupid idiot!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have a photo of her here. And on the end of her staff, you can see a familiar looking crystal sphere.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">H-Hey...! That's my photograph! ...Give it back! Ou-Ou-Ouuuuch!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>They look nothing alike!</thought> In any case... please take a look at this. This is the victim's staff, found at the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Aaaaah! The crystal sphere... It's gone!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">W-W-W-W... What!? What!? What!? What!? WHAAAAAAAAAAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">J-Just what does this mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If anyone jumped... or flew across the bridge that night... ...it certainly was not Iris! After all... She was not wearing her hood! More importantly... ...the crystal sphere found at the "landing site" was not hers either!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">T-That means... The one who flew... ...and dropped the sphere... was the victim, Ms. Elise Deauxnim!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Y-You can't do that! I saw it! With my own two-- Eyeeeeeeiiiz!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You honestly believe that...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Ms. Franziska von Karma. The only people who will accept that explanation... are scatterbrains and clowns!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Why are you pointing at me!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The victim's crystal sphere was found, near the bridge, on the night of her murder. Yet you expect us to believe this has nothing to do with the case!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">After the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... ...... What...? You mean... I'm the killer!? No waaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She makes a valid point... There is no evidence that Elise Deauxnim left Hazakura Temple that night. ...However, if somehow this crystal sphere... ...can be proven to have been dropped before the victim was killed... ...then this case is going to transform into something else entirely!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your response, Mr. Edgeworth? I want your final opinion on the disposition of this crystal sphere! If it is not related to the case, then this witness who you called... ...will have been nothing more than a monumental waste of time!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Can I prove it...? Can I prove that the crystal sphere was dropped before the murder took place...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>"Can I prove it...?" That isn't the issue. To simply "prove it". That's the only option! That's what he'd do... That's the way Phoenix Wright would do this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>No matter how I look at it, it's not possible... It is certainly strange that the crystal sphere was found near the bridge. But perhaps it is just a curve ball from the killer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmmm... Then I am left with no choice. The court sees no reason...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What is this!? Hey, Edgey! You're a defense attorney, aren't you!? If it was Nick standing where you are right now...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">If it was Nick, do you think he'd give up!? No! He'd find the truth, no matter what it took! No matter how crazy it seemed!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... <thought>Wright... At this moment, I'm standing where you should be. Which means there's only one thing to do! Think like you!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Your Honor. Allow me to prove something to you. I will prove that this crystal sphere is a vital link to solving this case!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You will do what!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That should come as no surprise. <thought>Because right now, I am Phoenix Wright, and I am indeed cornered...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I order you to present your evidence, Mr. Edgeworth! Evidence that proves that the crystal sphere was indeed dropped before the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Your response, Ms. von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Go, go, Edgey! Do it! Prove it! Win! Win! Win!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>His cheering... It's as though I'm listening to the ominous caws of ravens!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...So, Mr. Edgeworth. What will you do from here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">O-One more chance, Your Honor. I can't turn back after coming all this way. <thought>The time of the murder and when the crystal sphere was dropped... I need to find proof that the latter happened first!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This crystal sphere... It was half-buried in the snow, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's right. If it hadn't stopped snowing then it would have been game over. ...The snow would have totally covered it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That's all I needed to hear from you, Larry. ...Your testimony makes one thing quite clear.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-What...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">When the crystal sphere was dropped, it was snowing, even if it was ever so slightly...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">On the other hand, let us look at the scene of the murder. As proven earlier today... there is no snow on the victim's body.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Therefore! The crystal sphere must have been dropped before the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">On the night of the murder the victim did indeed go to Dusky Bridge! And there, something occurred that caused this crystal sphere to come loose!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What... What could that have been!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This sphere... There is some blood on it, isn't there?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Allow me to raise a certain possibility at this junction! The real crime scene was near the foot of Dusky Bridge!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just who is the fool? And which part is so foolish, Ms. von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That's not exactly true, now is it? To put it more precisely, what she saw was... ...the murder weapon being removed from the victim's body.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...No, it isn't!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You said it yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that statement is the truth... ...then Dusky Bridge could very easily be the scene of the murder. The murder weapon was not removed! Thus, there was no bleeding!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I've made it this far... The only place to take this is to the end! I just need to prove the possibility it happened as I presume...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, if the defense is ready, the court would like to have an explanation. Please show us the method by which the victim's body was carried to Hazakura Temple!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>No... That isn't it... I'm on the wrong track here. I need to charge on through this... Even if it makes things look bad for my client...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Try again, Mr. Edgeworth. And this time, without the scary glare, if you don't mind!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">On that snowy night... ...there is one way that a body could have been moved. The snowmobile.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As we know... the snowmobile was used that night. It was explained as having been used to dispose of the murder weapon... But it could also have been used to carry a body!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! Gyaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh... You're too late... Franziska von Karma. And in fact, the defense has proven something else entirely. We have shown that this case requires further investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Where was the victim, Elise Deauxnim really killed? ...If her body was moved, whatever for? And finally... Just what does this image mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...This witness certainly sits on one of the lowest possible branches of humanity. However! He would never utter a lie that could hurt a girl with whom he is enamored! He drew this, so it is something that actually happened. The defense stands firm on this point.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Ed-Edgey! Thank you...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...That settles it, then. I cannot give a verdict under these circumstances.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wright... I seem to have fulfilled my part in this...</thought> It is just as I thought. Franziska von Karma... You make a wonderful partner.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There was one reason, and one alone, for me being here. To expose the darkness lurking in this case, and then pass it on to Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">R-Really? That's what this was all about? You could have just told me that from the very beginning! Then I wouldn't have had Franzy whipping me all... Daaaaaayyyowch!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A shame that your chance seems to have slipped by you.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What a shame, Franzzzyyyyyyyy!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Ouuuouuuouooooouuuuuououuooououooouuuuouoouuch!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I cannot believe that the witness's testimony relates to an actual event. However, there has to be some sort of answer for the questions it raises. Have his words here today been the truth or lies? Next time we gather in this courtroom... ...those are the matters that shall be addressed! I am counting on thorough investigations by both the defense and the prosecution.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>And with this... The rest is up to you... Wright...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor! What do you think of the witness's statement!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't think there is a problem with it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... You say that with such gusto that I suppose I must agree that is all there is to it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Don't get smart with me! Get smart with this penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It would appear that even I can make mistakes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This evidence clearly reveals the contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Unfortunately, I'm afraid I can't accept that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well done, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-What?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was only testing you just now.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Well then, why don't you try testing this penalty, too!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It looks like I shouldn't have spoken in haste...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That statement contradicts the data provided by this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It does? How do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Forgive me, Your Honor, but you yourself just said that it does!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Don't try to play mind games with me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Curses... It appears I have yet to adjust to being on this side of the courtroom.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! This court sees no reason to further prolong this trial. Nor is there any need for more time to decide the case against the defendant. This case is extremely clear. I see no room for misinterpretation of the facts. This court finds the defendant, Iris of Hazakura Temple...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accused will surrender to the court immediately... ...to be held pending trial at a higher court within a month from today's date. That is all. The court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>