<xml>
<title>Bridge to the Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know how I've got spiritual powers, unlike you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, sure... You are a spirit medium, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But just like you, if I don't keep my powers sharp, they get dull, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... I guess so, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Glad you agree! OK, Pearly! You're up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Pearls...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So! That's why we need to go on a special "Spiritual Hot Spot Tour", Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh? I'm lost. What's this magazine you're shoving in my face?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It's the New Year's issue of "Oh! Cult!", Winter Spiritual Locations Special!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Oh. <thought>Pearls looks so happy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Maximize your spiritual powers with just one night of intensive training!" ...Oh! It sounds too good to be true!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll say. It sounds more like a scam to me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's at a spiritual retreat called "Hazakura Temple". It's way up in the mountains, and I bet it's nice and cold. ...Just perfect for training!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now I definitely don't want to go...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, I think I've heard of this temple before. It's a famous channeling dojo. It's hard for even real spirit mediums like us to make reservations up there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Reservations...? For a temple? Are you serious?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Don't worry! I've already made special reservations, just for us!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! And I signed up for the "Special Course"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That's nice. And the timing couldn't be better. ...Since we don't have a case right now anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Alrighty then! It's settled! Well, come on! Don't just stand there! Start packing your stuff!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes, Mr. Nick! You'd better start packing your stuff!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...? M-ME!? Why do I have to go!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, we have to be accompanied by someone over 20 years old.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! I don't have anything to do with spirit power. The only thing I can channel is a TV. ... So, um, is there a heated pool at this "Hazakura Temple"?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">No, but you can stand under a freezing waterfall!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Sorry, but I think I'll pass. I hate cold places.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaat!? No way! How can you be so selfish!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Come on, Mr. Nick! Look at this place! Doesn't it look beautiful!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nope. Not going. I'm gonna be nice and toasty at home....... .................What the...!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wh-What is it, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let me see that magazine! Th-This nun...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is she a friend of yours or something, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Th-This girl... I-It's...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">My name is Dahlia Hawthorne. I just want to say... It's an honor for me to be here in your noble presence.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Honestly, how can any woman ever count on you for anything? ...You disgust me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... It can't be! <thought>She was found guilty and should still be in prison...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I'll go.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hazakura Temple... I said I'll go.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yay! Isn't that great, Pearly!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes! Oh, thank you! Thank you, Mr. Nick! You'd do anything for Mystic Maya, right? Even walk over burning coals, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Dahlia Hawthorne... I knew there was no way she could possibly be at that temple... But, I just had to be see for myself... ...who this "nun" really was.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Brrrrr... It-It-It's so c-c-cold here, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe you should put on something warmer for a change!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-W-Well, it's supposed to be c-c-cold... It's t-t-training. ...Ah-Achoo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Her teeth are chattering so loudly, it's all I can do to make out what she's saying...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow, Mystic Maya! So this is the famous Hazakura Temple!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">P-P-P-Pearly... I-I-I-I... Ah-Achoo!</line>
<line speaker="???">Well, well, well... How nice to see you here. Welcome to our temple!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...! Th-Th-Thank you... Ah-Achoo!</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh my, my, my... Thank you for coming all this way. Come now, come now. You must have been cold.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's with the past tense...? We're freezing into human popsicles as we spea--!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ho ho ho. Well, we are high up in the mountains after all. In any case, we shouldn't speak here. ...Please follow me inside.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Th-Thank you. I was starting to think I would pass--</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh! Yes, yes! I almost forgot to introduce myself. I'm the head nun here at the temple. My name is Bikini.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-B-B-Bikini...!?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">That's riiight! Actually, that's my "temple" name. What do you think? It's a tradition to have one, and I wanted something that has a nice image to it. So I thought, "Why not choose a bikini?" Besides, it makes me seem younger. Wa ha ha ha! Ho ho ho!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It certainly does! Oh, I signed up for your "Special Course"!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well, my, my, my. Quite brave of you considering how cold it is! Young people can be so reckless with their health! Don't blame me if you become one with those you channel. Wa ha ha! Ho ho ho!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">R-Reckless...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Wa ha ha"...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Maybe you should take it easy tonight, Mystic Maya... We can come back another day.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But you went through all that trouble to get reservations for m--</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Yes, yes, yes, that's right! You've come all this way, so please, enjoy yourselves! There's still time before supper, so why don't you have a look around?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you think, Nick? Pretty awesome gate, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It sure is... It looks pretty well maintained, too. This thing kinda puts your hometown to shame, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah... Well, a lot of things have happened in Kurain Village. We used to be a lot richer, back when people hired us to perform channelings.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I see... But now the place looks a bit run down...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... I guess I was just born in the wrong time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That looks like the Main Hall where we'll be staying tonight. From here, it looks like one of those ice hotels you always hear about!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...They gotta have a heater or something in there, don't you think? I don't wanna die.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm not worried, I brought my hot-water bottle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you bring one for me?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you talking about, Nick? Who carries around 2 hot-water bottles?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Brr! If the cold doesn't kill me, the ice queen over here will finish the job...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, look! It's a cute little bell tower! I absolutely love the sound of a giant bell!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? So, which do you like better? That or the sound of money?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...! ...... Sorry, but I'll take money for the win, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What are you apologizing for?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh look, it's one of those snow motorcycle things!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Most people call that a "snowmobile", you know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Snow motorcycle things", "Snowblowmeal". Same thing. Hmm... Too bad we didn't invite Desirée. I bet she could race like the wind on this "Slowmobile"! Or maybe she'd give me ride on this "Blowsnowbile".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh! I told you, it's "snowmobile"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, do you think you could take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I may not look like it, but I can tell you I'm very much in demand. And to be quite honest, I'm finding this a little difficult to say...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...What IS she trying to say, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think she's trying to say that she's busy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But seriously Nick, what's the deal? Nothing has even happened yet and you're already shoving evidence into people's faces. You need to forget about work and relax a little.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Try to have some fun, OK Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, you're right... <thought>Sure. Pin the hypothermia on the lawyer is great fun!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Brr... It's fr-freezing in here, too! Achoo!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hee hee. It reminds me of the Meditation Room in Fey Manor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Pearls, you've been in an unusually good mood since we got here.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Well, kids are made of energy, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As for you, Maya, you look like you're about to catch a bad cold.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-W-Well, I'm not exactly a little kid anymore, I guess. Ah-Achoo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nngh... Is she going to make it...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet the writing on these sliding doors are instructions for spirit channeling... Kinda like how we scribbled math formulas on the bathroom walls to remember them. Except we couldn't go to the bathroom during tests... And I can't read these walls.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are straw zabuton cushions arranged around a hibachi brazier... I haven't seen a layout like this since I saw this really old Japanese movie on TV. ...If it wasn't for this hibachi, they'd probably freeze to death.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's an altar. It looks a bit old, but someone does a good job taking care of it. Speaking of altars, I remember seeing one like this in Kurain Village last year. I guess they really do have something to do with spiritual power after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a laughably large Magatama on the altar. If I can see Psyche-Locks with the tiny Magatama I've got... ...I can only imagine what kind of power this bad boy has under his hood!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a stack of straw zabuton cushions. Maya told me this type of zabuton is called "enza"... I suppose if I'd never come here, I'd have missed out on all these new things.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Look at this broken down old bridge, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, and look at that big canyon below us.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! There's a river down there! It looks like it's flowing real fast! ...What's wrong, Nick? You look like you've seen a ghost!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm just not very good with heights...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh... Hey! I've got it! Maybe you should face your fear and try hurling yourself off the edge? You know! One... Two... Three... Jump! It might be just what you need to get over your fear of heights!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, death is a real good way to overcome phobias alright. Anyway, it sure looks like a rickety bridge.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Can't argue there. That's probably why it's called, "Dusty Bridge".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Read it again, Maya. It says, "Dusky Bridge".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, it's practically the same thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like it's about 20 yards to that cliff over there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess that's where I'll be training tonight. Do you want to train with me, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And do the Special Course? I think not.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But it'd be so great if you had spiritual powers, too! <thought>Really? "I see dead people" sounds more like a cause for alarm to me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a narrow path going off in a different direction than that of the Main Hall.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The sign here is so old, the text seems to have vanished.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The path leads to a wooden staircase that goes down to the bottom of the canyon.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">OK, I'll write, "wooden staircase" on it then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Do you really think that is necessary? You'd have to be blind not to see the stairs.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, it can't hurt. Just pass me a pencil, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Graffiti is a crime, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, Nick! Why don't we hop across the bridge. It'll be fun!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not so sure... It looks like a bunny hopping across the bridge would destroy it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">OK, Nick. Then let's try to find a cute little white bunny and test your theory.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That right there sums up the fundamental difference between sane and insane.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Some letters are engraved into a roughly cut boulder.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"D-U-S-T-Y Bridge", huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It says, "Dusky"! "Dusky Bridge"! OK?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">C'mon, Nick! Take a look at that bridge and tell me it's not supposed to be "Dusty"! This sign is obviously wrong, and I'm gonna fix it! Now give me a pencil, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do I look like a pencil holder to you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can't believe there's a public phone here. Who would ever use it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The people who live here, I guess. I doubt they have any real phones there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, but it took like 20 minutes to walk here from the Main Hall! ... It would've been smarter of them to build the Main Hall here, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Maybe you should work on channeling someone who makes logical sense, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... So what's a "channeling dojo" anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh my, my, my... You don't even know that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Forgive him, Sister; for he knows not what he is saying.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well, well, well. Just call me Bikini and forget that "Sister" part. A channeling dojo is basically a spiritual power training ground. We have special holy items prepared here to help people boost their spiritual power.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Holy items...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">If you train an entire evening surrounded by these items... Aaah. It's quite mysterious. The spiritual power of these items seems to envelop you. Wa ha ha ha.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, she must have just gotten off the trolley from the land of make-believe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, so what exactly is the "Special Course"...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">You must be incredibly devoted to be interested in that at such a young age! It's a training session where you sit on a block of spirit ice and chant a spell... ...30,000 times! All while being showered in freezing cold spirit water.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eh...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">It's February now, right? You have to be careful this time of the year... If you don't watch it, you'll catch pneumonia or maybe even die of hypothermia... So be careful, you hear? Wa ha ha. Ho ho ho. Ha!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">How am I supposed to "be careful"...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh no... I knew I shouldn't have signed Mystic Maya up for this...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm, Sister... About this picture...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well, well. Look at that. I must say I look rather divine here, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, um, yeah. Unforgettable in every way.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">You mean it? Oh, I knew it! Wa ha ha ha! Ho ho ho ho! The makeup was pretty tough, but Iris helped me out.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Iris"...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">The cute little girl in the photo. She looks just like me, doesn't she? We're just a small temple here, so she and I run the entire place.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? That kinda sounds like fu--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry to cut in, but...! This "Iris"... Where is she right now?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh! Just listen to you! You haven't come all the way up here just to find a girlfriend, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... *glare*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, no! Th-That's not what I had in mind at all...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Anyway, Iris is in the Inner Temple preparing for this evening.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Inner Temple...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Yes, yes, that's right. Iris will be back this evening.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Why don't you go have a look at the Main Hall for now? Wa ha. Wa ha ha ha ha.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So she's in the Inner Temple, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Th-Th-The Main Hall... I th-think it's even c-c-c-colder in here! Achoo!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah! Mr. Nick! Do you smell that? It smells like meat and gravy!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, you're right! I guess it's pot roast for tonight! Yum!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Weird. I thought they would serve something a little more... well, traditional.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you talking about, Nick!? You think monks and nuns just sit around eating rice gruel all the time!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mystic Maya is right! Ooh! I hope there's mashed potatoes, too! I love mashed potatoes!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ha ha ha... What a cute little acolyte! Greetings to all of you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... Um, hello. <thought>Wow, this lady makes Maya look like a 6.8/10 on the weirdness scale.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Your outfit... Did you come here for the Special Course, too...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ha, ha, ha... Unfortunately, no. Actually, I'm...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Aaaaaaaaaah! Y-You're...! Y-You're...! You're Ms. Elise Deauxnim!</line>
<line speaker="Elise">Yes, that's right... You know of me?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-M-My name... My name is Pearl Fey! I-I'm your biggest fan!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Who is she, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... I see it now... Zvarri! A fortune-teller...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I-I've got all your books, Ms. Deauxnim!</line>
<line speaker="Elise">Ha, ha, ha... What a sweet thing to say. And please, call me Elise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, "books"...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick, don't you know anything!? Don't you even know who this is?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, um... ...An author, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Elise">Yes, and an illustrator. ...Of picture books.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Picture books, huh? Oh, now I get it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... I'm sorry I didn't know who you are. I don't get a lot of chances to really enjoy picture books.</line>
<line speaker="Elise">It's alright. I take no offense to that. My books are nothing but simple stories for children.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">And really beautiful pictures too, Ms. Elise! Your books always make me feel as if my heart has been purified.</line>
<line speaker="Elise">Ha ha ha... It makes me feel very happy to hear you say that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I do have to admit... She certainly seems like a kind, sensitive lady.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ms. Elise won an award last year for her book, "The Magic Bottle"!</line>
<line speaker="Elise">Yes... A friend of mine secretly submitted a story I had written to a publisher. They liked it so much that they asked if it was alright to make it into a book.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow... It must have been a really great story.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Maybe I should try to write a children's book, too. If I do, you can secretly send it to a publisher for me, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Elise">Recently, I've accepted a sort of... apprentice you might say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An apprentice?</line>
<line speaker="Elise">He calls himself Laurice... Laurice Deauxnim. I believe he's off doing some landscape sketches now... On Laurice's behalf as well, I'd like to thank you for your support.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Of course, Ms. Elise! Anything for you!</line>
<line speaker="Elise">Ha ha ha...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... Why did you come to Hazakura Temple, Ms. Elise? Are you here... to do some spiritual training?</line>
<line speaker="Elise">Ha ha ha... No, that's not it. I'm actually here to gather materials for a new book I'm working on.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow! I-I can't wait to read it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Pearls is completely taken with her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Elise">I wanted to do a book with a more Japanese feel to it this time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...So is that why you're dressed like you are?</line>
<line speaker="Elise">The children have a certain image of me in their minds. I don't want to disappoint them...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What can I say... She's really a sweet lady...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow, Ms. Elise, you're dressed up like a mountain nun!</line>
<line speaker="Elise">Yes. The good people here were kind enough to let me borrow this... I'm wearing training clothes underneath my robe, as well.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...I want a staff like that.</line>
<line speaker="Elise">You like the crystal sphere? It's real amethyst, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe we'll find one like that up here on this mountain. Good luck, Nick! I know you'll find me one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Deauxnim? What do you think about this?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! Do you think Ms. Elise is a suspect?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You may be Mystic Maya's special someone, but I won't let you do this to Ms. Elise!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A suspect? Why would I suspect her of anything? It's not like anything's happened.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Isn't it cute, Nick? Pearly's getting all overprotective of her new friend.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow! You mean you're cooking dinner tonight?</line>
<line speaker="Elise">That's right. Would you like to help too, Pearl?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes, yes! I want to help with whatever I can!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Pearls looks like she just won the lottery...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I'll help too, then...</line>
<line speaker="Elise">...No, it's fine. Please don't worry about it. Feel free to relax and explore the area with your friend.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh!? But...</line>
<line speaker="Elise">...Oh, yes! Please take this. I think it will be of help to you. It's a map of the area. We wouldn't want you to get lost now, would we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The "Inner Temple"... There it is, on the other side of the bridge...</thought> Well, if you insist, I guess we'll take this chance to go check out the other temple.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">OK! I'll see you two later then! Remember! You're not allowed to fight!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, Nick! Let's go! At least we'll stay warm if we keep moving!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Where did Sister Bikini go? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess she went to the Inner Temple... To go help that other nun out.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, right... I think her name is... Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah... That was it. <thought>I want to find out who Iris really is, but I'm scared of what I'll find...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa, that bridge was shaking like jello in an earthquake.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And at least half of the wood on that rickety bridge was rotting, I'd bet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Not to mention the last part only had like one board left on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's wrong with you? Your face is all green.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">C-Can you not pick on me for a second? I'm still trying to get over the shock that we made it safely across that death trap.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, I guess I'm a bit surprised, too... Yikes! That "temple" is in bad shape. It looks like it could collapse anytime...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess people don't use it too often. Is this really where you're going to train tonight?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That has to be it. It's kinda creepy around here... Like a ghost might jump out at you or something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A spirit medium afraid of ghosts...? Isn't it ironic, don't you think?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't care how much you pay me, I don't want to cross that bridge again.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No worries, Nick. No one is offering you any money.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's because no reasonable person would call that pile of popsicle sticks a bridge! The latter half of it was nothing more than a few planks of wood and some string!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, if we want to get back, we've got no choice but to cross it again, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Maybe I'll just stay... I've always dreamed of living in a little shack in the woods.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Wow, you really are scared, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It looks like this bridge is suspended by 4 of these wires.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...They're reeeally thin. Shouldn't they be just a little thicker...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, stop it! You're such a worrywart, Nick! If the bridge were really going to collapse... ...I'm pretty sure the boards would break before these wires ever did!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's wrong? You're turning into an over-ripe avocado again.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, wow! Look at these neat Buddha statues. Maybe I'll take one home with me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But there are so many. They wouldn't notice if I took just one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you kidding? Of course they'll notice! What are you gonna do with one of those anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Put it in the office of course! We can trade that wooden statue in the office reception area for one of these!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You know, come to think of it, where did that wooden statue come from anyway...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! There's a giant robot buried in the snow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Well, there's something buried in the snow, but... I think it's an incinerator.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh... Hee hee. But you've gotta admit it looks a lot like a robot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, sure... Anyway, I don't think it gets used much. It's looking pretty rusty.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Do you think this Giant Robo-cinerator can walk?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I told you! It's not a robot! ...And it's not especially big either.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Bah, you have no imagination. I thought it'd be real neat if you had to beat it to advance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A fight between a lawyer and an overgrown furnace? Who'd ever pay to see that!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! A half-opened gate! That's practically a welcome mat!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, except the sign on here says, "No Entry".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm, Nick. Rules are made to be broken, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You expect a lawyer to go along with that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, come on! You're such an old lady sometimes! Let's just go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't blame it on me when Sister Bikini puts a curse on you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Now you've got me scared. Um, let's just forget about it, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Looks like there's something written on it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't read it, but if I had to take a good guess, I'd say it says, "Inner Temple".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's the point of a sign if you can't read it? Must be tough for the mailman when he's delivering here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess the sign is a good indication of how long this place has been here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So that's the Inner Temple up ahead, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks kinda run-down.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, it wouldn't be very temple-like if it was all bright and shiny.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you're training here tonight, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup! Then everyone'll see my spiritual powers!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sounds like your stomach wants to show off its digestive powers instead...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder if that roast is ready yet?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Man, look at this place... It's just a tiny, freezing-cold room. So this is where you'll both be training, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? What do you mean, "both"? I'm the only one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? But I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pearly's just a little kid. She couldn't handle this kind of intense training.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So says the girl who I can barely hear over her bones chattering...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Anyway... The real training room must be behind that door over there. Yeah, I get the feeling it's back there, definitely.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If only because the cavern behind that door is giving off a real supernatural feel...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Um... Excuse me, but... Who are you...? ...Ah! ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You're...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hi there! We're just looking around since we're going to be staying here tonight...</line>
<line speaker="???">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...? Is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="???">Uh, er, no! It-It's nothing...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder why she spaced out like that. Don't you, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... D-Did you say something, M-Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Not you too, Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I... M-My name is Iris. I'm one of the nuns here at this temple.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm Maya Fey. It's a pleasure to meet you!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">The pleasure is mine... ... Oh, er, please excuse me! I have some... um, chores to attend to.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She sure is beautiful... and a bit spacey, I guess... I guess she's just not used to talking with urban sophisticates like us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That girl... It-It can't be, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look at this antique dresser. I wonder if there's anything valuable inside. Let's have a look... Hmph... Nothing! Just a bunch of clothes. Hey, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Huh! Oh, sorry. I was just... thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh? About Iris, I bet! Looks like you've been bitten by the love bug, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The actual training area must be on the other side of this door. I wonder what it's like. Phooey... It's locked. Come on, Nick! You know you want to open it for me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I can't.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... You've been in kind of a bad mood lately, haven't you, Nick? ...Zvarri! I know what it is! I-R-I-S.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ha ha ha ha ha! ♪Iris and Nick, sitting in a tree! K-I-S-S-I-N-G!♪</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A hanging scroll... It doesn't look that old either...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">AAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AAAAAAAAACK! Wh-What is it!? Why did you scream like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Th-This scroll...! It-It's my mother...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh... Whaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...It's Misty Fey. The Master of the Kurain School of Channeling...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are... Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes... The crest at the top of the scroll... That's the special mark of the Master of our tradition.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's what the mark means...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nothing... It's just that... I last saw her over 15 years ago... If it wasn't for that crest... I wouldn't have even known it was her. My own mother... And I can't even recognize her face.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a hanging wall scroll showing Maya's mother, Misty Fey. It's not that old. That crest at the top is the official mark of the Master. I wonder if this temple has some sort of connection to </line>
<line speaker="Maya">I think it does, actually. Supposedly, it was founded by a branch family member of the Kurain School.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll have to ask Bikini in more detail when I get the chance... About Maya... And the Fey family in general.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whew, we managed to make it across Dusty Bridge.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, you look green. Are you feeling alright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! What's wrong with you? Ever since we met Sister Iris at the Training Hall, you've been really quiet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!? Oh, um. Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey, you! ...Wait up!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...? You think he's yelling at us?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He must be. There's no one else around...</line>
<line speaker="???">Would you mind moving? You're standing right in my way. ... Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! I know you! You're...</line>
<line speaker="???">Whoa! Sorry! Gotta run! ...See ya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Hey! Wait a minute!</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, uh, nice to meet you. ...I'm Laurice Deauxnim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Liar! You're Larry! Your clothes may change, but you're still the Butz.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Shaddup! I'm... I'm... Lauriiiiice! And I'm just here to do a sketch of Dusky Bridge!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So... it really is our Larry. ...Not that I get why he's pretending to be someone else.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what are you doing with the last name, "Deauxnim"?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well I... I just... I wanted to start over again! With a clean slate!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A clean slate...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">You remember don't you? Last time?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The Mask☆DeMasque case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">After that, I started to realize I didn't like this guy known as Larry Butz! And that's when I came across it... The book of destiny!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The "book of destiny"...? Do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">"The Magic Bottle"! By Ms. Elise Deauxnim! It's so beautiful... So moving... So... So gentle. My heart felt cleansed! I-I was saved!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe I should buy a copy of "The Magic Bottle"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, Larry would make a great book salesman! I really want to get that book now, too!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">She's the most wonderful person I've ever met! I'd follow her anywhere!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, she certainly is a very elegant lady.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">You see? You see? Here's a photo I took of her in secret!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! That's a beautiful photo!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">You want a copy, don't you? It's OK... I just happened to have made extra prints!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Still, it's kinda hard to imagine you as a picture book illustrator... So tell the truth. You must have some kind of ulterior motive, right?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wh-What're you talking about!? I don't... I don't trust anyone anymore... Especially not women!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Talk about a bad case of denial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anyway... Can you even draw well enough to make a picture book?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Art isn't only about technical skill, you know. It's also about having a pure heart!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's why I'm asking. Can you draw well enough to make a whole book?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...! Hmm... Now that you mention it... I wonder.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It looks like you still have some doubt in your heart.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">It's true, I do... But when I first saw her, I felt it! Something inside me ended, and something else began.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh Larry, it sounds like you've fallen in love with Ms. Elise Deauxnim!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">No! Y-You're wrong! It's not her... It's the other girl!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Other girl"...? Uh oh... <thought>I got a bad feeling about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wow! You're even cuter than the last time I saw you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, really!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah, you look like a totally different person! Don't you think so, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe it's 'cause we're always together, but she looks pretty much the same to me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey, I remember her! That's Maya's big sister!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! You really do remember!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah, who could forget! A couple of gorgeous sisters! Hubba hubba!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You hear that, Nick! Gorgeous!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh yeah... That's right. When I defended Larry... Mia was still alive...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">I haven't seen her in a while, so I bet she's gotten a lot bigger.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it's only been 5 months since we celebrated Ron's non-guilty verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Maybe so, but kids these days grow up so fast.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...She hasn't changed a bit as far as I can tell.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Come on, Nick... I really doubt that. You just don't know 'cause you don't pay enough attention, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sometimes I really worry about what goes on inside this guy's head...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">She seems really motherly, doesn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What do you mean "seems" motherly? She IS my mother.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...She's your WHAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I'm gonna have to take a pass on answering that one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait a second. Why is he getting off so easy this time...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Elise is really something. She's like a mother to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, you can tell from the kindness reflected in her eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">When I first looked into her eyes, I just couldn't help it. I started blabbing about all the bad things I had done in my life. She just laughed that gentle laugh of hers and listened!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Are you sure she wasn't just laughing at you...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Whoo yeah! Her! My little Iris!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She's really pretty.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">This girl... She's perfect! She's exactly my type! I wonder if she would model for me. I want to draw a portrait of her.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, you always liked those model types, didn't you Larry? ...Hey, wait a sec! Didn't you say you were swearing off women...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh!? Yeah, that's right. Of course I have! I have... basically. But...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"But"...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">But... Iris is different. I feel like... I feel like I still have one chance left at the dream...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This guy will never change.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey, I know I may not look like it, but I'm an artist. I refuse to look at anything that doesn't have a radiant or beautiful motif.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Picky, picky, aren't you...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Pearly!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Dinner preparations are complete! Please come quickly to the Main Hall!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Alright! I can't wait to dig in, Pearly!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm going to go to the Inner Temple and call Sister Iris! I also want to have a look at where Mystic Maya is going to be training...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Boy am I stuffed...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure it's alright to eat that much before your training?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, this kind of training is a battle of endurance.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mystic Maya... Please don't do anything that might put your health at risk.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ha ha ha. No pain, no gain, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Nngh... I'm still worried about you...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well, well, well. Let's not dilly-dally shilly-shally. You must get ready for tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Elise">Good luck. ...Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Alright! Here I go! I'll see you all tomorrow, I guess!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Iris, please ring the bell at 10:00 for lights out, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, Sister Bikini.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">And then, after you ring the bell, I want you to come join us at the Training Hall.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I understand, Sister Bikini.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya and Bikini really seem excited about this training thing tonight...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Elise">...Well, Pearl? What are you going to do tonight?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Well, umm...</line>
<line speaker="Elise">If you'd like, you can come to my room. Perhaps we can read some books together.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">R-Really!? I'd love to! I, umm... I'm not very good at reading.</line>
<line speaker="Elise">Ha ha ha. Well then, would you like to practice reading with me?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah! I'd love to!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Pearls is absolutely smitten with Ms. Deauxnim...</thought> So Larry, what are you going to do?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh... Me? Um, well... I'm just gonna hang out in my room. I can't stand the cold at all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I totally hear you there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, Ms. Elise? So, for example, how do you read this?</line>
<line speaker="Elise">It says, "gravely"... That's kind of a tough word.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! OK! And what about this word?</line>
<line speaker="Elise">That's another tough one. It says, "roast".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What kind of a book is she reading anyway...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Well, I'm going to go wash the dishes and help clean up. I'll go visit you when I'm done, Ms. Elise!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, not much to do except head to my room and huddle under the covers, I guess...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... It's a whole different type of cold up here in the mountains! Argh... Why couldn't the nearest bathroom be just a little closer to my room...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yaaaaaaah! Oh! Ah, Ms. Deauxnim! Are you going to use the bathroom, too?</line>
<line speaker="Elise">Um, no. But... Have you seen Pearl?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No... Not since after dinner. I thought she said she was going to go to your room...</line>
<line speaker="Elise">I know... But she never showed up. I-I'm going to go look for her. ...Excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ms. Elise Deauxnim... A woman as mysterious in origin as her last name... But... The really mysterious one is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah...! S-Sister Iris...!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">G... G-Good evening...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The real mysterious one is this girl...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Um, are you on your way to the bathroom too, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I can't let this chance pass me by! I should try to talk with her... And maybe get some answers.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It's freezing cold out there. And dark, too. There's nothing I need to do, so I think I'll just stay roasty-toasty in here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... You're Sister Iris, right?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-So... um, when did you come to Hazakura Temple?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... I don't remember. Ever since I was a small child, the temple has been my home.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you've never left?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, I don't have any family left to take care of me... Sister Bikini... I've come to think of her as my real mother, as it were.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, I see... But you... Didn't you go to college? ...And maybe enroll with the Ivy University Literature Department?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">No, I never had an interest in going to a big university like that... My training is all the education I need.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But... Once in a while, when I get the chance, I make a trip to the nearby town. I can use a computer and a cell phone, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>That's not exactly something worth bragging about... But I don't see any Psyche-Locks... ...so I guess that means she's not lying...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">P-Please don't stare at me like that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What kind of a place is this anyway? I heard it's for training to increase your spiritual power or something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It must seem awfully crazy to normal people like you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I have to admit it is a whole different world up here...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I'm glad to hear you say that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Talking with dead people... Who does it help anyway? ...I hate it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Really? <thought>So then why stay in a place like this...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Instead of showing her things, I really need to just listen to her story! This girl... Just who is she?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I-I didn't realize it was so late. I have to go and ring the bell for lights out...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess it's almost 10:00 now, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">... Um... Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">If it's alright with you... I would like you to have this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But this is your hood...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It has the power to protect you from evil spirits.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come to think of it, Sister Bikini was wearing one of these, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">I pray for your safety on this dark, cold night.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I'm sorry, but I must bid you goodnight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a minute, Sister Iris...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Y-Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just now, you called me by my name... You said, "Mr. Wright". How did you know my name? I never introduced myself to you.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Th-That's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Sister Iris. Please, tell me the truth. You and I... Have we ever met before?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-Iris...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">O-Oh! It-It's almost 10:00... Perhaps we can speak again... tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So my hunch was correct... She does know me... I'll have to try to talk with her again tomorrow... ......... ...... ...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-What the...!? That blood-curdling scream came from the courtyard!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That scream... I'm sure it came from around here...</thought> ...Aaaah! <thought>S-Someone's there... On the ground...!</thought> M-Ms. Deauxniiiiiim!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I just stepped on something soft.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Hey! Don't step on my tummy like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What are you doing lying there in the snow!?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I was passed out! What do you think!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that blood-curdling scream was you...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">F-Forget about that! H-Hurry up and call the police!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is there even a phone in the Main Hall?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">No, but we still get reception up here in the mountains! You must have a cell phone on you, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, um... I didn't bring it with me--</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh, you're useless! I mean, even Iris has a cell phone... We've got no choice! You'll have to use the public phone by Dusky Bridge! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Run as fast as you can!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, ma'am...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">If you don't hurry, Iris will... Iris will...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...*huff*...*huff*... <thought>It's farther than I thought. The bridge is just up ahead. I have to go tell Maya what happened, too!</thought> ............ ...Aaaaaaaaaah! Dusky Bridge...! It's burning down! <thought>What the heck happened!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh? What is it? Is it me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Don't scare me like that, Larry! I almost had a heart attack!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">My name isn't Larry! It's Laurice!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry, hurry up and call the police! I'm going to the Inner Temple!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">D-Don't be stupid! The bridge is nothing but a burning wreck right now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Listen to me! There's been a murder! Here! At Hazakura Temple!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wha-Whaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The murderer might have fled across the bridge! I have to make sure Maya is safe!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">B-B-But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please! Call the police! I've got to go! ...Get outta my way, Larry!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">It-It's too dangerous! Nick, w-wait!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I must have been crazy... I knew how dangerous it was, but I still went for it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AAAAAAAAAAHHHH!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Niiiiiick----!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Weakened even more by the fire, the rickety old bridge's planks snapped and gave way. And as I was swallowed by the eternal darkness that surrounded me... ...a final, terrified scream rose up to pierce the frozen air of that harrowing night.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phone">*RIIING*... *RIIING*...</line>
<line speaker="???"><thought>Who could that be at this time of night...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes? Edgeworth speaking...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Edgey! Get up! It's an emergency!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Huh? Larry...? Do you know what time it is?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">It's not "Larry"! It's "Laurice"! Laurice Deauxnim!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>... This is nothing more than a terrible nightmare... I'll just roll over and...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">W-Wait! Don't hang up! ...It's an emergency! It's Nick! H-He... He took a really nasty spill!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, it wouldn't be the first time, so...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I'm not joking! His life is in danger!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What...!? What happened!? Tell me!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Talk about a guy with bad luck! He may already be dead! Anyway, you've got to come back! You're the only one that can help! My Iris... My beautiful Iris! She needs help...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Alright. I don't know what's going on, but... I'll be there as soon as I can.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I-I'm at the detention center! Please! Hurryyyyyy!</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's been one year since I left that country... I thought I wouldn't have to see him again for a while... Sounds like it won't be a pretty reunion... As if I expected anything to change.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">You're late, Edgey! What took you so long!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't want to hear it! I chartered a private jet to come as quickly as I could!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, you should've chartered a faster one! Anyway, just listen! Something happened to Ms. Elise... and Nick is... Maya... and Iris's Bikini... ...Huh? Say something, Edgey!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Before I came here, I stopped in at the hospital where Wright is. I believe I have a better understanding of the situation than you, at this point. The murder victim was the picture book author, Ms. Elise Deauxnim. She was found by Wright and the head nun. The suspect is the temple's younger nun. Then later, while Wright was crossing the bridge, it broke and he fell into the river. The hospital says that he'll need at least 2 days of bed rest.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Y-Yes! Th-That's right! You got it! B-But they arrested her... My sweet little Iris!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>And here I was, convinced HE was the one the police had arrested...</thought> However... I still don't understand what these two items are for.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They're things Wright gave to me when I was leaving his room. <thought>This is the first... He said some nonsense about being able to see into people's hearts with this... And the other... He couldn't possibly be asking what I think he is... could he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">I'm begging you! Iris's trial starts tomorrow! With Nick out of the picture, you're all I've got left! You're the only one that can represent her!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... What did you just say?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">You know! REPRESENT! DEFEND! What were you expecting!? Why do you think I called you anyway!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'm a prosecutor, Larry. A prosecutor. Do YOU understand what I'm saying? A prosecutor is a lawyer who...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Don't talk to me like a kid! I graduated from junior high, you know! Don't worry about it! I promise I won't tell!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But I...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I mean, I heard a paper badge had no problem fooling an entire court before!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...How could this country's judicial system have fallen into such decay!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Please, Edgey! At least listen to her... Listen to Iris's side of the story!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So Wright wasn't joking when he gave me this badge after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Thank you for coming. ...My name is Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Edgeworth. Miles Edgeworth. I don't know if I can be of any help, but... ...I will at least hear what you have to say. ...About the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">M-Mr. Wright! H-H-How is he? Mr. Laurice said that he... That he might even die...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Fortunately, he will be fine. <thought>Larry, you moron! How could you say something like that!?</thought> He was badly bruised when he hit the water, but otherwise he is unharmed.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... Thank goodness...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But, he's caught some kind of nasty cold.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">A cold...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He's running a high fever and is drifting in and out of consciousness.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I must be imagining things. This woman... I feel like I've met her before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The camera is glaring at me. "If something glares at you, it's only polite to return the favor," is what I was taught. ...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Um... Is something bothering you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hm? Oh, e-excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The guard is glaring at me. "If something glares at you, it's only polite to return the favor," is what I was taught. ...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Um... Are you alright, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hm? Oh, e-excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Going to a crime scene is akin to entering a jungle teeming with dangerous beasts. Before he goes there, a hunter needs to make sure he has plenty of ammunition. And in my case, that </line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Pardon me... Iris. I would like to ask you something, if you don't mind. I have the distinct feeling you and I have met before...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I-It must be your imagination, Mr. Edgeworth. After all... I hardly ever leave Hazakura Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hazakura Temple? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It's a place where those who wish to boost their spiritual power come to train. You need to undergo some very difficult training to release your inner spiritual power.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Spiritual power...? Did you go to that temple for that reason as well?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">No... I don't have any spiritual powers. I don't need them.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In that case, what are you doing at that temple then?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... I... I've committed some sins. Sins that I need to pay for. That's why I'm there, and why I continue to train... To purify my soul.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I want to ask you about last night... The night of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Alright... I helped to clean up after dinner, and then went back to my room at about 8:00. Later, I left my room to ring the lights out bell at 10:00.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Bell...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...We ring it at the same time each night.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... And then?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">A-And then...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I was told to go to the Training Hall, but... I went back to my room... and stayed there...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why didn't you go to the Training Hall like you were asked to?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...I-I was frightened.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>"Frightened"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">So I just stayed in my room and meditated... until the murder happened.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's more to her story.  I just know there is. Maybe  I should dig a little deeper.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You were asked to go to the Training Hall on the night of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However... You didn't go. Because you say you were frightened. What exactly were you so frightened of?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wh-What in the world!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Um... Is there something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'm sorry. It's nothing. <thought>It looks like she's not aware of them herself... These must be what Wright was talking about... The "Psycholocks"! I believe he said that I need to present this "Magatama" item to do something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I... I don't like to walk alone at night. And, last night was...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What about last night?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Er, oh... nothing. It's rather silly...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So there was something special about last night, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It looks like I have no choice but to break these locks...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So do you have any idea as to what really occurred last night?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...I think it was the result of the tremendous spiritual power that was unleashed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Spiritual power...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes. Spiritual training has been a cause behind many great tragedies. This incident was just another example...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Iris, I'm sorry, but I can't accept that. I'm a man of science. I don't believe in "spiritual power".</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes... I understand. Most people don't.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And I am certain that the thing that killed the victim was a human. So please, answer me this simple question... Were you the one who killed Elise Deauxnim?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... No. I'm not the one who took her life.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... <thought>That was foolish of me... It's not as if I can know for certain if she is telling me the truth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So do you have any idea as to what really occurred last night?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...I think it was the result of the tremendous spiritual power that was unleashed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Spiritual power...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes. Spiritual training has been a cause behind many great tragedies. This incident was just another example...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Iris, I'm sorry, but I can't accept that. I'm a man of science. I don't believe in "spiritual power".</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes... I understand. Most people don't.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And I am certain that the thing that killed the victim was a human. So please, answer me this simple question... Were you the one who killed Elise Deauxnim?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... No. I'm not the one who took her life.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... <thought>Those Psycholock things aren't appearing... I suppose that means I can believe that she's not lying.</thought> ...Heh.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't believe what I'm thinking... And here I just finished saying that I don't believe in spiritual power...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Is that an attorney's badge?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, this belongs to Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm actually a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh...! Then why do you have a defense attorney's badge pinned on your lapel...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, you see... I, um... I borrowed it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Who is the woman on this hanging scroll?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, I don't know the details, but... I've heard she's the Master of the Kurain Channeling Technique.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">M-Master?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes. Mystic Misty. She was a great spirit medium. ...That's what I've heard. I also heard that she went missing over 15 years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Spirit mediums... There's no such thing anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Mr. Edgeworth...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know all about them... They're nothing but frauds!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She doesn't know anything about it, of course... But there was a time, 17 years ago, when I met the "Master" myself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's called a "Demon-Warding Hood". ...I gave that to Mr. Wright last night.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He was wearing this when I saw him at the hospital today.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It's an important item for protecting acolytes from evil spirits.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If it's so important, then why did you give it to him?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Last night... I felt... something... I felt that something terrible was about to happen... I... I didn't want Mr. Wright to fall into its grip.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Well he wound up falling into something much deeper and colder... I probably shouldn't say that out loud, though. Thank god for inner monologue.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">...I was against the idea of our temple appearing in that magazine. I was afraid that... this type of a tragedy might occur.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In that case, why did you allow them to run an article about you?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It was Sister Bikini... She's actually rather fond of attention... Surprisingly so.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She certainly does look rather happy in this photo...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's Mystic Elise Deauxnim. She's a picture book author, or so I've heard.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Does she come to Hazakura Temple often...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">No... This was her first time. It's just that...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">She was a very important visitor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is that so?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, Sister Bikini told me, "Be certain not to offend her."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The victim, Ms. Elise Deauxnim... The prosecutor's office still doesn't have much information about her it seems...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Mr. Wright... How bad is his cold?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well his fever is very high. As a result, he's rather confused. He's worried about Maya, who is still trapped in the Inner Temple... ...And he's quite worried about you as well, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...Really?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... Naturally, once he recovers, I'll pass the baton back to him.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">No... Don't... I'm sure that Mr. Wright wouldn't want that... He wouldn't want to defend me.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh... That's Mr. Laurice.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'm sorry? Who did you say it was?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Laurice Deauxnim. He is Mystic Elise's apprentice, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Alright... Now who exactly is this guy...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">He's a very sincere, hard-working person.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Um... Did I say something wrong, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">E-Excuse me. I was temporarily at a loss for words. <thought>Take a trip... Come home... Be thrust suddenly into bizarro world...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">You want to know about me? There's not much to tell, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just let me get one thing straight. You were raised at Hazakura Temple, correct? And yet, somehow, you seem to know Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you two must have crossed paths somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...No, Mr. Edgeworth. Whomever it was... ...it couldn't have been me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What is that supposed to mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">I'm sorry... I don't leave the temple grounds very often... So I don't know very much about the outside world.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Thank you very much for listening to my story.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I visited Wright at the hospital before coming here. He asked me to take care of you...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...M-Me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, at the trial tomorrow... He asked me to defend you.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... If Mr. Wright has that much faith in you, Mr. Edgeworth... ...Then I will gladly entrust my fate in your capable hands.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But before that, I have one question.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you know Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Er... Wh-Why would you ask that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Whenever you came up in our conversation, he would begin to act a little... strange.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... Mr. Edgeworth... Are you his friend?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Friend? Well... In a sense, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... It was 5 years ago... That's when I... That's when I... deceived him.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You "deceived" him...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I heard that he was... in a lot of pain after what happened. I know what a weak person I am. That's why... That's why I thought it was best if he never saw me again. I wanted him to just forget about me, without learning the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Well, if you ask me, Wright is still suffering... And until he learns the truth, I don't think he will ever be able to truly recover. ...Iris. It's not too late. You should go to him. ...Tell him the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll defend you, but only if you agree to that one condition.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... Alright, Mr. Edgeworth... I promise.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Very well. I'll do everything in my power to get you an acquittal. <thought>That's enough information gathering for now. I should head to the crime scene...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It sure is cold alright... So this is it... Dusky Bridge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Ahem! M-Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Urk... Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Long time no see! It's been about a year? ...Or has it been longer?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It doesn't matter, Detective. What does matter is why you're shuffling around up here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, ouch! ...And there was a sharp left jab! Well, I'm happy to see you anyway, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let me guess... You were transferred into another section at work. A good choice. The vast amount of nothing up here must be quite easy to guard.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I heard you were back in the country and arranged to come all the way out here! Everybody was real nice. They even let me take charge of the investigation, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Gumshoe indeed! Like gum on your shoe, he's impossible to get rid of!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm supposed to report on the details of the crime scene, sir! Anyway! Here I am! Detective Dick Gumshoe! Reporting for duty!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Great. Um, thank you, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I thought Prosecutor Godot was gonna get here before me. That guy's a real mystery, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Prosecutor Godot?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It looks like a pretty good distance to that far cliff.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah... It's gotta be around 100 yards or so.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Detective... That's not even CLOSE to a hundred yards.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well... I gotta admit I'm not very good at judging distances.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's about 20 yards or so. And impossible to cross without a bridge, it seems...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's a little shack down that way called, "Heavenly Hall".</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A shack...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's like a run-down doghouse for losers that can't bear the freezing drafts of wind... Kinda reminds me of my apartment, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The name "Heavenly Hall" makes it sound like a palace...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Giving a hovel a great name is a crime itself! I'd call it false advertising! By the way, the name of my apartment complex is "Compton Castles"...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That's not such a great name, if you ask me.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, it's not such a great apartment either, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So this is the bridge Wright tried to cross?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Pretty reckless, if you ask me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm amazed he survived the fall from up here...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, he's one lucky guy, sir. Now I see how he manages to win his cases in court. Blind luck.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I think dumb luck suits Wright just a bit better.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Some letters are wildly engraved into a roughly cut boulder. "Dusky Bridge"... It certainly is an appropriate name.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You need to get some glasses, Mr. Edgeworth! That sign says, "Dusty Bridge". I can see how you read it wrong, though, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're the one who needs glasses, Detective. Try reading it one more time.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Ah! You're right! It's "Dusky Bridge" after all! ... I guess whoever wrote this made a mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! It's a public phone! You don't see a lot of these anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That's true.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Since we've got one here, why don't we take a photo as a memento!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, um, sure. Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, darn it! I don't have a camera with me! ...I'm gonna go buy a disposable camera! I'll be right back, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What's so special about public phones, and why is he so fascinated by them...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I just got back into the country, so I don't really know much about the case...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's simple!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, simple is as simple does, as they say.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, you've got no idea how much I've missed that biting sarcasm of yours, sir! ...But seriously, this one's a piece of cake. There's a witness that saw the whole thing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A witness...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, that Bikini lady.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Bikini lady"? Here? On this freezing cold mountain?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Well, you should talk to her yourself if you want the details, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I may have to talk to this "bikini lady"... I mean, "decisive witness" myself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So this is the bridge that Wright fell through?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup! I can't imagine being that reckless myself... "Look before you cross," is how it goes, right? Or was that "leap"...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And? Is there something on the other side?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, some old building they call the Inner Temple... But we can't get over there without a bridge, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nobody lives there, so it's usually not a problem... But someone was at the Inner Temple doing some training and now they're stuck there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I heard that from Wright. It's Maya Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh no... Her again...? Anyway, the air's really turbulent right now so we can't do an aerial extraction. No one's gonna be able to reach the Inner Temple until tomorrow, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Will she be alright in this cold...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So how did this bridge burn down anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We're almost 100% sure it was lightning.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Lightning?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So who is this Prosecutor Godot? I've never heard of him.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, he's a new guy... Showed up after you left the country! He's a complete rookie, but nobody can say a bad word about the guy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What kind of a man is he?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He just became a prosecutor recently, but he's good, sir. Real good.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If he's so good, how is it that I've never heard of him...?</thought> Is he the lead prosecutor on this case?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You bet he is! After all, "you know who" is right in the middle of it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"You know who"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Phoenix Wright, of course! For some reason, Godot has really got it in for Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, he seems to have some kind of a grudge.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what would be the cause of this grudge...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I dunno... Maybe he made fun of his mask or something.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>None of this is making any sense. I'd better look into this Godot myself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're telling me the bridge caught on fire due to a fluke bolt of lightning?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup. Last night it snowed for the first time in 3 days. It's a little unusual for lightning to occur during a snow fall like that... But according to the weather data, lightning definitely struck.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm, I see... This is a very detailed weather report... Almost too detailed... It even has the exact time that the lightning struck the bridge...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, that? We got that information from the witness's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Someone actually saw the lightning hit the bridge? Who is this witness?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Sorry. I'll go ask one of the local cops later, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? What's that thing doing on your lapel, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Is it really that odd?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You bet it is, sir! A prosecutor wearing a defense attorney's badge? That's like a detective with a license to kill!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Does this little thing hold that ominous of a meaning...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Have you ever seen this thing before...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, thanks a lot. I was getting kind of hungry! ...*chomp!*</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What are you doing, Detective!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ack! ...I thought it was some kind of candy that would fill me up, sir. Lately I've been feeling so hungry all the time...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh... Maybe his salary has been cut just a little too much...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's a lot we don't know about this victim... We don't know her real name, her background... We don't know anything really.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's rather odd... If she was trying to hide her identity, why would she become an author?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'll bet it was just one of those things. You know... She probably never expected to get so popular.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whenever something happens, this guy always shows up like he hasn't got a care. In fact, you know what...? Every time he shows up, I always wonder the same thing. "Maybe somehow he's actually the cause of all these incidents!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I wonder if Gumshoe has realized it yet... But you could say the exact the same thing about him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your face is more drawn out than the last time I saw you over a year ago.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">R-Really? I thought so!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, wait... It's not so much "drawn out", as "weary and tired", or maybe just plain old "thin".</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I thought that too, sir. My salary's been kinda on the low end... So yeah, my food options have been kinda non-existent. Off-brand chicken soup, off-brand spaghetti, off-brand bread... That sort of stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I thought you were really into instant noodles last year...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...I got really sick of the stuff after a while, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He's supposed to be Ms. Elise Deauxnim's apprentice or something.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I see.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, he drew a nice portrait of me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That's nice.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But he made me pay him 50 cents for it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'm sorry about that.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... You don't seem very interested in him, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I really don't want to talk about him. That's why.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I feel like I've seen this girl somewhere before! She wasn't from a prior case, was she?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nope, can't be. We did a database search with her fingerprints and came up with nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... <thought>I just can't shake this nagging feeling...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, everyone knows that you are quite popular with the ladies, sir... Maybe she's an old girlfriend that you sent to Dumpsville when you were younger.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">D-Detective! Where did you hear such nonsense from!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I didn't hear it from anyone. It's just sorta how I imagine you to be... sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...D-Do I really inspire this sort of frothing desire from the female masses?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I usually hear about promising young prosecutor candidates while they're still in school. But I've never seen or heard of this person.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I gotta admit... He's puzzling alright. He just appeared one day, big mug of steaming coffee in his hand...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... He sounds like an interesting man...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah... The whole prosecutor's office is really into double espresso macchiatos lately.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Look, I'm just your everyday, simple detective. Don't ask me such tough questions, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That's not something to be proud of, Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It looks like Iris is being interrogated right now.</thought> ...This place certainly brings back memories.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh yeah. Come to think of it, you got thrown in here once too, didn't you, sir? But you know what? I've never been in jail a single time!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I should think it's hard to land in jail when you're so harmless...</thought> Yes, well... If you're in jail, you don't have to pay for your own meals, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...*gasp!* ...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't get any funny ideas, Detective...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Too late, I already did.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>In any case... I guess I'll have to come back here later...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That camera is meant to monitor everything that happens in here. And right now, it's pointed straight at the guard.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The guard is staring at me with a puzzled expression on his face. Me... and the badge on my lapel. ...I get the feeling he recognizes me.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yo! Edgey! What took you so long!? I'm so cold, my brain's turned to sherbet.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I knew it was a mistake to race back to this country.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wh-What do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright is going to be fine, and the case itself isn't anything unusual... And I find myself taking a request to defend a woman accused of murder!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...H-Hey! Wait a sec! <cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> <cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn> What's going on here, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Um, it's hard to explain, but one thing led to another and...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What kind of lame excuse is that!? And you call yourself a defense attorney!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Prosecutor Edgeworth is a prosecutor, and that's why he's Prosecutor Edgeworth! "Prosecutor Edgeworth, Defense Attorney" just sounds plain old weird, pal! ...Right, Prosecutor Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I'm not sure what role I'm supposed to be playing anymore.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hmph! Dude, Edgey... I don't see you for a couple of years... ...and your heart turns to sherbet!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'd say more like sorbet. It is rather cold here.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Iris didn't murder her! Someone else did it! I just know it, OK!? So trust me on this one!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ever the romantic, aren't you, Larry? Nevertheless, I'll do whatever I can to prove her innocence. <thought>At least until I pass the baton on to Wright, that is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This gate looks quite old; strong enough to resist the weight of time.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's the Mr. Edgeworth I know! You got a real flair for words, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have always appreciated this kind of old, timeless elegance.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's exactly how I feel, too! Take this coat for example! Like a fine wine, it gets better with age!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even fine wine turns to vinegar and begins to stink at some point. ...I suggest you wash that atrocious rag you call a coat, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That must be the Main Hall back there.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A brilliant deduction, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............ Are you trying to flatter me, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm... A brilliant use of suspense to build the tension, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>According to Wright, the head nun has some important information. I can't miss the opportunity to speak with her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can see a small bell tower from here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, that just reminded me! There's something I've always wondered about...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Something tells me he's going to tell me what's on his mind, whether I like it or not...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We call a person who tells a lie a "liar", right? So why don't we call a person who rings a bell a "beller"? Or "truer" for a guy who tells the truth! Oh man, I'm not gonna get any sleep tonight!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I had no idea he was such a deep thinker...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose this type of thing is necessary up here in the mountains.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Say, this just gave me a great idea!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Something tells me he's going to tell me what's on his mind, whether I like it or not...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I've got an idea for a brand new invention! It might even make me rich!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">An invention...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah! A car that can travel on snow! I'll call it a "Snow Car"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So what do you think, sir? Would you go for a ride on something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Only after you take the first 1000 test rides.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Man, I'm telling you. Iris is so cute! Right, Edgey? You think so too, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What's wrong? Why are you so quiet?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To put it simply...Your comment has me highly concerned. Could it be that the reason you think she's innocent...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Come on! A girl that cute can't possibly be a murderer!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... ...I was right after all. I should never have come back.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">No, no! Don't worry! I see things for how they really are this time! Honest!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If I had a penny for every time he's said that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">It's just that... Well, Iris is a delicate flower. You can't force things too much. Know what I mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Huh...? I have no idea what you're talking about, Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh....Ah! Err. Forget it. I didn't say anything...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Larry, where were you and what were you doing on the night of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Larry...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What...!? Don't tell me... You think I might have done it!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Get lost! Go back on your chartered jet and get out of my sight, you creep! ...And I hope your plane crashes and you die!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I'll ask just one more time. On the night of the murder, where were you and what were you doing?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>As I suspected... a Psycholock!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">I'm sorry, man! You know me, I just don't remember! My short-term memory is a wreck, dude!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I need all the information I can get if Iris is to have any hope of being acquitted.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">B-But I've got nothing to do with any of this! I'm just a 25 year old jobless bum trying to be an apprentice artist!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If that's what you think, then get a job already!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">D-Don't look at me like that! I thought we were pals!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If we're friends then I'd appreciate it if you wouldn't hide the truth from me!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hmph, well... Sure... It's like, you know! See what I'm saying?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I have no idea what you're blathering about.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Come to think of it, when you were a kid, you were always saying, "When I grow up, I want to be a lawyer and defend people," or something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That was a long time ago.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">But see, now you've got the chance to follow your boyhood dream for a day! Edgey! You've gotta do it! You gotta save my little Iris!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... <thought>Grr... This is exactly why I hate childhood friends...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">...I still can't believe it. She was such a great person... But! Someone's pinning this murder on my sweet little Iris! Edgey! Please! I'm counting on you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well... Frankly, I was hoping you could give me a little more than that.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...Errr. Well then... I got it! I'll draw you a portrait! How about that!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Since you're kind enough to offer... alright.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">He was a good guy... A real pal to the end. When I look back now, I have nothing but good memories.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's with the past tense? He's not dead, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah, you're right. Anyway, the guy owes me. After all, I saved his life.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">If I hadn't called for help so quickly, he would have died. It's no surprise though. I used to be a security guard. It was all instinct, baby!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He has a point... He called me pretty quickly, too... I think Larry's pretty good at motivating people. I just wish he would try motivating himself once in a while!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh? Me? All you have to know is to remember not to call me "Larry" anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I'm a new person now. I've been reborn... as Laurice Deauxnim!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Alright, fine. Let me ask you something else then, Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Call me "Laurice"!! If you don't... ...then I'll call you... I'll call you... "Milise Deauxnim"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have a feeling that she's hiding something...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Could be... After all, she's shy and gets embarrassed pretty easily.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I don't think that has anything to do with it.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Why not? Look, I know all about this kind of thing. C'mon Edgey... You were a guy once! Lots of girls are like Iris. You know I'm right!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, you most certainly seem to have convinced yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Man, I love shy girls like her! It-It's just so... cute! You know what I mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Still doesn't listen to others, I see... I guess some people just never change.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey, I know I may not look like it, but I'm an artist. I refuse to look at anything that doesn't have a radiant or beautiful motif.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...He didn't even give it a glance.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">*sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! Hello there! Um, so how are you feeling?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Alright, I suppose. ...Huh? Who is this?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I... My name is... Miles Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">My my my. A handsome boy such as yourself is always welcome! *sigh* If circumstances weren't so tragic, I might just...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Please don't call me "boy".</thought> I'm sorry to trouble you... But I'm looking for a woman in a bikini.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well, you have found her. Now, what can I do for you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I'm sorry, but I don't see any bikinis...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Ha ha ha! If you ask nicely, I might give you a peek, big boy. Wa ha ha ho ho ho!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm... Mr. Edgeworth? This is the head nun, Sister Bikini... She's the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Why didn't you tell me that earlier!? This is exactly why your salary keeps on getting cut!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nngh... My stomach is already growling in protest...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">So... Um... What's the latest about my beloved Iris!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, first... I want to hear what you know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's flowing script written everywhere on the walls.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Man, I'd bet you'd have awful nightmares if you tried to sleep in here.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">This is our Main Hall, so it's protected by a variety of magic spells and charms... They're all designed to prevent evil forces from entering.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So if I slept here the uggie-woogie-boogieman wouldn't hunt me down for eternity? Alright!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Does this guy think about anything other than eating and sleeping...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! It's a warmed cat box! But where are all the cats?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It's called a "hibachi". It's for heating the room.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! Look at all these ancient straw frisbees!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Those are a type of "zabuton" cushions called "enza"!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Why are you giving me such a hard time? Huh, Mr. Edgeworth? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Because learning something new might actually be a good thing for you, Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's an altar with a giant Magatama enshrined on it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There are lots of candles lined up on it, too. You know... I haven't had a birthday party for myself in a while...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Maybe you should blow out those candles over there to make up for that.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth? Would you mind singing "Happy Birthday" to me?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">S-Stop that! Cut that out! Please don't blow out the altar candles!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That thing sure casts a strong presence over the whole room.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">This is the "Lesser Magatama". It's a precious heirloom containing a great many souls.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh...!? This is "lesser"!? What is the "greater" one like?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">The "Greater Magatama" is displayed in the Main Room of Fey Manor. It was supposed to be shown at the Treasures of Kurain exhibit... But, it was so large that they couldn't bring it through the doors.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There are more enza cushions in the corner of the room.</thought> ...What's that white piece of paper sticking out from under that stack...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm... Beats me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Would you mind checking that for me, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yes, sir! Here you are, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It looks like an old manila envelope...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Eeeeeeeeeeaaaah!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...What is it, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Th-This... This could be it! An ultra important clue! A super-special clue!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I suppose I should read it myself then.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It looks like a letter addressed to Sister Iris. "tonight at 10 at Heavenly Hall. ... ...unless you want your 'secret' to be exposed."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-This sounds like a blackmail letter...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nice going there, Mr. Edgeworth! Why can't I ever find clues like that!? You're an ultra-important prosecutor!! A super-duper prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, I suppose it takes a super-duper kind of dumb to miss a clue like this.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There are more enza cushions in the corner of the room.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nice going there, Mr. Edgeworth! Why can't I ever find clues like that!? You're an ultra-important prosecutor!! A super-duper prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, I suppose it takes a super-duper kind of dumb to miss a clue like this.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">First, I'd like to ask you about last night.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well, last night... we had an acolyte here for training. After dinner, the two of us went to the Training Hall in the Inner Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She must be talking about Maya...</thought> Approximately what time was that...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I suppose it was about 9:00 when we left here. Training lasts all night long. It's extremely exhausting. The channeling dojo's Head Nun must be in attendance at all times to keep watch.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wow, you're right! That does sound exhausting!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective, this is no time for flattery.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Some time around 11:00, you witnessed the incident in the courtyard. But your duty was in the Inner Temple. Why did you come back here?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Hmm... The way you're staring at me, I'm starting to get goosebumps! Ha ha ha ho ho!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh... I'm starting to get goosebumps myself, but for a decidedly different reason.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ho ho, you get the chills pretty easy, don't you Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Alright then... I'd like you to tell me exactly what you saw in the courtyard.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">It must have been past 11:00. Ah! No! I can't say it! It-It's too much for my poor heart!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! Calm down, lady! L-Let go of my tie!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...I saw two people! One of them was lying on the ground... Th-The other one was stabbing her from the back... with a sword!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Did you see this criminal with your own eyes?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I didn't want to believe what I was seeing...! ...But it was Iris!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You must have been quite shocked.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course she was! Try putting yourself in her shoes! It'd be like if you were stabbing Mr. Wright smack in the middle of a courtroom! And I happened to witness it from the witness stand! ...I'd be pretty shocked too.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I know it sounds insane... But that's what I saw. And when I finally realized what I was seeing, I screamed, and then... I passed out.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Unfortunately for us, her testimony seems to be pretty solid.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">However... The idea of Iris doing such a foul act seems... unnatural.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Unnatural"...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">The girl I know simply isn't capable of this sort of foulness...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I wonder what she means by that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As the head nun, it's your duty to stay with the acolyte at all times, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Yes, that's correct. I know I may look strong, but the truth is... I've got a bad lower back.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A bad lower back...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Yes, it's especially bad in the winter. So bad that I can't even lift a bucket. Do you remember how cold it was last night? My bad back felt as stiff as frozen glass. I just wanted to take a nice hot bath to ease my aching back... That's why I returned to the Main Hall.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you left the disciple all alone?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Don't be ridiculous! I would never do that! That's why I ordered Iris to the Inner Temple after she had rung the bell for lights out.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Yes, but she never went to the Inner Temple, did she? Did this head nun even see Iris? I think I'd better try to get some more details...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So who is this acolyte that was to train at the Inner Temple...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Her name is Maya Fey... I treated her very badly, I'm ashamed to say. And after she went through the trouble of signing up for the Special Course...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">"Special Course"?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">It's a training session where you sit on a block of spirit ice and chant 30,000 times...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You don't mean to tell me she's still doing that over at the Inner Temple, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">No, no, no. Of course not! You don't have to worry about that one little bit. Last night, we still hadn't started the training session itself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, um... That's good to hear.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...Oh! Dear, dear! There's one thing I forgot to tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Uh-oh, I don't think I like the sound of this.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Do you know that small girl? I believe she is Mystic Maya's little sister.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Maya has a little sister...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, you mean little Pearl! That's Maya Fey's cousin.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Little... Pearl...?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I thought she was going to visit Mystic Elise after cleaning up dinner... But I haven't seen her at all since late last night! She's nowhere to be found!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-You mean she...!? She was with the victim!?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">It's all the fault of my stupid, creaky old back!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A little girl who was with the victim on the night of the murder... is gone!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">As they say... "The plot thickens!"</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Th-That's...! That's one of the Fey clan's very own Magatamas! That's a priceless treasure you've got there!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">W...Wow! I'm impressed, sir! You never fail to surprise me!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Yes... You don't look it, but now I can see you're a real fan of the occult!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh, of course this piece couldn't possibly be real, but to have such a nice replica... Clearly, you are a big fan of the Kurain Tradition!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">W...Wow! I'm impressed, sir! You never fail to surprise me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I should have known better than to show this thing around...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Huh... Ahh! Well, well, well... Look what you've found! That's the Master of the Kurain Channeling Technique, Mystic Misty Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Fey"...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">It's been nearly 20 years since Mystic Misty's disappearance. Apparently, she intended to pass on the Master title to her daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Who is this daughter?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well, I myself am part of a branch family of the Fey clan. But even I am not privy to information concerning the main family...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well, well, well! That's a Demon-Warding Hood! Acolytes are highly susceptible to possession by evil spirits, you know. That's why we always wear these for protection.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">What are you waiting for? You won't get any protection just by holding it, you know! Put it on already!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No! I can't...! I was just...!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">... Ha ha ha ho ho ho!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ho ho ho! It's like it was made just for you, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you mean by that, Detective!?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">It looks absolutely marvelous! You've just got to keep it on for a while!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this some sort of divine retribution...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">About this picture...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Well look at that! I look pretty s-to-the-exy, don't you think!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, ah... Y-Yeah. Absolutely.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Up until recently, we've avoided exposure in such magazines. But this time we had our reasons...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is that so? For exampl--?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Ha ha ha ha ha!!! Well, why deny the world the sight of such a lovely face!?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...Ohhhh! H-How could such a... terrible thing have happened...? It's all... It's all... It's all my fault!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well come on, lady... I don't think you need to take all the blame yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Quiet! What do you know anyway!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Ouch. You're scary!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">With that stupid 5 o'clock shadow and that stupid old coat of yours... It's too bad that you weren't the one that disappeared!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... ...Why does she have to take it all out on me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Her anger does seem a little... manufactured.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you know anything about this old, crumpled-up letter?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">... Is that addressed to Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup, it clearly says "To Iris" on it.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">I can't believe it... That girl doesn't have any secrets from me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ah... So Sister Bikini didn't know anything about it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">This man... His face betrays a life of suffering and great weariness of the world.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Um, sure.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">But even so... I can't believe this guy actually jumped into the river! Think of all the fun things he might have enjoyed if he had just lived... Relentless spiritual training alone is no way to lead a complete life, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It sounds like she's got some major regrets she's dealing with... Hmm... Perhaps I should let Gumshoe explain Wright's situation to her for me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-Hey! Don't look at me like that! Do you own dirty work! ...Sir!</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">This is Mystic Elise's apprentice, is it not? I think he might have a bit of a crush on me... Sweet boy at any rate.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh, I don't blame him. Sister Bikini understands the temptations of young men.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Sure.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">But I'm afraid it wouldn't be proper to abuse my position. I am head nun, after all. But, in return, I did allow him to draw a portrait of me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I pray it was a pose that maintained your modesty. For everyone's sake...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You said you went with Maya to the Training Hall in the Inner Temple last night. Did you happen to see Iris while you were there?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Of course I saw her. I told her to meet us after ringing the 10:00 bell for lights out.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So you're saying Iris came to the Inner Temple then?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Of course she did. Iris has always been a good, obedient girl. After that, I had Maya begin her training ceremony.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>But that doesn't fit with Iris's story at all... She said that she never went to the Inner Temple!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">As they say... "The plot thickens!"</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">It's all my fault... Me and my stupid back! Mystic Elise has been murdered, an important acolyte is trapped... ...and a little girl has been lost!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You know you really shouldn't be so negative. It creates bad karma...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">...Quite right. I need to do some more training myself, I think...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">She's a very important visitor, you know! An honored acolyte!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Honored"? How so?</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">The Fey name is synonymous with the Kurain Channeling Technique. Therefore, she must be a spirit medium of great power indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Now that you mention it, one year ago... ...there was a case that was about the Master of the Kurain Channeling Technique!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Detective. I detest talk of supernatural drivel. I suppose now you'll say she has midi-chlorians?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ho ho ho. So it gives you the creeps, huh, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...That's got nothing to do with it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Oh, this poor girl... Where could she have gone...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, we checked out her home and she's not there.</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">And she's nowhere in the vicinity of the temple either...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Which means... ...there's only a few other possibilities as to where she could be.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! Do you think maybe she fell off the bridge and was carried downstream...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Why do you have to be such a pessimist, Detective!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nngh... I was just trying to think like you, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ironic. I became a pessimist only after I had the pleasure of working with you!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm, about this here...</line>
<line speaker="Bikini">Hmm... Let me see... Well, as you may know... In order to see reality for what it truly is... ...we strive to break our attachments to much of the transient, material realm. I guess you could call me an "immaterial girl"!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I guess she lives in an immaterial world, huh Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I'm just no good with people like her. She reminds me too much of my mother.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... May I speak now?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh? Sure.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't care how you feel about her personally... ...just tell me what you know about her and how she's related to the case.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... Don't you think you're expecting a little too much of me? I'm just a 25 year old jobless bum trying to be an apprentice artist! Ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I'm actually starting to feel jealous of this guy. ...Just a little.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hmm. I don't see Larry anywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Maybe we scared the poor kid away!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>His heart was shut tight with a Psycholock. I guess I'll have to look for him now... What a thorn in my side.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And this is where the murder took place, sir! Other than removing the body, we left everything else untouched!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thanks, Detective. I'll just have a look around. <thought>It looks like the police are still investigating...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh yeah, by the way... I thought I'd better ask, just to be sure... Are you really gonna defend that nun, Iris, at the trial tomorrow?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I will... I gave her my word and now I must follow through with my commitments.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, in that case... I've gotta be careful... Gotta make sure I don't leak the prosecution's whole investigation...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't worry about it, Detective. Just keep your mouth closed and I think most of it will flow out on its own.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Roger, sir! I know exactly what you're saying!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very well, Detective... <thought>Thankfully his diarrhea of the mouth is permanent...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a lantern... I suppose they light it at night.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's something elegant about the light of a fire. At the end of each month, I always like to relax in my room by candlelight.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective... Can you not afford to pay your electricity bill...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...How did you know?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's this...? It looks like a wizard's staff.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That belonged to the victim, Ms. Elise Deauxnim. There's nothing strange or magical about it. ...Oh yeah! Listen, this is just between us, OK sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... What?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is top-secret stuff! Don't tell anyone about this.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Alright.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The truth is... When I was a kid... I wanted to be a wizard!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">......</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's it? That's what you wanted to tell me?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This staff was made from a very strong kind of wood...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...What about fingerprints? Were there any on it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Just the victim's.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So the sword from this gold statue is actually the murder weapon?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It sure is. It's called a "Shichishito" by the way. Nasty piece of work, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's still blood on it... I suppose this is the victim's blood?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup. It's all over the blade. And speaking of "all over the blade"... There are fingerprints all over the hilt of the Shichishito, too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Fingerprints...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Naturally they match the prints we got from the younger nun, the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Her fingerprints are on the murder weapon...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... What's wrong? You're looking really solemn.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is this how it is for Wright? Is this what it's like to be a defense lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, I figure it doesn't feel really good.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...To be honest, it feels more like it's detrimental to your health.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Main Gate must be just over that stone wall.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah, stone walls... I jumped over a few of those in my time. ... Most of them are good memories, but not all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective... Perhaps someone should introduce you to the concept of paucity of words...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Main Hall of Hazakura Temple is above us here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey... You're right! But I'm pretty sure the Main Hall didn't have a 2nd floor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hazakura Temple was built on a steep part of the mountain. The front and back of the Main Hall are on different levels.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh... That makes sense... But wouldn't it be easier just to build the place slanted, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I fail to see how he can consider that to be an even remotely good idea.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! I just love skiing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Really? You don't um... seem like the type. Well, what about sleds?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sleds? Nah. They're a little too kiddy, you know? Messes with my "hard boiled" image.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...What's with the silence, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I...Is the world starting to go mad?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The victim is the famous picture book author, Ms. Elise Deauxnim. Her entire past, up until she won that writing award last year, is a total mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's hard to believe in this day and age you can still find people like that.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The estimated time of death of the victim was between 10:00 and 11:00 PM on Feb. 7th. Cause of death was blood loss resulting from a stab to the back by the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The murder weapon...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The victim was found skewered with a giant sword, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-That's terrible...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, but there's one strange thing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The victim's entire body was covered with bruises. The bruises are consistent with falling from the height of a two-story building.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A two-story building...? That would be about the same height as that room in front of us, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, you're right. Way to go, Mr. Edgeworth! That just happens to be the room that Elise Deauxnim was staying in!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Maybe she was pushed out of the window after she was stabbed by the sword?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Now then, Detective. Let's see if we can summarize what we've learned so far.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OK! Let's take a look at the map. ...According to the testimony of Sister Bikini, the head nun... ...she and Maya Fey headed to the Inner Temple right after dinner was finished. At 10 PM, after ringing the bell for lights out, Iris went to the Inner Temple. When she got there, Bikini had her take over while she went back to Hazakura Temple. After taking a hot bath to soothe her back... ...Sister Bikini witnessed the murder in the courtyard! If you want more details, you should ask Bikini herself in the Main Hall.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The Inner Temple, huh...? I'd like some more information about that place...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The trial begins tomorrow, but who's the prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm pretty sure it's that Godot guy, but... ...nobody can get a hold of him, so they're looking for a replacement.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's really weird. All of a sudden, no one can reach him! Hmm, I wonder if the rumors are true. Maybe since Mr. Wright caught a cold and won't be defending, he just lost interest.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I intend to appear in court in the role of defense lawyer. However... I would be quite unhappy if it came out that I'm actually a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, I can see why. But I'm not the one you have to worry about... I think the real problem is gonna be that judge...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes, he certainly would remember my face, even after such a long absence. That's why I requested another judge preside over the case. We've only met each other once. There's a good chance he won't remember me at all.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yeah, but... what about the prosecutor? Everyone in the prosecutor's office must know you! Wouldn't it be a problem if someone there made a big stink, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's no need to worry. I pulled a few strings and arranged for a prosecutor of my own choosing.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wow, Mr. Edgeworth... I had no idea you had such a powerful string to pull!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is this Inner Temple that Maya was supposedly training at...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">According to Bikini, it's an old building they use for training the acolytes. It's on the other side of Dusky Bridge.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The bridge that burned down, huh...</thought> Is there anything else on the other side of that bridge besides the Inner Temple?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nope, not a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nothing?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The other side is surrounded by cliffs on all sides... In a way, it's kinda like a little island out there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So the only thing there is the Inner Temple...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I hear it's not the kind of place a person could survive in.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Please be alright, Maya...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, so I think I might have already told you about this, but... The truth is... When I was a little kid...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You wanted to become a wizard, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, that's amazing! How did you know that!? So? What do you think? I'd make a really great one, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We just had this conversation a little while ago, Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This sword represents the multiple branches that life can take, all ending as one.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... I've never heard that one.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You know what I think about sometimes? What kind of life would I have had if I hadn't joined the Homicide Division.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...So you think about that kind of thing too, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course I do. I think about it a lot. Me as a traffic cop. Me as a detention officer. Me as the Blue Badger...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I guess he doesn't have any plans to leave the force.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is the witness who saw the crime take place out there in the temple courtyard. I'm pretty sure it's gonna be her testimony that'll be key to this case, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you mean she's going to be a witness in the trial tomorrow...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course! A nun is as trustworthy as you can get! We got this one in the bag! ... Oh. I-I mean, I've always been on your side, Mr. Edgeworth, sir! So yeah, this is a pretty tight spot we've gotten ourselves into, huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Now I understand why Wright is always breaking into a cold sweat...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wonder if Maya is alright? I could never show my face to Wright again if something were to happen to her.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aww, it'll be OK. If that ever happens, you can just show him my face. How's that...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ack! Um, I didn't mean it like that, sir! It was just a silly little joke!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wonder if there is another way to get across to the other side? The support wires for the bridge are still intact, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That bridge is almost 20 yards long... I know I may look like it, Mr. Edgeworth, but I'm no super hero.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>In any case, I just hope Maya is alright...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What about Pearl...? Has no one seen her at all since last night?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Seems that way... Apparently, she hasn't gone back to Kurain Village either, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But it's true that she was with Elise Deauxnim at some point last night?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No doubt about it. Ah...! Y-You mean that maybe whoever killed Ms. Deauxnim also...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">D-Don't jump to any crazy conclusions!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oooooouuuch! ...You sure have one mean punch, Mr. Edgeworth! It's down-right fierce!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah... Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I came back because I need to ask you a few more questions, if you don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But I... I've already told you everything that I...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Iris. Please remember. I'm on your side. You can tell me anything.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Y-Yes... Th-Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I just finished speaking with the head nun of Hazakura Temple. She testified very clearly as to what happened. She said she saw you stab Ms. Elise Deauxnim with a sword.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And one other thing. She said that when Maya Fey began her training at the Inner Temple... ...you were there as well.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">What...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">When I spoke with you last, you claimed that you never went to the Inner Temple. And yet, Sister Bikini says she met with you at the Inner Temple that very night.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">B-But I... I didn't go there! I didn't go to the Inner Temple last night.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... It looks like she's unwilling to tell me the whole truth. I wonder if I'll find the answers I'm looking for if I break those Psycholocks?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This letter... It appears to be addressed to you.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... I think it's someone's idea of a joke, Mr. Edgeworth. That's why I threw it away.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She's not giving me a straight answer for some reason. I'm going to have to find someone else who can give me more information about this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">I-Is that the murder weapon?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, it is. Have you ever seen it before?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Y-Yes. Mystic Ami was holding it... in the courtyard...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>And apparently, the head nun witnessed the whole sad affair... She saw you stabbing Ms. Elise Deauxnim with this very sword last night...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh... That's Mr. Laurice. He's a very sincere, hard-working person. He was even kind enough to draw a portrait of me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Knowing Larry... ...this woman is exactly the type that he would fall in love with at first sight.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'd like to ask you about Sister Bikini, the head of Hazakura Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">She raised me as if she were my real mother.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"As if she were your real mother"...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I was left at Hazakura Temple when I was just a small child. And she's taken care of me ever since.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Forgive me for sounding rude, but what about your family?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... I'm sorry, but I'd rather not talk about this.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh... This is the woman who was to undergo training last night. She seems like a very strong, reliable woman.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... <thought>Whatever else anyone has to say about this Iris woman... ...I can't exactly say she's the best judge of character.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">This is the trainee's younger sister, correct? She's cute as a button! And she seems to really love mashed potatoes and gravy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">She even said she was going to have the leftovers for dinner the next night... And then she took the leftover potatoes and the whole pot of gravy with her to her room.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's quite an appetite for such a little girl...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Since I have been handed this case, it is my duty to dig up all the answers. Understand?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Y-Yes, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The smallest flame can sometimes bathe a case in a whole new light... In my years in court, I've seen it happen over and over again. That's why I'm committed to searching until I have those answers. Now then, is it really true that you didn't go to the Inner Temple last night...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Y-Yes, I swear... I already told you that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes. You said you didn't go because you were frightened.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...Th-That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that's the case... ...then the obvious question is, "What were you so afraid of?"</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Iris... I wonder. Is this what frightened you so much that you couldn't even leave your own room!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps THIS is what you were afraid of! ...Well!?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I-I'm sorry, but... you're wrong...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Huh...? Why is your voice trembling like that?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It's just that... Your eyes... Your eyes are scaring me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Urk! <thought>Blast! I must be trying too hard to bluff.</thought> ...Please excuse me. I'm still not used to this role I've been assigned.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">N-No, I should apologize... I'm sorry for being such a scaredy-cat.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Anyway... I'm still determined to find the answers to this mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But I'm telling you, I really was in my room all last night.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I found this in the Main Hall. It is addressed to you.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah... Th-That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, Iris...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Why... Why are you glaring at me like that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You were scared of the blackmailer who wrote this to you, isn't that correct!?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Aaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Was it the evidence or the power of my glare that broke that lock...? Oh well, I don't suppose it matters either way.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">B-But, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I thought that letter was just someone playing a prank on me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A "prank"?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, yes... After all, even if I did have a "secret"... ...there's no one to tell it to that would cause me any grief.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Hmm... I wonder about that.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Sister Bikini is like a mother to me. I would never hide anything from her!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, you may not have anything to hide under normal circumstances. However! Last night was different.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unfortunately, I don't know the exact nature of your secret yet. However...! Whatever it is... ...there is one person you didn't want your secret told to!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...Mr. Edgeworth. Is it just possible that maybe... ...you yourself have a deep, dark secret in your heart?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...! Why do you say that...!?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">As they say, it takes one to know one.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>How could she have known about that...? Is she peering into my soul!?</thought> ...It's true that there is a deep-seated darkness in my heart. However, the only way I can get rid of it is to fully uncover the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You mean... the truth behind my secret?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Phoenix Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You mean something to Wright, it seems... And I can tell he holds a special place in your heart as well. That's why you didn't want him, of all people, to know your deep, dark secret. Well? What do you have to say?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... I should've expected as much... Especially from a friend of his...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">After dinner, this letter was waiting for me in my room. As I said, I was frightened by it...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is this "Heavenly Hall" the letter mentions?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It's a small mountain shack at the base of Dusky Bridge.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A small shack, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It's more like a broken-down shack that no one would ever want to go near.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... Where is it on this map...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...It's around here. To get there, you must follow a small path down from Dusky Bridge... The reality is, to get to the Inner Temple, I had no choice but to cross that bridge. But the thought that such a terrible criminal could be lurking at Heavenly Hall... I... I was so scared by the whole affair that I didn't want to think about it at all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So is this the secret that you locked away in your heart?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It looks as though I may have to visit this "Heavenly Hall" now. Maybe I'll find some sign of our mystery blackmailer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes. That's exactly right.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The trial starts tomorrow... I promise you, I will win. I'm going to win so that you and Phoenix Wright can see each other again.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But when I do... ...you must promise me that you will tell him your secret.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">... But it's pointless...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why would you say that?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Because I may know who Phoenix Wright is... But... He has no idea who I am.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whoa! Not much of a view down here, huh? It's still better than the view from my apartment, though.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tsk! Someone's here! Hide yourself, Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh! Why why why!? Why does this always happen!? Whenever I find a girl I like, they always run away! I even chased one of them to Tibet... Next it's going to be prison, I guess. ...I'll steal that detective's wallet. That'll get me locked up for sure. ...Nah. I can't do that to someone who looks like he's down on his luck.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...He's just talking to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Shh! Be quiet and listen!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I knew it... I shouldn't have done that! I blew it again...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>"Done that"? What did he do, I wonder...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! You! About what you just said... I got an objection!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wh-Wh-Wh-What the...!? Ed-Edgey! You dirty rat!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*glare* <thought>Gumshoe... You oaf...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-I'm sorry, sir! Before I knew it, I was shouting out, "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>". And in a loud, commanding voice, too! I even pointed with my pointer finger!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You've watched too many trials.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">OK, Larry, the jig is up. What have you got to say for yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Ungh...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is the Eagle River, sir. It runs pretty fast, so it doesn't ice over, even in the winter.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If it had iced over, Wright would have been in some serious trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You're right about that! He would've landed on the ice, and slid downstream to who knows where.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Not exactly what I meant, but alright...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a little far, but I have a pretty clear view of Dusky Bridge from here.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Ahh. I still can't believe it! ...Really.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...? What is it, Larry?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh! Err, uhh, nothing. It's nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sounds pretty suspicious to me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Something about that statement smells... And you know what they say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">These go all the way to Dusky Bridge. It's a pretty long, but easy, walk.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I fell down 4 times on my way down here, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh, sorry about that, Detective. I ate four bananas and tossed their peels on the stairs on my way down here...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... What!? So that's what I was slipping on!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Be careful on the way back. Those deadly banana peels are still out there.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm... That's a real important piece of information right there, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is this festive-looking ornament?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">It reminds me of art class in grade school. We used to have a lot of fun decorating the classroom with origami. Remember?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Well, I...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh, yeah... You were never any good at it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah, this guy was so bad, he couldn't even fold a dollar, let alone a crane. Everyone tried to comfort him, but he would just sit there sobbing.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Really? I never would have expected that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Be quiet already! I'll never forget the shame of that day! You want a crane! I can now make a perfect quarter-inch crane without a single flaw!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... You know, Edgey... Nothing for nothing, but a quarter-inch crane without a single flaw is not easy.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, that's quite a feat, Prosecutor Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Grr... This is exactly why I hate childhood friends...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's a horrible graffiti problem you've got there, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">You don't know anything, Detective. This is art! It's an expression of my bittersweet love for Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Larry. Do you know what the difference between graffiti and true art is?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... It's how the artist himself defines it, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... <thought>I should've seen that one coming.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, if that's the case, then all of my lunchboxes are masterpieces too, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The straw roof is totally covered with freshly fallen powdery snow.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wow, makes a nice image, doesn't it? I always did like the rustic look.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Heavenly Hall"... I suppose it's an appropriate name in some sense.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">You got that right. Look at that bridge up there. This place has to be heaven, because that thing is hell.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... You would do well to remember, Larry... ...that this is a sacred place to some people.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is this little shack anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, I just discovered it myself yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And why were you down here in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Err, come on... I'm an artist... I was looking for a good place to sketch. This is a great little place! It's err... artistic. It's quiet, it's cold, it's got no power, and it looks like it's about to collapse.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Sounds a lot like my apartment there, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>One thing's for sure... No one is likely to show up and disturb you here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">So can I get you something to drink? Some hot water, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...He's getting all buddy-buddy on us, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...Listen to me, Edgey. You've gotta do this... You've gotta save Iris!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why are you so sure she's innocent? Because she's cute?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Watch your mouth! Anyway, I've made up my mind about it! I'm going to marry that girl!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm... Mr. Edgeworth is pretending he didn't hear you, so I'm gonna ask for him. Have you already asked this girl to marry you?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">No, no. Not yet. But I can tell how she feels by the look in her eyes! She's got this "I really want this man to carry me over the threshold" look! I'm sure Nick would be surprised! He'd never imagine that I could marry such a beautiful girl like that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Something tells me he would be shocked, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's why I didn't want her to do anything dangerous. I mean, what am I gonna do if she gets hurt?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... What is this guy trying to say? He lost me about a mile back...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... If we really want to know the answer to that... <thought>...we're going to have to drag him onto the witness stand.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Come to think of it, you still haven't answered my question. Where were you and what were you doing last night?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Aww, man... Don't you have anything else to talk about? With that kind of attitude, you'll never be a ladies' man like me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">O-OK, OK! Chill out with those scary eyes! I got it! If you really wanna know, last night... ...I saw something incredible.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Something incredible"?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...Yeah, yeah. But let's not talk about that now. Let's talk about the good old days. What do you say? Come on, I'll pour you a nice cup of hot water.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why hasn't he realized... ...that I absolutely despise talking about the "good old days", especially with him?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What exactly did you see last night?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well... It's kinda hard to say...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">It's one of those things... Ya know what I mean...? It's like... It's not so much "what" I saw, as it's the situation in general... You see what I'm getting at? Whew, that's a relief. Thanks, buddy. Ha ha ha ha ha.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I have the strangest urge to smash this guy against those big, nasty locks...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's the staff that Ms. Elise was always carrying... M-Ms. Elise... Whyyyy...? ...... ...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is it, Larry?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">There's something missing from this staff...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's something missing...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh, it's Maya. Nick was trying to go save her, you know. But instead, he wound up falling off the bridge. I'm not surprised though. Nick always gets himself into trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Well if that isn't the pot calling the kettle black...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">I just hope that Maya doesn't catch a cold, too...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Or something worse.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh, hey! It's Pearl! But she's way cuter than this Pearl I used to go out with... Like, in a kid-cute way, yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, well... Apparently she hasn't been seen the whole morning.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wh-What did you say!? Edgey! Why are you wasting your time with me then!? What's wrong with you!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">If anything happens to her, I'll never forgive you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Wow, I guess he's right for a change, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Now I feel like I'm the bad guy in all of this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Alright, now you're going to tell me what you really saw last night...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Whoa. You're really upset, aren't you, Edgey? OK, I'll talk!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Huh? <thought>That was a bit too easy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah, anyway! It was awesome! Never seen anything like it! At around 10 o'clock last night, it started thundering. I'd been sleeping... I'm not sure for how long. Suddenly... ZING! The world in front of me went white! Like I'd just been slapped in the face by my old girlfriend, Naomi!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...And then?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">And then... It was on fire! The bridge was on fire!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Dusky Bridge caught on fire!? Are you saying you saw it with your own eyes?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey! Why are you giving me the evil eye!? I'm telling the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... There are still 3 Psycholocks remaining... That means he's still trying to hide something...</thought> By the way, Larry... Where were you when you saw that happen?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wh-Wh-Wh-Where you say? Wh-Wh-What do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you mean, "What do I mean"!? ...Just answer the question!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I-I was in my own room... by the Main Hall! Where else would I be!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As usual, you're as transparent as an empty jelly jar. The problem, I suspect, lies there...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Th-Th-Th-Th-There? Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Whaddya mean th-th-there?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's impossible for you to have seen lightning strike Dusky Bridge from your room!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Look at this, Larry!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... Hey, forget about that. Try drinking your hot water. If you don't drink it fast it's going to get cold.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh, sorry... <thought>It's cold alright... The water... And my evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well? Have you calmed down yet?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Um, yes... I'm going to think it over again.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">H-Hey, I'm telling you... there's nothing to think over! I was in my room doing "she loves me, she loves me not" with a bunch of flowers.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is a map of the area. Take a look around the vicinity of Hazakura Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wh-What am I looking for?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think that should be fairly obvious. The Main Hall is surrounded by trees and it's impossible to see the bridge from here.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What...!? Why didn't you tell me that before!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Well? How about it?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">How about what?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you feel like talking now?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">About what?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... <thought>It looks like it won't be that easy after all...</thought> ...You leave me no choice. I'll have to move on to the next step. You weren't in your room at the temple. So then... Where were you?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Y-Y-You don't know that I wasn't in my room!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So where was Larry, and why was he there...? If I've read the situation up to this point correctly, the answer is fairly obvious.</thought> ...Very well then. Let's test my theory. The place you witnessed lightning striking Dusky Bridge from was... here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is where you were! Well, what do you think, Larry!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh... Not much I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I'm sorry, but what kind of answer is that?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, you were just making small talk, right? Like "How are you doing?" or something.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Larry. Look at the expression on my face. Do I look like I was just making small talk?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">To be honest? No... I guess not. Ha ha ha ha ha...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It appears I didn't think it through carefully enough.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The place you saw the lightning strike from was naturally Heavenly Hall!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...Wh-Why would I be hanging out in this old shack? It's freezing cold, there's no electricity, and it could fall apart at any minute...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Larry... How do you know that anyway? How do you know there's no electricity? After all, it's not that dark yet.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Ah... Uh-oh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In other words, you have just provided evidence to prove my theory... My theory that you've at least once in your life visited Heavenly Hall after sunset!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I have to admit I'm impressed, Edgey! You're in a totally different league from Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That's nice. Now tell me. What were you doing at this cold little shack last night?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's what you might call... A "Fair de Core".</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think you mean "affaire de coeur". Could it be you were... waiting for someone?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Ooooh nooo! Y-You really are one scary guy, you know...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe that last night, you were waiting for this person to come meet you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>> </line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Well, Larry!? Was it THIS person...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...You know what? You should save your finger pointing for the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tsk...!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">It's no wonder people call you a workaholic. You work too hard! You should be like me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Well, I'd rather "work too hard" than "hardly work" like a loafaholic like you...</thought> In any case... I know you were waiting for someone!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah, but... It's like I said. It's an "affaire de guerre".</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, Larry. You mean "affaire de coeur". At least I think you do.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's only one person you'd wait for in a horrible place like this, Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I told you before... Don't call me "Larry"...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The person you were waiting for was... Iris!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Ohh... Suddenly I feel cold all over, Edgey.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No doubt because of my chilly glare.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">So you think I got the hots for Sister Iris, huh...? D-Do you have some kind of evidence!? You got something that proves I was waiting for her!? Or are you just guessing?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This is where I draw the line and end this ridiculous little game...</thought> Here's the evidence that you were waiting for Iris...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I-Is it just me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, I'm the one that suddenly feels cold...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Maybe it's because of my cold laugh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Grr... I hate making such stupid mistakes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Do you really have the evidence you say you do, Edgey?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Here's your evidence. You called her to this spot with a pathetic blackmail letter!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh! H-Hey! G-G-Give that back! You're embarrassing me! What are you doing with that anyway!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's not important! ...I misjudged you, Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Taking advantage of a woman's frailty like that! You should be ashamed of yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Ohhh... OHHHH!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">First of all, what's this at the top of the letter? It says, "Salutation here"!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">W-Well that's what it said in that book, "Letter Writing for Dummies"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're not supposed to actually write that! That's where you're supposed to write, "Dear Iris,"!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">WAAAAAAAAH!!! I'M SO SOOORRY!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you were here in Heavenly Hall last night, were you not, Larry? And you saw the lightning hit Dusky Bridge, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">S-Sorry, Edgey...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry doesn't cut it, you scumbag! Threatening a young lady like that...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">*gulp*... ... Wait, hold up.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...What now, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What are you talking about!? What "threatening" stuff!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'll tell you what! You tried to scare Iris by threatening to expose her secret, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What do you mean threaten!? When did I threaten her!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">"...unless you want your 'secret' to be exposed..." That sure sounds like a threat to me, pal! Blackmail, in fact!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Gimme a break! It's a love letter! Haven't you ever been in love!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What did you just say!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">My love for her burns so hotly, it could melt all the snow on this mountain!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">O-Oh? Then what is this secret you mention!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Come on, Edgey... Don't you get it? I'm talking about the secret love between her and me! Obviously she wouldn't want old lady Bikini to know about it, right...? About our... hot and sour... bittersweet love affair!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Alright, then why did you send a love letter in a business-like manila envelope!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Give me a break! It's not my fault I didn't have any other envelopes! Yeesh!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Then why were you so quick to apologize, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">It's cuz Edgey gave me that scary look of his!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... ...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What's wrong, Edgey? Why are you so quiet all of a sudden?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's it? That's all those huge locks were about? I-I don't understand why you were so defensive...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, I dunno either... I guess the thing is... ...you shouldn't expect too much from a guy like me. ...Hey, come on. Don't let it get you down!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you mean, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't forget what this guy said just a minute ago!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">If you really wanna know, last night... ...I saw something incredible.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... He's right!</thought> Larry!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wh-What!? Y-You're looking at me like a hungry dog that just found a bone!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What was this "something incredible" you saw last night...? ...You're going to tell me, Larry! One way or another!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I... I already told you, didn't I? I saw lightning strike Dusky Bridge!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and I believe it was the incredible sight you saw. But now that I think about it, something doesn't quite ring true.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wh-What doesn't?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that's all there is to your story, your heart wouldn't have had all those locks! Yes, Larry... I believe you saw something last night. Something more incredible than lightning.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... Wh-What!? Wh-When!? Wh-Where!? Wh-Why!? H-How!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! What do you think you're doing!? If you hide anything from Mr. Edgeworth, I'll arrest you on the spot, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Ah... Aaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Nooooooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What's wrong, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">D-Does this mean I have to do it all over again?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wh-Why are you glaring at me like I'm next to be hit by a bolt of lightning!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I've just about had it with this harlequin... If I really want to drag the truth out of him... ...I'll just have to drag him to the witness stand!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There aren't any clues here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It looks like I still don't have enough information. I need to investigate further and gather some more evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Blast it...! I've made too many errors...!</thought></line>
</xml>