<xml>
<title>English Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Guard">Who's there?! Is somebody there? It's probably nothing, but... Hey, what are you doing?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... I'm feeling queasy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, Nick! It's just like I said!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... M-Maya. What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're such a worrywart. I knew you'd get all jittery before the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not like that! It's just...I didn't expect to have to stand in a foreign court...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, we don't know much about the court system here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Legal League of Attorneys would like this to be an exemplary case.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm. So that'd make you an exemplary attorney. I hope you don't infect any British lawyers with your nervous attitude.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're making it sound like I'm a virus or something... My name is Phoenix Wright. I'm a defence attorney. And this is Maya Fey, my...uhm...assistant, of sorts.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Of sorts"?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess I should explain why she's dressed up like that... But it's a long story and we don't have the time. We've come to England on the Legal League of Attorneys' exchange. I'm acting as a representative of the American Legal League...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, they probably sent you because you don't ever seem to be busy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We weren't supposed to stand in court, so we thought it'd be like a vacation. But here we are. As usual, we've been dragged into a strange case.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick. So, what do you suppose this trial's all about? What if it was this?! Look, check out today's newspaper. "Elusive jewel thieves at large in London! Scotland Yard on red alert!" Wouldn't THAT be cool?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh. Maya, don't get your hopes up. We're here on an exchange. It should be a simple, textbook trial.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">London's a big city. What are the odds of us getting a case like that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, that's boring.</line>
<line speaker="???">...Sorry to have kept you waiting.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">How do you do? I am Ms Darklaw, teacher at the Owl Cote School for Young Women. Espella, this man is your defence lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Pleased...to meet you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix Wright, attorney at law. Pleased to meet you.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhm... I'm Phoenix Wright, your attorney. Pleased to meet you...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's with this girl? Can't she hear me?</thought> Is this girl...the defendant in today's case?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">That is correct. She's the pupil I'd like you to represent. She's pleading guilty, so there's not much you need to do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pleading guilty...?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I suggest you accept the punishment proposed by the prosecution.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what...? <thought>What kind of request is that...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhm, Espella? ...What are you accused of?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Have you not received the case materials?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, we haven't. And we weren't told anything...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">My, my. Forgive me for this oversight. Here, this is the case file.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Well then. I entrust Espella to you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's... Wait, WHAT? <thought>No way! I didn't even have time to look through the case file!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Espella, please be a good girl and don't cause any trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ ...I'm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......! <thought>Did she just mumble something?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm...not a witch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E...Espella? What did you just say?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And so, another trial begins. And as always, I've got no idea what's going to happen!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">All right! Let's do it, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court is now in session for the trial of Espella Cantabella.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">The prosecution is ready, Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How about the defence? Are you ready?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh...uhm... Yes, well I guess you could call it "ready", Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Hmph. I hear it's your first appearance in a British court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">The Legal League of Attorneys' exchange, was it? Sounds like fun. Hope you're enjoying the sights. You can take it easy today. Don't worry, Prosecutor Flynch will take care of everything!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's treating us like amateurs, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh boy... This looks bad. Can I really defend this girl?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, I see. Well, since this is your first case here... I will ask you a few simple questions, to make sure we're on the same page.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh! Er, yes. That's...that's fine by me. <thought>Dang, time to sink or swim.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Answer my questions, then, Mr Wright. What is the name of the defendant?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's, uhm... It's Phoenix, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-what?! What are you saying, Nick?! The "defendant" is the person accused of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Why don't you move over to the defendant's seat then, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh. I'd...I'd rather not. <thought>That was bad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really, Nick, you should think sometimes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I will ask you once more.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That would be Darklaw, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-what?! What are you saying, Nick?! The "defendant" is the person accused of the crime! Get your act together or Ms Darklaw might just sue you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess the pressure got to me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I will ask you once more.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That would be Espella Cantabella, Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Phew, that's the first hurdle...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Hmph. I see you're terribly proud of yourself for answering that basic question.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's move on to the next question. What is the nature of the offence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmmm...what crime is Espella accused of?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, Espella seems like such a timid girl. You think it's something minor, like shoplifting?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe. I wouldn't call it "minor", though... <thought>It can't be anything major like that large-scale jewel theft...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please answer the question. Can you name the two offences?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhm... <thought>Did he just say "two"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! Think! What other petty offence could it be?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know! I'm clueless about this case. We weren't told anything about it at all!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">My, my. Could it be that our esteemed visitor left his common sense back home?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">All the evidence is in the Court Record. You haven't forgotten that, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... <thought>That's it! The Court Record...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right! That's what you always refer to! The Court Record! Touch the Court Record icon to view it at any time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yeah, it just slipped my mind... <thought>It must be the nerves...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, let's check it now! Touch Court Record!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The Court Record holds all the evidence from this case. I'd better take a look!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Right, defence, you've had enough time to ponder my question. What is Miss Cantabella accused of?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It might be...fraud and assault.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"It might be", Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Oh ho ho... I thought you were a barrister, but it seems you are nothing but a swindler.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I...ugh...I'm sorry. <thought>How could I make that mistake?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">She didn't do that, Nick! Only a fraud would accuse a cute girl like Espella of fraud! Check the Court Record! All the info is in there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right. I need to touch the Court Record icon...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It might be...murder and theft.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait, Nick! You're wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What do you mean, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's no way that Espella killed anyone!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Ho ho ho. Some barristers only make matters worse for their clients.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's right, Nick! If you keep this up, it'll be your fault when Espella's found guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right... I'd better think again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Check the Court Record! All the info is in there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right. I need to touch the Court Record icon...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, according to the Case Outline, it was theft and assault.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Indeed. What disgusting crimes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Is that correct, defendant?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No kidding... She doesn't look like a violent girl, at least not to me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now that that's settled... Prosecutor Flynch. Please briefly outline the case for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Yes, Your Honour. The incident took place on a small freighter, moored at a harbour on the River Thames. The freighter was carrying goods away from London. The defendant illegally boarded the ship and tried to steal some of its cargo...but she was discovered by a crew member and captured by the ship's security guard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So she was caught red-handed...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">And she violently resisted when found by the crew member?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Violently resisted"...?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Indeed. She picked up a steel pipe and hit the crew member on the head.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds pretty vicious...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So that's the "assault" she's accused of...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what did the defendant attempt to steal from the freighter?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">A stuffed toy, Your Honour. It's the Metropolitan Police mascot, PC Badger.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, Nick! I want one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I see that "mascot" made a career for itself in England. Who would've thought...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think we all have a clear picture of the incident now. The prosecution may begin.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">The prosecution calls its first witness. Bring him in!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's something fishy about this trial... And there's something even fishier about my client... There isn't an ounce of expression on her face... I'd better keep my eyes wide open!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Witness, state your name and profession.</line>
<line speaker="???">............ A ship is always at risk...at every hour, minute and second! That's where I come in. I am a peacekeeper...the one and only guardian to an otherwise defenceless ship! The name's Smiles. Johnny Smiles... Security guard supreme.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Er...yes. According to the police report, the witness was patrolling the freighter on the night of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yeah...I was! Patrolling the freighter! And my expertly trained eyes leave nothing unseen!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll go blind if he keeps smiling like that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr Smiles. We would like to hear your testimony. Describe what happened during your night patrol.</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yessir! Johnny Smiles will reveal all!</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">That night, I went on patrol as usual, ZZZO.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph... And so... The woman you arrested was...?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">It was the defendant, Espella Cantabella, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">And as per standard patrolling procedure, all lights were on and you saw her clearly. Is that correct, Mr Smiles?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Y-yessir! I am an expert after all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? Is it just me or did he hesitate before saying that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yessir! <thought>Argh! I'm starting to talk like that guy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Let us see now how skilled our visiting barrister is.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph, yes. By the way, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, Your Honour?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Our cross-examination process should be the same as anywhere else... But just in case, would you like to have it explained to you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The cross-examination procedure... Should I ask for an explanation?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm...well, I guess it wouldn't hurt to refresh my memory...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! What are you thinking?! That prosecutor is already patronising us. Just imagine what he'll be like if you ask!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... It's my first time in a British court... I'm kind of nervous. And my mind's just gone completely blank.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... Anyway, what you do is listen to the guard's testimony really carefully. Then, if something's suspicious, you press the witness and see what happens.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Press, huh... It does sound just like what I've always been doing.</thought> Got it, Maya. I'll do my best.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, thank you, I'm fine. <thought>I press the witnesses on all suspicious statements to gather information. And when there's a contradiction, I present evidence, just like I always do!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, let's do it, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence may now cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">That night, I went on patrol as usual, ZZZO.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Ah, that's right, it's not something you'd know, not being a security professional. That's our special jargon. It's how we talk about the time in our trade!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Let me get this straight, "Mr Professional": you're using LETTERS...to tell the time...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Smiles">See, "ZZZO" stands for "22:20", which is 10:20pm!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh...right. So, "10:20pm"...? That's very accurate. How can you be so sure about the time?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Um, well. That's when the TV show I always watch in the security room ends.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">TV show...?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">I'm meant to do the rounds at 10:00pm, but for a pro like me it's just a guideline.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That doesn't sound very "professional"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Anyway, I was patrolling the ship, like I do every night!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Your Honour, may I?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, Prosecutor Flynch?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">I would like to get the events straight, while referring to this Crime Scene Photo. The defendant and the crew member were fighting in the back of the cargo hold, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yessir! They were fighting right under that emergency light.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Some items are spilling out of the broken crate.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Indeed, that crate was broken by the defendant, with a steel pipe. Incidentally, the items we can see spilling out are stuffed toys depicting London's own police mascot, PC Badger.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. The Crime Scene Photo shall be added to the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness may continue his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Ah, that's right, it's not something you'd know, not being a security professional. That's our special jargon. It's how we talk about the time in our trade!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Let me get this straight, "Mr Professional": you're using LETTERS...to tell the time...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Smiles">See, "ZZZO" stands for "22:20", which is 10:20pm!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh...right. So, "10:20pm"...? That's very accurate. How can you be so sure about the time?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Um, well. That's when the TV show I always watch in the security room ends.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">TV show...?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">I'm meant to do the rounds at 10:00pm, but for a pro like me it's just a guideline.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That doesn't sound very "professional"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Anyway, I was patrolling the ship, like I do every night!</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">My keen ears latched on to some suspicious noises coming from the cargo hold.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">That's right! An expert of my calibre can always tell when a noise is suspicious! When my smiley sense starts tingling, it means there's a crime taking place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...So can you tell us more about the noises you heard?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">It was...that's right. The sound of two women fighting! Naturally, I sprang into action. And I arrived at the crime scene in the blink of an eye!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In other words...you went to the cargo hold because you heard strange noises, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yes. That's about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm back to where I started...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Your Honour, may I?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, Prosecutor Flynch?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">I would like to get the events straight, while referring to this Crime Scene Photo. The defendant and the crew member were fighting in the back of the cargo hold, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yessir! They were fighting right under that emergency light.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Some items are spilling out of the broken crate.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Indeed, that crate was broken by the defendant, with a steel pipe. Incidentally, the items we can see spilling out are stuffed toys depicting London's own police mascot, PC Badger.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. The Crime Scene Photo shall be added to the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness may continue his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">That's right! An expert of my calibre can always tell when a noise is suspicious! When my smiley sense starts tingling, it means there's a crime taking place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...So can you tell us more about the noises you heard?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">It was...that's right. The sound of two women fighting! Naturally, I sprang into action. And I arrived at the crime scene in the blink of an eye!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In other words...you went to the cargo hold because you heard strange noises, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yes. That's about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm back to where I started...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Smiles">I sprinted at full speed to the cargo hold, but I was too late to stop the blow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">The defendant, Ms Cantabella, hit the crew member with a steel pipe, didn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yes, that's right! As I opened the door to the cargo hold, the defendant struck the victim's head. Had I arrived a second earlier, I would have gladly stopped the blow with my own head!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't think a second would have made much of a difference...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't take this "expert" too seriously, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">The witness saw the defendant deal the blow, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yessir! I expertly witnessed the crime scene with my very own sparkling eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is that so... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Your Honour, may I?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, Prosecutor Flynch?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">I would like to get the events straight, while referring to this Crime Scene Photo. The defendant and the crew member were fighting in the back of the cargo hold, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yessir! They were fighting right under that emergency light.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Some items are spilling out of the broken crate.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Indeed, that crate was broken by the defendant, with a steel pipe. Incidentally, the items we can see spilling out are stuffed toys depicting London's own police mascot, PC Badger.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. The Crime Scene Photo shall be added to the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness may continue his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">The defendant, Ms Cantabella, hit the crew member with a steel pipe, didn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yes, that's right! As I opened the door to the cargo hold, the defendant struck the victim's head. Had I arrived a second earlier, I would have gladly stopped the blow with my own head!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't think a second would have made much of a difference...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't take this "expert" too seriously, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">The witness saw the defendant deal the blow, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yessir! I expertly witnessed the crime scene with my very own sparkling eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is that so... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">The next moment, I captured the criminal... expertly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Precisely! Naturally, she abandoned all hope, seeing a security pro like myself join the scene. She dropped that steel pipe she was holding to the floor, with a clank.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. I see, I see. That's what a guilty person would do in that situation.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Exactly, You Honour. There is no need to continue this cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Your Honour, may I?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, Prosecutor Flynch?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">I would like to get the events straight, while referring to this Crime Scene Photo. The defendant and the crew member were fighting in the back of the cargo hold, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yessir! They were fighting right under that emergency light.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Some items are spilling out of the broken crate.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Indeed, that crate was broken by the defendant, with a steel pipe. Incidentally, the items we can see spilling out are stuffed toys depicting London's own police mascot, PC Badger.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. The Crime Scene Photo shall be added to the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness may continue his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Precisely! Naturally, she abandoned all hope, seeing a security pro like myself join the scene. She dropped that steel pipe she was holding to the floor, with a clank.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. I see, I see. That's what a guilty person would do in that situation.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Exactly, You Honour. There is no need to continue this cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Within seconds I had established there was nothing out of order at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Not a thing. Well, aside from the defendant swinging that pipe around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could someone else have been hiding in that room?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Flynch:</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Uhm... Yes! I carry my trusty pocket torch for precisely such a task! I'd have noticed anything suspicious in an instant!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Your Honour, may I?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, Prosecutor Flynch?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">I would like to get the events straight, while referring to this Crime Scene Photo. The defendant and the crew member were fighting in the back of the cargo hold, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yessir! They were fighting right under that emergency light.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Some items are spilling out of the broken crate.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Indeed, that crate was broken by the defendant, with a steel pipe. Incidentally, the items we can see spilling out are stuffed toys depicting London's own police mascot, PC Badger.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. The Crime Scene Photo shall be added to the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness may continue his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Not a thing. Well, aside from the defendant swinging that pipe around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could someone else have been hiding in that room?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Flynch:</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Uhm... Yes! I carry my trusty pocket torch for precisely such a task! I'd have noticed anything suspicious in an instant!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhm... I was just looking at the evidence in the Court Record... and I get the feeling there's something funny about this testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're saying that there's a... contradiction?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's all he has to say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">If what he says is true, then Espella really is guilty...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And she does admit to the crimes...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-yeah, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But there's something not quite right in Smiles' testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, let's press the witness to see if we can squeeze out some more info!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Press...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Touch the Press icon on a statement to press the witness about it. If you keep pressing, you may just hit upon the truth in their story!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The Press icon, was it? All right, let's give it a shot!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's all he has to say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, Nick? What do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We managed to get our hands on some new evidence, but... Pressing alone can only get us so far.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhm, yeah. That means it's time to present evidence to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Present evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Compare what the witness is saying with the evidence in the Court Record. Sometimes they won't match up. And that means they're not telling the whole truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right! Thanks, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, you're making it look as if I'm the attorney here! Touch the Court Record icon to compare the evidence and the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I need to present the evidence that contradicts the testimony.</thought> ...Okay then, let's try that! <thought>Espella may be saying she's guilty, but... ...that doesn't mean this witness is telling us the whole story! I need to uncover the truth by myself!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're saying that there was nothing out of order in the cargo hold... Well, that's a bit funny.</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The point is, one of the crates in the cargo hold appears to have been tampered with.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Flynch:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please take a look at the crime scene photo. There's this broken crate where the fight took place. But also... there's another crate here that seems kind of strange, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Argh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This crate, sitting quite a distance away from where the fight took place, appears to have been forced open. Isn't this the sort of thing a security guard should immediately notice?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Ehm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You testified that you established there was nothing out of order at the crime scene. So how come...you didn't notice something so obvious?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Ughhhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! That's...that's certainly a serious oversight. Particularly for someone claiming to be an expert.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Flynch:</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Smiles:</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">E-excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">I am an expert guard! Focused, thorough, precise. A true professional! To prove it, I will testify once more! You're all dying to know why I ignored that one crate, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness shall continue his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What excuse do you think he'll come up with, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who knows... I've got a bad feeling about this, though. <thought>What did he actually see?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Smiles">It's only natural that I missed the other crate. The lights in the cargo hold weren't on!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">W-wait a moment! The security company claims that the lights were on during the patrol!</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yes, yes. That's the official procedure, you see. But those light controls can be such a pain in the... Wait, no, that's not it! I mean... The truth is, an expert like me doesn't need those lights to do his work! Not when I've got this! The focused beam of my trusty torch cuts through darkness like a laser!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness will refrain from pointing the torch in this direction! Justice may be blind, but I'd rather not be!</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Oops, sorry, Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This "trusty torch" shall be added to the Court Record as evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Eww, what is that?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it, You Honour?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This...this pocket torch is covered in something sticky!</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Ah, it seems my sweet little buddy's been up to some mischief.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Sweet little buddy"? Do you mean your chocolate?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Johnny left sticky fingerprints all over his flashlight...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ugh... Don't look at me! I'm not touching it...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">It's only natural that I missed the other crate. The lights in the cargo hold weren't on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Don't spread the news, but between you and me, I'm not very good with the light controls on that ship. Even a security expert like me has their flaws, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So he just neglected his duty...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Didn't you say before that you're "focused, thorough, and precise. A true professional"?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yes, that's true, of course! Always focused, thorough and precise, except when I'm cutting the odd corner. I aim to be a well-balanced professional, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Ah, um, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even Flynch looks unsure of how to handle this guy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Smiles">But of course I had this! A guard's best friend is his trusty pocket torch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Flashlight? It's a pocket torch. Ever watch crime dramas? Torchlit night patrols and all that? I've always thought it looked so cool. In fact, that's why I became a security guard!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Really? That's...a unique reason... By the way, what about the chocolate smudges on the flashlight...err, "torch"?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">A well-prepared guard has a torch in his right hand and a chocolate bar in the left! It's like an emergency ration. I'm so hot on security issues that it tends to melt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So the flashlight is covered in fingerprints from his sticky right hand.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Smiles">The emergency light was on, mind. So it wasn't so dark I couldn't see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">The defendant and the crew member fought under that emergency light.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, yes, there it is. In the back of the room.</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yessir! The cargo hold was faintly lit up by that little red light there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the regular lights are on in this picture...</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Well, yeah. I switched them on before the police came.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">I didn't want to risk my bright career over my slightly different take on the rules. After all, I am an expert. It's all in the details!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You're an expert, all right... An expert in bending the rules...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Smiles">I saw that girl stand right in front of the crew member as she attacked!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yes. I got there, opened the door and then...BAM! That's when it happened. I felt it in my shades. They spoke to me: "Johnny, you're looking at a crime here!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh... Huh? W-wait a second! You were wearing sunglasses?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yeah! What's a security guard without a pair of shades? These babies are a part of me.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">W-witness! You...were patrolling the freighter with sunglasses on?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Of course I was! Whatever I do, I do it with style! Is a bit of vanity a crime? Don't you wear your specs for the same reason?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Vanity? I wear them because I'm short-sighted, I'll have you know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You've got that right, Flynch... So, Johnny had sunglasses on in a dimly-lit room...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you think he actually managed to see anything? Nick, check the Court Record. There might be a contradiction in Johnny's testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, good idea. <thought>So there might be a contradiction, huh...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">And there was no one else in that room. You have Johnny's word for it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Not a possibility, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">That wharf is fitted with CCTV cameras. The recordings from that night have already been examined... Not a single person was seen leaving the ship.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If there are security cameras monitoring the ship... then why do they bother keeping Johnny around, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa, whoa... Not so loud, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. So there were no other intruders.</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yessir! That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, man. Some guard he is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">That prosecutor could have at least checked if the lights were on or not.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. You know...maybe this hasn't been all that properly investigated.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">......! You think so?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>In any case...some things the guard said are kinda strange. Let's see what he says when I show him some evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're sure the defendant was standing right in front of the crew member?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Absolutely! They were facing each other the entire time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, that's weird...because it clearly contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">What...what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to the victim's medical report, the blow was dealt to the back of the head.</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">...The back of the head...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you understand now? If they were facing each other, there's no way the victim could have been hit from behind!</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Ye............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! Can you offer an explanation for this contradiction?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Yes... Explain yourself. It's the first I'm hearing of this!</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yessir, I...um... It's... It's...strange, isn't it...? I'm totally sure they were fighting face-to-face! I'd swear this melting chocolate bar on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It doesn't look like he's lying. But then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Look at me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what are you doing, Maya?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I was just checking if I could hit the back of your head while you were facing me. It doesn't seem doable. Especially for someone as vertically challenged as me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How about you keep your dangerous little "experiments" inside that head of yours, Maya...? I kind of like living, thanks. <thought>At least we've learned a couple of important things... First, that this witness is unreliable! And second... that the prosecution didn't investigate this case properly! If my gut feeling is right... there's much more to this case than meets the eye! Now's my chance. What should I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't get ahead of myself... It's better to wait and see what happens.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you doing, Nick?! This is our chance! This is when you're supposed to point your finger and wave it in people's faces! You've gotta do it while they're floored by that contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honour! The defence asserts once more... that the defendant, Espella Cantabella, is innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what...?!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">This is...foolishness! Just who do you think you are, anyway? Waltzing in here, with your ridiculous assumptions. Balderdash, I say! That's not how it was supposed to be!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......! <thought>What did he just say? "Not how it was supposed to be"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">In light of this new development, the court's opinion... is that the defendant is in no way cleared of suspicion. However... The witness' [sic] testimony has been proven unreliable.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's more like it! Looks like I'm starting to win over the judge!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Flynch:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="???">Smiles:</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Isn't six months barely past the probation period?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">You're saying Goldilocks there is innocent. In other words, that she didn't assault anyone... and that she didn't steal this toy? Isn't that so, Mr Lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. At least... we have yet to see any proof that she tried to steal it.</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">............ Heh heh...heh heh heh... I got you there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What...? Got me how?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">I have...heh. A decisive piece of evidence! The proof that that girl was trying to kidnap PC Badger!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">You DO?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even Flynch is shocked...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Smiles">When I seized the girl at the crime scene... she was clasping this in her hand! She didn't even seem to notice.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">It...it would appear to be PC Badger's tag, Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now that you mention it...this mascot does have some sort of an ill-fitting tag attached. What's this engraved on the tag? Is that an address?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? You mean there's an address written on there?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">It would appear to be Scotland Yard's, and their telephone number. It is Scotland Yard's mascot, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This tag...it's been ripped from one of the PC Badger toys?</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Yessir! The suspect was caught in the act of nicking this very toy! The tag was ripped off during the fight!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what?! Then this tag is...</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">What we have here is the decisive evidence that she was trying to steal the cargo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No waaaaaaaaaaaaaay! <thought>I wasn't expecting evidence like that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Flynch:</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Sorry, Mr Prosecutor. I am an expert at what I do... and my expert advice to myself was that I'd better keep this as my "secret weapon"! So I waited for the right moment to single-handedly settle this trial!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Ughhhhh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like Flynch and I are both in uncharted waters now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This tag is vital evidence. It will be added to the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Uhm, defence? Mr Wright, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Prosecutor Flynch?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Your appearance in this court was a very hastily decided affair...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's true. That call from the Attorney's Association came out of nowhere...</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Perhaps, in all the confusion, the request from your "client" escaped your attention. Were you not instructed to accept the sentence proposed by the prosecution?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come to think of it, Ms Darklaw did say something about that before the trial...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">She's pleading guilty, so there's not much you need to do. I suggest you accept the punishment proposed by the prosecution.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">That's what you were asked to do. You have convinced us all of your skill, so your good name will not suffer. Why not simply admit the defendant is guilty and call it a day, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph... What do you say to that, Mr Wright? Depending on your stance on this matter, the court may now pass the verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>My stance? That's something I don't need to think twice about!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I understand. The defence agrees to end... Argh! What are you doing, Maya?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, y'know...just conducting one of my "dangerous little experiments"... I wanted to see if a heavy pipe to an attorney's head would help him see some sense! C'mon, Nick! If the trial ends now, Espella will be found guilty! Tell me you're NOT okay with that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, Maya... I have to respect the client's wishes. There must be a good reason behind Ms Darklaw's request.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, Ms Darklaw isn't your client. Espella is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>That's right. The reason I'm here is to defend Espella and prove she's innocent! I can't let the trial end now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defence requests that the trial continue!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Wh-what?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defence stands by its assertion... that Espella Cantabella...is not guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">............ Very well, Mr Wright. If that's your desire, then I, too, have a request to make. ...Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Prosecutor Flynch?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">The prosecution calls its second witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......!</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">H-hey, wait a second! What about me? Come on, guys, don't forget about Johnny! Let me start over from the top, no detail omitted!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">I suggest you leave the witness stand and go back to witnessing your crimes on television.</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Y-yes............ Yessssssssssssssir!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe a break is in order. The court will now adjourn for a 15 minute break. Mr Flynch, prepare your witness. Is that understood?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">...Yes, Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defence has no objections. <thought>Looks like Flynch finally got serious about this case. And that means... the real game starts now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phew. Glad the first part's over. That witness was quite a...character.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I bet he'd love to be one...in a crime drama. He'd end up making it a comedy, though. I'd hate it if poor Espella was found guilty because of his shaky testimony. But at least now it looks like we might be able to get Espella a "not guilty" verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I hope that cheered Espella up a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ack! <thought>I forgot about Darklaw!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">She's reading my newspaper.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe it's just me, but she doesn't look pleased...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">......! Oh, it's you. I appreciate your efforts, Mr Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhm, thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">But while I understand your drive to win this case...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-my drive?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...This is not the time for your personal ambitions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I told you before, didn't I? That Espella is pleading guilty, and that you should accept the proposed punishment.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">This...incident has already been settled between our school and the police.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But, Ms Darklaw! Espella could be innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Believe me, it will be in Espella's best interest if you end the trial as soon as possible. The more this trial drags on, the more traumatic it is for this poor girl.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I...I'm sorry... <thought>She may be saying that she's guilty...but is she, really?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">In any case, Mr Wright... We don't want our school being shoved into the limelight because of this case. So if you could please refrain from picking at meaningless details, such as that toy... Get this trial over with quickly. This is your client's wish, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ I understand. I'll do my best.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">It's a relief to hear that... Let's go, Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Yes, Ms Darklaw.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What the heck was that all about?! We've been bustin' our butts in there trying to prove that Espella is innocent, and she expects us to just give up NOW?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why are you yelling at ME, Maya...? <thought>But when you think about it, Darklaw's acting very strange...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Her own pupil's on trial, and she just stands around reading other people's newspapers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... What's she so busy reading about, anyway? There's nothing about Espella in that paper. <thought>Was she checking the soccer scores or something?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The break is almost over. We'd better go back. <thought>Flynch looked really confident about this new witness... I'm Espella's defence attorney. I'll stand by her no matter what.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will now reconvene. Prosecution, is your witness ready?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Of course, Your Honour. Bailiff, please bring her in!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, state your name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="???">My name is Olivia Aldente.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">The warm winds of the Mediterranean Sea carry the spicy scent of a seafood stew... A 'ot Sicilian stew that soothes the 'earts of sailors braving the raging waters. Blessed be the Sicilian cuisine and il nostro mare!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Yes... Ms Aldente is employed as a cook on the freighter where the crime happened.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A cook? That's, uhm...interesting attire you are wearing, Miss Aldente.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">This is my work outfit. It gets very 'ot in the kitchen, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It will be a pleasant change after that chocaholic guard. He got up my nose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nice to see the judge is remaining impartial...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Ms Aldente discovered the defendant in the cargo hold when she went for supplies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She found Espella? That would make her... the crew member that Johnny saw fighting with Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">That is right, Mr Wright. Ms Aldente was the first person to discover the intruder.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then she is the victim of assault! Hit with a steel pipe...how cruel!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">If I'd only 'ad my precious kitchen knife with me at the time... I'd 'ave shown 'er my eccezionale cutting skills. *giggle*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, look at that! She's an expert potato peeler! You'd better watch out around her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'll keep that in mind.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, we will now hear your testimony. Describe to us what happened in the cargo hold.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Certamente! Gladly!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">I went to the cargo hold to check the supplies. It was past 10:00pm.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. According to the medical report, you suffered a laceration to your head, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Ah, that. It's covered by the chef 'at, so you can't see it now... But when I chop up veggies, it 'urts in the rhythm of the strikes, chop-chop-chop!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That sounds most terrible, Miss Aldente.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">I should 'ave been more careful, but she looked like a little, piccola girl.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm. Olivia is much taller than Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. Espella's about the same size as you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I may be short, but I'm well-proportioned, and that's what matters!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Your Honour, the prosecution would like to present... the decisive evidence that proves the defendant's guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">This is a photograph of the defendant's fingerprints on the steel pipe. As you can see, the fingerprints are very clear. They were left by the assailant. They have already been examined and found to be those of the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph... Well, that settles it. This is undoubtedly decisive evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what?! <thought>The fingerprints on the weapon are Espella's?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Just to put your inquisitive mind at peace, Mr Wright, there were no other fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This photograph shall be added to the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Heh heh. Have I not warned you, Mr Wright? Further examination is but a waste of time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... What do we do now? This evidence clearly points to Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ We're pleading that Espella's not guilty. And if she's innocent, then... this witness is lying! All we need to do is expose that lie. <thought>I've got to think straight and focus on finding the truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">I went to the cargo hold to check the supplies. It was past 10:00pm.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Know the saying "a thirsty sailor will drink the 'ole Mediterranean Sea"? That's why I always need to make sure we're properly stocked up, sweetie.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh. <thought>Is she making those sayings up?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Flynch">The incident occurred at 10:20pm, when Smiles was doing the rounds.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... Understood. And what happened in the cargo hold?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">And I found that girl, 'iding and clutching one of them bizzarro toys.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">PC Badger, was it? The girl 'eld it in a tight grip, like a sea 'awk 'olds its prey!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you certain it was the defendant?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Uhm, it was kinda dark in that room, but... I swear on Neptune it was 'er!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">The witness was engaged in a face-to-face fight with the defendant. Even if the room was poorly lit, there is no doubt she would recognise her assailant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Espella was holding PC Badger... Did she intend to steal it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What did the witness do upon discovering the intruder?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">She made as if to run away, so I tried to stop 'er. Then she grabbed a pipe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Mhm. She 'ad nowhere to run though, 'cause she was at the far end of the room. I'm really good at catching chickens that try to run from the knife...so I caught 'er, rapidamente!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">And when you caught her, things took a violent turn?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Yeah...she was so small, you know, you wouldn't think she 'ad that in 'er... There was a steel pipe propped against the wall, right next to 'er...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was it the pipe from this picture?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Mhm, yeah. She picked it up and 'eld it in both 'ands. And then...</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">She's short, but she fiercely swung the pipe at me. I tried to dodge...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Flynch:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Espella's fingerprints... That's hard evidence. But then again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What is it, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhm, there's something about those fingerprints...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, it sounds like you're on to something, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't get too excited. It's just a hunch. <thought>These fingerprints... They don't look quite right to me, for some reason. Espella swung this pipe, while holding it in both hands?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Flynch">In any case, pray tell us what happened after the defendant took a swing at you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">but she 'it me on the 'ead. I blacked out for a few minutes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Uhm...sort of... It was dark, so I'm not exactly sure 'ow it 'appened. See, I'm clever with my fingers but not that good at dodging steel pipes, so I got 'it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And you're positive there was no one else at the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Yup. Ah, that cute guard suddenly walked in, sort of nonchalantly. Now that I think about it... The door suddenly opened and I turned towards it... That must be when I got 'it! So it was 'is fault...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Oh, I'll 'ave my revenge. They say my special spice blend is too strong for 'uman consumption... I don't think 'e will ever be able to taste chocolate afterwards! *giggle*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She says while smiling... Scary...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Johnny said he saw the moment Olivia was hit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, and he didn't see anyone else in the room either...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">So, when I came to, the guard boy 'ad already captured that girl.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There doesn't seem to be anything wrong with her testimony... Still...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm? Got any ideas, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This one piece of evidence has been on my mind... It's not something easy to see but...it feels out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm. I didn't notice anything. I'd better take a second look at the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've got nothing concrete, just a hunch to go on, but...should I present "that"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're claiming that the defendant swung the pipe at you... Well, that's impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Why do you say that, sweetie?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defendant's fingerprints were found on the pipe. However... There is a contradiction here!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">A...contradiction? Im...impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is most interesting. Well then, the defence shall explain... What in the photo of the fingerprints contradicts the testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It is the very fact that there are fingerprints on the pipe!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And...why would that be a contradiction?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If we assume that the defendant didn't touch this pipe...then it's inexplicable that her fingerprints should be found on it!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">...Let me tell you something, Mr Wright. What is truly inexplicable is the fact that a person such as you should be an attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-excuse me...?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">It is an established fact that the defendant's fingerprints are present on the weapon. Or do you mistrust the expertise of our British forensics technicians?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">I see you're at sea with this 'ole attorney business, sweetie!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gaaaaaaaaaaahhh! <thought>The fingerprints on the weapon are definitely Espella's... Maybe I overlooked some other possibility...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Well then. The court shall ask once more...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the position of the fingerprints, Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh? The position?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the location of the fingerprints, Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh? The location?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to the witness' [sic] testimony, the defendant held the pipe like this... In order to hit the witness on the head, she raised the pipe like so.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">That is preciso what she did!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And then she struck from above. But here's the problem... Think about the fingerprints that she would have left, had she done just that...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What are you getting at, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look closely at the way I'm holding the pipe. In this situation, the fingerprints... would look like this. The thumb is above the other fingers.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed, there's no doubt about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now take a look at the fingerprints that were actually left on the pipe.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Goodness! The...the thumb. It's... ...below the other fingers!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Wh-whaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. Ms Aldente...</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">What...what is it...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Had the defendant attacked you as you described... the fingerprints would have been the other way around. Which means... something's not right with your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">......Argh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! What is the meaning of this? These fingerprints were submitted as decisive evidence! How come this contradiction was not brought to light before! [sic]</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Ah! Noooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Aldente, what do you have to say about this?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... Excuse me, Ms Aldente?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Know 'ow to bring out the full sweetness of a sweet potato?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">You use a pinch of salt. Interesting, right? You use salt to make something taste sweeter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not following...</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">I remember it now. It was the other way around, not as you'd expect it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">I'm sorry, I got a bit confused. You'd normally 'old a pipe like that... But she's so small and the pipe is 'eavy. She 'eld it the other way.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The other way?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Not like this... She 'eld it in this way!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">I'm telling you I got confused. Olivia's sorry, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How could you mistake the way she held the pipe if she was right in front of you?!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Oh, why don't you go fry an egg! What does it matter if she 'eld it one way or another? You wouldn't call a slightly salted sweet potato a salty potato, 'cause it's still a sweet potato, no matter what you add to it.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">The witness probably has a point, doesn't she, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So the defendant attacked the witness holding the pipe backhanded... It seems a bit unnatural, but it does make sense, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Indeed it does, Your Honour. There is no problem with this evidence after all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Does the defence agree?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I agree there are no problems with this evidence, we'll be one step away from losing this case... There's gotta be a contradiction somewhere in that fishy testimony! Could Espella have hit Olivia holding the pipe backhanded?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't prove anything now... Maybe I'll get another chance later...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wake up, Nick! It's now or never! Espella will be found guilty if you don't do something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, Maya, there's nothing I can do... <thought>I need evidence to prove a contradiction. I guess it's time to improvise... I'll raise an objection first and have a look at the Court Record when they ask me for proof...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Ms Aldente, I'm afraid that... you're in a pickle now.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">I...I don't really see why.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Adding a pack of lies to a testimony can turn things very sour for a witness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. It would seem that the defence is prepared to prove its claim... that there is a contradiction in this witness' [sic] testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Correct, Your Honour. <thought>I won't know until I try...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence shall now present evidence to the court! The evidence contradicting the assertion that the defendant hit the witness holding the pipe backhanded is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, well. I will ask for your opinion on this, Prosecutor Flynch. I don't understand what the defence is trying to say.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Oh, we could say that things have gone sour for Mr Wright, rather than the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Accusing me of lying is in really bad taste, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gwahhhhhhhh! <thought>I messed that up big time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Say, Nick. Do you think she even got hit in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She did. It says so in her medical report: "laceration to the back of the head". You can't see it because it's under her chef's hat.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Espella and I wouldn't be able to see it anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Because they're both so short... ...! That...made me think of something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defence? Are you still there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes! Please give me another chance!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Hmph! No matter how you slice it, you can't prove anything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Aldente, you previously testified... that you were using that hat to cover the wound you received in the assault.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">It's normal for signorinas to cover up things they don't want others to see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's not all. You also described the defendant as "little", if you recall. That is to say, Ms Cantabella is, at the very least, shorter than you.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">I've grown tall and 'ealthy thanks to the wonderful Mediterranean sunshine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let me ask you then... How did a girl shorter than you, holding a heavy pipe backhanded, manage to land a blow to the back of your head? I'd say it's impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">...!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The fingerprints on the weapon show that the defendant held it backhanded. But even if she didn't... it is highly unlikely she would be able to hit Ms Aldente's head like that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-order! I will have order! What is the defence getting at...?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Flynch:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.........!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That is so. Does the defence have any comments?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't deny that... It's clear that Espella did hold that pipe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... She held it like this, right? Why would she do that? It'd be hard to hit anyone like this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>When she holds it like that, it looks as if...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court recognises the validity of the prosecution's objection. Fingerprints on the weapon prove that it was used by the defendant...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Flynch:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, the defence may elaborate on its idea.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What I say next will turn this trial around!</thought> The defendant's fingerprints were left on the weapon when she...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">While cornered by Ms Aldente, the defendant reached back and grabbed the pipe!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Indeed. She picked up the pipe that was leaning against the wall and held it in both hands.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Mhm, and then...she charged at me!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Hmm, yes. It is quite possible that she would hold the pipe backwards, having picked it up from behind.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">So...what's the problem? That only proves it was 'er who assaulted me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems to be just as the witness says. Wouldn't you agree, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's really not my day... I can't believe I got that wrong...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's wrong with you, Nick?! I'm tempted to hit you again with that pipe just to knock some sense into you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm... I'm sorry. I'll get it right next time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">While cornered by Ms Aldente, the defendant attacked her with the steel pipe!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So...what you're saying is... that the fingerprints were left on the weapon when the defendant attacked, not when she committed assault? ............ Isn't that the same crime?!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">It's the same crime, Mr Not-So-Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Mamma mia! 'E finally got it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's really not my day... I can't believe I got that wrong...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's wrong with you, Nick?! I'm tempted to hit you again with that pipe just to knock some sense into you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm... I'm sorry. I'll get it right next time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, naturally... she held the pipe with both hands when she stopped it from coming down on her head.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-stopped it...?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">W-with both hands...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's right! Like this!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">......!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please take another look at this photo. These are not the fingerprints of an assailant... but rather, the fingerprints of a victim who was defending herself!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which brings us to the conclusion... that Ms Cantabella didn't attack the witness! She was in fact a victim, desperately trying to defend herself!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">This cannot be!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And if Ms Cantabella was a victim... Who was the real assailant? There's only one person who could have done it.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The only other person at the crime scene... was Olivia Aldente! ...It was you, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Kyaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! If I cannot have order, the court will be adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="???">Be quiet, ALL OF YOU!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">You just don't quit, do you...? A lousy lawyer like you should get the chop! 'Ow about I show you my knife up close?!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Flynch:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Arghhhhhhhhhh! You prickly sea urchin!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Flynch:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Aldente:</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm, she's the only one in the courtroom wearing gloves.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">There was...THAT guy! The guard! 'E was wearing gloves too!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The guard... Oh, was that the previous witness?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Oh, that's right! Gloves are part of the guard's uniform, by regulation!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">See! That guard, Johnny, 'e was wearing gloves that night too!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. What do you say to that, Mr Wright? Since you're claiming that the assailant is the person who had gloves on, that would make the guard a suspect as well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Could Johnny be the culprit?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It is certainly possible that Johnny was the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Bzzt! Wrong answer, Nick! You're not gonna get anywhere with that! What you've got to do now is grill that fishy cook! Witnesses are like food. If you wait too long, they go rotten!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Speaking of food, I bet Maya's gonna make me treat her to one of her usual "post-trial hamburger feasts" when this thing's done...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">And don't forget to check the evidence. There might be something useful there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh yeah! I've got to remember to check the Court Record...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Johnny Smiles is not the culprit!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Why not?! Anyone with gloves could've done it, didn't you just say that?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Um, no, I didn't...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">However, it does seem plausible that the guard could have done it. He was wearing gloves, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm afraid that's impossible, Your Honour. ...And I have proof.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You...do?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Fascinating. Let's see this "proof", if you really have it... Please enlighten us as to why Smiles cannot be the culprit. Provide the proof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">You'd better take all that lawyer says with a grain of salt.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">You appear to be but an unseasoned attorney after all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That doesn't really cut the mustard.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence's theory boils down to nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... That definitely left a bad taste in my mouth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">To put it simply, the culprit must have been wearing gloves. So...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So I need to prove Smiles wasn't wearing any...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's check the Court Record again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr Smiles is, to put it nicely, what you may call a free spirit. There is no guarantee he would follow the rules and wear his full uniform! And this evidence proves he did not wear gloves!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">W-wait! Don't throw that filthy torch at me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Will someone please wipe the chocolate off this evidence?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Your Honour, this chocolate is the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr Smiles was snacking on a chocolate bar during his patrol. That's why his flashlight is in this sorry state... and covered in his chocolatey fingerprints. Therefore, we know that he didn't wear gloves when patrolling the ship that night! Rule-breaking, chocolate-loving Johnny Smiles was not the culprit!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Wh-whaaat...? That's ridicolo! It's too silly!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Flynch:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Flynch:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">...! Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What was that? Did Olivia just freeze for a second?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor Flynch. Explain to the court about this toy...this new piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">This is the stuffed toy the defendant tried to steal that night.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... One of its legs would appear to be missing. The poor thing.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">This mishap befell PC Badger as the witness and defendant were fighting. The captain of the freighter reported the damage after the defendant's arrest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So this is the stuffed animal Olivia snatched from Espella...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. The court would like to hear the witness' [sic] testimony regarding this evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">...Witness, your testimony. Excuse me... Witness, you have been asked to testify!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">...Ah... I'm so very sorry! I got a little upset from all these accusations! I'm not used to this...to being called a liar...</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Ah, yes. It's only natural. Don't worry about that. It's all that slimy attorney's fault!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-why do I feel like an eel on a chopping board...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness will now testify. Tell us how you retrieved this toy from the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Gladly! Oh, il nostro mare!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder what she's saying. I don't get it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whatever she said, I'll make sure this is the last time she says it in court!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aldente">I wrestled this toy back from that thief and then gave it to the police.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, I see. What a commendable attitude, going to such lengths to protect the cargo.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">I may not be a security guard, but I'll do what it takes for the sake of our ship!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It didn't do much good in the end. This PC Badger is way too damaged to be sold.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aldente">These lovely little toys are made at a workshop in London. We transport them down the River Thames, distributing them to children as we go.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Didn't she call them "bizzaro toys" earlier? And now suddenly they're "cute"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what about fingerprints on this toy?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">It is a soft toy, after all, so no usable fingerprints were found.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Well, that is unfortunate. Regardless, the court accepts it into evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence may now cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">I wrestled this toy back from that thief and then gave it to the police.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Naturalmente! I caught 'er red-'anded. She WAS trying to steal it. I'm telling you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, to be honest... it doesn't sound like she's lying...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">But... Is Espella really a thief?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We can't be sure about it... Just picking something up doesn't make you a thief. Anyway... <thought>Something else in her testimony is on my mind right now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Has the defence changed its mind about the innocence of its client now?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, continue your testimony. What did you do after coming across the defendant?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Yeah, that's the one. No doubt about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, but if that's the case, things simply don't add up.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Wh-what doesn't add up...?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Uhm, if it's about the leg, it's that girl's fault. It got ripped off because she wouldn't let go...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The problem is not something that's missing from this stuffed animal. On the contrary... It's something that shouldn't be there in the first place!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">S-something that shouldn't be there...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that is, of course...this item.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">That...that's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the final piece of evidence received from the guard, Mr Smiles.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Yeah, that's the one. No doubt about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, but if that's the case, things simply don't add up.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Flynch:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence must have some basis behind these claims. The court would like to see some evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence shall now present to the court... the evidence that illustrates a contradiction within this toy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">There, I finished it!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">My, my, well done. I'd like to try that sometime too.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. I was just about to say the same thing.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, no one's looking at your evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... I'd better think of some other evidence to present... and fast.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The evidence...is this!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">That...that's...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is this the tag that was hanging from PC Badger's neck?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">T-tag...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the evidence received earlier from Mr Smiles.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">When I found that girl, I thought I couldn't let 'er get away with our precious cargo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Yeah. The workshop where they make them is by the River Thames. We come to pick up the cargo regularly.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">As it's a regular direct delivery service, we did not see the need to investigate the cargo.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">If you confiscated our cargo for inspection, I wouldn't be able to carry out my cooking experiments.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Confiscate? What the heck is she cooking with exactly?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Flynch">I think we can all see how committed Ms Aldente is to her work.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Commitment and passion are the main ingredients of every dish I cook!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Naturalmente, I 'ad to get that toy back from 'er first. Its leg got ripped off, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Mhm, yeah. It came off easier than the shell of a freshly boiled lobster.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see...hmm... <thought>This thing does seem kind of flimsy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Stop picking on PC Badger! He may be a plushie, but that's no reason to make fun of him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not made very well, though. It looks like it might just come apart if you pull it a bit...</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">I ripped it out of the girl's 'ands and kept it with me until the police came.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">But there's no way I could've attacked 'er with the pipe! I was 'olding the toy in one 'and.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Aren't you forgetting who's the victim 'ere, sweetie? I am. And I didn't strike myself with that pipe. Aren't you getting things backwards? Feeling dizzy? Maybe you 'aven't been eating properly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... She's right. Someone else must've hit her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Uhm, maybe I shouldn't be saying this, but...</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">I don't remember much about when I was 'it. But I got the toy back, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Yeah, and the room was dark 'cause only the emergency light was on... But there was definitely no one else in that room. Only me and that little girl. So it 'ad to be 'er that 'it me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's not having second thoughts about that, it seems.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's it, huh.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This one's easy. I know what to do.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're finally starting to act like your normal self! That jet lag must've hit you like a ton of bricks, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There is a clear contradiction in Olivia's testimony. It's time to present some evidence and expose her lies!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Smiles">When I seized the girl at the crime scene... she was clasping this in her hand! She didn't even seem to notice.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">It...it would appear to be PC Badger's tag, Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Strange, isn't it? Something was definitely ripped off this plushie... But it wasn't its leg... It was the tag.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">.........!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You noticed it too, didn't you, Ms Aldente? If this is the stuffed animal that Ms Cantabella was holding when you found her... then why is the tag still on it?!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Kyaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! I will have order! What is the meaning of this...?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Hey, you...tasteless-looking prosecutor over there!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Y...yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">What's this about a tag?! You didn't tell me anything about that!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">If...if you'll please calm down...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's no use blaming the prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He didn't even know this tag existed.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Flynch:</line>
<line speaker="Smiles">Sorry, Mr Prosecutor. I am an expert at what I do... and my expert advice to myself was that I'd better keep this as my "secret weapon"! So I waited for the right moment to single-handedly settle this trial!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">For better or for worse, this tag's existence has only recently come to light. Neither the prosecution, nor you, Your Honour, knew about it before this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Gwah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But then...why is there a tag on this toy? How come this toy has a tag?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The answer is simple. There is a tag on this stuffed animal because...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Before handing in the plushie to the police... the witness placed a new tag on its neck!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And...what would she have done that for?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's...um... Maybe she wanted to conceal the fact it got damaged in the fight.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Flynch:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ugh.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">C'mon, Nick! That would be pointless.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">'Ow about we 'ang a "Useless Attorney" tag on your neck, darling?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, great... Let's all play "gang up on Phoenix", guys...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr Wright. I'll ask again and you had better get it right this time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, most likely... Ms Aldente took a different plushie by mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's that? She took a different one?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The toys all look the same, so she ended up picking the wrong one...</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Flynch:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ugh.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">What you said was so ludicrous that I raised an objection for no reason!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">'Ow about we 'ang a "Useless Attorney" tag on your neck, darling?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, great... Let's all play "gang up on Phoenix", guys...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr Wright. I'll ask again and you had better get it right this time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is only one possibility... Ms Aldente. Before handing the plushie in to the police, you swapped it for another!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Kyaaaaaaaaaaah! Listen to yourself! Why would I even do something like that?! Ridicolo! And...that's right, that tag must be a fake!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A fake? Why would you think that?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">That chocolate freak must be trying to frame me, that's what it is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Flynch:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Yes, what 'e said! The guard lied to show off, that's all there is to it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Did Johnny produce bogus evidence to draw attention to himself?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's possible, perhaps. But not very likely.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Ah, see! Next time I see that guard...I'll test my new knife set on 'im!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However, it's easy to check whether this evidence is genuine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's an interesting theory, but it's impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">And 'ow do YOU know?! You! I'll...dice you like an onion!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anyway... Was Mr Smiles lying? There's an easy way to find out.</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">What......</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">How do you plan to check it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By checking the fingerprints, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Fingerprints... Arghhh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to Mr Smiles' testimony... when he seized Ms Cantabella, she was holding the tag in her hand. Therefore... her fingerprints should still be on that tag!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Kyaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Have this evidence investigated immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That was awesome, Nick! We've almost got her now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr Flynch, I have a question for you.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Wh-what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When you searched the crime scene...did you find a toy without a tag?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Well, Mr Flynch? Did you?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Ugh... N-no... We, uhm... Considering the circumstances, it did not seem necessary to investigate quite so thoroughly... But at the very least, I can tell you that all the toys in the crate had tags on.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Excuse me, Your Honour?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It appears no stuffed animal was found without a tag. Which means that it may still be hidden at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">...Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honour, the defence requests that the ship be searched! Thoroughly this time! Send a forensics team there immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're requesting another search?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Flynch:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That is exactly why it's important.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All these plushies are the same. There's no need to swap one for another. And yet... Why is the witness getting so worked up about it?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">That's... That's just...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I had a feeling that there was something odd about this case... A stolen stuffed animal...and an assault connected to it... There had to be more to it. There had to be...another crime under the surface.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is it. What should I do...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The witness is already pretty shaken. I'll wait a while and see what happens.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">No, Nick! Olivia's lost the ground from right under her feet! It's time to deliver the final blow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Got it, Maya, thanks. I've got to press on... I just need to take a deep breath and say what I think is right...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup, that's the spirit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Your Honour! The defence insists on a search! Should a plushie without a tag be found on the ship... then there's a strong possibility that this case will be resolved!</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Flynch:</line>
<line speaker="???">Nooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">You can't! No, no! You can't search it again! You just can't!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-witness...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Aldente! Why did you swap the stuffed animal? And why are you so afraid of having the ship searched? PC Badger holds all the answers!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">........................</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I...I say! Mr Wright! Could it be...that you already know the reason behind the swap?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Of course, I don't have any definitive proof. But... when it comes to pointing out a possibility, I might have something. Hmm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well then. Let's see some evidence! Do you have any evidence that would explain why Miss Aldente is against the search?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Look at this 'alf-boiled attorney! I'd advise to boil 'im for at least an 'our... and even then 'e may end up quite bitter, when 'e realises what a fool 'e was!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm, where'd it go? That big tuna...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like I chose the wrong thing.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We got this far! We can't let her give us the slip now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's not looking good. I've got to think again... For some reason, Olivia couldn't hand the other plushie in to the police. And I should be able to figure out why!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, let's ask again... Can the defence present relevant evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is a certain article in this newspaper... "Elusive jewel thieves at large in London! Scotland Yard on red alert!"...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, that robbery. I have heard about it, of course. A group of thieves robbed a jewellery shop and made away with about 50 pieces of jewellery. Many extremely valuable stones were stolen, as well. Scotland Yard's under great pressure to find them.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">All packages sent out from London are being scrutinised by the police. And what does this have to do with our case? Nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I beg to differ. The jewel theft took place in London... and that's where our freighter picked up its cargo.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">L-London... Ah... It...it can't be. Witness...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That night, you discovered the defendant in the cargo hold. She was holding one of the plushies. You knew you had to get it back. You had to get it back at all costs. But why go so far for a mere plushie? There is only one possible reason! You couldn't afford to have the police discover what was inside of it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We have just received a report from the team investigating the crime scene. This toy was hidden between a storage unit and a pipe.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The toy has been cut open and the contents examined... and this was found inside. A pink diamond worth approximately 100,000.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">We have also received a report from the crime lab. The defendant's fingerprints have been found on the tag.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you have anything to say, Ms Aldente?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">............ I lost, didn't I?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So...so you are a...</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">Yeah, I'm one of them. I'm one of the jewel thieves. My role was to get the loot out of London. The police never check the regular shipments from that workshop. We decided to take advantage of that blind spot.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Indeed, the regular direct delivery service has been overlooked by the police.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Possibly because that workshop produces the very mascots representing the police!</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">The other crew 'ad nothing to do with it. I used their ship...that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was you who hid the jewels inside the plushies...</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">There was one jewel in each toy. I was carrying them away one by one.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defendant happened to pick one of those toys up...</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">I 'ad my 'eart stand still when I saw that girl in the cargo hold. Whenever I was free, I stood guard in front of that room...and yet she got in somehow. So there she was in the room with the 'idden loot, one of the toys, in 'er 'and!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhm. So, how did Espella get in there?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">I don't know if she was trying to steal the toy or what. But I just 'ad to get it back from 'er! No matter the cost! Then I 'anded in a different toy. I made it look like it was ripped in the fight. It would 'ave been over for me if the police 'ad found any of the jewels...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But, wait... Who was it in the end? Who hit Olivia?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, I almost forgot about that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aldente">At first...I thought it must 'ave been...that... little girl that 'it me... But now I don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't know?</line>
<line speaker="Aldente">No one else was supposed to be in that room... But what if there was someone in the shadows... Some mischievous person 'idden in the darkness...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This was a most unusual case. It cannot be said that all mysteries have been resolved... but it has become clear that Ms Cantabella is innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Ugh......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honour?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would seem that I owe you thanks for helping us see the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no need to thank me, Your Honour. I was just doing my job, like I always do.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is that really the smartest thing you could come up with?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And...Mr Flynch.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Y-yes, Your Honour!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This trial was part of the Legal League of Attorneys' exchange programme, wasn't it? May this trial serve as a lesson for you too! Is that understood?</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">............Oh... It is as you say, Your Honourrrrrrrrrr! Don't look! Don't look! Don't look! Don't LOOK! Without my glasses...I can't see and I don't want to be seen! Where are they? Where are they? Where are they? Where...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem, well then. The court has reached its verdict. I pronounce the defendant, Espella Cantabella...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Congratulations! You did it, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...thanks. <thought>I guess I should be happy... but Darklaw's cold gaze is staring daggers through me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ Thank you, Mr Wright. You are better than I thought. Had I known earlier, I would have asked you to prove Espella innocent from the very start.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, I'm glad you're happy about the verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Espella, come and thank Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ Thank you, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">G-glad I could help...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Hmm? Hey, Espella. What's that big book you've got there?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Oh, please forgive her. She's a bit shy, you see. She's very fond of books. At any rate, now Espella can return to her peaceful life at our boarding school. And it's all thanks to your hard work, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Now, please excuse us. We have some formalities to attend to.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh. Yes, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Mr Wright. You were truly outstanding in that courtroom today. Farewell.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Phew, it's finally over.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, something's still bothering me about this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The person who hit Olivia... where did they go?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's true... We don't know who actually assaulted Olivia.</thought> If it wasn't Espella... there must have been another person at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But neither Olivia nor Johnny saw anyone else!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The room was dark, save for the emergency light. I'm sure someone hid in the shadows. And Johnny was wearing sunglasses... I'm amazed he saw anything at all. He missed all those clues, so it's not much of a stretch to imagine he missed the perpetrator too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How about we head back now?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay! Let's go check out Tower Bridge while we still have some daylight left!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm? What is it, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There, on the couch... Isn't that Espella's book? It IS the book she was holding. We should return it to her. Hey, Nick, let's see what kind of stuff Espella likes to read.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just quit it, Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Labyrinthia, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, look!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick... Look, that's us, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph? Whatever do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is clearly a, uhh...a contradiction... umm... I think.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Making a face like that does not make your objection any more credible, Mr Wright. I'm not in a good mood today, so I shall punish the defence with a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey, don't take it out on me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...And how are they even related?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...They aren't, are they?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed, they are not. And here is your penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Penalty... That sounds pretty serious when said by the judge.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Does it, now? I do not see any contradictions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. And now, that is a penalty. The defence shall think very well before speaking to the court again. Or else...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This judge is really good at threatening people...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! There is no need to prolong this trial. The verdict is already clear as day. There are no doubts nor ambiguities. The court will now issue its verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defendant will be placed under arrest... and will undergo a regular trial at the High Court within a month. The court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>