<xml>
<title>Farewell, My Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Engarde">Adrian did it...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's what it looks like.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Dude, no way! That woman couldn't do anything like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In court today, there will be a mountain of evidence that will implicate you.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">A mountain of evidence...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm certain there is someone out there trying very hard to pin this whole thing on you.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Please, Mr. Lawyer! Dude, like I said yesterday... I'm "refreshing like a spring breeze", alright? I can't let any sort of scandal ruin that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I understand...</line>
<line speaker="???">Well, it's almost time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">We must get a complete acquittal today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know... I can't focus on Maya's situation right now. ...Or Pearls' either. No matter what, I have to focus on winning this case by the end of the day!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Indeed. Well, let's get going!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is Wright!</line>
<line speaker="???">Good morning. This is it, Mr. Attorney; the day of the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya... She's unharmed, right!?</line>
<line speaker="???">Well... When I checked on her earlier this morning, she seemed a bit, how shall we say, tired.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="???">Don't worry. People don't die that easily. Besides, what you really should be concentrating on, is winning today's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">G...Grrrr...</line>
<line speaker="???">For myself, you must win today's trial. Which is why... I sent you a little present this morning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Present? What in the world would you want to give me!?</line>
<line speaker="???">You'll figure it out once the trial opens... even if you don't "like" my gift... I expect you to graciously accept it, and win the day's contest... If you please.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The kidnapper sent me a "present"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Mr. Lawyer dude? Who was that...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, um... No one. It has nothing to do with you, so forget you heard anything!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...Dude, did your nose just get longer?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Matt Engarde. Are the prosecution and defense ready?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I say! Mr. Wright! What happened to Ms. von Karma!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I don't know, Your Honor! <thought>Why are you getting mad at me!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">...Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please be quiet, bailiff. Court is in session. If you must tell me something, please keep it brief. Now then, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Prosecutor... Prosecutor von Karma has... This morning, Ms. von Karma was shot by an unknown gunman!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... WWWWWWWHAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sh-Shot!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Somehow... I think this is the "present" that man was talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His "present"...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ms. von Karma is one of the top prosecutors in the country at the moment. If she disappeared... This would be to your "advantage".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Th-This... This is totally insane!</thought> M-Ms. von Karma! Is she alright!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't have that answer! ...</line>
<line speaker="???">She's alive and in stable condition.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's good... Phew. ... ...! Y-Y-You're...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I thought he'd show up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Your Honor... Due to the circumstances, Ms. Franziska von Karma can not appear in court today. I, Miles Edgeworth, will be taking her place. The prosecution is ready... naturally.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. von Karma was shot in her right shoulder, and is currently undergoing surgery. Luckily, I have looked this case over and am familiar with the details. The prosecution seeks to prove the guilt of Mr. Matt Engarde.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-The court acknowledges the prosecution.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Wright. I finally found the answer I was struggling for on my long journey this past year. By the time this case comes to an end, you too, will know the answer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, the prosecution would like to call its first witness... Please bring Detective Gumshoe to the witness stand!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Witness, your name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">My name's Dick Gumshoe, sir. I'm a detective down at the precinct... for now.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"For now"...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">After this trial's over... I'm supposed to turn in my badge, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>D-Detective Gumshoe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution has no need for a depressed witness. Lift your head up and face forward like a proud officer, Detective Dick Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, let's have your testimony. If we want to explore the various facets of this case, we must start with that.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Get ready, Phoenix. This is going to be one very rough fight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... It would have to be with Edgeworth as my opponent.  <thought>The answer he was "struggling" for... Interesting... Show me this "answer" you finally found, Edgeworth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This murder happened after the Hero of Heroes award ceremony, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... After the award ceremony ended, the victim was alone in his room...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir! Both the victim and defendant went alone to their rooms, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Mr. Wright, you may begin your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This murder happened after the Hero of Heroes award ceremony, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you please give us a brief timeline of what happened after the ceremony?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OK, pal. The ceremony started at 6 PM. It ended around 8 PM... and then there was a short break. A special post-ceremony show was supposed to start in the lobby 30 minutes later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's when the victim's body was found, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Which is to say, the murder occurred during that thirty minute break period.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Please continue with your testimony, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The victim, Juan Corrida, was found dead in his hotel room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The person who discovered the victim's body was Adrian Andrews, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who is this "Adrian Andrews" you're talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She's the defendant, Matt Engarde's, manager. She's a really pretty lady... sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, so she's a pretty lady... I wonder if she will grace us with her presence...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">When the post-ceremony show was about to start, she went to get Mr. Engarde. After visiting his room, she next went to the victim's room to get him for the show, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... And that's when she found the victim's body...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">After looking into the cause of death, we believe he was definitely murdered, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The cause of death... Wasn't that because Mr. Corrida was stabbed in the chest...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Only a careless amateur would believe something so brainless as that, pal. Take a good, hard look at the crime photo. Now, a real pro's attention would be drawn here, to this bandana.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mmm... "Banana"...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, his "bandana", sir... That's the thing wrapped tightly around his neck, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, yes, yes. I see. His banana-scented bandana.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then, what about the knife...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It seems to have been stuck in the victim's chest on purpose after his death.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... We have a crafty murderer on our hands here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">At first, we thought there was something suspicious about the empty guitar case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And why did you think that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Because it was empty, pal. The Jammin' Ninja doesn't go anywhere without his bright red guitar. And we couldn't find it anywhere at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! Then how about this theory! A fan really wanted the guitar and did the crime to get it! How's that!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, we thought of that too... But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The only fingerprints on the guitar case were the victim's.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Only the victim's, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see. Ah, so much for my theory then...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">However, we later found out that the guitar case had nothing to do with the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What convinced you it had nothing to do with the case?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The guitar wasn't at the Gatewater Hotel that night.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, where was it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The bright red guitar was eventually found at the TV studio. The victim, Juan Corrida, had apparently only taken the case with him, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So you mean he forgot to put the guitar inside the case...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir. Even when he was onstage for the ceremony, he didn't have his guitar.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that guitar case was empty even before he got to the hotel...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, that's right. So it really had nothing to do with the case after all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Our first order of business should be to gather more info from his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But there might be a trap set up for us somewhere...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Maybe. However, setting off traps is a part of a lawyer's job too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you say so...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Of course, we're supposed to escape from them too, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe that is enough. First, the victim was choked to death with his bandana. Then, after the victim was dead, the killer deliberately stabbed him with a knife.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Which brings me to my next point. Why then, did the police arrest Matt Engarde...? Because there was reason enough to suspect him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Here it comes... Looks like Edgeworth's back in full swing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Detective Gumshoe, please testify about this matter.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Matt Engarde and Juan Corrida were huge rivals with each other.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So the defendant's fingerprints were found on the knife used in the stabbing.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It was sort of sticky on the handle, so the fingerprints came out pretty clearly, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...And there's this button.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That was found in the defendant's clothes, was it? Hmm... And is this button also covered in blood...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, and we know that the blood on it is the victim's blood, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All of this points very clearly to the defendant, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, it most certainly does, Your Honor. Ready to give in yet, Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmph! I'll find the hole in your argument somehow!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You can press as hard as you'd like. Just hurry up with your usual pointless questions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Grrrrrrrrr...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Matt Engarde and Juan Corrida were huge rivals with each other.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But in terms of popularity, Mr. Engarde won, did he not?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Yeah. But you know what's ironic, pal? Juan Corrida was always one step behind Mr. Engarde in everything. This year it seemed like he'd finally caught up, ready for the big, final showdown.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But Mr. Corrida lost the Grand Prix in the end...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is too bad... He must have been pretty downhearted after losing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">They each thought the other guy was "in his way". That's motive enough in my book.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait just one second here! Mr. Engarde was beating Mr. Corrida in the popularity polls!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, yeah, I guess, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which means that in the defendant's eyes, the victim was not a rival at all! Which means he had no motive to kill at all!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes, I quite agree. Well, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, it's not... Well... I guess if you put it that way, then yeah, the defendant would've had no motive...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective. I'm beginning to see why you were fired.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Eh!? N-No! Not you too, Mr. Edgeworth, sir! That's...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I look forward to your pension negotiations.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">N-N-N-NOOOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, now, Detective. Let's continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">*sniffle* Noooo... Not my poor pension too...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective! If you value your money, I suggest you proceed!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yes, sir! We can talk about my pension later, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Um, what about what I was saying...? Hello? Anyone...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">As for evidence... There's the Jammin' Ninja's button.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you have any proof that button belonged to the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? What do you mean, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh. Umm, let me put it this way... I'm asking you if you have any evidence to back up your claim that, "this button was ripped off of the Jammin' Ninja's costume".</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? But can't you tell by just looking at it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A-And the victim's blood is on it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anyone could have smeared that blood on there afterward.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... M-M-Mr. Edgeworth... Help me... sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Alright! I knew it had to be this piece of evidence. Now to reel this one in...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Thread.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The button was attached to the costume by thread, obviously. And that thread snapped when the button was torn off. If you match up the ends of the thread on the costume with the thread on the button... it's a perfect match.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, that's it! They're a perfect match, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's Edgeworth for you. Never misses a beat.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It was ripped off of the ninja costume and was found in Mr. Engarde's "hakama".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When was this button found?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Pretty soon after the body was found, we rounded up everyone who knew Mr. Corrida. And then we did a search on them all. That's when we found the button.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So it was almost immediately after the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The police didn't have the free time to lollygag and play tricks, unlike some people...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey! What is he trying to say about me here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The defendant's fingerprints were also all over the knife.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How were the fingerprints arranged on the knife?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? What do you mean, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By examining the fingerprints, you can determine how the defendant held the knife. For example, did he hold it normally, or overhand...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! Is that what you meant!? Well, we didn't actually think of that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't believe the bumbling of this department...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hopeless. Were you paying attention to the testimony, Wright? The defendant's fingerprints were "all over" the knife. There is no way to determine how the knife was held at the moment of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So is the defendant the owner of this knife, then?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The defendant bought the knife for the crime... Which makes this a premeditated murder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is no way this was a premeditated murder, even if he bought the knife!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry, pal. This isn't just some pocket knife. It's not really useful for anything, and you can't just walk around with it either.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh. Well, this is not good... If the prosecution can prove it was a premeditated murder, we're done for...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">...Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">There's something very interesting about what the detective said just now. Think carefully, before it's too late.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A button covered in the victim's blood... And a knife with Engarde's fingerprints!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Be grateful. If the judge were more rash, he would've already pounded his gavel in closing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We're still in a world of trouble...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, before any battle, you must find your enemy's weakness. So let's find the weakness in this testimony, no matter how small it may be, OK Phoenix?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a second!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the basis of your argument that this was a premeditated murder is simply that my client "bought a knife beforehand"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's right, pal. The defendant...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Did not buy this knife.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-Huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a good look at the handle of this knife, and you'll know what I'm talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It has a "Gatewater" seal set into the handle...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">"Gatewater"...? I think I've heard that name somewhere before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's the name of the hotel. The Gatewater Hotel.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Uh oh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The murder knife was actually property of the hotel! Which means this murder was not premeditated!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, that is very true! This is a very big...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What is it, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sorry, but the defense is simply too careless.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think whether the crime was premeditated or not... has already been determined.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-How so!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I admit this knife is hotel property. There is no one currently on the police force that is dumb enough not to realize this.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...But I didn't kn... Oh... *whimper*</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The question is... Where did this knife come from?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Why that's obvious! It came from the victim, Mr. Corrida's room...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry, Your Honor, but that is incorrect. The victim ate a last meal before he was murdered. With that being the case... I would like to draw the court's attention to what is on top of the table.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There is a knife and a fork on the table! Then... Where in the world did this knife come from!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If it pleases the court... I would like for us to recall the room of the defendant, Mr. Matt Engarde. Especially what was on top of his table... There is something missing... Perhaps, it is a single knife? We investigated the leftover dishes for fingerprints, and while we were investigating, we came to the conclusion that Mr. Matt Engarde's knife was missing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Engarde had gone to the victim's room with the knife he had used during dinner. Why would he carry a knife on a visit? To kill, of course. And with that, I believe the prosecution has proven... This was a premeditated murder.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Amazing, Mr. Edgeworth. Absolutely brilliant. A brilliantly clear deduction.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It seems like Edgeworth had this planned from the very beginning...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This must be one of those "traps", and I just walked headlong into it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">A murder weapon with fingerprints, and a button from the victim's costume. There is quite a sizable amount of evidence here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can safely say that any further deliberation is a waste of Your Honor's time. Although... I wouldn't mind if the defense were to present evidence not yet shown to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Evidence not yet shown...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">He means evidence that the court hasn't seen yet. In other words, new evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What does the defense have to say about this, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, well...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix. The judge is favoring the prosecution right now. If we answer with something wrong here...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That gavel of his will be ringing out to the sound of our defeat!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, do you have something important and necessary to present to this court?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This has to be another trap! Better if I don't say anything than risk throwing out a bad piece of evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Looks like the defense isn't saying a peep on this one.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Which means this court is adjourned.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix! We will lose this case if you give up here! So you had better show the judge something! Quick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Slow down! We all know I have a tendency to be wrong more than... I can't even say it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's one...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One piece of evidence that catches my attention. Something that this court has yet to see!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. I will say this one more time. I do not feel this trial needs to continue at all. ... However, I am giving you one chance... and only one.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What the judge is saying, Wright, is don't try pulling one of your usual bluffs here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I mess this up, it's curtains for all of us!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You may now present one, and only one piece of evidence. Now then, what is this important evidence that you must show to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry, Wright, but this time, your bluffing steered you wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can see nothing strange about this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I am a man of my word, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This... is a wine glass, is it not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please look at the photo of the crime scene one more time! The scene is a mess because of the victim's struggle against his assailant. The vase was broken, his makeup is all over the floor... These were all things that were at one point, sitting on top of the dresser.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, yes, I see your point.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However! This glass that is sitting on top of the dresser is mysteriously untouched. The only thing that had not fallen over along with everything else is this wine glass! This piece of evidence is more than strange enough to warrant further consideration!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well? What do you all have to say...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, well, yes, it is a little peculiar...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, isn't it!? I thought it was!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You can stop looking at me with those puppy dog eyes of yours now. Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is it, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your opinion...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You don't need my opinion. Because there is no special meaning to that glass.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's safe to say that the glass was set there after the crime took place. By the person who discovered the body, Adrian Andrews, for example. She could have easily been so shocked that she set the glass down without thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That does sound very plausible. Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Could Ms. Andrews really have set that glass down without thinking...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's possible that is what happened. There's nothing that points to Ms. Andrews not being the one who set the cup down. And if I raise an objection here, that would only make the judge slam his gavel down...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You can't think like that, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Right now, you're hanging on by a very thin thread. Anything else you can grab onto right now is better than nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So in other words, push as far as we can go...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I appear weak here, the trial is over. I can look for my proof later! For now, I should trust my instinct and point with certainty!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">They just might fall for it, if you're thought-provoking enough!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense would like to challenge the prosecution's theory. We would like to see something that proves it was Ms. Andrews who set the cup on the table!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... You've turned the situation on its head yet again, as usual. Mr. Edgeworth. Do you have any proof to back up your claim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's no way he has any. He's just bluffing!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unlike Mr. Wright, I never say anything unless I have the evidence to support it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're not thinking hard enough today, Wright. Did you think this wine glass escaped my notice?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-Then...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course it has been thoroughly inspected... for fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Fingerprints...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There were only one set of fingerprints left on this wine glass.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Only one? Well, whose were they!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They were not the victim's nor the defendant's. Rather, they were of one Adrian Andrews.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That is why I said that the person who had discovered the body had left it there. Are we done here, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grrr! I can't believe I fell into another trap!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Andrews was probably holding the glass when she went to see Mr. Corrida. But upon seeing his dead body, she was stunned, and set the glass down on the dresser.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... What you just said makes a lot of sense.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tsk tsk tsk... Now do you see, Wright? You can't change any part of my scenario as it explains everything all too well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Grrr!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've thought long and hard this past year about what it means to be a "prosecutor". And from here on out, I will show you the answer I have come to discover!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Wait a second... Mr. Edgeworth! I think the prosecution has provided enough evidence for me to enter my verdict...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unfortunately, I can not allow you to pass judgment yet. The prosecution has yet another witness we would like the court to hear from.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Another witness"...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Bailiff! Please bring in the next witness!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What in the world is Mr. Edgeworth thinking?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, witness, please state your name and occupation...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Witness! Your name and occupation, please!</line>
<line speaker="Ray Gun">*rata-tat-tat-tat-tat...*</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Uurrngh!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">...Heh. G.O.T.C.H.A!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Grrrrrrrrr...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder what happened to that calm composure he had earlier...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, Edgey-boy! It's been what, a year since we last met, hasn't it? You should be more happy to see me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I saw the report with her testimony, but who knew that under that helmet... it was the wicked witch of the witness stand!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I tell you, this time I know what I'm supposed to do! So today, I'm going to tell you anything and everything! Even things that don't have to do with that terrible crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms... Witness... "That terrible crime" is all this court needs to know.</line>
<line speaker="Ray Gun">*rata-tat-tat-tat-tat...*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oof!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Shush! I'm talking to my dear Edgey-Wedgey right now! Don't interrupt us, gramps!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, madam.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No no no, please, by all means interrupt her! Please! *ahem* Anyway, witness, your testimony please.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">It's true what they say that youth are hotheaded nowadays. Not that I mind at all, Edgey. Now then, what should I start with...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The witness was on security detail at the hotel on the night of the murder. Is this correct, Ms. Oldbag?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">It was a great job being able to see my dearie Juan! It was almost too much for my little heart to handle!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You mean... You were a fan of the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Look, everyone is crazy over that Engarde, saying he's cute in a fresh way, or something. But not me! I wouldn't say anything so silly. After all, I have no interest in a little child like him. I'm only interested in a real man: Juan Corrida!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Um... But those two were the same age...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Anyway, as I was saying, I was pacing in front of his room that night.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very well. Please tell the court what you witnessed the night of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Leave it to me, Edgey-poo!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Anyway, after the ceremony, I went to pace around in the hallway in front of his room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So Mr. Engarde came out from the victim's room...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">See! It has to be him! He's the murderer!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Well, Mr. Wright. You may begin your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Anyway, after the ceremony, I went to pace around in the hallway in front of his room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Oldbag, what was your post on that night?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">The lobby. I was supposed to help set up the stage for that trifling show. But I refused to help, I'll have you know. It was for that Lead-headed Samurai's show. Heh, I even took out a few of the nails.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe it was a good thing the show didn't go on...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Besides, that manager with the glasses seemed to be working hard at it without me. So I thought I'd take a break and spread my wings a little.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's when you went to hang around the victim's door?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">There was something I was interested in finding out, you know...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something you were "interested" in? And just what was that?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">It's not some little thing I can just go around telling everyone, you know. It's top secret, between me and Juan. Ah, and Edgey, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth. What is this thing she was "interested" in...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have no idea. I despise gossip, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Gossip"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If this has something to do with the case, then you can append it to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It looks like we shouldn't force it right now.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... And did the witness stay in the vicinity of the victim's door the entire time?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, since I was on the job, I made sure to keep a good eye out the whole time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? Then would you tell us the number of people who went in and out of Mr. Corrida's room?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I have no idea! I wasn't born so I could count things for those who didn't pay attention in class! That's why ever since I turned 20, I quit keeping track of how old I really am!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Yes, well, that would explain why your age was not recorded in the report.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In any case... The witness then saw someone, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That's when someone showed up! It was a man coming out of poor Juan's room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who in the world was that!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I'm not allowed to say! This sort of information has to be carefully guarded from the masses, sonny. The man that came out of Juan's room... It was... He was...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes...? He was...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">... Ah! I'm too scared! I can't say his name out loud!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, what I wouldn't give to have Franziska's whip right about now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, I guess I can tell you, since he was such a bad boy anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">It was Engarde. Matt Engarde. He was trying to sneak his way out of Juan's room!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You saw my client!? Are you sure about that!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Yessey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Annoying brat! When I say I saw someone, I saw that person!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I get a sense of déjà vu? Maybe to avoid a mess like last year, I should delve into this a bit further...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please tell the court about the man's face in more detail!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">You don't need me to tell you about his face! That soft, gentle look in his eyes and his effeminate lips! His right eye covered by his silky hair! His sparkling, shining teeth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His teeth were... shining?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, he's shining all around in this week's pin-up poster, dearie.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... This week's pin-up...? Why do you... I mean! I don't care how he looks in this week's issue! Please stay with what you saw that night!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What? Engarde's face is the same no matter where it is, right, you whippersnapper!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, Mr. Wright. Was this testimony just now important or relevant in any way?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess it really wasn't that important after all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*sigh* Mr. Wright, do you know why we say time is valuable? If not, I suggest you learn.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">You've wasted three minutes of this woman's youth. That's more valuable than gold to me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And my intelligence seems to have reverted to that of a toddler...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course it was important, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then perhaps you would like to point out what part of that testimony was important!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't really have to put it that way to get me to say...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. There is something much more valuable than a person's pride. And that is "time". Please don't waste this court's precious time with worthless questions!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor... <thought>I think I just wasted his good favor...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was the man you saw carrying?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">In which hand? His right or his left?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Ah, now this is a real mess. I mean, I can't be expected to answer such a vague question!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. Please be more specific with your question, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry... What was the man you saw carrying in his right hand?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Ah, he wasn't carrying anything in that hand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then how about his left?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Empty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Well, this whole thing has been a lot of nothing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, Mr. Wright. Was this testimony just now important or relevant in any way?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess it really wasn't that important after all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*sigh* Mr. Wright, do you know why we say time is valuable? If not, I suggest you learn.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">You've wasted three minutes of this woman's youth. That's more valuable than gold to me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And my intelligence seems to have reverted to that of a toddler...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course it was important, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then perhaps you would like to point out what part of that testimony was important!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't really have to put it that way to get me to say...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. There is something much more valuable than a person's pride. And that is "time". Please don't waste this court's precious time with worthless questions!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor... <thought>I think I just wasted his good favor...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please tell the court about the man's clothes in more detail!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What a troublesome man you are. Really, as if something like that matters.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But it does.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Um... Now what was it... Oh, yes, it was that thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What thing?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That gaudy thing he's always wearing. That racing jacket.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ah, he was wearing that at the detention center too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That thing's meant for nothing but seducing women out of their pantaloons! Hmph! Men!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, right...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, Mr. Wright. Was this testimony just now important or relevant in any way?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess it really wasn't that important after all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*sigh* Mr. Wright, do you know why we say time is valuable? If not, I suggest you learn.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">You've wasted three minutes of this woman's youth. That's more valuable than gold to me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And my intelligence seems to have reverted to that of a toddler...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course it was important, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then perhaps you would like to point out what part of that testimony was important!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't you see it, Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! I request what the witness said about the jacket be appended to her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I don't quite see where you're going with this, but alright. Witness, please...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Ah well, I don't like to badmouth anyone without reason, but if I must...</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"He was wearing his flashy racing jacket. Honestly, it's all just for show."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You saw my client!? Are you sure about that!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Yessey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Annoying brat! When I say I saw someone, I saw that person!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess I'm going to have to press a little harder on this one... There's got to be some sort of huge contradiction I can find here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">He was wearing his flashy racing jacket. Honestly, it's all just for show.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure the defendant was wearing a racing jacket?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What do you think? It's not like I've seen him in anything other than that horrible thing. I'm sure he was wearing it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She is so sure of herself that it's to the point of self-absorption...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">She may not remember things or be mistaken here and there, but I don't think she's lying.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's bad for us. Really bad.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">But, that's how the human mind is. It also has the tendency to jump off-topic. She's strayed onto a few interesting side-topics this time too, hasn't she? But that's what makes her a sweet old lady, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's because you're not the one who has to question her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Oldbag...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What!? Don't say my name for no reason!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know what this is?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Aaaah! It's button number 2 on the Jammin' Ninja's costume!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now I KNOW she's an obsessed fan... She identified it in a single glance!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Give it here! Give it here! If you don't give it to me, I'll punish you with this!</line>
<line speaker="Ray Gun">*rata-tat-tat-tat-tat...*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow... She really is a die-hard fan to want a button covered in blood...</thought> This button was discovered on Mr. Engarde's body during a full body search.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">See! See! This button proves beyond a shadow of a doubt it was that rascal Engarde!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was caught up in the pleats of his Nickel Samurai hakama pants.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">See! See! And Engarde is the Nickel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Witness! Now, it may just be me, and I do have an active imagination, but just now, didn't you say that the defendant... Matt Engarde was wearing his "usual racing jacket"!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">... ... ... Ah... I'm so sorry. Sorry that you judge people based on what they wear! If I wore the trendiest dress, then maybe you'd think I was the most gorgeous woman ever! But instead, I have to put up with wearing this ridiculous-looking outfit. You'd agree this outfit is hideous, right? I've got a tape recorder stuck on my chest! Lemme tell you, it's HEAVY! So heavy, I wish we would have switched to CDs ages ago! But I'm keeping that dream alive for all those kids out there, I work hard with a smile on my face, don't you understand!? Now, take a look in the mirror. Your clothes are about as interesting as a documentary on curling! You should take a tip or ten from Edgey-poo. Now HE'S got style!</line>
<line speaker="Ray Gun">*rata-tat-tat-tat-tat...*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now hold your tongue still there for one second! So what you saw in actuality, was not Mr. Engarde, the man... but Mr. Engarde, the Nickel Samurai!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">But when you think about it... They're really one and the same anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Oldbag! This is a very important point we're talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Edgey-poo! Do you think so too?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, it might be something worth thinking about.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just say, "It's important" and agree with me for a change!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! Think carefully and try to remember as much as you can before you testify!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">*sigh* Alright, if you insist.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should be the one sighing, not you!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Engarde... Engarde... Yes, now I remember!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I knew it... I knew you'd say he was inside that costume!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What? Did you think there could've been someone else inside that costume? Don't be a bad little boy, thinking such rude things.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... But the possibility does exist!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Ah, young'uns today. I told you, there is no way it was anyone else.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">H-How do you know that?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Because... I said so. And what I say is the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>At least she's just as delightful a witness as she was a year ago...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. You may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Engarde... Engarde... Yes, now I remember!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you please get on with your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hmph! Watch your language, young man! What sort of tone is that to take with an elder! My youthfulness isn't what it used to be, so you should forgive me for everything! If you keep on barking at me like that, I'll start singing at the top of my lungs!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, what?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">"A striking figure by the sea, standing all alone is he. He's the Nickel Samurai!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...She's actually singing... Someone help my poor ears.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth. Can you please do something about this racket!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Witness. I'll give you a piece of gum later if you'll be good and stick to just the facts.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">OKAAAAAAAY! ... You promise, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright. I'll be sending the bill for the chewing gum to your office at a later date.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Remind me to send you a thank you note later too, Edgeworth, old chum...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">The Nickel Samurai, that's right, it was the Nickel Samurai that I saw!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Be a little more careful with your testimony, please! Not too long ago, you said he was wearing his "racing jacket", and now he's not!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">"Not too long ago"...? Then let me ask you this! When you were itty-bitty, what was your grand dream?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What did you want to be when you grew up, whippersnapper!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My dream, huh...? Well, I... uh, wanted to be Judge Wackner, hero of the Public's Court. So what!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">See! And look at where you are now! You're not Judge Wackner, are you!? Are you!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">"What I said earlier"... Who puts any weight into things like that!? The "now" is everything! I can't be held responsible for the "past"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Since when did court become theatrics over testimonies?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">All that matters is that man was inside that costume. Isn't that enough!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Yes, it would have been convenient for him to wear his costume during the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And why would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That way, no one could see his face, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But there's still no advantage for him that I can see. In fact, you would think the costume would make him stand out all the more!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">... You are such a annoying child, you know that? You disagree with everything I say...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Isn't that what YOU'RE always doing to me!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I got it! Maybe it was more troublesome for him to change in and out of his costume!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">He had to go to that post-ceremony stage show right after the crime, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was there anyone else scheduled to appear at the post-ceremony show?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, all the contestants were supposed to go onstage in a friendly gesture thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that included the Jammin' Ninja...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Of course it included him! That's why when Engarde came out of dear Juan's room, I didn't give it a second thought.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">So he must've worn that Nickel Samurai costume when he was stabbing poor Juan.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So let me ask you one last time. The person you saw, it really was the Nickel Samurai?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">As showy as ever. Haven't I been saying that from the very beginning!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Can I throw in the towel yet?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You don't need to think too hard on this one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">There's a contradiction in her testimony and it's sitting in plain sight. The question is what that contradiction means for us...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I have to figure out what you're talking about first, but OK...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Yeah, so, it's a knife. Big deal. If you're trying to scare me with that, I'll have you know it won't work!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No no, that's not my intention at all...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's the knife that was used in the murder, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor. Do you know why this piece of evidence is important to this case?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't even have to ask. It's because the defendant's fingerprints are on it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Is that what you're driving at...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That is exactly what I am driving at.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What are we driving at? And whose car are we driving?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If Mr. Engarde was really in the Nickel Samurai costume at the time of the murder, then it's impossible for his fingerprints to have been left on this knife! Actually, he would have wiped all previous fingerprints on this knife right off!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, that's right! The Nickel Samurai wears gloves, doesn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He probably took his gloves off before he began the stabbing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And why would he do something like that? To leave his prints on the murder weapon? There is no way he would do something like that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, there is one possibility!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then let's hear your "possibility"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's very simple. The defendant went to the victim's room while in costume as the Nickel Samurai. At that time, the defendant held no intent to murder. He was probably just going to relax and talk with the victim about the stage show. Which is why he took his gloves off!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... But the murder still did take place...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's well known that the defendant and the victim had bad blood between them.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, yes... I have heard of that... Well, Mr. Wright? What do you have to say about Mr. Edgeworth's theory...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So let me get this straight. Edgeworth's theory goes like this: When the defendant went to the victim's room, he had no intentions of killing him. Now, up to this point, are there any problems with his theory...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh... I can't see any real problems with his theory...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">But if you let Edgeworth's theory stand, then we're one very large step closer to a guilty verdict. Look at the Court Record again and take another shot at it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, I just have to think about it one more time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, please make your decision soon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I think I need a little more time on this one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This theory contradicts something in an earlier testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What are you babbling about...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, for argument sake, let's suppose Mr. Engarde was the killer. If that's the case, I think it's impossible for the killer to have gone to the victim's room without intent!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Naturally, you point to the one piece with the least value... but with such vigor! Enjoy your energy while you can. Humans don't live forever... Neither do lawyers.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You sure like to think you can bluff your way out of things, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix, pay attention! Let's pretend for a second that Mr. Engarde is the murderer. Now from that angle, if he didn't have a murderous intent from the very beginning, then that means there is a certain object that shouldn't be at the crime scene, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"A certain thing"...? What certain thing...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How are you doing over there? Busy collecting your thoughts?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Alright, let's give this one more try... and with even more spirit this time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This knife. This was used by Mr. Engarde at dinner.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes, we did establish that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which means that if my client was, in fact, the killer... Then he brought this knife with him when he went to visit Mr. Corrida.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However, you just said it yourself. "At that time, the defendant held no intent to murder." If that were true, then why would he bring a knife!? He wouldn't, would he!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which means, Mr. Edgeworth, your theory was flawed from supposition one! And one more thing! If the murderer was wearing the costume at the time of the murder... Then there should be glove marks left on the knife! Which means the defendant's fingerprints shouldn't be all over it like bees on a hive!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that brings me to my final point... This knife was planted by the real killer to hide their identity and mislead us!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Order! Order, I say! Order in the court!! Was this knife really planted by the killer!? Why would the murderer do such a thing!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's to hide the way in which the murder was carried out, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">M-More of your nonsense!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take another good look at the autopsy report! The victim actually died from strangulation! The killer tried to hide thisx by stabbing a knife into thex victim's chest!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But doesn't the autopsy admit that the cause of death was strangulation?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, yes, the real cause of death was easily discovered...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then I'd say the knife did a terrible job of "concealing" this fact!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Aha ha ha...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And that laugh doesn't do a very good job of concealing your error either!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! I will ask you one more time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's to frame my client, Mr. Engarde, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">To frame...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A-Aren't you forcing the interpretation just a little too hard on this one!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But we just established that the witness saw the "Nickel Samurai" in costume, and if that were true, then there shouldn't be a single fingerprint on this knife!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Grrrrrrrrr! Witneeeeeesssssss!!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">... Looks like I've made your life a tiny bit more difficult, huh Edgey...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnnnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, did you or did you not really see the Nickel Samurai?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, I guess at first I might have forgotten, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you saying you mixed up Mr. Engarde with the Nickel Samurai, his character on TV!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">But I mean, I can't really do anything about that! Look, I was waiting around in front of their doors because, well... Well, I wasn't waiting around for the Nickel Samurai, that's for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>She wasn't waiting for the "Nickel Samurai"...?</thought> Alright then... Who were you waiting around for then?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">... Hmph! That's top secret to anyone outside of security!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I have a feeling that you were waiting for Mr. Juan Corrida. Am I correct, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Ha ha ha. The way you think, you are a sad amateur with a terrible case of near-sightedness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Amateur...? Me...? What am I an amateur of...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So Oldbag was waiting around in front of the victim's room... But it doesn't sound like she was waiting to catch a glimpse of Mr. Corrida...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Maybe... Phoenix! Maybe the old bag was waiting around for "that" person!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, if it's who I think Mia's hinting at... It's certainly possible...</thought> Ms. Oldbag. You were waiting for this person to come out of the victim's room, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia">What are you talking about, Phoenix!? She could've waited until the next century and this would never have appeared!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ouch... Busted... Guess there's no fooling her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You two! What do you think you're doing flirting in my courtroom!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We weren't doing anything like that... Honest... <thought>Well, back to the drawing board on this one... Oldbag was waiting around in front of the victim's room...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who is this person...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is Adrian Andrews, Mr. Engarde's manager.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But why would the defendant's manager be in the victim's room...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems that this is the latest rumor in circulation, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Hmm... Oh... This is... Well, this is... Hmm, hmm... Hah, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The judge seems to be really into the "article"... If it can be called such a thing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then this manager with the initials A. A.... Are you saying it's...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Adrian Andrews. Without a doubt, the witness thought so as well.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">... Hmph. Looks like you found me out. Well, that's fine. I can throw away this whole sworn to confidentiality stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Witness...? What in the world are you...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Watch out, Phoenix. I've got a bad feeling about this... A very bad feeling.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I got some information... Some very secret information from a certain source. So that's why I was doing my own little investigation... In secret, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But what for...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, just for myself... Personal reasons and all that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Well, Mr. Edgeworth. How will you proceed from here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I really don't want to do this, however I cannot simply let this point slide.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Very well then. Witness, please testify about this "secret information".</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Get ready! This is going to take the wind out of you young'uns!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm sure we're all capable of handling this... Really, it's not like we're ten years old.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That Engarde is one evil, evil man!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defendant sent his manager...? What a distasteful topic for this court!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What!? Nobody's above gossip! And isn't there a saying!? "The truth is never pleasant."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Never heard that one before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth. What about this Adrian Andrews person...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We have looked into this matter, and found that the "truth" the article proposes is, in fact, baseless gossip.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... But should this be true... Then this proves that the defendant did bear ill-will towards the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...So this means I have to smash this rumor once and for all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Wright. You may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Be careful. The old bag seems rather excited right now.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That's right! Engarde is nothing but your average foul-blooded youth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, as the old saying goes... You've gotta burn old bags with fire! Time to fire up the afterburners and hit the highway to the danger zone!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That Engarde is one evil, evil man!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can't say something like that without proof! That's just slander!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">But it's true! That woman was getting intimate with poor Juan! Look! It says so right here, doesn't it!? "Manager to the stars, Ms. A. A.!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the name of the magazine this came from is "Gossip Land"...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What? Are you saying that "gossip" is all just a pack of lies? Hmph, what do you know? I suppose next you'll swear to me that the "news" is 100% truth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Honestly, sonny. You can't discriminate between the news and gossip!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, discrimination is bad, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Discriminate? When did I do anything like that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Anyway, Engarde will never get me to say "touché"!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">He thought he could ruin poor Juan by causing a huge scandal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A scandal...? What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">You're a dimwitted one, aren't you? I can't believe you don't know what a "scandal" is! Honestly, what are they teaching kids in middle school these days...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, no no! I wasn't asking what the word "scandal" means! Even I know that much!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well! That Engarde thought he could own a monopoly on popularity!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">So to do that, he sent his own manager to get in close with Juan!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't have any proof that Mr. Engarde did any such thing!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">You must be suffering from shock; the shock of hearing the truth. And now, since you're in so much shock, you can't do anything right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You're right, I can't do anything, but boy do I wish I could do something about you.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Alright then, sonny, show me what you've got! Can you show me proof that Engarde didn't bear any ill-will towards Juan!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not going to let you push me around that easily!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Heh. There's many a man who've said those exact words and paid dearly for them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe you should brace yourself this time! Here is my proof that Mr. Engarde did not hold any ill-will towards the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">...Is that it? You can take it from here, Edgey-poo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">EH!? Wh-What are you handing it over to me for!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I want you to give that jagged-headed baboon-boy a message for me! Please? Tell him that no matter what he does, the only thing he's good at is failing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Um... What she said, Wright! Or should I say... Baboon-boy!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I agree this isn't much of a piece of evidence... Baboon-boy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Did I just gain a new nickname here...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I don't have anything to offer.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Seeeeeee! Just as I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">And you were lecturing me about saying things without proof! You've just given me a free pass to say whatever I want whenever I want, silly boy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Me and my big mouth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That's the way the cookie crumbles. For you, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I cannot condone such dirty tricks! So I took action!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what do you mean by "I took action"...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Like I already told you, I was lying in wait close to the crime scene! Once that slimy woman came out of Juan's room... I was going to capture her, and teach her a good lesson. Something you young'uns need!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You were going to "teach her a good lesson"...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I was going to make her eat the damaging beams of my ray gun! Like this!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">N-No, stop!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, it was too bad that woman didn't come through the door that night.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">...Oh, and this is top secret, you got that!? Nobode else but you and me know yet, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What!? I'm a busy woman! Tea time with the kids is over!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Secret information that no one else knows yet... If that's true, then how do you know this "secret information"!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Huh!? Well... That's... because I'm a pro... Yes, that's it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I-It's a secret! Even if you drill a hole into my brain, you'll never find out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How in the world did that old bat get such a "secret" piece of information...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you don't be a good girl and tell me where you got this secret information... You won't get to go home today!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Umm... Edgey-boy! What are you doing!? Help me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eh!? What do I have to do with this!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Just do this for me... You'll get your reward.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. I don't want your reward, but you don't leave me much of a choice...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The witness could have gotten her information from anywhere! It's even possible that it was spontaneously made up inside the witness' head!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And he lectures ME on "reckless blabbering"!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">As long as we don't know where this information came from, it's quite a waste of time to focus on this line of questioning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Where did Oldbag get her inside information...? There has to be something I can use to figure it out!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So no one else is supposed to know this "secret information" correct? If that's true, then why do you know it, Ms. Oldbag...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Wh-Wh-Why are you looking at me like that...? Stop that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Witness! I'm sad to say it, but this is how you found out this secret, isn't it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You call that "proof"!? It looks more like proof of spite towards the witness! If you have nothing to back up your claims, then they are no more valid than "gossip"!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection sustained. Witness, please feel free to ignore the defense's gesture of ill-will and continue.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Okie-dokie! See, nothing can get me down!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great... That did nothing but set me back a few minutes of my life...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should probably think a bit more about this... I don't want to do anything rash... For now, maybe I should sit back and watch how things play out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Sounds like just another tidbit of gossip, doesn't it? But you can't just ignore it either. It makes your client look bad either way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I don't think I heard anything really out of the ordinary just now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">There has to be something we can catch her on...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah... And when I find it, I'm going to press the heck out of it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The "investigative photographer", Lotta Hart...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh yes... I remember that mischievous girl.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She reported that she had lost a certain note she had written to herself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">She reported such a thing...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On that piece of paper, she had written down some of her outrageo... er, impressions about the relationship between the victim and Ms. Andrews.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Wh-What!? Outrageous ideas, you say!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No no no, I said impressions.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Then... Then...! Then everything written on this piece of paper is completely meaningless!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah! That's it! That's the note!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Ah! AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHH! Noooo! You see, this is something completely different! This is my top secret list of groceries to buyyyyyyy!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, then you are the one who took Ms. Hart's note?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I'm a huuuuuuuge fan of Juan's, that's why! That infamous, puffy-haired whippersnapper... She's working with that evil Engarde! She said so herself! "En garde! I'm his sidekick!" She was so happy, smiling like a silly duck. I was only checking what she had written!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">... Edgey-poo! You believe me, don't you!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I was only trying to help out like the angel I am! It's only one little piece of paper! I've never taken anything else before!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You really should come with a supply of cheese to match your vintage whine.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, it was only a piece of paper. I suppose we can overlook this just this once.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She looks like she's really sorry... Should I forgive her?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I let up on her now, she'll get away... I have to find some way to inflict a deafening blow to the prosecution!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess we should forgive her.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hmph! Who the heck are you to decide who should be forgiven, you delinquent!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Grr... <thought>Number of endearing qualities: ZERO.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix. You can't go easy on her. She's no frail old lady.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You should be pressing her until she gives in!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mia is really scary today... *gulp*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Witness! You said that the only thing you stole was that note. Is this correct?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">S-S-Stole!? Why don't you listen more carefully, you annoying brat!? I saved this piece of paper from the terrible, lonely trash can! That's all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're lying, dammit! And I can prove it!!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Are you putting my credibility under scrutiny again!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Oldbag! I don't believe that the note is the only thing you stole that night!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. More than the witness' credibility, perhaps you should be worrying about your legal standing, or should I say, falling?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm setting the volume down to low so I won't have to waste my time with your objections!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I never knew the judge had hearing aids... Argh! Now's not the time to be wondering about health conditions! OK, one more try!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Oldbag! That note was with a camera, inside its case, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A camera...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yesterday, Lotta Hart was raising a huge stink over her camera. She kept saying something like, "My sweetie $1,600 camera disappeared on me!"</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why... Why... Witness!!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What is it, gramps?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you have the note, then it is only logical that you have the camera too!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Grr... Looks like you found me out again, sonny... Is this the camera you're looking for?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, that's...!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What!? Even though I look like this, I'm still a person, you know! I still eat meals like you, I fall in love... and "borrow" things from people!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Um... I think your definition of "borrow" is a little off...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I saw that woman's business card and that's when I noticed it said, "Slimebag Celebrity Photographer Extraordinaire"! Well, when I saw that, I had to know what sort of pictures she had taken! I'm a professional security guard! It's my business to know these things!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Check this camera's photos. Hurry! We must examine them at once!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Edgeworth... What do we have?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is only one photo that seems to be relevant to this case.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please present it to the court! Th-This is... This is the Nickel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">See, I told you! That's the guy I saw!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This proves that the witness was not lying earlier about this matter.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What does all this mean, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This photo by itself does not prove that the person in it is the defendant. However! In his own confession, Mr. Engarde clearly stated that... At the time of the murder, he was still in his Nickel Samurai costume!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that is the case, then... this Nickel Samurai is...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How did it come to this...? I think this brings us to the end. We have examined every piece of evidence thoroughly. Final comments, Mr. Wright? The court will consider them before we close. Do you agree that this photo is decisive evidence against your client?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If this photo really is decisive, then we're done for! But if I raise an objection here and blow it, then I would put Maya's life in jeopardy. I can't make a mistake here! There is only one road out of this mess!</thought> This photo that Lotta took... There's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is nothing strange with this photo.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. I have done nothing to alter this picture either, in case you're wondering, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... And it seems the defense will rest on this matter. In that case, there is no reason to further prolong this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Is this really alright with you, Phoenix!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well... There's nothing wrong with this photo that I can poi--</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Try again! Take another good look at it! And if you still don't see anything... Do something... anything to prolong the trial!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Chief! W-Wait, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, Mr. Wright? I'm about to enter my verdict. Please address me with your comment afterwards.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, no, I'm sorry, but this can't wait...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? Let me guess. You are going to point out some peculiarity with this photo?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What? Why didn't you say so earlier!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's... There's something strange with this photo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I knew this was coming, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your thoughts, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think we can all agree there is nothing strange with this photo. There is no way for the defense to debunk this photo, even with a bunker buster.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Debunk with a bunker buster"!? Is that what you're planning to do, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Um, anyway, please look at the photo one more time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you really believe you can honestly find something wrong with this photo, then you should only need one chance, correct...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Well... <thought>I have to find something wrong with this photo! I can't let this chance go by! Where in the heck did she take this picture anyway...? It's all out of focus! Why can't she take a good shot, especially when it counts!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, let's hear your objection. What about this photo is "strange"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's this person here, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You mean the "Nickel Samurai"? And what is wrong with that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At the time of the murder, Mr. Engarde was in his own room! Which means this Nickel Samurai is a fa--</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you think that's all it takes, you should reconsider your choice of occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think it's about time you retired!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, it looks like there was no problem with this photo after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The problem was with the brain of that lawyer, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You are the one who let your last chance fly away from you, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The strange thing is somewhere around here! ...I think.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Somewhere"...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Around here"...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">"I think"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Am I seeing something you all are not...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, it looks like there was no problem with this photo after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The problem was with the brain of that lawyer, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You are the one who let your last chance fly away from you, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I would like to direct the court's attention to this one area right here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What are you pointing to? His ankles...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you could see this person's ankle, that would be one thing... However you can't.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-And...? What does that mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The "Nickel Samurai" in this photo could not have been Mr. Engarde!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is the meaning of this!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wonder if you would care to elaborate... With actual facts, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's take a look at the Nickel Samurai's poster. Please pay particular attention to the area around the bottom of the hakama.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">His... His socks... You can see his socks...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly! However, in this photo... The Nickel Samurai is clearly holding his hakama up just to walk!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is only one explanation for this! The person inside this costume is clearly much shorter than the defendant! <thought>Alright. I think I've turned things around for myself this time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's curious...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What is?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Edgeworth is unusually calm today...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's true...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">He's just letting the trial run itself; as if he's only along for the ride.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Along for the ride"...? What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I can only think that perhaps he doesn't feel under attack at all...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He doesn't feel under attack!? Then, he's not taking any damage!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth! Where does this leave us!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If the person in this photo is not Matt Engarde... Then everything the prosecution has tried to prove has become meaningless!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Hmm... I thought it would come to this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright. I have something I want to ask you. I think you have proven that the person inside this costume is not Matt Engarde. In that case... Who IS this a photo of...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who is the person wearing the Nickel Samurai costume?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Don't stress out over this, Phoenix. It's very simple. What you should be focused on is Edgeworth's attitude, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah... Why is he so calm...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Let's hear your thoughts. Who is the person in this photograph...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you saying this is who you think was in the costume...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... Um... Well, I know there isn't a lot to back me up here, but...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sometimes I wonder about you. Do you just pick the first piece of evidence you see?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I can't believe it. I didn't think you would mess up here of all places...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh... And I really thought I had it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, would you care to try one more time?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-Adrian Andrews...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you want to know who that Nickel Samurai is, it is none other than this woman!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And why would you say it would be Ms. Andrews!? What in the world points you to her?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">For starters, she's short. And, she can freely move in and out of Mr. Engarde's room. Finally, she had dinner with Mr. Engarde that night.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And how does that all add up?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It means that it makes it very easy for her to get a certain item. ...A certain knife with Mr. Engarde's fingerprints all over it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The knife that was used as a murder weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why don't you just say what it is you want, Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to do this now! This is my last chance to turn things around!</thought> The defense motions to indict Ms. Adrian Andrews in the murder of Juan Corrida! It was Ms. Andrews who tried to frame the defendant for the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order!! ORDER!! It looks like this trial has hit a most unexpected development! Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court is issuing a subpoena for Ms. Adrian Andrews! A verdict cannot be passed without first hearing her testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Alright! This is it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">This... is kind of bad for us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">If Adrian Andrews is summoned to court as a witness... It means that the trial will go on for another day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One more day...? Ack!! <thought>If I don't get a verdict TODAY, then Maya...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, we shall set Ms. Andrews' testimony for tomorrow...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-What am I supposed to do!? The judge is about to adjourn the court!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to do something... The trial must go on! But I don't have anything left... No evidence, no nothing!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, court will adjourn for tod--</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please, Your Honor! Continue the trial! You must pass a verdict today!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can't do that. We cannot hear Ms. Andrews' testimony if she is not--</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I abhor wasting such valuable time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor. I request that you please continue with today's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But... We cannot continue due to this unexpected development!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tsk, tsk. "Unexpected" development? I think you underestimate me, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what do you mean by that...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That Mr. Phoenix Wright would slave his way to subpoenaing Ms. Adrian Andrews is all happening according to plan... Even if Wright was a bit slow to catch on...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-Wh-Wh... WHAAAAAAAAAAAAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is the meaning of your statement, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Adrian Andrews is currently waiting in the prosecution lobby... She is the next witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>Everything... Everything was planned out in advance by that man...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Somehow, I knew there was no way Edgeworth would overlook Ms. Andrews... Looks like this battle is far from over.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. We will call the next witness. However... Before we proceed, we shall take a 10 minute recess. Please prepare your witness in that time, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will now take a 10 minute recess.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Dude! I can't believe that Adrian... No way! Not cool and collected Adrian Andrews!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She is your manager. It would have been very easy for her to pull this off. The only person who had easy access to the knife you used at dinner was, well... Her.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">So after the ceremony, during the break, huh...? I was sleeping like a log the entire time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">See, she could have also easily planted that blood-covered button in your hakama.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Hmm... Because she was the one that came to wake me up? ... Then... Dude, you're saying it really was her...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. She is the real killer... She was the one who murdered Juan Corrida.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">But... Why!? I thought she was buds with Juan...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She has her own agenda.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">H-Her own agenda!? Wh-What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure you'll see by the time this trial's over. It'll be alright. I'll get you acquitted by the end of today.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Get me a verdict that's refreshing like a spring breeze, OK Mr. Lawyer dude?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix... You think her motive is related to Celeste Inpax's missing suicide note, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes. Ms. Andrews depended on Ms. Inpax for her strength and will to live. But then Ms. Inpax suddenly killer herself. It sounds like she left a suicide note, and the person thought to have hidden it...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...Is Juan Corrida, the victim of this murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's why I think that Ms. Andrews got close to Mr. Corrida... All to get the suicide note back!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That sounds plausible... But one thing bothers me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, what...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Who was it that first told us about their relationship? Better stated, Mr. Andrews' co-dependency with regards to Ms. Inpax...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... It was Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It looks like he's still the one in command of this ship. Don't let your guard down yet.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court will now reconvene. Now then, Mr. Edgeworth, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution calls the witness subpoenaed by this court. Ms. Adrian Andrews, the person who discovered the crime in Mr. Juan Corrida's room!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is your occupation?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I am the manager of the defendant in this case, Mr. Matt Engarde.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Now then...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Before we begin, Your Honor, I have one request.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh, yes, sure. What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I'm sure everyone in this room is wondering the same thing, and would love to find out more about my relationship with the victim. After all, it was the topic of a certain weekly "magazine" recently...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, no, I have no idea what you mean. I've never even heard of "Gossip Land"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If the judge was ever a prosecution witness, he'd do all my work for me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Anyway, I was wondering if you could please tell us about your relation to the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes, I was seeing Mr. Corrida. I was also aware of the rivalry that existed between Matt and Juan... But this was a private matter between Juan and myself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, so it was a "fry 'n bait" matter... or was that "bait 'n fry"? Reminds me of fishing...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">But I... But I didn't kill him.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No one has accused you of that.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I've got a feeling someone will soon...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think we all understand your relationship with the victim now, Ms. Andrews.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very well then. Witness, please testify to the court about what happened when you discovered the murder that had taken place.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It was time for the show to start, so I went to get Matt from his room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You poured yourself a glass of juice...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes. Sadly, I didn't remember not to touch things at the scene of a crime... And I disturbed the crime scene by moving this one thing...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And that is when the fingerprints on the wine glass were made, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Well, Mr. Wright, you may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix. She is one cool and collected customer, and she has the brains to match.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... I know.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">In order to catch a person like her, you have to avoid head-on confrontations. You should disrupt her pace.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Disrupt her pace...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">She's the type of woman who is easily thrown off by things inconsistent with her thinking so you have to attack when she least expects it. The instant you let up on your offense is the instant this trial is over. Understand?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It was time for the show to start, so I went to get Matt from his room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what was Mr. Engarde doing at the time...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">He was taking a nap. He was worn out from his mini performance as the Nickel Samurai during the ceremony...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, Mr. Engarde did say he was taking a nap...</thought> Then I guess you could say it could not have been taken out of his room, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Excuse me? "It"...? What are you...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright. I thought years of school would have taught you how to construct a sentence. If you can't make a sensible sentence with a subject, then I'll make one for you. Watch. Did you, Ms. Andrews, remove Mr. Engarde's knife from his room?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...No.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Subject, verb, object Wright. Did you skip basic grammar? The witness may continue.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">After that, I went to Juan's room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And why did you do that...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">As a friendly gesture, Juan was to make an appearance with the other Heroes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So the show was supposed to be a "show" of friendship, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that the only reason?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I beg your pardon? What are you implying...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You had a certain goal in mind when you started to get close to him, correct...? So perhaps you had a more personal matter to discuss with the victim...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... Sorry, but I didn't have any such intentions in mind at that time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't get her to talk without a strong piece of evidence, I guess...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should back off... As long as I don't have any proof, she's not going to talk.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">May we continue now...? Witness, what did you see when you got to his room?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">And there was his dead body. I... I was in shock...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were "in shock"...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">What? Was I not supposed to be?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ms. Andrews is a very calculating person... And despite how "close" they were, I doubt she had romantic feelings for Mr. Corrida...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Anyone randomly stumbling upon a dead body would be in shock. And you can't seriously expect that a young beauty like her would not be shocked.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Somehow, I don't think beauty has anything to do with being shocked or not...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Andrews, I would like to confirm with you one more time. When you discovered the dead body of Juan Corrida, you were in great shock. And that's when you poured yourself the glass of juice, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">And what of it...? My mind really was a complete blank at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your mind was a complete blank? I didn't think that was possible for you.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Aren't you rude today? I was so dazed that I made one careless mistake... That one thing...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What "one thing"?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Um, never mind. It's no big deal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What was she starting to say just now...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, it probably doesn't have anything to do with the case, so...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Stop right there. You finally got her to open her mouth on this one, and you're going to let it go? Now is the time to get as much out of her as we can.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Andrews! I'm convinced that as you said, you made a "mistake" at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What I really want to know is what this "mistake" was.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm, actually... So would I...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I... I'm sorry... It's just... It's kind of... embarrassing... When I... When I set the glass down on the dresser... I accidentally... knocked the flower vase over...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">F-Flower vase...? Are you talking about the one on the floor in the crime photo...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This mess of glass shards!?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It was originally on top of the dresser... but when I bumped into it with my elbow, it fell... onto the guitar case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-Why did you withhold such an important piece of information!?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I'm sorry... I thought that since the crime scene was already in disarray, that people would simply assume the vase was just another part of the mess.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It looks like yet another fact has come to light here. Please add this and anything else you have to reveal to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I'm sorry... But... I have nothing more to add... I didn't touch anything else.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"I was the one who knocked the flower vase over, where it fell onto the guitar case."</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">What I saw was, naturally, the exact same scene as in the crime scene photo.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the photo you're referring to, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes, the one with the knife lodged in his chest...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the guitar case was like this too?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes, it was open and empty, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And then, what did you do next, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I felt as though I was about to faint, so I poured myself a glass of juice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Juice...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes, there was a bottle of tomato juice on the table, so I helped myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you didn't drink any of it, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There were no lip marks left on this wine glass to suggest that anyone drank from it.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I... I wasn't feeling terribly great, so I set the glass down. Without drinking it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Andrews, I would like to confirm with you one more time. When you discovered the dead body of Juan Corrida, you were in great shock. And that's when you poured yourself the glass of juice, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">And what of it...? My mind really was a complete blank at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your mind was a complete blank? I didn't think that was possible for you.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Aren't you rude today? I was so dazed that I made one careless mistake... That one thing...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What "one thing"?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Um, never mind. It's no big deal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What was she starting to say just now...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, it probably doesn't have anything to do with the case, so...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Stop right there. You finally got her to open her mouth on this one, and you're going to let it go? Now is the time to get as much out of her as we can.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Andrews! I'm convinced that as you said, you made a "mistake" at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What I really want to know is what this "mistake" was.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm, actually... So would I...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I... I'm sorry... It's just... It's kind of... embarrassing... When I... When I set the glass down on the dresser... I accidentally... knocked the flower vase over...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">F-Flower vase...? Are you talking about the one on the floor in the crime photo...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This mess of glass shards!?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It was originally on top of the dresser... but when I bumped into it with my elbow, it fell... onto the guitar case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-Why did you withhold such an important piece of information!?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I'm sorry... I thought that since the crime scene was already in disarray, that people would simply assume the vase was just another part of the mess.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It looks like yet another fact has come to light here. Please add this and anything else you have to reveal to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I'm sorry... But... I have nothing more to add... I didn't touch anything else.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"I was the one who knocked the flower vase over, where it fell onto the guitar case."</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I was the one who knocked the flower vase over, where it fell onto the guitar case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What kind of flower vase was it?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It was a glass vase... and it was fairly big and heavy. I thought I would try to take Juan's pulse... So I set the glass I was holding down on the dresser. And that's when my elbow accidentally hit the vase...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's odd. I thought she was always in total control of herself...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's what she would like people to think. Always be mindful of the gap between the perception and reality.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It doesn't sound like there's any glaring contradictions in her testimony just now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">I warned you earlier that she would not crack so easily. The only way to make her is to...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Keep on the offensive and not let up.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The only way you're going to catch her is with some very strong, decisive evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to find something! I just have to! ...For Maya's sake...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You testified that you knocked the flower vase over. Is this correct?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And are you sure it fell onto the guitar case?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I-Is there some problem with what I said...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not "some" problem, it's a "major" problem. It's true that the top of the guitar case was wet with water. However, that's exactly what is so strange! Ms. Andrews! You testified that the vase fell onto the guitar case! However! If that was true, the case should have gotten wet on the inside, not the outside!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That's very true!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Furthermore, there is one other strange thing about this guitar case.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And wh-what is that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's take another look at the crime scene photo. The remains of the vase are scattered on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what is wrong with that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If the guitar case was open when the vase fell... The glass shards should be INSIDE, not outside the case!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is your point, Wright!? That the case was closed at the time the vase was knocked over? Is that all!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No. Think back to what Ms. Andrews testified to! She said that other than the vase, she didn't touch anything else!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, that's right... She did implicitly say she didn't touch the guitar case!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But... But this whole matter with the guitar case is a dead end! The bright red guitar was found at the studio! It has no bearing on this case at all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... That may very well be, however... <thought>An empty guitar case does seem to have no relation to this case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It seems that there is no deeper meaning to the guitar case. Well, Mr. Wright? Do you think we need to hear more details about the guitar case?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, the case was empty, and I think that's all we really need to know...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wait! Phoenix! Don't you remember what I told you earlier? What's important here is that you disrupt her pacing. You have to attack her when she's not expecting it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, let's move on to a different matter...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, Your Honor, I've changed my mind. I would like her to testify about the case.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Wh-Why are you changing your mind NOW!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, looks like I disrupted the judge's pacing... Now comes the real deal... *gulp*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The empty guitar case... I believe this is a crucial piece of the puzzle!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh! I can't believe ANYONE would reach for straws like this! But it is you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't believe I'm doing this either...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Alright. I'll follow along... For now. Ms. Andrews, please testify to the court about the guitar case.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I don't remember too clearly because I was a bit dazed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It looks like this really wasn't a very important point.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This wastefulness is such a familiar feeling by now that it's almost... comforting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, anyway, I'll just go ahead and start the cross-examination...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Using "anyway" to change the topic; a convenient escape for a weak man.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I don't remember too clearly because I was a bit dazed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">During your testimony just now, did you remember those events clearly in your mind?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... Well, you see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure you are the one who opened the guitar case?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">She's... She's waiting for someone to tell her if she should answer or not...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Her "co-dependency" is coming through, huh...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Ms. Andrews...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Y...Yes, it was me...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I suppose I must have opened the guitar case... after I knocked the vase over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you opened the guitar case then?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Y-Yes... Well, maybe...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Why did you open the guitar case?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Corrida's dead body was right there in front of you, wasn't it? I would think that the first thing you would do is call for help, not open a guitar case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As the witness has said multiple times, when she found the dead body, she was "dazed".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Maybe I... Maybe I was curious to know if the bright red guitar was alright or not. I thought, "Maybe the criminal took it."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why would she care about the bright red guitar...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">But, getting back on topic...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is no way you were the one who opened the guitar case.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Why would you say that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's elementary, my dear. Because the only fingerprints on this guitar case are those of the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, Ms. Andrews?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... You shouldn't assume that I must have left prints just because I touched the case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">What if I were to tell you that I was wearing gloves at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Gloves...? But why would you be wearing gloves at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It was the night of the award ceremony. So of course I dressed up for the occasion. Yes, now I remember... I'm almost sure I was wearing a pair of thin gloves.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see... Well, Mr. Wright. It seems the witness was wearing gloves at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, I guess so... And I guess that makes sense.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. You're the epitome of a half-baked idea.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">A brain is to be used, not to look pretty for med students carving cadavers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like I need to bake my thoughts just a little longer...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, if the defense has no further objections, let's return to the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were wearing gloves...? Isn't that a little strange?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Why is that strange!? Do you have something that would prove I was not wearing gloves at the time...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think it's time for you to go home now, Wright... Before you hurt yourself, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hurt myself...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's alright, Mr. Wright. You don't have to push yourself so hard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I was trying a little too hard there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, if the defense has no further objections, let's return to the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It's not a big deal though, right? The case was empty after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was it really empty?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was just wondering if maybe when you opened the case, the guitar was still inside.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How long have you been a lawyer, Mr. Wright!? Have a little professionalism. The bright red guitar was found at the studio. These trials would be over in half the time if you would just pay attention.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, pay more attention, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is no way you were the one who opened the guitar case.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Why would you say that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's elementary, my dear. Because the only fingerprints on this guitar case are those of the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, Ms. Andrews?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... You shouldn't assume that I must have left prints just because I touched the case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">What if I were to tell you that I was wearing gloves at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Gloves...? But why would you be wearing gloves at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It was the night of the award ceremony. So of course I dressed up for the occasion. Yes, now I remember... I'm almost sure I was wearing a pair of thin gloves.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see... Well, Mr. Wright. It seems the witness was wearing gloves at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, I guess so... And I guess that makes sense.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. You're the epitome of a half-baked idea.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">A brain is to be used, not to look pretty for med students carving cadavers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like I need to bake my thoughts just a little longer...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, if the defense has no further objections, let's return to the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were wearing gloves...? Isn't that a little strange?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Why is that strange!? Do you have something that would prove I was not wearing gloves at the time...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think it's time for you to go home now, Wright... Before you hurt yourself, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hurt myself...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's alright, Mr. Wright. You don't have to push yourself so hard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I was trying a little too hard there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, if the defense has no further objections, let's return to the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">As for why I opened the case... Even I don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was that because you were "shocked and dazed" at discovering the victim's body?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes... That's probably it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not going to get anywhere if I continue pressing her like this... The only way to make her talk is with evidence... I guess I should give it a try...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is no way you were the one who opened the guitar case.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Why would you say that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's elementary, my dear. Because the only fingerprints on this guitar case are those of the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, Ms. Andrews?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... You shouldn't assume that I must have left prints just because I touched the case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">What if I were to tell you that I was wearing gloves at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Gloves...? But why would you be wearing gloves at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It was the night of the award ceremony. So of course I dressed up for the occasion. Yes, now I remember... I'm almost sure I was wearing a pair of thin gloves.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see... Well, Mr. Wright. It seems the witness was wearing gloves at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, I guess so... And I guess that makes sense.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. You're the epitome of a half-baked idea.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">A brain is to be used, not to look pretty for med students carving cadavers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like I need to bake my thoughts just a little longer...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, if the defense has no further objections, let's return to the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were wearing gloves...? Isn't that a little strange?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Why is that strange!? Do you have something that would prove I was not wearing gloves at the time...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think it's time for you to go home now, Wright... Before you hurt yourself, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hurt myself...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's alright, Mr. Wright. You don't have to push yourself so hard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I was trying a little too hard there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, if the defense has no further objections, let's return to the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Come on, Phoenix. We can't afford to let up on her now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wasn't planning on letting up, but...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">She's at her weakest now, so this is our chance!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, if we had a weapon to hit her with...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">I'm sure a weapon is hiding somewhere in the Court Record, waiting to be found.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have your proof right here. This wine glass.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">The wine glass?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You left your fingerprints very clearly on this wine glass.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even if you took your gloves off when you poured yourself this glass of juice, wouldn't you think it was just a little strange... That you put your gloves back on, just to open the guitar case!?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Ugn!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Looks like you hit the nail on the head this time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I believe that guitar case plays a very important role here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But it's just an empty case...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I wonder if it really was empty though...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But the guitar... The bright red guitar was at the studio!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix, drop all of your presumptions. What was in the guitar case was not the bright red guitar.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You don't mean... it was a bright WHITE guitar!? Wait, that's not right either...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, I admit it would be unnatural for someone to do that. So the witness was not wearing gloves, despite the fact that on the case...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor, this is obviously the defense's usual misdirection tactic at work. Steer the court towards an unrelated topic, and lull us all into his misguided...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Your Honor! Please recall that Ms. Andrews had testified that the vase "fell onto the guitar case"! Which means that the case was closed when the crime took place! However, it is wide open in this photo of the crime scene! I am sure this guitar case has some relation to the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you are so sure, Wright, then I'm sure you can somehow substantiate your outrageous claim, correct!? Please, enlighten us as to why that guitar case has anything at all to do with this murder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Can you do that, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, well... Let's suppose for a second... That the bright red guitar was not the only thing that could have been in the case...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The bright red guitar not being the only thing...? Y-You don't mean to suggest that a bright BLACK guitar was inside the--</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, you intend to push your theory that the case was not empty!? Is that it, Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wouldn't say something I didn't intend to prove!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Deflate that head of yours! You haven't proven anything yet! Now then, let's have it. What was inside this case at the time of the murder!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And why would something like that be inside a guitar case, let alone this one?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, Mr. Wright, why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... I just thought it might have been possible...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have a suggestion. Why don't you put that in the void where your brain is supposed to be!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, and never bring it out again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Can't a foolishly foolish fool get some love...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you still think you can prove your theory? Can you prove that the guitar case was not empty at the time of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-This is... This is a photograph...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, but what is important is what is in that picture, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-In this picture...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It doesn't take a genius to see what I mean! What I am proposing is... Inside the guitar case was the Nickel Samurai! The hero's very own costume!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Wright! Explain yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright! Are you saying that the witness opened the guitar case to take out a costume!? What insane point would there be to doing something like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That insane point would be to wear the costume, of course. Ms. Andrews put it on to hide her identity so she could make her escape. After all, you couldn't let anyone see you leave, could you, Ms. Andrews?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I refuse to accept your theory! Do you have anything to support such a preposterous idea!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just outside the door was an investigative photographer who was starving for a big scoop. And in the end, she managed to get this shot, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You... You mean this photo!? Order! Ordeeeer! It looks like we've wandered into quite another mess again, haven't we...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Nice job, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, you know my strategy. Speak first, think later!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So the real murderer was hiding inside a costume...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait one second, Your Honor! The Nickel Samurai's costume would have been Mr. Matt Engarde's! Why would something of the defendant's be in the victim's room!? And inside the guitar case, of all places!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, true... That is a little baffling... Mr. Wright, the court would like to hear your thoughts. What was this Nickel Samurai costume doing inside the guitar case...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think it may have been stolen from Mr. Engarde...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-Stolen!? But why would someone do such a thing!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe the thief wanted to interfere with the post-ceremony stage show.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And so, if he didn't have his costume, then Mr. Engarde would be forced to go naked!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Maybe YOU should be stripped naked and run out for making a mockery of this court!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-EXCUSE ME!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Matt Engarde did not take his costume off after the award ceremony! He even testified that he took a nap while still wearing his costume! Is this not correct!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Ah, yeah, he did say something like that, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*sigh* That's what I thought. Let's try that one more time, shall we, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Engarde did not take his costume off during the break period... In that case, the costume we are talking about was a spare one.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then... are you saying that on the night of the murder... there were TWO Nickel Samurai costumes at the Gatewater Hotel!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, that is what I am saying.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And how do you explain the costume that was inside the guitar case...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would mean that the victim himself had planned to bring this spare to the ceremony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... But why!? The victim, Mr. Corrida, was the Jammin' Ninja. Why would he secretly bring the Nickel Samurai's spare costume with him...? What could be the reason behind such a peculiar act?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Ah, so that's what he intended...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What are you mumbling to yourself about now!? Have you just been rambling all this time without any sense of inner monologue!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!? N-No, I just...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, please explain yourself! Why do you think the victim had the Nickel Samurai's spare costume!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix... Are you sure you can explain this one? Think carefully before you answer... And then answer with gusto! I believe in you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright. This is what I think. The reason the victim brought the Nickel Samurai's spare costume to the hotel was...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix! What are you doing!? Are you crazy!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I, uh... I presented the evidence with gusto, just like you said!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I told you to present it with gusto, yes... But I seem to recall the sentence before that was, "Think carefully"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What is the meaning of this, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">This one is pretty tough. I really think you should look carefully at the Court Record. And then search through your memories! The answer is there, I know you'll find it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then. Are you ready to try again, Mr. Wright? Minus the wrong evidence this time?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is this...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the night of the murder, after the stage show, the Nickel Samurai was going to hold a special press conference.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A press conference...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, the Nickel Samurai was supposed to confess something at this conference.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I heard about this as well. For once, you're not making something up, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But what struck me as strange was that Mr. Engarde himself said he had no idea he was supposed to be holding a press conference that night.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But how can that be!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The way I see it, that can mean only one thing: The conference was set up by none other than the victim, Mr. Juan Corrida himself!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-The victim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. The spare Nickel Samurai costume was prepared for that very conference! Mr. Corrida was going to hold the press conference as the "Nickel Samurai"!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He was going to dress up as the Nickel Samurai and hold a conference!? But why would the victim do such a thing!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's something I don't quite know yet, however... What I am concerned with right now is what he intended to reveal at that conference.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Nickel Samurai was going to "confess" something. And by "confess", I'd wager he was going to reveal something about "himself".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which means that Juan Corrida, posing as the Nickel Samurai, was going to speak about Matt Engarde!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I guess that is what it would mean...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But, if that's the case... that's not a "confession"! That's "public disclosure"!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Ms. Andrews...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I can see why you are pros at what you do.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Pardon me?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes, just as you say, the press conference was set up by Juan.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Andrews! Please offer us an explanation for this!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I was the one he asked to help set it up. And the person who prepared the second costume for him... That was also me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You...!?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Juan had bet everything on the Jammin' Ninja this year. And if he lost the Grand Prix... He was going to make sure Matt was going down with him. That's what he thought anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He was going to ruin him, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It looked like somehow, Juan had in his hands a secret so powerful... that it would destroy Matt's acting career had it been revealed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And do you know what this "secret" of Mr. Engarde's is, Ms. Andrews...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... That's something only Juan knew. I... I don't know what it is.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah... I see.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I... I've probably been coming off quite suspicious to everyone, but that's to be expected. I've been trying to protect Matt, after all...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Protect Mr. Engarde!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And yet again another strange bit of truth comes to light it seems... Ms. Andrews, if you could, please tell us the truth about your behavior!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes, Your Honor. I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">From the moment I saw the crime scene, I had a feeling that Matt was the murderer.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... This does account for everything...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Well... I am the logical type.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">We're finally seeing her true self. She is more nervous than a scared rabbit.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If there are no objections, I feel that I can pass a verdict based on this testimony. Now then, Mr. Wright, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like somehow everything has swung to the opposite end of the scale again... That just means I have to put my weight into this and turn her logic upside-down!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">From the moment I saw the crime scene, I had a feeling that Matt was the murderer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you say that was your "intuition" speaking to you?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Don't confuse my methods of reasoning with your own.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">If you want to prove that someone did something, you need three things.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Three... things?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">A motive, an opportunity to commit the crime, and finally... decisive evidence. And if you think these three things through, the answer becomes quite clear.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You should have already known that, Phoenix...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They didn't teach that to us in school... At least, not from what I remember...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">May I continue now?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Matt had to kill Juan no matter what.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So would you say this "need" came from the press conference?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes. Do you know why Juan chose that event and that hotel for the conference? Because that was when he could cause the most damage to the public's beloved Matt Engarde.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And you knew of this plan, didn't you, Ms. Andrews?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes... because I was the one who set up the conference and prepared the costume.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... I'm sure Mr. Engarde himself didn't know anything about a press conference.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Oh really? Can you show me any proof that he didn't know about the press conference?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Anyway! The important thing here is that this information was not in your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I agree. Ms. Andrews, please correct your testimony, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">"Grasping at straws" now, are we, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"Matt had to kill Juan no matter what." to "I know what his motive was. ...But I don't have any way to prove I'm right."</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I know what his motive was. ...But I don't have any way to prove I'm right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Has Mr. Engarde done something to hurt or betray you personally?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... Why do you ask?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were the one who helped Mr. Corrida with his press conference... And that event was supposed to bring down Mr. Engarde, yet you still helped out!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The person on trial right now is Mr. Engarde, Wright. What the witness was thinking, helping the victim with his plan, is none of our concern. In any case, this means that the defendant had a motive to kill.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I keep doing this to myself...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">And he didn't have an alibi for what he was doing at the time of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But didn't you already testify earlier that Mr. Engarde was... "Taking a nap in his room"!? Are you telling me now that, that too, was a lie so you could cover for Mr. Engarde!?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I'm not telling you anything of the sort. When I went to get him for the show, he honestly was sleeping. However, as to whether he was sleeping the entire time, that I cannot say. I was too busy setting up the stage at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I keep trying, but I can find no flaws with what Ms. Andrews has said. I can't say the same for some people here in this courtroom, however.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The judge is glaring straight at Mia...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">He's glaring at you, smart guy!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">My thoughts were confirmed by the evidence, of course; the button and the knife...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can hardly call the knife "decisive evidence"! The fingerprints on the knife could very well be a clever camouflage!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Then... What about the button?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The button...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It's clear from the crime scene that the victim and the murderer fought. And during the fight, the killer ripped the button from the Jammin' Ninja's costume.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're talking about this button, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">That button was found in the pleats of Matt's hakama, isn't that correct? I would think that makes it very decisive evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Looks like you were out-foxed again, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Anyway! The knife doesn't prove a thing! Please fix your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I can't stand the sight of a man who can't gracefully accept his defeat.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>... Thank goodness Mia can still look at me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">With an icy stare, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Andrews, for Mr. Wright's sake, please add this information to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"My thoughts were confirmed by the evidence, of course; the button and the knife..." to "That button was torn off of Juan during his fight with Matt."</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">That button was torn off of Juan during his fight with Matt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And how do you know that?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">When the ends of the threads on the button and the costume were matched up, they were found to fit together perfectly... Or so I heard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, I've heard that before too. But why would Ms. Andrews know about this case down to such a fine detail?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Don't look at me like that! Just because I'm prepared and you are not!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh... And I thought I had her this time for sure. If there's anything to trip her up on, it has to be here. ...But where and what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">But I'm Matt's manager... So I felt that I had to protect him...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But what you really did was stab the guy in the back, didn't you? And at the worst possible time.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Who's to say she really "stabbed the guy in the back" as you put it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This witness could have disclosed things about Mr. Engarde at any time. Why, then, would she wait until there was a large audience before doing so? It's the same reason why Mr. Corrida planned such an elaborate conference. Ms. Andrews wanted to cause Mr. Engarde as much damage as she possibly could! This witness bears ill-will towards the defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This isn't the "Phoenix Wright Wax Philosophical Power Hour". And please, stop slandering the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As I expected, Ms. Andrews' testimony seems pretty solid.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Really? Because to me, it sounded a little wishy-washy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wishy-washy? <thought>Well, I guess we'll see if I press a little more...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You should know this by now, but you'll need strong, decisive evidence to make her talk.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it, Chief! <thought>...I'm going to pin you down this time, Ms. Andrews!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the victim's autopsy report. It clearly states that the cause of death was "strangulation by a scarf".</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">S...Strangulation...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The knife stab to the victim was done after the victim had already died.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-And what does that mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's examine the evidence. This button has the victim's blood on it. Which would mean that it was ripped off of the costume... when?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">After the knife was stabbed into the victim...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly! Which means... It is impossible that this button was torn off during the victim's final struggle, because the victim was strangled to death in that fight!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right, Ms. Andrews. There is no way this button was ripped off during the struggle. This button was consciously pulled off of the victim's already dead body!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Wh-What is the meaning--</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is the meaning of this, Wright!? So what if the button was torn off the body after the victim had already died? What does that change!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let me ask you one simple question, Mr. Edgeworth. Why was the button torn off? What purpose did that serve?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What "purpose"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We now know this button was not torn off during the fight. So the murderer took the time and effort to purposely rip this from the victim's body. That would mean that the murderer had something in mind, wouldn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Does this mean... Does this mean you know what the murderer wanted to do with this button!? What was it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe this was the criminal's first crime and since it went so well, the person wanted something as a memento...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright... I'll give this button to you as a memento.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A reminder to never set foot in another court of law again for as long as you live!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes... I think it would be for the best if you stayed away from the attorney's bench.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-W-Wait! Please, Your Honor! I... I'll get it right this time! I'm sure of it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was to destroy the evidence, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... To destroy the evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, we heard you the first time! And which blasted piece of evidence was the person trying to destroy, Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! If you continue like this, I'm afraid you'll only destroy yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is only one logical reason for doing something like that. It was to pin the crime on Mr. Engarde!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is no way anyone would put a bloodied button in their own pants! That's right! Mr. Engarde was set up! By the real killer, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And... The real murder is...? Well, Mr. Wright!? Who in the world is the real killer then!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Finally... I can't believe I managed to bring this trial all the way up to this point...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix... You can't let your guard down yet! Not until the very end!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The real killer, the person who planned to frame Mr. Engarde is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright. Which of these four doesn't belong here? Up, down, left, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, "Wright"?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thank you, I feel much better. I'm relieved to know you can at least pick that much out. I worry about you. You seem to fail every time you try to make logical sense!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Or in other words, "think before you speak", Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is it just me or is everyone ganging up on me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough dawdling now, Mr. Wright. We don't have all day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Adrian Andrews! I choose you! You are Mr. Corrida's killer!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!! Mr. Wright! This is a very grave matter! Do you have any evidence that supports your charge...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Any evidence"...? ALL of the evidence points to Ms. Andrews!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Wh... How preposterous! You can't stick any of that on me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't, can I? Would you care to test me?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Then... Then what about this knife!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The knife was used to stab the victim after he had already been strangled to death. It was used to throw suspicion onto Mr. Engarde, naturally. A knife covered in the defendant's fingerprints could only be taken from his room. And the only one who had dinner with him, and knew which knife to take, was you.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...Tsk! Th-Then! What... What about the button that was found in Matt's hakama!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This button was removed from the victim's body after he had already died. The only people who could've done so were the person who found his body or the killer. However, if Mr. Engarde was the real killer, there is no way he would have put such incriminating evidence in his own hakama!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Ughn...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The only person who could have put this button into Mr. Engarde's hakama, is the person who went to wake him from his nap... which is you, yet again, Ms. Andrews.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I... I see... What about the empty guitar case...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is also another piece of evidence that incriminates Ms. Andrews. That costume was used to hide the real killer's identity as they fled the crime scene. Now, who could have known that there was just such a costume inside the guitar case...? It could only have been the person who prepared the costume for the victim. And that person is... you, Ms. Adrian Andrews!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">N...No... I...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But Ms. Andrews' fingerprints were nowhere to be found on the guitar case! And it was you who proved that she was not wearing gloves at the time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...! Th-That's right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's because she did not intend on leaving any prints. If anyone had found out that she had touched the case, they would have asked her why. So to avoid leaving any prints, she used a towel or something else to open it. But! The glass of tomato juice is a different story! Ms. Andrews purposefully left her fingerprints on the glass to show that yes, indeed, she was the classic "dazed discoverer" of a dead body!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Aaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And to top it all off, there is this photo! A photo of the killer as they exited the scene of the crime. No reasonable person on Earth can believe this Nickel Samurai is Mr. Engarde! He would be much too short for his own costume if it was him.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Speaking of how tall people are... Ms. Andrews, you're also kind of short in stature, are you not?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">P-Please... Stop...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, how about it, Ms. Andrews!?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've got her this time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Andrews...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... I... I... I refuse... to testify.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was that...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Th-There's a law... It says I can't be forced to testify about something... if it can incriminate me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, yes... You are absolutely correct, Ms. Andrews. The law does provide us with a way to avoid self-incrimination... by allowing a witness to not testify if the testimony can cause damage to themselves.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAT!? <thought>"Pleading the fifth" is not something most people would think to do on the spot! Actually... Thinking back to yesterday in Mr. Engarde's room...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Y-Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">A-Alright... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's it. That's when Franziska planted this idea into her head... She must have told Ms. Andrews to not testify if things looked bad.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You did a good job proving everything up to this point, Phoenix. But there is still one thing you haven't done.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something I haven't done...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh heh heh. What's wrong, Wright? Are you finished already? Run out of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is so humorous, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sure you realize this as well, Your Honor... But, everything the good lawyer here has proven up to this point is meaningless.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Everything you have proven is circumstantial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Circumstantial...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, circumstantial. You have yet to provide a single piece of definitive proof. Proof that Ms. Andrews, did in fact, harbor a wish to murder Mr. Corrida!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Ms. Andrews! You... Did you want to kill Mr. Corrida...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I believe this may lead to me incriminating myself, so I will abstain from answering.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But Ms. Andrews... If you do that, it would be the same as admitting your guilt, don't you think...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Maybe so, or maybe not. There is nothing to prove it either way. Besides, you don't even know what crime I would be "guilty" of due to my silence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>NO!! She's taking that defiant attitude again!</thought> M-Mia! What should we do...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Somehow, we've landed in the worst possible situation.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think we have reached a certain conclusion at this point in time. Ms. Adrian Andrews has refused to testify. And the defense's theory that she is the actual murderer... has not been fully substantiated with solid definitive proof.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But! That's not true!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In this situation, there is only one thing this court can do. And that is to declare a recess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Recess...!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I request that both the prosecution and the defense look further into this matter. And at tomorrow's trial...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>T-Tomorrow...!? We don't have a "tomorrow"! If we don't get a not guilty verdict today, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please wait, Your Honor! Th...That's not necessary! The trial... Please continue the trial!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What are you sweating for...? Your client is getting one more day to live, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That... That's not it! This isn't about that. Edgeworth! I know you know who the real killer is! Please... Let the trial continue! If I don't get the verdict... then Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But it's impossible to continue as long as the witness refuses to testify. Now then, this court is...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is not impossible for this trial to continue.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth! Wh-What are you...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's true Ms. Andrews holds the right against self-incrimination; however, if the topic of conversation were something unrelated to whatever she may be guilty of, then she has no right to withhold testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes, that is very true, but...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Actually, there is one little thing that I'm curious about. Ms. Andrews.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">When you found the victim's dead body, you poured yourself a glass of juice.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Y-Yes... And...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can't help but think how unnatural that is. Usually when one finds a body, they are shaken up, not stirring a glass of juice.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">So my actions were "unusual"? But I've already...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Before you speak, I want to state that if you have a reason behind your actions, I would like you to testify to that effect.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Testify...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor! I would like to request that the witness testify again as to what happened when she first discovered the victim's body! Whatever we find out in this testimony should in no way implicate the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I don't know what it is about Edgeworth today, but I can't get a good read off of him. Is he friend or foe? I just don't know...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court acknowledges the prosecution's request. Ms. Andrews, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">That glass of juice... I didn't really pour it for myself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So you poured that glass of juice for the victim. Why didn't you say so in your earlier testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...I didn't think I needed to include something so trivial.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix. Please be careful here. If you can't find anything wrong with this testimony, then there's nothing left...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know. <thought>Edgeworth... What the heck is going on in that brain of yours...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Wright. You may begin your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">That glass of juice... I didn't really pour it for myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... There wasn't anyone else in the room, right?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Of course not.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then... who did you pour it for?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Mr. Wright. There is a rhyme and reason for everything. Can you wait just a little longer for it to be revealed to you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In other words, Wright, "Be quiet and listen."</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Precisely! I couldn't have said it better myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Unnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I was surprised when I walked into the room and saw it in that messy state.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, it was a "mess"? Are you sure it wasn't messy because of your fight with Mr. Corrida...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I understand your frustrations at not being able to prove your theory. However... Before you go accusing people of crimes, go find yourself some evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grr...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And then, what did you see next, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">And Juan... He was sitting slumped over and tired-looking in the corner.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Slumped over?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes, he was just sitting there with his head tilted forward, eyes closed. He really looked like he was sleeping.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Is it just me or did that right there sound a little... odd?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">When I saw him sitting like that, the thought that he was dead didn't cross my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then what did cross your mind?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I thought maybe he had smashed everything up in anger because he lost the Grand Prix. And then felt tired after his rampage, so he decided to take a nap... Anyways, that's what I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. So you didn't think he was dead at all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">To be honest, I thought he had just fainted or something. So I went to pour him some juice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You thought he fainted...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I thought he was asleep at first. But then, the room was in such a messy state... I thought maybe he had gotten into a fight with someone...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And that's when you went to pour the glass of juice?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes. He always has a hard time waking up. So Juan always has a glass of tomato juice to drink.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see. And after that, what happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">When I realized that he was dead... That's when I knocked the flower vase over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And how did you come to realize that he was, in fact, dead?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I shook him over and over, but I never got a response... So I set the glass down on the dresser and tried to take his pulse. I... I was shocked... and staggered backward...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And knocked the flower vase over. So that's what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">... This is what it all comes down to.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">This is the absolute end for both sides... And Adrian is letting her guard down. Phoenix, now is our best chance yet to kill the prosecution's case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Isn't that a bit harsh...? Ms. Andrews... Will you tell us the truth this time...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you honestly didn't think he was dead when you found him?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">No, not at all...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even though this is what you saw when you discovered the body?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What is the meaning of this!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't it obvious, Your Honor? There is a knife sticking straight out of Mr. Corrida's chest! Anyone who saw this scene would have immediately thought that here was a dead man!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Ah... Um... That's... Well, you see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I doubt a single person in the world would mistake this for someone who fainted, and then so nonchalantly go pour something to drink!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Your point is...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Andrews! Your testimony just now... It was all one giant lie!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Ungh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And your lie has proven one thing very clearly. That you are the real killer!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It looks like the defense has somehow brought the ugly truth to light. The defendant, Mr. Matt Engarde, is not guilty after all...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">That... But that's impossible! You're wrong...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Ms. Andrews! Try to have some composure!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It... It wasn't me... It wasn't me, I tell you! It was Matt! I swear it! He's the one who killed Juan!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you were the one who refused to testify! And your reason for not doing so was that you "might" end up incriminating yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Th-That's because...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Andrews, I will give you one last chance. What exactly are you hiding that may "incriminate" you?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... I... I... I refuse... to testify.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then there is no need for this court to continue any further. Mr. Matt Engarde's innocence has been clearly demonstrated.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is... Is it... over...? Have we... Have we found the truth at last...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">What's wrong, Phoenix?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Usually... Well, usually, the real killer confesses his or her guilt. And now that I think about it, this is the first time someone hasn't.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, I would like to hand down my verdict for Mr. Matt Engarde.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor. The prosecution feels that it would be premature to pass down a verdict at this time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The reason is quite simple. This witness has yet to speak the absolute real truth.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The "absolute real truth"...? What are you...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Witness... Don't you understand yet?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't know who planted this silly idea in your head, but as long as you "protect" yourself through your silence, Matt Engarde will go free. And in his place... YOU will become the guilty party!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...Th-That's... That's a lie! I... I don't believe you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I... I was told... If I spoke... If I spoke, then it would be all over... And Matt would never be declared guilty...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-What in the world is she talking about!? Has she lost it!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I... I can't speak about it... I'm too scared...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's Franziska von Karma...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Don't you rememeber, Phoenix? Ms. Andrews lives by gripping tightly onto the words of another. Because she doesn't have the strength to believe in herself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th...Then, right now... Ms. Andrews is...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yesterday, she was tossed a life-saver by Ms. von Karma. "Don't say a word, no matter what happens. If you do, Matt Engarde will be acquitted." Ms. Andrews undyingly believes in those words right now, and is clinging onto them...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Th-Then what should we do!? This... This is the first time I've ever come across anything like this! But Ms. Andrews has to be the killer, right!? All we have to do now is... is get our not guilty... That is my only priority!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It wasn't me! I'm begging you, please believe me! I didn't kill Juan! Help... Please... Someone... Help me...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court can't continue on like this, therefore I'd like to hear what you intend to do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What I intend to do...!? Wh-What am I supposed to do!? What am I supposed to say!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright! I suggest you think very carefully about this! Think about what this witness did, and what she did NOT do! And think about who is the real mastermind behind this crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who's the real mastermind? Isn't that obvious!? There's no one else it could be except the woman crying over there! ...Right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Come now! What will you do!? What kind of man are you, Mr. Phoenix Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No matter what she says... Ms. Andrews is the only person it could be! Not to mention... I don't have a choice. I have to win a complete acquittal today!</thought>  Y-Your Honor! The defense believes there is enough evidence to substantiate our claim! Therefore, we motion that this court passes a verdict of "not guilty" as soon as possible!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm disappointed in you, Wright! What have you learned in this past year!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to win a complete acquittal today... There's no way around that! But... I can't bring myself to do it like this! Not when she's making a face like that...</thought> Ms. Andrews! I would like to know what you are really hiding!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Wright! Are you sure you know what you're doing!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, Mr. Engarde would get an acquittal, but in his place, you would be found guilty! Is this... Is this how you really want this trial to end!?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">B-Be quiet... How dare you!? You... You're trying to trick me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I commend you for trying, Mr. Edgeworth. However, it's clear that the defense's theory is the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...Y...You're wrong...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Such a shame...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I had hoped things wouldn't come to this, however...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What is it, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Andrews. Since you absolutely refuse to testify... It falls on my shoulders to disclose this to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...S...Stop...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This witness... How should I put this... She has an illness.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And because of this illness, she has tried to commit suicide in the past.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">S-Stop... Please stop...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No matter how much you want to hide it, it's no use. I have the evidence right here.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Ah! Th-That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's the second part of the suicide report; the attempted suicide report!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What will you do now, witness? You know what I am about to do, don't you? I will now reveal to the court, the true nature of the pitiful woman known as Adrian Andrews!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The secret of her co-dependant nature... Having other people know about it scares her more than anything else in the world...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Please! Please STOP!! I beg you!! If people find out... If people find out... I... I'll...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you're going to say you would "choose death", that is of no concern to me.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Edgeworth... How can you be so cold...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, before you die... I will pull the truth from your breathing lips! ... No matter what I have to do.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, will you tell the court yourself, or shall I!? Either is fine with me.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... ... ...I... I'll talk. But please... Help me... N-Nothing matters anymore...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">When I first saw him... I really thought he had fainted. Honest.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-Stabbed the body!? With the knife!? But why would you do that!?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Isn't it obvious? To pin the blame on a certain person... A certain cowardly man!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh... What do you mean by all of this...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It might take this court a little while to understand, but... This is the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">The real killer is Matt! That scumbag of a man! I'll never forgive him! He's trying to escape his guilt again! Just like last time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Last time"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, Ms. Andrews stabbed the victim, Juan Corrida, in the chest with the knife. However, she didn't do it with murder in mind. She did it with the intent of framing Matt Engarde for the murder... And this! This is her "crime"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-WHAT!? How is this possible!? I mean... Wasn't Ms. Andrews supposed to be the real murderer!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Please get over your shock and commence the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">When I first saw him... I really thought he had fainted. Honest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you could tell from the state the room was in, that there must have been a fight! Are you telling the truth when you say that you did not know he was dead?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">He... had a scarf tied around his neck... But that scarf is a part of the Jammin' Ninja's costume... So... So I didn't think anything about it was strange... His head was also... tilted down a bit, so I couldn't see his face that well... That's why I thought I'd wake him up... and went to pour the juice...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">When I realized he was dead... That was when I formulated my plan.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is this "plan" you had?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... I knew right away the murderer was Matt. I knew because Juan... He was going to expose Matt's weakest weakpoint to the world. So Matt did this to stop Juan, and silence him for good. That's when I thought, "I should forge some evidence and pin this crime on Matt."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So the forged pieces of evidence were the knife and the button...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">The first thing that came to mind was to plant the knife.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Once I made sure there was no one in the hallway, I made a dash back to Matt's room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was so you could get the knife, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">The knife Matt used at dinner had his fingerprints all over it. I thought if I used that, then the police would certainly turn their eyes towards him. Matt was napping with his costume on at the time. I slipped in, took the knife, and returned to the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">And then... I stabbed Juan's dead body with the knife, and ripped off the button.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you were the one to stab the victim with that knife.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It gives me goosebumps to think about it now... What a horrible thing I did... But... At the time, I couldn't control my own body. It moved on its own. Then, when I stabbed Juan's dead body... I suddenly realized something. If I used the button somehow, I could make Matt look even more suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you thought to rip one of the buttons off and then plant it in Mr. Engarde's hakama.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes... That's what I had planned to do. ...But things never go that smoothly, do they?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Just when I finished and was returning to Matt's room... I had a bit of an inconvenience.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An "inconvenience"...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">There was a woman with a camera at the ready, loitering in the hallway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm willing to bet my spikes it was Lotta...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">There was also a woman with a ray gun at the ready pacing back and forth...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's Ms. Oldbag for you...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I had already been caught and made into a big scoop for a certain weekly tabloid once, so I couldn't very well go out looking like myself and get caught again.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">And that's why... That's why I ended up using the Nickel Samurai costume.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were the one who prepared that costume, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes. I took it from Global Studios... I also put it into Juan's guitar case the day before the award ceremony.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You did this in preparation for the press conference, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes, Juan wanted to wear that costume and hold a press conference in it. He was going to disclose Matt's big secret there.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what is this "secret"...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... ...That, I don't know. Anyway, I thought that if I were to leave Juan's room in the Nickel Samurai costume... then people would think that Matt was the "real" murderer. I was very careful not to leave any fingerprints when I opened the guitar case. I absolutely did not want anyone to know about the costume.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't want to concede, but this testimony... it rings of the truth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">I'm sorry, Phoenix...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, please, don't apologize to me. We were both taken by surprise.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Still, I'm sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think we've heard enough! So, after that, you went back to Mr. Engarde's room and planted the button?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...Into Matt's hakama? Yes. After that, I folded up the costume I was wearing and put it into a bag. Then I snuck it out of the hotel and got rid of it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-My word... What does all this mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...Mr. Edgeworth, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">The real criminal... is Matt Engarde!! Yesterday... That woman prosecutor sat me down for a talk...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Franziska, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">She said that I should under no circumstances confess to what I had done. That if I just kept quiet, then Matt would be found guilty for sure... I... I had no choice but to believe in her words...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What this witness has done is clearly unlawful. However... As long as her testimony stands, we can be certain she is not the real killer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait, Your Honor! The defense still...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's pointless. At this point in time, it is not possible to indict Ms. Andrews on anything.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, exactly. There isn't a single piece of evidence that points to her as the murderer. The cross-examination of this witness is over. And so is today's trial. You couldn't establish that the witness was the culprit. Please let it go, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth, please place Ms. Andrews under arrest for further questioning.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Understood, Your Honor. The prosecution will arrange for her detention immediately.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's all. Court is adjourned for today!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Today's... Today's trial... It's over...! And I didn't win an acquittal!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Witness... Would you mind if I asked you something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>Edgeworth...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">What is it...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Before you leave court today, I wondered if I might look at one thing. The card in your hand. It's had my interest for quite some time now. What exactly is it...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Oh, this...? Mr. Wright also asked about this. Although I didn't remember at the time you asked me about it, Mr. Wright, I remembered just now. I found this in the room on that day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"The room"...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"That day"...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes. I found this card when I discovered Juan's body. It was lying there right next to him...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You found that card... next to the victim's body?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I suppose I must have unconsciously slipped it into my pocket... ...But it's not as if this card has any relevance to Juan's murder, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, I guess not. But it's still a strange card, if you ask me... But as far as a clue to this case...? I don't see why...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Witness! That card... Give it to me! Hurry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Edgeworth...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you have any idea what you have stupidly, yet inadvertently done!? This... I can't believe you hid this from me all this time!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I... I didn't mean to...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wh-What is this all about...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've never seen such an emotional Edgeworth in my entire life... That card... What in the world is it? And what does it mean...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't sound very sure, Mr. Wright. Objection denied.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection denied. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This evidence clearly reveals the contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are the evidence and the statement just now related?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They aren't, are they...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Wright, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness's statement is clearly faulty, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry, but I can see nothing faulty. Unfortunately, I will have to penalize you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh, I must be on the wrong track...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! This court sees no reason to further prolong the trial. Nor is there any need for more time to decide the case against the defendant. This case is extremely clear. I see no room for misinterpretation of the facts. This court finds the defendant, Matt Engarde...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accused will surrender to the court immediately, to be held pending trial at a higher court within a month from today's date. That is all. This court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>