<xml>
<title>Farewell, My Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Maya">Alright! Yes! Did you hear that, Nick!? Did you!? The Nickel Samurai! He did it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, he sure did... *sigh* I'm getting too old for this.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ah, I'm proud of the guy for doing the series justice.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">U-Um... So the person everyone was cheering for... I guess he got the prize?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup! You know who we're talking about, right Pearly? "The Nickel Samurai"!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">No. Every Sunday, I only watch the Educational Channel's "Kids' Masterpiece Theatre".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">OK, that's it! From now on, it's "The Nickel Samurai"! All the kids watch it!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Do you like "The Nickel Samurai" too, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nah, Nick's an old fart, so he's not allowed to watch it anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. But I do like "Kids' Masterpiece Theatre".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, I didn't know you were so young at heart, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! You're a grown-up! You're not allowed to watch it anymore! You're supposed to act your age and have interests that match. ...It's very important.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aw, give it a rest, Pearly!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Looks like I made the right choice in inviting everyone here. I'm glad you're all having a good time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aaaaah... It's like a dream!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Too bad for the Jammin' Ninja, though. Last year, he lost to The Pink Princess: Warrior of Little Olde Tokyo. I thought this might be his year...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah... Oh, hey, did anyone else think that the Jammin' Ninja was a bit different today?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Different? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, well, he wasn't carrying his bright red guitar.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Hey, you're right! Strange he'd walk around without his signature guitar.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...*sigh* I will never understand these people and their shows...</thought> Anyway, Mr. Powers, thank you very much for tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">A-Aw, it was nothing... I owe you one, so it's just my way of saying thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Come on! It's time to get going to the lobby! There's a post-ceremony stage show that's supposed to start real soon.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">And then, I heard there's going to be a press conference after that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A press conference? Is he going to make a speech about winning this year's prize?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Uh, well, not exactly... Something about the Nickel Samurai confessing something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Confessing...? Sounds pretty serious.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Argh! Nick! COME ON! You don't want us to be the last ones there, do you!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yeah, Mr. Nick! Do you!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why me...? The show doesn't even start for another 20 minutes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a grand set of doors over there.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">And behind those doors is an equally grand lobby.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Shall we go and take a look, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, wait up! This grand dessert is calling to me... It's saying, "Eat me now!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This sure is one luxurious hotel. Almost to the point of gaudy, with how it blends together everything "fancy" imaginable. <thought>Speaking of fancy, didn't that bellboy give me something like that last year?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">That chandelier is really something, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I thought it was a kind of space ship...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick. How about we get one of these for the office?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One of those hanging from our poor, weak ceiling? I don't think so.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If this is all a dream, I don't ever want to wake up! And all the directors and stars that were here to see the heroes, wow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I had no idea who most of them were.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Neither did I.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, you've got to cut that "news only" habit out. Your new show is going to be "The Nickel Samurai!" Every Sunday morning at 8! Oh, I know! We can watch it together starting next week! I'll come wake you up extra early to make sure, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, I'm fine... You know, you really don't have to on my account...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The awards ceremony was just held on that stage. It was really fabulous.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You just reminded me of the circus for a second.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, shows like that are guaranteed to be good, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What can I say? This is a really high-class hotel!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I've never eaten this kind of salad before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Pearls, having eaten only vegetables all her life. She's been missing out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't worry! Any leftovers belong in my happily awaiting stomach anyway!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're such a glutton, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ah, I lose this one to Maya. You sure can eat.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, a growing girl needs her nutrients!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A growing girl? Exactly how big do you plan on getting...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you very much for inviting us today.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Aww, it was nothing really. Guys like us don't get to come to a place like this often, so I thought I'd invite you all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Mr. Powers! What have you been up to lately?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Well, since "The Pink Princess" successfully wrapped up last month, I've been on a kid's exercise show... ...while wearing a rabbit mask over my face...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I'm still really sorry about all the headaches I caused you that time, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, well. What's done is done, so let's forget about it. <thought>This is Will Powers. He's an action star. His popularity exploded when he was the Steel Samurai. And he was the first case Maya worked on with me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You can't tell by looking at you, but you're a really nice guy with a love of kids.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ah, thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't believe they're going to make a movie based on the Nickel Samurai.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can't believe it either, but for a different reason!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Steel Samurai. An epic story of one hero in a desperate fight against his arch-enemy, the Evil Magistrate in the city of Neo Olde Tokyo. And last year, they started a new series, "The Nickel Samurai". The new series seems to be a hit with the kids too.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">The Steel Samurai is a show I have a lot of strong feelings for, so I hoped that maybe I'd get a chance to do something in this new one...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah... It's too bad... It'd be great to see you on the show... With the new actor, Matt Engarde. He's super popular right now.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Un-gard...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like Pearls doesn't know who he is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">This year it's going to be the Nickel Samurai vs. the Jammin' Ninja at the box office!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Jammin' Ninja...? Who's that again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So who is this "Jammin' Ninja" again?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's a hero, duh. His symbol is a bright red guitar he's always carrying.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A ninja who's always carrying around a bright red guitar...? How does that even work!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">With a scarf around his neck and a guitar in hand, he rises to stardom in an ancient time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A ninja... Who becomes a star??</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! A ninja who becomes a star!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">There's a strong rivalry between the two of them. Global Studios' Nickel Samurai and Worldwide Studios' Jammin' Ninja. They even air at the same time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know what I heard? I heard those two don't get along at all. The Nickel Samurai's Engarde and the guy who plays the Jammin' Ninja, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The Nickel Samurai speaks French!? Oh, you mean Matt Engarde, the actor...</thought> I guess even the world of heroes isn't a sparkling, happy place.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Y-Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ah, I really owe you one. If it wasn't for you guys, I don't know what would've happened. What you did... It was a real tight spot I was in, and you fought so hard to get me out. I don't care what happens. I'll never forget everything you've done for me.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">So, you're going to study to become a lawyer too. Am I right or am I right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">It must be real tough. There's all those thick books with hard words you have to read...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh, um... Well...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, yeah. Mr. Powers doesn't know that Maya's a spirit medium...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I thought he'd be able to tell by my clothes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe he thinks that you've got some strange hobby on the side or something.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Hey, wait a sec. What's that's supposed to mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">So are you Maya's little sister?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm sorry, but no.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Oh, then you must be Mr. Wright's little sister!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Again, I'm sorry, but...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Then... Whose little sister are you?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm sorry, but I'm an only child.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Oh, I see... S-Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Pearl looks so sad... She looks really sorry too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">Hey, is my face really all that scary? Kids won't come anywhere near me... But when I cover my face, they're all shocked because then they figure out who I am.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Well, I don't think you look scary.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Me either. I think your face makes you look like a very kind person!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Aww... Those two are making Mr. Powers tear up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">S-Sorry. Thanks for taking the time to take it out and show it to me, but I'm really sorry, I don't know a thing about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow, what is with this place? Looks like I've stumbled into Oz or something. Way in the back, there's a sign for the bathroom. I bet we have a little time to look around before the show starts...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can understand flowers in front of the dressing rooms, but what are stuffed bears doing here...? Could it be that there's an action star who has a soft spot for teddy bears...? ...Nah, can't be.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Compared to the flowers on the other side of the hall, these are much more gorgeous. Let's see... Record companies, fan clubs, company workers, family... Carrying all these flowers home would be hard, I think...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a piece of paper taped to the door that says, "Juan Corrida's Room". "Juan Corrida"... His name just sounds like a star's name. I've heard it before, but I don't know anything about him at all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are toilets in each room in this hotel, but since all sorts of events are held here, there are bathrooms for people who aren't staying here to use as well. Perfect for people like me, who can't afford a stay here in the first place...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"To Mr. Engarde From the Global Studio Staff" Ah, it'd be nice if lawyers got flowers too. Something like, "To Mr. Wright From All Your Grateful Clients".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a piece of paper taped to the door that says, "Matt Engarde's Room". "Matt Engarde"... I've heard that name before. Oh, yeah. Maya's always yammering about him like the obsessed fan she is...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Sounds like the post-ceremony show is about to start.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Alright! I'm so pumped! I wonder if he's going to show off his special move today? "Nickel Samurai Smelting!"</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Actually, what I'm interested in most is the press conference.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You mean the "big confession" the Nickel Samurai's going to make after the show? So what is it? Don't you know what it's about, Mr. Powers?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Uh, well, I'm not the Steel Samurai anymore, so I don't have any idea.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Bah.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">S-Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ah, so I guess you are all going to the press conference then?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">If that's the case, then here, take these tickets so you can get in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you very much. Well, let's get going to the lobby.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It looks like it's over this way, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">OK! For great justice!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">They called this so suddenly that something about it just seems off, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean the press conference?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah. He said, "There's something I'd like to confess if I win." I heard he faxed his request for a conference in to the office only yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yesterday... <thought>Yeah, that is kind of sudden.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">But I guess his manager set everything up somehow, so he was lucky.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Nice manager.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Only a really gaudy hotel would have such a large, gaudy lobby to match.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah, I think they're going to have the post-ceremony show over there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They're using a compact stage, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh... I'm all ready to use my special "Samurai Power".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya looks like she's ready to start a fight...</thought></line>
<line speaker="PA Notice">Your attention please, your attention please. The Nickel Samurai's Post-Ceremony Stage Show will not be held tonight due to unforeseen circumstances.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">WHAAAT!? WHYYYYY!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oww! You didn't have to pinch me! Pinch yourself if you don't believe it!</line>
<line speaker="PA Notice">We are asking for everyone's cooperation at this time. So please stay where you are. ...This is a special request from the police.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Police? Did they just say the police?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">D-Do you want me to go check out what's going on?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, wait, I'll come with you...</line>
<line speaker="???">Freeze! You two! Didn't you hear the announcement just now!? It just finished telling you not to move!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Th-That voice... I've heard that voice somewhere before...</line>
<line speaker="???">Honestly, youth these days can't be bothered to listen to other people when they talk! Just the other day it was the same thing! There was a small footbridge with a sign next to it that said, "Beware, Bridge Out!" And along comes a snot-nosed little punk kid right up to the bridge. I tried to tell the boy the bridge was out and it was dangerous, but would he listen!? No, of course not! He said he'd be careful and only walk on the "in" part of the bridge since the "out" part is what was dangerous! I am not kidding you here! The kid said that and really meant it! WELL! I really let him have it then, and knocked him clear off of that bridge! Honestly, kids these days don't know right from wrong, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">This non-stop chatter...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-It can't be... ...Ms. Oldbag?</line>
<line speaker="???">...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What is it, you young whipper-snappers!? Do I know you!? ...Wait. YOU! You're Powers, aren't you!?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Y-Yeah. Um, about what happened back then...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">You didn't get nominated last year either, did you? Oh, that's right. You're doing that children's exercise program, trying to play nice.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ah, yeah, that's me. Thankfully I still have a job...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I love that show, and you're a hoot! You're the "big brother" character, right? Yes, even with your face covered by a mask, I know. You ended up with a rabbit face. What a work of art, but that's how it is, you know? I mean, if you didn't wear the mask, who knows how many TVs you'd break? Really, and shame on those kids exercising around you. They're getting what they deserve. This is why I thought you shouldn't be anywhere...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Look at my uniform and tell me you can't tell I'm a member of security!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But that outfit...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Annoying, noisy brats get the blaster!</line>
<line speaker="Ray Gun">*rata-tat-tat-tat-tat...*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, it looks like there's a fancy restaurant on the second floor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You STILL feel like eating?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I mean, since we're here, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Don't pull the "since we're here" trick on me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What a beautiful mansion. Do you live in this wonderful world every day, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, no, this is my first time in a place like this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm going to say these cameras were set up to cover the post-ceremony stage show.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But I wonder where everyone's gone, abandoning their cameras like this...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess something big must have happened...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the stage for the post-ceremony stage show.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">There was supposed to be a press meeting after the show, but now...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like no one will hear what the Nickel Samurai had to confess after all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We're here, so we might as well take some pictures. OK, everyone, sit in a chair!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But we're all out of film...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't worry about it. There's a zillion cameras over there we can borrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, hey! You can't just go and "borrow" an expensive professional camera like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Oldbag, what are you doing here? What happened to your position at Global Studios...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, that old place? Well, since "that" incident, they've been letting people go. When they cut the security team, I got the pink slip.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What incident? What did you do?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I didn't do anything, you young'un! Don't you remember? That incident a year ago... When this lady got on the witness stand and testified.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">And you! Weren't you the one who was bullying me; this fragile girl at heart!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... I plead the fifth.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">But you know, I think maybe I rubbed the upper management the wrong way by testifying. ... Yes, that has to be it! Everything is all your fault!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Me!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I thought about being a bodyguard at first, after being handed ol' pinky.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You? A bodyguard?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">For your friend! That fiery, good-looking guy with the red jacket and the ruffles.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">M-Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">But...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That sort of arrangement would be entirely too troublesome for me.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That's what he said to me. What did I ever do to deserve that!?</line>
<line speaker="Ray Gun">*rata-tat-tat-tat-tat...*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um... So, did something happen?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I don't have all the details, but, it looks like another one of those "incidents" happened again.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">A-An "incident"? Like a "murder" kind of "incident"?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Maybe. You see, I'm a bit of a devilish woman. So wherever I go, a rain of blood will come pouring down. Bet you didn't know that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, then shouldn't you quit being a security guard, at least for other people's sake?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Silence, whippersnapper!</line>
<line speaker="Ray Gun">*rata-tat-tat-tat-tat...*</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">These eyes of mine are real pros now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Pros"? Pros at doing what?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">At doing police work, of course! My eyes are like a hawk! And my professional eyes spot a messy incident! A messy, bloody incident! That's why I don't have time for you meddling kids and your petty little things!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Hey, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What is it? I don't like that devilish smile playing on your lips...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's make like we're going to the bathroom, and check things out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No way. The police told us not go anywhere, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh!? How B-O-R-I-N-G! You're such a boring guy! You've got no motivation! No spirit!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Huh? What? What's going on? Are you giving Mystic Maya trouble again, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not you too, Pearls... Please don't stick your little nose into this one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So listen to this, Pearly. This one time at lawyer camp, Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-OK! I get it! Let's go take a look.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yay! I know you couldn't say no to me, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That's right. You'd walk over miles of hot coals for Mystic Maya, wouldn't you Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That would be EVERY time we work a case together...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, what are we waiting for? Let's go already! You can come along too, Pearly.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Goody! I get to come! I get to come!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's nothing really out of the ordinary here...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Are you looking for the "something" that the old lady was talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Doesn't look like it happened here. Well, we'd better go look somewhere else.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Alright! Then, let's try...</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Are you by chance, Ms. Maya Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, yeah... That's me.</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">You have a phone call waiting for you at the front desk.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A call? I wonder if it's someone from Kurain Village...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What's wrong, Mystic Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, nothing. I'll just go on ahead to check it out, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">OK.</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Right this way, Ms. Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Let's go look somewhere else now, Mr. Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, OK.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">This is a little exciting... And a little scary...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a grand set of doors over there. It's the doors Maya followed the bellboy out of.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So, that's called a "shan-deh leer", right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What is that for? What does it do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it's for lighting up a room, Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, Mr. Nick? Can I look down now? My neck hurts...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They haven't cleaned up all the food yet. There's a sad feeling hanging in the air now that the party is over...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The awards ceremony was just held on that stage. It was really fabulous.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You just reminded me of the circus for a second. I wonder if everyone is alright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I heard that Berry Big Circus just recently started holding performances again...</thought> I'm sure they're all fine, Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It's a feast fit for a king!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It was the first time I ate that food. What was it called again? I think it started with "key". Key... Wee?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right, a "kiwi".</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I don't know what to say. It's a sweet but sour fruit all in one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Pearls, having eaten only vegetables all her life. She's been missing out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A lobby with a grand staircase always feels enormous. But right now, the only thing filling this enormous room is anxiety about the murder. ...I really hope nothing else bad happens here...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These cameras must belong to the press that came to cover the conference. They're all basically doing the same thing: staring at the empty stage.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Seats for the spectators of the post-ceremony show and the press conference. But it's too bad neither event is going to be held now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Oldbag, what are you doing here? What happened to your position at Global Studios...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, that old place? Well, since "that" incident, they've been letting people go. When they cut the security team, I got the pink slip.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, I guess you must have done something... um... "deh-plor-ible"...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">"Deplorable!?" I would never do such a thing! Don't you remember? That incident a year ago... When this lady got on the witness stand and testified.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">And you! Weren't you the one who was bullying me; this fragile girl at heart!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... I plead the fifth.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">But you know, I think maybe I rubbed the upper management the wrong way by testifying. ... Yes, that has to be it! Everything is all your fault!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Me!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I thought about being a bodyguard at first, after being handed ol' pinky.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">"Body...guard?"</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">For your friend! That fiery, good-looking guy with the red jacket and the ruffles.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's not talking about Edgeworth, is she...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">But...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That sort of arrangement would be entirely too troublesome for me.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That's what he said to me. What did I ever do to deserve that!?</line>
<line speaker="Ray Gun">*rata-tat-tat-tat-tat...*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, but what in the world just happened?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I don't have all the details, but, it looks like another one of those "incidents" happened again.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">A-An "incident"? Like a "murder" kind of "incident"?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Maybe. You see, I'm a bit of a devilish woman. So wherever I go, a rain of blood will come pouring down. Bet you didn't know that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, then shouldn't you quit being a security guard, at least for other people's sake?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Silence, whippersnapper!</line>
<line speaker="Ray Gun">*rata-tat-tat-tat-tat...*</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Those two sound pretty serious...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That southern accent can only mean...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Hey... Lotta...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Come on, do a gal a favor and tell this cop I'm just doin' my job and I've got rights...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah, YOU!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... Detective Gumshoe...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey pal, help a guy out! Tell her that only the police are allowed here! This is the scene of a murder, so she should leave this to us pros...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">A... A murder!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aw, shoot! Me and my big mouth!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">See! I knew it! My gut instinct told me so!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I always trust my gut! A murder, it said! And that's what it is! A genuine murder!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-Hey, wait...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, man... I'm in trouble now...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... Detective Gumshoe... A murder...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah, no, that's not it. I got my facts mixed up for a second there, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">U-Um... Mr. Nick? Is the dead person the Nickel Samurai...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Why do you ask?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Well, Mystic Maya was rooting for him, so...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It wasn't the Nickel Samurai that got bumped. Actually, the Nickel Samurai is the one under suspicion of doing the bumping off...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The guy that died was this hero named the Jammin' Ninja, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Jammin' Ninja...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, that woman with the big puffy hair that looks like cotton candy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean Lotta?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That woman... She was there that time too, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That time?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...When Mystic Maya did that channeling...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, that time... Well, Lotta's a journalist, so that's why she was there.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Jer-nal-ist...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It looks like she was hanging around here before the murder happened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Hanging around"...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, hiding in wait in front of the Jammin' Ninja's door, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But why would she...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She wouldn't tell me, pal. Just said something about "Gettin' my big scoop"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Scoop? What sort of news could she be after...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the victim was the Jammin' Ninja?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Jammin' Ninja...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He was on a really popular rival TV show to "The Nickel Samurai".</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The victim was the action star, Juan Corrida. He got a huge push and rode the express train to stardom. I mean, even I know who he is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, even I recognize his face...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But I heard lately that Matt Engarde's been taking the wind out of his sail. I'm telling you, pal, as far as who's popular, those two are hogging all the limelight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess there's no space for Mr. Powers at all, huh... Poor guy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Engarde... Um... That's the Nickel Samurai, right...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup. I mean, no! You've got to say it with more umph! "The Nickel Samurai!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Anyway, so now that Juan Corrida's gone, that means Mr. Engarde has the whole stage to himself, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I wouldn't bet on it, pal. We can't have that happen, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Can't have that happen"? <thought>What's that supposed to mean, I wonder...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-Why was Mr. Engarde arrested?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry, pal, but that's not something I can tell you. We just started the investigation, so we don't want any leaks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like yet another "Steel Samurai" hero is in hot water...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... Mr. Nick... If Mystic Maya knew about this...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I know. She'd make me take this case... I know...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I was really shocked by what happened to her in that one case. I didn't know she had such an awesome power!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Awesome power...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I thought maybe I should do some self-improvement and take up a hobby. So I went out and bought some Morning Glory seeds and planted them, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's a good way to improve yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ho ho ho. Well, it's nothing really...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That girl is number three on my "People I've Seen A Lot Of Lately" list.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? Then who's number one...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">As if you need to ask. It's YOU, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Ah... So who's number two?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Maya Fey. ...But it looks like she's not around this time.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It must be nice to be such good friends with each other, isn't it Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Somehow, I don't think that's the real meaning of Detective Gumshoe's list...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I look good! I think I've lost some weight, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's only wishful thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wishful thinking, huh? ... In that case, I wishfully think I've lost some weight!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wishfully think he might face the facts one day...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Lately, I've been on the instant noodles only diet, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm not a real fan of action shows or anything... But I know who Juan Corrida and Matt Engarde are.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can't talk about one without talking about the other, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">They even debuted around the same time. So they have this real fiery rivalry with each other. Kinda like you and me, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I never knew he thought of me as a rival...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The Nickel Samurai! He really took the Grand Prix tonight!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya's a big fan of his.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Really? ...Oh, I'm sorry then.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Why are you sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Matt Engarde was just arrested, pal. ...On suspicion of murdering Juan Corrida.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you take a look at this for me?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Listen, pal... I'm not leaking any info about the evidence to you this time. If I do, my salary's really gonna get it... And then I won't even be able to get those instant noodles down at the discount market!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know this person?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You meet a lot of people as a detective, pal. So we make extra sure to not forget people because that's our job. ...Now, having said that, I don't remember ever seeing this person before.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Which means that you're kind of forgetful, aren't you Mr. Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's not what it means... Not exactly anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Hey! So what's going on, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like Juan Corrida has been killed.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Wh-Wh-What!? Juan is... He's...!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like he was murdered... And a suspect was arrested. That suspect is Mr. Matt Engarde.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Y-You're joking, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nope. They arrested the Nickel Samurai on suspicion of murdering the Jammin' Ninja.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ooogh... Not again... I feel sick.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">"Again"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...About a year ago, something just like this happened, Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I still can't believe... No way... No way Matt would...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...? What's Mr. Powers got in his hand...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">...Oh, before I forget... This... This is for you, Mr. Wright. I got this from the bellboy that came by earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...For me...? But why?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I don't know. All he said was it was for Mr. Phoenix Wright, the attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Matt is the most energetic and active actor out there right now. The Nickel Samurai really sealed his place as a pop idol, but... he kept adding fuel to the fire of his rivalry with Juan anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Juan... He's the Jammin' Ninja, right?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Those two would butt heads over everything they could think of. But I'd say that Matt was the one who almost always came out on top.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess some people only know how to relate to others by butting heads like a ram...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">Juan said that he'd take Matt on this time too, so he joined a rival TV show.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">And that was "The Jammin' Ninja"...?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">The stylish Nickel Samurai and the burning Jammin' Ninja... Well, things turned messy real fast with those two using their shows for their "war". And the final tally... Look around... It's pretty obvious how things ended up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Matt even won the Grand Prix this year... The final win over his rival, I guess...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Engarde was going to hold a press conference, wasn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">That's what I heard. Though if you wanted to get technical about it, it was the Nickel Samurai's conference.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Nickel Samurai's...?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah. He was supposed to wear his costume and give the press conference that way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So he was supposed to be in-costume...? But why?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I'm not sure... They don't keep me in the loop anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">It was almost right after you guys left. An old man who's a bellboy at this hotel showed up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's when he told you to give this to me...?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why... Why give me this transceiver...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">Hey, where did Maya go off to?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She got a phone call.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Oh yeah, that's right. She was heading for the front desk just now. She sure stands out in a crowd, doesn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Hey, is my face really all that scary? Kids won't come anywhere near me... But when I cover my face, then they're all shocked because they figure out who I am...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I think your face makes you look like a very kind person!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Aww... Mr. Powers is getting teary eyed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">He debuted around the same time as Matt in everything, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah, it started out small... First it was singing contests, then swimming competitions... Then it was bowling tournaments, and then it was who could throw the best New Year's parties... Juan was always trying to one-up Matt. But lately, those two were escalating to more and more dangerous things... I thought that no good would come of it all, so I began to worry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Too bad Juan's story ended so soon...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">Matt's younger than me, but you can practically see his star potential.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">His star po-ten-shial...?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I got his autograph the other day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Feels kind of wrong now, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I don't care what people say! Matt didn't kill Juan! I know he didn't!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Umm... I'm honored you're asking me, But I have no idea who this person is. Umm... Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, it's OK. You don't have to apologize so much.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">S-Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... I was just wondering... Where's Mystic Maya? She's been gone a long time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that she mentions it, she was only going to answer a phone call...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Maybe she got lost. I'll take a quick look around for her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wh-What is it, Mr. Nick!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? I... I'm not sure... <thought>Did this transceiver just...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, hello? Wright here...</line>
<line speaker="???">Is this Mr. Phoenix Wright, the attorney?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And you are...!?</line>
<line speaker="???">You don't need to know who I am. I think you have other things to be concerning yourself with... Such as...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Heeelp! Niiiiick!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-Mystic Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya...?</line>
<line speaker="???">So, Mr. Wright. Wouldn't you agree that the more important issue is the fate of the girl?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Her fate? Does he mean what I think he means...?</thought> Maya! Where are you!? Are you hurt!?</line>
<line speaker="???">Come now. Don't fall apart on me yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Th-This... No! This can't be!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Now that I have your attention, Mr. Attorney, I have a modest proposal for you. If you do what I require, then I will return to you your valuable "item" unharmed. ...What is this called again in your fancy lawyer terms?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">..."Kidnapping for ransom"...</line>
<line speaker="???">Yes, that's it. This is a kidnapping.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah! Mystic Maya! Mystic Mayaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>M-My sight... Everything's fading away... Maya... Maya... Maya's been kidnapped!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">You there? Mr. Wright, are you there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-How much!? How much do you want!?</line>
<line speaker="???">Very good, Mr. Attorney. I'm glad you have such a good grasp of the situation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hurry up and state your condition! And then return Maya --</line>
<line speaker="???">Money is not what I seek.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What?</line>
<line speaker="???">What I want is a certain verdict. I would like a complete acquittal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Complete acquittal!? Wh-What in the world have you done to need...!?</line>
<line speaker="???">I am not the person you will be representing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What...?</line>
<line speaker="???">You are currently at the Gatewater Hotel, are you not? And I know that a murder has just taken place there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Juan Corrida was killed, and the suspect is Matt Engarde...</line>
<line speaker="???">You are, as expected, quite on top of things, Mr. Attorney. Now then. What I want is very simple. I want you to obtain a complete acquittal for Matt Engarde.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Matt Engarde? But why?</line>
<line speaker="???">He did not kill anyone. I can attest to that. However...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-However!? However what!?</line>
<line speaker="???">However, someone is framing him for the murder. A very smart someone who is setting him up to take the fall...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>If I agree and do what he wants, can I believe he'll keep his end of the bargain!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">You are, of course, at liberty to believe me or not. However, there is one thing you can take as fact. Right now, your very precious "item" is with me, in my possession.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mmngnhhh... Heeelp!... Nngmph... NIIIICK!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya!</line>
<line speaker="???">You have two days. Of course, tonight, he will be in questioning with the police. But the trial is in two days. At that trial, you will win a not guilty verdict. Remember, you only have one chance. One chance, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-One...!? Y-You expect me to get a not guilty in one trial day!?</line>
<line speaker="???">Yes, exactly. I don't believe I was wrong in choosing you, so don't let me down.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aagh!</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, yes, that's right. Now that I am playing the role of the kidnapper, I can't pass up this chance to say, "And don't even think about callin' the cops!" ...Hmm, not great, but you get the idea.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Dammit! Who... Who the hell are you!?</line>
<line speaker="???">Alright, I'll tell you that much. My name is... ...De Killer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-Mr. Nick! Wh-Where is Mystic Maya!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...She's been kidnapped.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">N-No... ... It's all my fault! If only I had gone with Mystic Maya...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not your fault, Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But it is! It is! Mystic Mayaaaaaaaaaa! Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Mr. Wright... I think we... I think we should tell the police what it's [sic] going on...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No! We can't do that! If we do, who knows what will happen to Maya...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! What about the detective we saw earlier...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Detective Gumshoe!</thought> Yes, that's it! Wait here, and I'll be right back!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Alright! I'll take care of Pearl while you're away!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT!? RAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAANSOM!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Shhh! Not so loud! ...The ransom is complete acquittal for Matt Engarde.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wait, the deal is "complete acquittal" in exchange for Maya, you mean...? Then this means Matt Engarde is obviously the killer, pal! No doubt about it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the guy said that Mr. Engarde is innocent...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You really believe what a KIDNAPPER tells you, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess he has a point... If Engarde is really innocent, then why the kidnapping?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And on top of everything else, there's all this evidence we keep finding.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The guys with the eagle eyes are really lapping it up like they just caught a huge fish.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But it's strange. There's so much evidence that it feels like something's wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's too much evidence? Is that possible? <thought>Actually, didn't the kidnapper say something about Engarde being "set-up"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Anyway, looks like you won't be leaving here tonight, pal. Just sit tight and cooperate with the investigation. Tomorrow you can start yours.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...A-Alright... <thought>Isn't there another way...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We've also got to be careful about pushing the kidnapper the wrong way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're right...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nnngh... Oww, my head... <thought>Wh-Where... Where am I!? I wonder if I'm still in that hotel... Wh-What happened to me...?</thought> Nick... Pearly! ... <thought>Come on, you guys. This isn't funny anymore...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">I see you have awoken.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaah! Wh-Wh-Wh-Who are you!?</line>
<line speaker="???">Me? ...I am known as "De Killer".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"D-De Killer"!? You mean like an "ASSASSIN"!? <thought>I... I'm too young to die!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Don't worry. You are not my target. ...For now anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A-Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah! Nick! Nick! Where are you!? ...Help me...</line>
<line speaker="???">Yes, that's right. Only one person can save you now, and that is Mr. Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Huh? Wh-What? Nick... Nick's going to save me...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Calm down and be a good girl. Think of this as a business transaction.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A... A business transaction?</line>
<line speaker="???">I am going to contact him now. I hope you'll cooperate and play your assigned role well.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Nick... What's going to happen to me? Nick... Pearls... ...Sis...</line>
<line speaker="???">... Is this Mr. Phoenix Wright, the attorney? ... You don't need to know who I am. I think you have other things to be concerning yourself with... Such as...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Good morning!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, morning Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! Mr. Nick! Come on! Let's hurry and go see Mr. Engarde!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We have to wait a bit, Pearls. Visiting hours don't start until 9 AM, so...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, I see. Ah, Mystic Maya! If only... If only I went with you that time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Pearls... She's been like this since last night... We managed to get home somehow, yesterday evening... Thanks to Detective Gumshoe gently holding her by the hand and leading her here... But by the looks of it, I don't think Pearls got any sleep at all last night.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! Mystic Maya... She's alright, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, she's alright. Either way, I'm going to save her. You can trust me on that.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Please... Please... Help her...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm only able to stay this calm and collected... Because Pearls is doing the crying for the both of us...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...No matter where I look in this familiar space I call my office... No, I can't let my mind wander now! I don't have the time! I've got to get going on this case!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... I have a thought...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You're going to represent Mr. Engarde... aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. I don't really seem to have a choice.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, but what if... What if he... ...is the real murderer? What would you do then, Mr. Nick...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Would you fight to get a not guilty for a murderer to save Mystic Maya...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls... Let's talk to Mr. Engarde first, OK? ...We can think all the bad things we want, but it doesn't change a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Y-Yeah, you're right... I'm sorry. I... I can't stop thinking about it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls... You're really worried about Maya, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... I don't have anyone else left in this world.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">My family's all gone...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Her family...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">My father...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">He left my mother and the village behind and went away.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">And... my mother... She did that thing... all for me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mystic Maya... She's like a sister to me... ... She is all I have left in this world...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She looks out of it... Maybe I should leave her alone...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We couldn't wait for visiting hours to start, so Pearls and I came down here early... To visit one Nickel Samurai, charged with the murder of the Jammin' Ninja...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">G-Good morning. How are you today?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know this situation might be a little tough for you...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... We're...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Oh, sorry dude...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">I already signed up...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Excuse me...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">I already have life insurance. I signed up a long time ago cause my job is, you know...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Oh! No no no... We're not insurance salespeople!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Really...? Dude, I really don't need that right now either.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Fire extinguishers. I mean, this building isn't my house, so...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... No no no... We're not here to sell you fire extinguishers either! I'm a lawyer. My name is Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">A lawyer...? ... Hold on a sec. I'm gonna ask my manager, OK? ... ...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">The Nickel Samurai sure is a strange person, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think "strange" is an understatement.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Sorry about that. You're just in time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">You're a lawyer dude, right? My manager's looking for a good one right now, so how about it?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-Mr. Nick! This is our chance!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to make him let me take his case! I have to!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Smile, you're on candid camera. Mr. Engarde keeps sneaking glances up at the security camera on the wall... I wonder if he is still trying to be a star?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitors the visitor's room. He's so quiet, you could forget he was even there... If he wasn't watching everything. He's pushed up against the wall... Kinda like a magnet on a refrigerator.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry to intrude, but I would like to ask you a few personal questions.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Um, that's OK, but dude, my autobiography's coming out soon, so... If I say stuff without the publisher's approval, then I'm gonna be in real hot water... Hold on a sec. I'm gonna ask my publisher, OK? ... ...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Engarde is so lucky! He has so many people he can talk to.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Umm... I don't know if he actually has anyone he can really talk to...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Sorry about that. Like I thought, the publisher said it'd be "real bad" if I said anything, dude.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Does he have a mind of his own!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Engarde, I would like to ask you about the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Oh, are you covering this for a tabloid as a side job, dude? Um, um... Well, if you want my statement on this, you should ask through my staff...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No no no... I'm not asking on behalf of a tabloid...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Hold on a sec. I'm gonna ask the president of the studio, OK? ... ...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Is he alright, Mr. Nick...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If we're talking about Mr. Engarde's brain here, I wouldn't put my money on it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Sorry about that. The studio president said, "Even Neo Mt. Fuji itself knows that I'm not the murderer!"</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, Mr. Nick? What's "Neo Mt. Fuji"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a mountain in the city of Neo Olde Tokyo; the city the Nickel Samurai protects.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Engarde, this is an attorney's badge.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Dude, I'm sorry, but I don't have the free time to be looking at things like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">I'm much too busy with Nickel Samurai stuff right now.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">I don't have the time to take a lawyer's correspondence course...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why does he believe I'm a salesman!? Insurance, then extinguishers... Now this!!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a ticket for the press conference. You were going to give one after winning the Grand Prix, right?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Huh? Me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. While you were in-costume no less.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Um, I never heard anything like that, dude. I only heard about the stage show. I always leave that kind of stuff to my manager.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He didn't know...? That's odd...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Mr. Nick? What are you going to do with that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know yet, but I figured I could at least show it to him...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Is that a transceiver? Hey, it looks like a real nice one too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I got it as a "present" from someone.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Hmm? Interesting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've also been instructed to take your case.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Is that what you heard from the transceiver?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Dude, that's terrible! Don't let some disembodied voice boss you around!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This coming from a man with a cell phone on his wrist...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">I've seen him somewhere before... Is he a member of my fan club?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's Mr. Powers. Isn't he supposed to be kind of like a mentor to you?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Powers...? Oh yeah! He's the guy on that kid's exercise program. I gave him an autograph just the other day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He doesn't see Mr. Powers as a mentor at all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Man, it's too bad he's dead...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You killed him... That's the most logical conclusion, don't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Dude, what are you talking about!? You're making a huge mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If that's such a mistake, then why did they issue an arrest warrant for you!?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Hold on a sec. I'm gonna ask the guy in charge of this place, OK? ... ...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Stars sure know a lot of people, don't they?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if that phone even really gets reception in here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...Um, I guess you're right about the warrant after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ladies and gentlemen, I believe we might be making some progress here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Yeah... I'm such a handsome devil.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... Um, yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">And I'm way good at sports! Karate, tennis, judo, soccer, football, hockey, fencing... Dude, it's no wonder I'm so popular.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... Um, yeah... <thought>You're also good at sitting in a jail cell, Mr. Popular.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Dude, I know I like to throw money around, but it's not like I buy anything and everything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's nice, because it's not up for sale anyway!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Um, dude, this person looks like a member of my fan club. Hold on a sec. I'm gonna ask the fan club president, OK? ... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, "dude", you know what...? Forget I asked...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... ...Well, dude, I think it's about time for me to get going.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please, wait! ...I really need to take your case!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">There's always other people in need of a lawyer, right? Want me to introduce you to a few?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Please! Please let Mr. Nick represent you!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Man, oh man. Lawyers these days. Now you dudes use kids to pull in clients too?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you don't take me as your lawyer, then De Killer is going to...!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... Wait... What did you just say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"De Killer"...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">D-De Killer!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...What's he doing? He looks like he's mulling something over...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... Alright, dude. I accept your terms.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">I'll let you represent me in court.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">W-We did it! We did it, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, yeah... <thought>I don't feel any better for it... And he doesn't look too happy either...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Go ahead, ask me anything. I'll help out as much as I can...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Man, I thank my lucky stars that people know my name.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, you're quite the hero, and you're in the national spotlight.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I didn't know who he is... Does that mean I'm not a good citizen...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Ah, it's really great to be the Nickel Samurai. Dude, lately, I just keep on getting more and more popular.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>True enough... "The Nickel Samurai" is very popular among high schoolers and secretaries right now. I guess Mr. Engarde has a way of catching the eyes of women...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Do you know my motto? "Refreshing like a spring breeze." That's what I am.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">A spring breeze...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">That's why this kind of scandal is disastrous, dude. I mean, even if I get out of here tomorrow, it's still gonna look bad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Everyone loves a good scandal...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you tell me about your activities last night?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">After I got the award, I took a break and went back to my room. I had that post-ceremony stage show to do. So I was in my Nickel Samurai costume.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And you were alone the entire time?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">My manager was running around being busy, so yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because of the press conference you were supposed to have after the show?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">I told you, dude. I have no idea about any press conference, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's strange... I thought the Nickel Samurai was going to confess something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Anyway, when I was leaving my room, that's when I noticed it was kinda noisy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Corrida was already dead at that time...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Yeah, that's what I gathered anyway from my manager.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>With the way he's always talking about his manager, it's as if she runs his life.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">And that's when the detective in the green coat showed up. He searched me... And then, out of the blue, the dude arrested me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About you and the victim, Mr. Juan Corrida, what sort of...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">That's got nothing to do with anything, dude. Man, with that face of his, you can't even tell he's the same age as me. And he wanted to try making a "Jammin' Ninja" movie, even though we all know it'd fail.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Nickel Samurai still won in the end, right?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Yeah. I took the Grand Prix by storm. So why would I, the winner, have any reason to kill the guy anyway? Dude, you'd think it'd be the other way around, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Do you know why you were arrested?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">I guess maybe my full body search went badly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did they find something on you?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">They found a button from the Jammin' Ninja's costume.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A button...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">I don't get it either. It was caught in the pleats of my samurai pants, or "hakama".</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Aaah!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Dude, I really think someone planted it there though. I'm serious.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if that's what really happened...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>...I guess this is about all I'm going to get out of him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Let's ask one last thing. Let's test Mr. Engarde to see if he really is innocent or not...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-We can do that...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes. If you use this...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya's Magatama!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">He won't be able to hide any secrets from you, Mr. Nick. I'm sure of it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I get it...!</thought> ...Mr. Engarde, I'd like to ask you one more question. Please answer me honestly.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">What is it, dude?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you kill Mr. Juan Corrida?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please put the phone away and answer this question yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Alright. Just so we're clear, dude, I didn't kill anyone, and that includes Juan Corrida, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Well, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nothing. Not a chain or lock in sight.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Which means... I think it is alright to trust him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, it does appear that way. Well, at least I can breathe a sigh of relief knowing my client is innocent.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Um... The trial's tomorrow, right? I'm counting on you, dude.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, at least we were able to get Mr. Matt Engarde as our client. And we know that he didn't do it... Which is very important...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So! So now what should we do!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, the trial is tomorrow. And we only get this one chance. There's only one way to prove Mr. Engarde's innocence. We have to find the real killer.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">OK! Then let's start looking!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is a giant building just outside the window. It's the Gatewater Hotel, a high-class, luxury hotel. Actually, the crime happened at the recently completed hotel in the center of town, the Gatewater Imperial Hotel. ...Just how far are they going to expand their empire...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! I'll water it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, it's OK... I already did that...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...The watering can... Where are you, Mr. Watering Can...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Pearls gets too wound up if she's not doing something to distract herself... I hope Charley can withstand Typhoon Pearls...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">This is the Nickel Samurai... right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! Please take care of Mystic Maya, and be her "Nickel Samurai", alright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Difficult-looking legal books stand in a formidable row. They mock me.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! Do you need to look something up in one of these law books, Mr. Nick!? Wh-Which book is it!? Which book do you need!? ... Umm... I can't read those hard books, and... um... I can't reach them either...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-It's OK, Pearls. Really.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My desk. Since I don't have time to sit, it's unusually clean...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! I cleaned it up some more for you last night! ...Because I couldn't sleep...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Since there were no Psyche-Locks, then that means we can trust Mr. Engarde to be innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I really feel much better knowing that. Ever since last night, I was so worried that I kept wondering... "What if he is the real killer...? What then...?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, I have something I want to ask you, Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">OK, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why are you so interested in how Maya and I get along? I mean, she and I don't have anything special go--</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Huh!? Wh-What do you mean!? B-But I thought... I thought you and Mystic Maya were... I-I've been mistaken all this time!? No way...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Aaaah! She really wasn't kidding! Pearls actually believes Maya and I are... ...Maybe I should've just left it alone...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! Stop it! Don't hide your true feelings from me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ow! She slapped me!!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That's a lawyer's Sacred Treasure, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I feel like it has a mysterious power, just like my Magatama...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, well, I guess I can let her think what she wants on this one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, Mystic Maya... I wonder if you're alright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure she's OK. We have to be patient for just one more day. I'm sure we can save her. Trust me.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">If there's anything I can do, please tell me, OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">To tell you the truth, I really want to grow my hair out, just like Mystic Maya. But my mother wouldn't let me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think your hair now suits you perfectly.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">R-Really? Th-Thank you! *fidget, fidget*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*fidget, fidget*</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm sure that Mr. Detective would be our ally if we asked!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I think so too. <thought>Looking back, we've known each other for a while now... He's always been trustworthy... A bit "off", but still trustworthy. What a paradox.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">He's a really kind and nice old man, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Pearls is really perceptive when it comes to people... But what does she mean by "old man"...?</thought> Hey, Pearls? What about me...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What about you, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>On second thought, I don't think I want to hear this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, there are still so many things in this world that I don't understand yet. ...Honestly, I still don't have enough training.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, no, it's OK. I don't have any ideas myself...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm sorry. I'm really sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Ah, the lawyer dude. So what did you find out?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, well... I'm still in the middle of investigating...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">I see. ...But I've already told you everything I know, dude.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Dude, like I told you, I don't know anything about that press conference. I leave that kind of stuff to my manager.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...This is harder than pulling bass from a river...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">So, why are you carrying around that transceiver...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wanted to ask you about it.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">And why do you do everything it tells you to do? You know, the messages it sends you, dude.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>On second thought, he probably doesn't have anything to do with Maya's kidnapping.</thought> ...That's a secret.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">OK, whatever, dude.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Look, dude, I didn't kill him. I mean, the Nickel Samurai kicked the Jammin' Ninja's butt, right? So it's not like I felt threatened by the likes of him.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Being rivals sounds like a sad way to relate to another person...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hey! What do you think you're doing!? You can't come in without...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Good morning.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hold on, it's YOU! What is going on around here!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">U-Uh... Um...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I heard poor Juan was killed. Is that true!? It's a bad rerun is what this is. Another "Steel Samurai" doing the most evil of deeds.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, you know... That's not entirely...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I'll have you know that I was a huge fan of Juan's! Why, oh why, do all the stars I'm interested in drop one by one like flies!? It's always been that way! Ever since I was a little girl in elementary school! The class hamster was fine until it was my turn to clean its cage, and then it died! The other kids started calling me the "Queen Reaper". I swear that's what they dubbed me! "Whoever you name in your evil spell dies within three minutes," they would taunt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Actually, I wanted to ask you about the murder and what happened...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hmph! Don't push me, boy!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... Mr. Nick? I... Um... I couldn't hear everything she said... because she was talking too fast...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Oldbag, could you please speak a little slower...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Don't boss me around, you spiky-haired, smarty-pants!</line>
<line speaker="Ray Gun">*rata-tat-tat-tat-tat...*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the stage they were going to use for the post-ceremony stage show. After the show, there was supposed to be a press conference, but...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Even Mr. Engarde himself didn't seem to know, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How does the person who's supposed to give a conference not know about it...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">My dear Hammer died a year ago in that dreadful murder. And only recently did I finally find a star that makes this heart go *badump* again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I don't know what to say...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I ask you, why does every star I cheer for always ends up kicking the bucket?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I'd watch your words! No one's going to get away with saying anything bad about my Juan!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I haven't said anything...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, I don't believe a word that woman says anyway!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What woman?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That irritating, backwater girl with the afro and the horrible country accent. I mean, what is that manner of speaking supposed to be? And why does she never stop? Honestly, women these days. They don't know the meaning of the word "modesty". When I was a young maiden, I was so beautiful even the flowers of the field blushed. But despite this, I pressed flowers, or read the stars, or wrote beautiful love poems or</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Pearls? Are you thirsty?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, a little.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK. I'll go get you some juice or something.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Th-Thank you very much.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hey! Are you paying attention!? Young'uns today!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So I'm guessing Ms. Oldbag heard everything from Lotta...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I want to ask you about what happened around the time of the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Ah, I don't know anything about that. I was here getting ready.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Getting ready? For what...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">The show, of course! ...Well, and the press conference afterwards.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Cue mysterious music for the magical press conference.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Anyway, I don't know anything about the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">... But.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">But if you're talking about what I saw, that's different. I saw it very clearly!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I saw the most important moment of the night!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-The most important moment!? You don't mean...!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, so now you treat me with respect, you disrespectful child. When you speak to your elders, you should always be polite. Really, kids today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please tell me! What did you see!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">The murder last night was gruesome, wasn't it? But then, what murder isn't?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Please don't stray onto another tangent... Please...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">If you want to hear more, then show your respect and bring this lady a present!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please tell me! What did you see on the night of the murder!?</line>
<line speaker="Ray Gun">*rata-tat-tat-tat-tat...*</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">P-Please! Mystic Maya's life is...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Ah, but you haven't given me my present yet. ...Hmm... Let's see... I'll only tell it to you if you can bring me Juan's autograph!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What an unreasonable request... You might as well have asked for the moon!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I don't have anything to say to delinquents like you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grrr... She's clamming up like the old clam she is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Please! Anything would be helpful!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well then, how about I tell you my measurements?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Um... No, that's okay... Really.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">She really doesn't like you, does she Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know, I know...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like the investigation is still in full swing. The hotel staff and the police are running around like a bunch of headless chickens.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I wonder if we can do any investigating of our own in this kind of atmosphere...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well, got to roll up the sleeves and try, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a grand set of doors over there. It's the doors Maya followed the bellboy out of, only to disappear... ...If only we had all gone together...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That is such a beautiful sight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The chandelier?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes. But I can't believe it... I can't believe that such a terrible murder happened under such beautiful lights... It's shocking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The awards ceremony was held on that stage just last night. It was really fabulous.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You just reminded me of the circus for a second. I wonder if everyone is alright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I heard that Berry Big Circus just recently started holding performances again...</thought> I'm sure they're all fine, Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">We ate at this table last night, didn't we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I was really happy then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wish I could make you smile again... Even for a second...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey! Yer here! Been waitin' for ya, Mr. Lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lotta...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey! Mr. Cop fella! The thief's showed his face!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Arrest him! Put him on trial! Find him guilty! Give him the death penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What's wrong, Lotta!? Are you feeling alright?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Looked here and there and up and down the mountain, but it ain't here! So why don't ya just hurry up and give it back to me, ya creep!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, what are you looking for...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">My CAMERA! C-A-M-E-R-A! It's my life blood! I'm gonna die without my $700 camera!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Your camera...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Look, don't lots of people say the criminal always goes back to the scene of the crime!? And lookie lookie, here ya are!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yep. Here I am... Faced with a Lotta trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can understand flowers in front of the dressing rooms, but what are stuffed bears doing here...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I didn't touch them! Wasn't me, I tell ya! I give ya my word!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I get the impression Lotta helped herself to one of them...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Compared to the flowers on the other side of the hall, these are much more gorgeous. Let's see... Record companies, fan clubs, company workers, family... Carrying all these flowers home would be hard, I think...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yeah, that's what I thought too, so I was a nice enough gal to lend a helpin' hand! ...Secretly, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have a feeling one of these days, I'm going to end up defending her in court...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a piece of paper taped to the door that says, "Juan Corrida's Room".</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">So that's the scene of the murder, I reckon. I thought somethin' had gone on that night, but I didn't never think it was murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a piece of paper taped to the door that says, "Matt Engarde's Room".</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So Mr. Engarde was here during his break, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what he claims. <thought>Hmm... The crime scene... If he had wanted to get to Mr. Corrida's room... He would have had to pass through this hallway.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you lost your camera...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">It ain't no ordinary camera! Ya buy it in a store and it's $1,600 brand new!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Huh? But didn't you just say you bought it for $700?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I had a nice long talk with the guy at the store... About five hours, I reckon. I made this itty-bitty scratch on it and the manager got all huffed up in the face... He gave me his talkin' to and was real mean about it too. He done made me cry at that!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">When did you lose your camera?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Last night, after the murder happened. Musta been when I was busy runnin' around lookin' into things! That's when I lost sight of my dear, darlin' expensive sweetie!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lotta, what did you capture with that expensive camera of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I don't rightly know. I snapped a shot of anythin' that caught my eye. So I don't 'member. ...And 'sides, I couldn't get anythin' for my big scoop.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if Lotta's missing camera is even connected to the murder...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lotta, please tell me what you know about what happened at the time of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well, from before the ceremony last night, I was hangin' around here in this area. Yeah, actually I was here until around the time Mr. Engarde was arrested.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What were you doing here...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">You sure you went to school, City Boy? Wherever Lotta Hart goes, there's a story to be found! A big scoop to be had!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A big scoop...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I told ya before. I'm gonna be the best tabloid photographer the world's ever seen! Reckon course that means I'm always lookin' for the perfect shot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder what "scoop" she was after this time...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Although, I was also on the look out for the other stars that were here, so... maybe I wasn't here the entire time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lotta... Are you sure you weren't here the entire time? So you could take a picture for your big scoop?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well... Maybe I was. But that's what real journalists do! I got some juicy inside info, so I thought to myself, why not get a picture for proof?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What kind of story was it that you would hang around here...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Oops, sorry, Mr. Lawyer. Can't be tellin' you that. Trade secret, ya know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not again... Why does everyone have something to hide...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">We've been stopped, haven't we?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ha ha, yeah! Take that, Mr. Lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm glad someone around here is happy... Ms. Lotta and your "I rule!" smile...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were on the hunt for your big scoop last night?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">It's just a bunch of tabloid photos. They ain't got nothing to do with the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It looks like we have no choice but to remove the Psyche-Locks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I guess so.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey, what's that? ...A press conference ticket? How come I ain't got myself one of them!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Please don't direct your anger at me...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Why in tarnations wasn't I invited to that!? How come someone on the bottom of the popularity chart like you got the info, but not me!? Info like that is worth nothin' to ya, am I right or what!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Is that the kind of person she thinks I am...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Are you going to stand there and take that, Mr. Nick!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Nngh... And I just bought that camera... Who did it!? The thievin' rascal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please don't look straight at me while you're saying that...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">When I find the bugger who went and done this, they're gonna pay with a bullet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And if you do that, don't expect me to defend you...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Now that I think about it, she isn't with y'all today, is she...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">She's a spunky one! You shouldn't have been lettin' her outta yer sight. Who knows what she's up to now...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Like you're one to talk...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ah, just wanna say sorry to ya.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">For...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well, I really, absolutely thought you were the murderer.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">You know... Last time, that thing with Maya Fey...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-Wh-What!? But why!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I mean, you were all worked up, ya know?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">*sniffle* ...Meanie...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lotta, that was very insensitive of you!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">This kind of hairstyle is pretty hard to get, ya know. Hard to care for too. Just the other day, I ran my hand through my hair to fix it up, and suddenly, out pops this dollar coin! That's gotta be like hittin' the jackpot!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow, that's really lucky!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sigh* What a deep conversation that was...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I don't really care for 'em "heroes" or whatnot.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">And shows they got for kids, those adventures are just plain ol' borin'! Now, adults. We get more caught up in messy, sticky, real situations! ...Even me...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">O-Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Sounds like the tyke's gettin' what I'm goin' with this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait a sec here! Don't go around getting her mixed up in things like that!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">This old granny? Ah, she kept on glarin' at me with those eyes of hers. As if it's my fault. Kept babblin' how she won't forgive people who write "trash" about her Juan... ...Ah, yeah, we sorta got into a little fight, ya know...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A "little" fight? Knowing those two, it was probably more of a blabbering contest.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Do you know anything...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">...*sigh*... I've told ya how many times now? I'm a journalist. I've got so much info runnin' laps in my head I forget things here and there!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Please don't get so worked up over this...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hah! I don't care if ya beg me! "Be extra tough on kids!" That's this gal's motto on learnin' youngsters.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... Where are we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We're in Mr. Matt Engarde's dressing room... This is our client's room.</line>
<line speaker="???">May I help you with something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, uh... We're...</line>
<line speaker="???">You're Mr. Engarde's lawyer, correct? I gathered as much. I also looked for lawyers on my end, but to no avail.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... How did you know I'm his lawyer...?</line>
<line speaker="???">You were just saying that he is your client. In a situation like this, the only person who would use such a word would be his lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow...</line>
<line speaker="???">It's simple deduction, really. The trial is tomorrow, and Mr. Engarde's situation is looking rather grim. So you came here, one stop in your mad dash, to find clues to build his case, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, you're not totally right, but you're not totally off either.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It's really not the time to be showing off, Mr. Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I am Adrian Andrews. I hate to waste time, so let's get down to business.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Alright... <thought>She may be of small stature, but appearances can be deceiving...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's probably Mr. Engarde's suitcase. For someone who was only going to be here for the award show, this is a lot of stuff. Looks like he has about three days' worth of clothes in here.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Stars really are different from us, aren't they...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's the bedroom over there.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That's a bed...? Wow, they have really big beds here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's some samurai-looking clothes on the sofa here.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, I think that jacket looking thing is called a "happi".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whatever it is, I'm sure something like that would make a great souvenir. Maya would be absolutely thrilled...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like dishes left over from dinner... A dinner for two, at that.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm sure they're Mr. Engarde and Ms. Andrews' plates.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like they had T-bone steaks... What's with Global Studios and T-bone steaks...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a giant bone sitting on the plate.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... I don't really like meat...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...? There's something... weird about this plate... I just wish I could put my finger on what it is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I assume the first thing you need to know is what everyone was doing that night, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, that is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Then I will tell you. Before the award ceremony, I had dinner with Mr. Engarde. In this very room, I might add.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Dinner"? What did you eat?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I told you. I hate to waste time with trifling details. If you took a look at the table yourself, you wouldn't need to ask me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I bet she's a lot of fun at parties...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">When the award show was starting, I headed for Viola Hall.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And after the show ended, you came back to this room...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">No, I had some small errands to run. I helped with the preparations in the lobby.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... <thought>Preparations for the post-ceremony show, I guess...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">When it was time for the post-ceremony show, I came back to call for Mr. Engarde. After that, I went to visit Mr. Corrida...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's when you found his body, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You really held strong through everything...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah... She does seem to be mentally tough as nails...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, so... About you and...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Stop right there. Don't expect me to believe you have been talking to me without knowing how we relate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I have no idea why Mr. Engarde chose you as his lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why did she have to go and say something like that...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick... Calm down and hang in there. I'll give you a shoulder rub to relieve your stress later, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I already gave you my name earlier, but I'll add that I'm Mr. Engarde's manager.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His manager... Speaking of managers, did the victim, Mr. Corrida have one?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">No, he did not.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He didn't?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Global Studios has a very different policy from Worldwide Studios in that Worldwide Studios does not assign individual managers to their stars.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">This industry is very ruthless and unforgiving. Actually, you look quite ruthless and unforgiving yourself to your poor partner. Dragging a little girl like her to places like this. Honestly.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You're wrong! I... I'm doing this to help Mystic Maya...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls... Calm down and hang in there. I'll buy you a juice later, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you have any ideas?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">As to...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As to why Mr. Corrida was murdered?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Why would you ask me about such a thing...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm just doing my job. So, do you have any ideas?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Ms. Andrews...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Sorry, but there's nothing more I have to add to this conversation.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Is it a Psyche-Lock, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... There's getting to be more and more of these lately.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know something, don't you? About why Mr. Corrida was murdered...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Why are you asking me? Don't tell me you can see inside my heart.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No, but I can see the locks you have on your psyche.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">If you don't remove her locks...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, it's worthless to even ask...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were the one taking care of the arrangements for this press conference, right?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But Mr. Engarde said he "didn't know" about it.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... Is that what he said...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Actually, I didn't know all the details either. It was a request from the publicity department. All I did was help out and do what I was asked.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh... I see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder about that... I wouldn't take her to be the type of person to do something without knowing the details.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">That's Mr. Will Powers. He's an actor contracted with Global Studios. He's a very nice man. A man with a good heart. ...But that's all he is and ever will be.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Urk... What a horrible thing to say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...Society doesn't care about genuinely nice people, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? For a second, her face twisted in pain...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I wonder if something happened to Ms. Andrews...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you know the victim, Mr. Corrida?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes, I knew him. The world is such a small place, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Did you know about his rivalry with the Nickel Samurai?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Honestly, they were like children when it came to that. Time and time again, those two competed with each other over the most uninteresting things. ... If either one of them weren't so stubborn, then maybe no one would have needed to die.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">! <thought>...I've got a hunch that this woman knows more than she's letting on... She must know why Juan Corrida was killed!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I asked to become Mr. Engarde's manager. He's a pleasure to manage with his nice disposition.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Mr. Engarde does seem like a rather weak-willed man; always doing as he's told...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">He's always saying, "my manager," right Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I hate talking about myself. It's a trifling matter, that's why.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry... <thought>Take away that layer of sarcasm and she really does seem to hate herself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, I'd like to ask you about this...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I told you. I hate trifling matters. It's a waste of time to show me things that are of no relevance to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow... This is the first time I've been shut down this badly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick... Where are we...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We're in Mr. Juan Corrida's room, Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Corrida...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim... Which makes this the crime scene too.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! It's you! So!? What's happened!? The kidnapper! Has he contacted you again!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not yet. He probably won't until we win Mr. Engarde's acquittal.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm... You doing OK, pal? Hanging in there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I just want Maya to be alright...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We don't have a lot of time left, but I'm going to help you as much as I can, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you do that? Even if we want to look around the crime scene...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Just this once... "Special circumstances" right, pal? I'll even tell you everything I know. But you've gotta keep quiet. It's my neck on the line here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, that's right. I got you guys a map of the hotel, pal. Here you go, little missy.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow, you're giving it to me!? Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ha ha. Wouldn't want you to get lost in a hotel too big for its own good.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! I got a map!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's great, Pearls!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... Um... But Mr. Nick, I can't read what it says...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are all sorts of things in this refrigerator...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">The carrot juice bottle and the tomato juice bottle are both empty...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Empty...? <thought>It's too much of a hassle to throw them away, I guess.</thought> They're all vegetable juices. I guess he must've been a real health nut.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Oh! There's a beet, some ketchup, and a bottle of strawberry jam too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe red was his favorite color...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow, there are a lot of bears!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Alarm clock ones, collector's editions, stuffed teddies, plastic models... It's pretty overwhelming... Is there a kind of bear he doesn't have...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">There's even a few in the trash can...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I get the feeling maybe the guy didn't really like bears.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Poor teddies...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>I don't think I want to "bear" with the trauma the last case caused me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What's wrong, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hmph! It's so messy here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Pearls really likes things neat and tidy, I take it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">There are a lot of electronic things in here that I've never seen before. Hey, Mr. Nick! Tell me what they are, pretty please?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK. That over there is a "watch". You wear it on your wrist.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... I know what a watch is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oops. For a second there, I forgot I was talking with Pearls, not Maya...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a suitcase. There are so many things in it that I bet it barely closes. There's his clothes, a dryer, an electric shaver, a calculator...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Do all stars pack too much stuff like Mr. Corrida?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like Mr. Corrida had dinner last night.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">This bottle... It's tomato juice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We had a lot of food at the award show last night... But I wonder if the stars had gone onstage after only eating a meager meal like this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So that's a bed, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup. It's big, but it's a bed.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Aaah! Mr. Nick! It's sooooo soft!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Big beds must be a rarity for her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Bottles of cosmetics are scattered all over the floor. This is probably where Mr. Corrida fought his assailant.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What's this glass fragment from...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A flower vase maybe? There are flowers on the floor, but I don't know what they are.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You don't know much about flowers, do you Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is... a guitar case, I guess. A little beat up, but still useable.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That's strange. The guitar is not here...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe he forgot to bring it to the show?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But Mystic Maya... She said the bright red guitar was the Jammin' Ninja's signature item...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's true...</thought> Huh? This guitar case is wet. But it's only wet on top of the lid...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yeah... There's no water inside the case... This is water, isn't it...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a beautiful wine glass, and there's... tomato juice in it.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ewww. Tomato juice. I don't really like it much.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a bottle of it on the table over there. That's probably where this came from.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But doesn't it seem weird?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What seems weird?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I mean, everything else is scattered all over the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>She's right. The flower vase was broken and the make-up is strewn everywhere.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Why is this glass the only thing that's still alright...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know what was the cause of death?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, technically, the final autopsy report isn't out yet, but... one look at the scene of the crime should tell you, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The scene of the crime...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. Here's a picture.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a knife in his chest.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, pal, that's the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So he was stabbed to death...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">They're looking at the fingerprints down at the lab right now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There were fingerprints on the knife?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup. And it looks like they're pretty sure they're Mr. Engarde's prints, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's bad... Real bad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why was Mr. Engarde arrested?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Because we had evidence on him.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Evidence...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It looks like the victim, Juan Corrida, really put up a big fight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, one look at the crime scene and you can tell. There's signs of a struggle everywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, yeah. During the fight, his button came off...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mr. Engarde said something about a button... Something like, one of the Jammin' Ninja's buttons got caught in his "hakama"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But that's not all...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There was a witness, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A witness!? Wh-Who is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That lady... Ms. Oldbag.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Please... Anyone but her!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The prosecution has plenty of evidence to make a solid case... Not to mention there's something at the crime scene that was a little off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something that was a little off...? As in...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">As in, that's for you to figure out, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Alright, let's try to figure it out, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's your "present" from the kidnapper, huh? While you're talking, it sends and receives radio waves... If we could trace that...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yeah! We could use it to find out where the bad guy is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It uses radio waves, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I got it! I'll go find a radio scanner, and let you borrow it, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What can you tell me about this guitar case?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, that. This is just what I heard, pal, but that's the Jammin' Ninja's signature item.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The guitar case?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No, not that! What do you take me as? I mean the guitar inside, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But... The guitar is missing.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, we looked for it too. It's not normal for a person to forget to bring their most famous item to an award show.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's starting to sound like that red guitar is related to this case after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So about this wine glass...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah, so you noticed it, pal. The whole crime scene was a mess, but this glass was the only thing that was untouched.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You noticed that too, Detective Gumshoe...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No, actually Ms. von Karma noticed it first.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... Pearls noticed it before me too... Hey, wait a minute. So... does that mean Ms. von Karma's coming here...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, she's coming. Man, you're going to be in so much trouble, pal. I think it'd be best if you didn't bump into her here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can bet the instant I see her, I'll be running the 1,000 meter dash.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You look at this photo and you can't help it. It makes you want to say, "I can't believe this is the scene of a murder."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Stabbed with a knife after a struggle... A clue is sleeping in this photo somewhere... I know it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...For what?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I really want to help you look for her, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Detective...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If anything happens, let me know, OK? I want to help in any way I can!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, little missy. Listen good, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">OK. What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't ever pick up a whip, OK? Don't even think about it.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If you ever find yourself thinking you want one, try to make due with a good slap to the face. Got that? Slap the person in the face. Promise me, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Personal experience tells me Gumshoe should be careful what he wishes for...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If I had a choice, she would be number three on my list of people I don't want to see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Because I'm in the number one spot?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't get all high and mighty on me here. You've taken a tumble into second place, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Really? Then who's in first...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ms. von Karma's miles and miles ahead of you in this race.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She's really scary... Right now... M-Ms. von Karma... You really don't...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's so scared of her that he's whispering now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, why don't we let bygones be bygones, pal? Look, this guy is guilty. A buck says so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One dollar...? Sure you're not talking about Pearls' allowance money?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I... I can't bet any more than that... My salary... It's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It doesn't matter what we think... I still have to defend Mr. Engarde in court or else!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I thought she was an alien from outer space.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, probably because she's wearing that strange helmet.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nah, even with her helmet off, I thought she was an alien, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I think that's probably best kept to yourself, if you know what I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She's Mr. Engarde's manager, right? No matter what I do, I really stink at talking with people like her. As soon as I open my mouth, I get all flustered. See, she's one of those women with a brain. She's someone who "gets things done".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, she does give that sort of impression, like she's got it all together.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Compared to her, you can easily tell I'm a "can't do anything right" kind of guy. That's why I get all nervous and start messing up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I feel sort of bad for him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you know about this?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um... There's nothing special I can tell you about this, pal. Look pal, we don't have a lot of time. Why don't you show me something more important? If Ms. von Karma saw me here like this... I'd have to switch sides real fast...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wh-What's that beeping noise, Mr. Nick...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I've heard this sound somewhere before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's Ms. von Karma...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whenever I hear that sound, for some reason, she pops out of nowhere and whips me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come to think of it, that did happen the last time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">S-Sorry! I've gotta make myself scarce! Later, pal! Eowww!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*gulp* Would it be too much to ask for you to be nice to me for a change...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Owww!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Uwaah!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He was so scared, he just froze up on the spot...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Victory is yours? Is that all this means to you...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ow! Now what did she throw at me...!? What is this...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Well, I guess this means I've gotta get back to the precinct now, pal. If you ever need me, come down to the Criminal Affairs Department, alright? And if you can, try not to let Ms. von Karma see you...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick, what's this piece of paper...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's called an "autograph".</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Auto-graff?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's got Mr. Corrida's name written on it, so it's his autograph.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I can't read it at all. To be honest, I've never seen writing that looks like this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, it's a special way of writing called "cursive".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look here. See how it says, "To my dearest Wendy" in more normal letters here?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Th-This sloppy, unreadable writing! It's crazy and cruel to give this to someone!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hold on...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wendy... I've heard that name somewhere before...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Oh, Mr. Wright! How are you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, Mr. Powers. Have you been here the entire time?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah. People connected to the murder aren't allowed to go home, let alone leave...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you tell me a little more about the Nickel Samurai TV show?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">OK. "The Nickel Samurai" is an action hero program aimed towards kids. It's the sequel to "The Steel Samurai".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">This time, there are three Samurai Brothers: Aluminum Samurai, Tin Samurai... And of course, the Nickel Samurai. It's a love "Y" in Neo Olde Tokyo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... ... W-Wait... A love what...?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">A love "Y". This girl, Sayo, works at a tea shop and all three guys fall for her at the same time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... I guess the "Y" shape is like the 3 brothers colliding over this one girl?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Anyway, Sayo is actually the daughter of the evil Strawberry Clan's leader!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sounds like an unusual situation. Like Romeo and Juliet... times three.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Y-Yeah... Strange thing is, this sort of forbidden love story is really big with the office ladies.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yes, Pearl?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wh-What happens next!? I want to know! Ms. Sayo... Does Ms. Sayo fall in love? She does, doesn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Every Sunday at 8 AM.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm going to stop watching "Kids' Masterpiece Theatre" starting this week!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't believe she's really considering it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what's the "Jammin' Ninja" TV show like?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">It started from a remake of an old movie, to tell you the truth. The Jammin' Ninja is, like the Samurai shows, aimed towards kids. It's the story of a ninja who can't climb a wall, but became a big pop star.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Uh, what?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">He was a really lousy ninja. Absolutely couldn't do any ninja things right at all. But boy could he sing! With his trusty bright red guitar in hand, he took the ancient world by storm.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A... A ninja... With a bright red guitar...!?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">And then, the final fight in front of his beloved Princess Misola! "Jammin' versus the Muromachi Five!" Suddenly! Our brave hero catches a not so Jammin' cold the night before Battle 3!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aww, that's too bad for him...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Y-Yeah... But this kind of pop music-based love story is something high school girls really like.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yes, Pearl?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wh-What happens next!? I want to know!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Jammin'... The Jammin' Ninja! Will he be able to sing!? What about Princess Misola!?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Every Sunday at 8 AM.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Umm... Which show should I watch...? Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't believe she's really  considering it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you mind telling me about this "gossip"?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ah, so you're interested in it too! I figured you would be!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I have such a weakness for celebrity gossip too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh really... You too, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah. So take a look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like a tabloid Ms. Oldbag would read...</thought> Alright, let's see here... "Jammin' Midnight Rendezvous!?"</line>
<line speaker="Powers">"...to the mysterious, yet beautiful manager to the stars, Ms. A. A.!" ...Y-You see now, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">You can stop pretending to be in the dark, Mr. Wright! Juan Corrida didn't have a manager of his own. Which means if we're talking about a certain manager with the initials A. A....</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Adrian Andrews...?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Y-Yes, exactly! This is big news!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But... It seems kind of odd. That woman, Ms. Andrews... Together with the biggest rival of her client...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ah, it's that wonderful thing that can only happen between two people...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Powers looks so happy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Pearls is just following along, not having any idea as to why he's smiling...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">Well, like the saying goes, one man's garbage is another man's treasure.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I can't believe it... A kidnapping...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Do you remember what the person looked like who gave this to you?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">It was that bellboy. And... And I didn't suspect a thing because he looked like such a normal old man...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Old man, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">That guitar case... That was Juan's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm guessing you've seen this case before?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">It's pretty famous by now. It stands out because it holds THE bright red guitar.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The bright red guitar... The Jammin' Ninja's signature item.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But if the guitar is so important, how could he forget it for the award ceremony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That does seem a little strange...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">I... I'm sure he won't hurt her and he'll let her go soon...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Mr. Wright. I believe in you. You will save her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I never would've thought I'd see her here of all places. The last time we saw each other was during that really bad incident... You know... I mean, when I look back now, I think of the good things, so it's not so bad, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I would love to go back in time and relive a few of those good things... *chuckle*</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Th-That's not funny...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, I guess not...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">Hey, that's Ms. Andrews! She's Matt's manager. Actually, I was interested in her for a little bit. Just a little...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... So Mr. Powers likes this type of woman...</thought> What do you know about Ms. Andrews...?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Well, see... Here's the thing. I don't really KNOW her know her... you know?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">There's sort of a small rumor going around about her right now...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">A rumor...?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ah! If you're interested, I can give you a little bit of the details!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's so happy, he looks like a lion that's just found his next meal...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think about this article...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... Hmph. If you're talking about her thing with Juan, I always thought she was a bit careless in the way she handled it... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's it?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...That's it.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">That's my manager. Did you meet her?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">What do you think? Strong woman, right? And she takes good care of me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...You're such a mama's boy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Alright, I'll be honest with you for now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then, please! Tell us what you saw!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">But, aww, what a waste. And here I have a perfectly good chance to have a little fun at you young'un's expense. Because I am a little devil, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Um... Doesn't that imply you aren't a good person...?</thought> Alright, I'll give you what you want...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">You're Engarde's lawyer, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well, yes... but...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Then forget it! There is no way I'm telling you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But why!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Th-Th-That's! That's Juan's autograph!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, it is.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">And... And it even says, "To my dearest Wendy" on it! Th-That's me, right!? Right!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">My name is Wendy Oldbag, so that "Wendy" has to be me, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, it may say "Wendy"... But somehow, I don't think Juan had THIS "Wendy" in mind when he signed it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, please, give it to me! Let me have it! Please!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, un. I can't let you have it, just like that.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Yes, yes, I know. Then how about an exchange!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, she must really want this autograph...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">My offer isn't good enough for you!? Fine, Mr. Wright. You win. Wendy Oldbag, ready to open up her heart! All for my dearest Juan!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I feel bad for you now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I tell you, I saw him that night. I saw him coming out of Juan's room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're kidding!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh no!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">It was about ten minutes before Juan's body was discovered. It was just a coincidence. I was on my way to the toilet, minding my own business.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And...? Did you tell that to the police?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, of course! I thought I could get a gift certificate or two out of it, maybe more.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Gift certificate...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I've been recruited again for that part at the trial. You know, the trial tomorrow? This time, you're gonna get it! I'm gonna work hard to get your client pronounced guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But Mr. Engarde hasn't done anything bad...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I don't care about details like that! I know he did my dear poor Juan in! I just do! That yellow-bellied chicken!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">A yellow-bellied chicken...? I wonder what that would look like...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I trust my senses. I know when someone did something bad, and I say he did it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What did Mr. Engarde ever do to her to deserve this...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What did Mr. Engarde do to you to make you so...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">You don't know!? That guy! He framed my Juan! He created that scandal that plagued poor Juan!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What's a "skan-dal"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... Um, I'll tell you about that after we get home, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Poor Juan, led astray by the wiles of that vile temptress...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick... What do "viles" and "wile temptress" mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! Um, how about we just listen to what Ms. Oldbag has to say for now, OK Pearls? So, Ms. Oldbag. Who is this "woman" you're talking about...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">...Adrian Andrews, of course! Who else!? That guy, he shoved the girl onto Juan on purpose!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His own manager? But why...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I thought lawyers were smart! It was to create a scandal to make Juan lose face! That girl drove Juan into a scandal that dragged his reputation through the mud!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like a pretty standard definition of a scandal to me...</thought> Why do you know about that anyway, Ms. Oldbag?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I'm one of Juan's biggest fans! I'm always out there gathering information! There's nothing I don't know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And do you have proof that Mr. Engarde did what you say he did...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Next week's issue of a certain magazine says so!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... Of course. A tabloid...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Next week... Doesn't that mean it's something people don't know about yet...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why would Ms. Oldbag have information like that...? And where did she get it...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hee hee hee...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hmm, it doesn't look like Mr. Scruffy Detective is here...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great, now even Pearls is calling him "Scruffy"... Thanks Franziska.</thought> They said something about an investigation briefing earlier, right? Why don't we come back and try again later when they're done...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">OK... I guess that's all we can do, right Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Detective">"...a break and spit it out, you lowlife scumbag... ...a turkey sandwich? Don'tcha eat ham every day? Get sick of it or something?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He must be doing image training for interrogations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These are the detectives' desks. There are computers and files on each one. Funny, they're a lot tidier than I expected. I guess the detectives don't spend a lot of time at their desks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be the chief of the detectives here. He's glued to his computer screen.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">WHAT!? The Hero of Heroes award ceremony... The grand prize got away from the Jammin' Ninja again!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Shouldn't you be reading something more important...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A poster of a female police officer... Wait, no. That's the latest "Babes in Uniform" calendar. My bad.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Aww, it's kind of cute. Mr. Nick, what is this stuffed animal's name...?</line>
<line speaker="Chief">That's the "Blue Badger"! It was my idea! I made it! It's this precinct's mascot, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, wow...</line>
<line speaker="Chief">I'll get him assigned mascot of every police station, if it's the last thing I do!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I hope you succeed in your mission, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lotta, will you please answer my questions? On the night of the murder, why were you loitering around the victim's room?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I told ya, didn't I? For my scoop!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What I want to know about are the details of this "scoop".</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Th-That's not somethin' I can tell ya. I mean, that there's my bread and butter...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright then. An unpleasant tabloid photographer looking for a scoop... I'm going to say that you were looking into a scandal.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Grr!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could it be that you, Lotta Hart, were looking for a break with a huge story? Perhaps an unfolding scandal between Juan Corrida and this person...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Who the heck is that...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">You think us journalists are all a bunch of idiots...? Ya can't fool me! I'm a pro!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh, really...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">So... Who's this person anyway...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If you're such a pro, why don't you do your own research and figure it out!</thought> Um, let's try that again, shall we...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Th-This woman...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She's Adrian Andrews, Matt Engarde's manager.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Mmph!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Nickel Samurai's manager, caught secretly meeting with his rival, the Jammin' Ninja. It would be the hottest story of the season, wouldn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">You're pretty good at this guessin' thing, Mr. Lawyer. But ya can't just make up any ol' thing and think it'll make the papers. Ya gotta have backup.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Backup...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yeah, yeah. Ya gotta have that... that what's it... "newsauce"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Um, you mean, "news source"...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">That's it! So show me somethin' that shows that Juan guy had somethin' with Ms. Andrews!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">You really think I'm some kind of idiot, don'tcha!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Don't ya know pros don't go for a lead without proof it's somethin' worth going after?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, if the pro we're talking about is you, then this looks right up your alley...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">As if!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like I touched a nerve there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Now listen here, City Boy. Show me a good, solid newsauce or else!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the article from a certain weekly tabloid. "Jammin' Midnight Rendezvous!?" "...to the mysterious, yet beautiful manager to the stars, Ms. A. A.!"</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">...Aaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Corrida didn't have a manager of his own. What's more, his rival, Mr. Engarde's manager... Adrian Andrews... She has the initials A. A.! You saw this article and then thought to take some pictures of them as proof. That's why you were lurking around Mr. Corrida's door last night!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Waaaaaah!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were looking into Mr. Corrida and Ms. Andrews' affair, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">You got it! I was gonna get myself a scoop by catchin' 'em in a secret meetin'!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But there's already an article about it in one of the weekly tabloid magazines... It's no longer breaking news.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Whatcha just say!? Her initials are "A. A." What kind of vague thing is that!? That ain't no proof of nothin'! People are gonna wanna see real proof! Well, at least I do. So that's what I was doin'! Getting photos!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I'm gonna whip up the reader's interest with some gossip and a little misleadin'. Then spice it up a little and have myself an exclusive story!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, Lotta, nice journalistic integrity you got there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I already finished writin' up my spicy article, ya know. But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">The paper I wrote it on, my note to myself, it's gone.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Your note to yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">It was inside the case of my $1,600 camera. They done run off together. I came here for my big story! Didn't come 'ere to have my treasure disappear on me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, I understand...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">It's enough to make a gal go bonkers, I tell ya! What's with people now, anyway!? I never thought I'd see the day when someone done steal somethin' from me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You really want that note back, huh...? <thought>I've got no idea why though. The story on that note is probably a bold faced lie...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">She's got one of them personalities like she's... "whipped" without her "whip"! Ha ha, how's that!? A pun worthy of a joke book, yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Sorry, I zoned out.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ah, well, I'll forgive the wax in yer ears this once and tell it to ya one more time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe said they had an investigation briefing...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yeah... Oh! He's back!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, so you came, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why the blunt greeting?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, because there's nothing to be friendly or happy about.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, things look perfect this time around. The evidence and testimony are airtight...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... But... We can't just roll over and die! We have to stay positive!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Detective">"Freeze! Police! Everyone against the wall, hands where I can see 'em! Hey, what are you doing, Gumshoe!? Their hands, not yours!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He must be doing image training for arrests.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what do you mean the evidence is airtight...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't give you all the details, pal, but there's two big pieces.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">T-Two!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And both of them are in this photo. The first is the button that's missing from the victim's chest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... That's the button that you found during your body search of Mr. Engarde...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup. I found it in the folds of the Nickel Samurai's special pants.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Uh... And the second one is...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The knife in his chest, pal. The fingerprints on the knife in his chest, to be exact.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Fingerprints...? Um... Whose are they?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You didn't even have to ask, little missy. It's obvious. They're Matt Engarde's.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Tomorrow's trial... Talk about being stuck between a rock and a hard place...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what about this "airtight testimony"...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's that old security lady, Ms. Oldbag.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I thought so...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What do you mean, you thought so? Did she tell you something, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, well...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And I even told her not to open that mouth of hers and blab to anyone...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Her blab knob is stuck on ten, and there's no turning it down... Trust me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, well... Ms. Oldbag saw it all, pal. She saw Mr. Engarde come out of the victim's room around the estimated time of death.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">N-No way!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What can you tell me about this guitar case...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, that. This is just what I heard, pal, but that's the Jammin' Ninja's signature item.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But... The guitar wasn't in his hotel room...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, we looked for it too. It's not normal for a person to forget to bring their most famous item to an award show.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's starting to sound like that red guitar is related to this case after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The stuff in that glass is tomato juice, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tomato juice...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I heard the victim really loved that stuff. Favorite drink in the world.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It was his favorite drink? <thought>First time I've heard that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We're pretty interested in this bit of gossip ourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The scandal with Mr. Corrida? But why?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, two years ago... A woman committed suicide.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Suicide...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Her name was Celeste Inpax. And she was Juan Corrida's manager.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim's manager...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But that's not all, pal. Ms. Inpax was Ms. Adrian Andrews' mentor... She taught Ms. Andrews everything she knew about the business from square one.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Her mentor...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A woman who was both Mr. Corrida's manager and Ms. Andrews' mentor... Could her suicide have something to do with this case...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Do you want to know more about her, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm not a real fan of action shows or anything... But I know who Juan Corrida and Matt Engarde are. Juan Corrida, though, he was always desperately trying to be better than Matt Engarde.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's something interesting about this woman, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what is that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You don't know? Haven't you heard the gossip about her?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gossip, huh... I wonder if he knows anything about that article...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If I'm caught leaking info to you here in the precinct, my neck's gonna be in a ringer, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Y-Your neck!? No!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah, I mean my "neck" as a joke... But yeah, ask me about things that have to do with the case only, alright pal?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She was the victim's manager and was also Ms. Adrian Andrews' mentor. It's been two years since her suicide, and now those two are linked again by another death. Or maybe it's just a coincidence...? But... Waaah!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">M-M-Ms. von Karma!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Y-You don't... You don't mean...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Th-That's...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">W-Wait... Please wait, sir! If I don't get this month's pay, I'll star--</line>
<line speaker="???">"I would've won." Is that what you want to say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That voice... E-Edgeworth!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's been a long time... Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Th-This person... This is Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What am I going to do with you...? Still blaming others when things go wrong? You haven't changed a bit, Franziska.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you talking about the Von Karma family creed? "To be perfect in every way..." Then let's hear it, Franziska. How are things going? I hear you are having a rough time maintaining perfection in this country.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You seem to be getting crushed under the weight of it all. That's why I came back.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Still the same wild mare she always was.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... </line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">How much do you know...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What do you mean "how much"...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...Mr. Lawyer. I may be your client... But... I hope you will keep yourself out of my personal life.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Ah, no, I would never...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... ... Now, if you'll excuse me... I have a lunch appointment I have to keep...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You're in DETENTION! Who in the world are you going to eat with!? The security guard!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This Celeste Inpax lady... Somehow, I get the feeling she is a very important person in all this...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Hmm, looks like Ms. Andrews isn't here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's not good. I still have a few questions I want to ask her...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">And she has that Psyche-Lock on her heart, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well, we don't have much of a choice. I guess we'll have to come back later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Detective">"Hang in there! You'll be OK, buddy! You're not injured that badly! A hang nail isn't... ...H-Hey. Gumshoe! GUMSHOE! GUMSHOOOOOOOOOE!!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He must be doing image training for when a fellow officer is injured.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I thought you, the Prosecutor Miles Edgeworth, had gone and died!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I never wanted to see you again!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think that's enough of a "warm welcome" for someone you haven't seen in a year...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you going to run tomorrow's trial...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You heard her, right? That wild mare hasn't given in yet, it seems. So, no, I don't think I'll be making an appearance.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your hatred for me is quite unhealthy. Not to mention one-sided. But I will say one thing...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You can't win on your own at the trial tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is that supposed to mean...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have something definitive that you lack. And that's the definition of teamwork. It's the power to find the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"The truth"...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In order to understand this case, you have to understand a certain "truth". ...Well, if you ever feel the need for my assistance, it is available to you. I'm not in charge of this case, so I can be a bit more generous with information.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just what is going on inside his head...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A lot of things may have happened, however Manfred von Karma was still my mentor. And a "perfect win record" is proof of a Von Karma.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...One year ago, you could not establish guilt in a few cases... Are those losses the reason you suddenly disappeared from the Prosecutor's Office? Did you leave because you had lost your "perfect win record"...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To think your motivation for prosecuting trials was so selfish... It'd been better for everyone if you never came back from the dead, Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I see. Then let me ask you something. Why do YOU stand in the courtroom? What is your reason?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, if it was Franziska, she would almost definitely say,</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... The courtroom is not a personal battlefield for prosecutors and lawyers. I stand in the courtroom to defend my client. ...To save their lives.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To save your client, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Those who think only of their own ego-driven goals... Those kind of prosecutors are reprehensible to me. Even if you're a "prodigy"... Or someone like you, Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... It looks like there is still a lot you have yet to learn.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"A lot I have yet to learn"? Me...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hmph. Well, that's enough for now. The time when you will see is coming soon enough...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Inpax's death was most certainly a suicide. Of that there is no mistake. However, we could not find her suicide note. That's when the police began to suspect that someone had hidden it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The suicide note? But how do you know Ms. Inpax had even written such a note?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There was no solid evidence, however... We did find traces of ink on her right index finger. Which makes the likelihood of a suicide note very high.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But who would hide such a thing...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The police think it was Mr. Juan Corrida himself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-The victim...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He was the one who found her body. Which makes him the only person who had a chance to hide her suicide note.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mr. Corrida hid his own manager's suicide note...? But why...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As long as her note is missing, any speculation beyond this is meaningless... For now, I think you should look this over. This is the suicide report... Part one anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Part one...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, how are "Adrian Andrews" and "co-dependency" related?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Adrian Andrews' attempt at suicide... was a few days after the death of Celeste Inpax.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And why did Adrian Andrews think about committing suicide...? Quite possibly because she had "lost her will to live."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lost her will...? But why would she...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Her pillar of strength, her mentor Celeste Inpax, was gone forever. That's why.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-Why would that...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Is this what they call, "following someone to the grave"...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">After her attempted suicide, Adrian Andrews started attending counseling sessions. She is a person who looks for someone she can trust unconditionally. And once she finds that someone, she blindly follows them. Without someone to guide her, she feels uneasy and can't carry herself through life.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! And that's... That's her "co-dependency"...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">When Celeste Inpax suddenly committed suicide, the world before her turned pitch dark... That's according to Adrian Andrews herself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then... That means her super-confident attitude...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's all a faade. She's only copying her mentor's behavior to hold herself together.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How terrible...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't like to look through reports. I like suicide reports even less. Worst of all are the reports that have multiple parts like that one. That has two.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Two parts?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What you just handed me is the first part of the report... Here is the second part.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The second part of the report is about an attempted suicide...</thought> The attempter's name...! It's "Adrian Andrews"!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-Ms. Andrews...? Um, what did she do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She... She tried to kill herself...? She doesn't seem like the kind of person to try and kill herself...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You think she's a strong career woman? That is just her image. Adrian Andrews... She has a certain secret she's always trying to hide.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">A secret...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Her "co-dependency". That's the key word.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Co-dependency"... The word most unsuited to describing that woman...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Appearances can be deceiving. It's such a clich saying... But it's clich because it's true.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Andrews...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>To think that behind that unwavering, brave front... She's been hiding this weakness in fear...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is an interesting rumor about this man...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean the one about Ms. Andrews getting close to him? But that's pretty common tabloid fare, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't take things at face value when there's more to be found...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">While I was abroad, these deplorable types of actors became popular, I take it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, "refreshing like a spring breeze" is his motto...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"R-Refreshing"!? And what is so refreshing about a spring breeze!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like the pollen is not treating him well this year...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Adrian Andrews... She holds a large secret within herself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A secret...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You can't help but feel that this whole case revolves around her...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... This woman is another key to the case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Do you really think so?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">She was Adrian Andrews' mentor a long time ago, but suddenly, she was called away by a production, and became Juan Corrida's manager. And then, a few months later... Celeste Inpax died.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But her death was a suicide, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. But there is still one riddle left unsolved...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A riddle...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Her suicide note. It went missing. No one could find it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A suicide note that just vanished, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have no interest in talking about useless evidence. Put a little more thought into what you show me... Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Still as stuck up as ever...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We are looking into leads, but we can only look into a few key players with our limited resources. There's no reason for us to waste our energy investigating this person.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why don't you just tell it to me straight and say, "I don't have any info"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Oh! Ms. Andrews is here. But it looks like she's talking with someone...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's... Franziska von Karma!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ms. von Karma...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, well, you see... I'm his lawyer, so...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Following you...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Th-That's you, Ms. von Karma! You're the one doing the following!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You're always following after that Mr. Detective with the little beard!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wh-What is that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that noise we heard was this receiver... I feel really sorry for poor Detective Gumshoe now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Y-Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">A-Alright... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What were those two talking about...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ms. Andrews... She seems a little dazed, doesn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why was Juan Corrida murdered? If you ask me, I think you know the reason he was killed.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why are you hiding things? Don't you realize you're putting Mr. Engarde's life in danger by your actions?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... Why do you ask questions for which I have no answer? The truth is, I was not that close to Mr. Corrida.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were not that close...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">That's right. I've never been good at being intimate with another person.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You are not good at being intimate with another person? Somehow, I highly doubt that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I'm very bad at connecting with people. They're so depressing for the most part.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">But I especially dislike feeble-minded individuals.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, well...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">That's why I don't think I could ever be intimate with you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So... I guess she's saying I'm both depressing and stupid...?</thought> But I am certain you were very close with the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Say that all you like, but you still don't have any proof.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You and Mr. Corrida had an intimate relationship, did you not...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... A silly third-rate tabloid article. If you even had half your wits about you, you wouldn't believe such rubbish.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it seems quite a few people bought into this story.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Hmph. As to be expected in a world filled with crooks and liars.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Note to self: Stay on her good side.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">In any case, I despise interpersonal relationships like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... However... What if there was a need for you to get close to someone...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Me? Need to get close to Mr. Corrida? As if there was ever such a need.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Didn't you get close to Mr. Corrida for this person's sake...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...Do you really still not understand?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It's not in my nature to enjoy doing things for others.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But... You're a manager...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It's called a job. I am in charge of Mr. Engarde the star, not Matt Engarde the man.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">And you are not my client.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is this my subtle hint to "go home"...?</thought> But... I know you must have had a need to get close to the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Celeste Inpax, your mentor.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Why do you know about Celeste!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Inpax... She committed suicide, didn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But it looks like no one knows why. Right before her death, she was Juan Corrida's manager. So, I believe you got close to Mr. Corrida so you could find out more about her suicide.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...Y-You have a great imagination. You may have a future yet as a slimy muckraker for a putrid third-rate tabloid!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Ms. Andrews...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Th-There was no mystery surrounding her death. None. It would be pointless for me to force myself into a relationship for nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is that really true...? Was there really no mystery at all?</thought> I don't believe you were completely at ease with the way her suicide was resolved!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Get a hold of yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">If you want advice on doing yourself in, I suggest asking someone, like the police.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Which translates to... "Go take a long walk off a short pier"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ms. Inpax's suicide note was never found, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like the police were under the suspicion that someone had hidden it. Like maybe the person who discovered her body, Mr. Corrida.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">J... Juan?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And, Ms. Andrews, I believe you thought the same thing! That is why you became intimate with Mr. Corrida!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I-I've sat by quietly and listened to your insulting ramblings long enough!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It's true that Celeste was my mentor, however, allow me to say this again: It had nothing to do with me! I didn't even know that her suicide note was never found! I'm a person who doesn't care about what goes on in the lives of others!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's the impression you like to give, however...</thought> I don't think that's who you really are.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have evidence that says otherwise. This is proof that Celeste Inpax was someone very special to you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, how about it, Ms. Andrews?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I'm sure even those among your lawyer colleagues find it hard to hate you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">They probably pity you. After all, you are dangerously close to being a failure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Pity"...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Although, thanks to your little spectacle, I feel much better about myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sigh* This evidence isn't strong enough to give up the truth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...By now, even someone like you should understand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Andrews... You... You went through it too, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Went through what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A suicide.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Andrews, you look and act like a very strong woman who has it all together. You don't ask for anyone's help and you live by yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Y-Yes. I've been very independent ever since I can remember...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However, that is all just a lie. A faade.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've always searched out people on whom you can depend on.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Th-That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were dependent on Ms. Inpax, weren't you? Which is why... When she passed away, you lost everything you had.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">S-Stop!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... When Celeste passed away so suddenly like that... I died a death of my own. But... No matter how hard I tried, I couldn't stop thinking about what had become of her note.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You must have heard about the police report... The one that said the police suspected Mr. Corrida of hiding Ms. Inpax's note... You heard about it, and thought to recover it from him by getting close, am I right?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If that's the case, then everything changes.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What topic did we start this conversation on again?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It was "why was the victim killed"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. Somehow, Ms. Andrews... It seems that you have become the one most likely to want Mr. Corrida dead...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">M-Me...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Inpax was everything to you. ...And then she died. And you would do anything to find out why she killed herself. ...Even commit murder.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Murder...!?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It's true. I am a woman who can only live in insecurity. I'm physically small, and I don't really have a lot of self-confidence. I've pushed against all that, though... I've tried to live strongly. I never wanted anyone to find out the truth...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ms. Andrews...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">This one thing... It's the one thing I wanted to take with me to the grave... It was my secret. Mine and mine alone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">You probably think I'm a worthless human being right now, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please, Ms. Andrews. All I want to know is the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">After Celeste passed away, I heard that someone had hidden her suicide note... And that someone was Juan Corrida. Celeste... Without her... Without her, I became scared. Everything... Everyone seemed like they were out to get me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you got close to Mr. Corrida to recover her suicide note, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... Looks like that tabloid reported the truth after all. Ironic, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, like they say, where there's smoke, there's fire.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">And if they purposely add fuel to the fire, they keep the celebrity world burning.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">But as for the suicide note? I didn't and wouldn't kill anyone for it. It just doesn't suit me, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... Well, that's enough for now. I still have work to do, so...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Oh, I have one small favor to ask. My... attempted suicide... I'd like for you to keep it a secret.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ms. Andrews...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">If... If people found out about my weakness... I... I would sooner choose to die than live.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-A-Alright! I understand! We'll keep it a secret! <thought>Ms. Andrews... I guess she's the "always thinking" type... She never says anything carelessly, it seems...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Thank you very much.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick... Can I ask you something...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ms. Andrews has been playing with that card in her hand since a little while back...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That card...? Yeah, I guess she has...</thought> Ms. Andrews, what is that card you're holding...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Huh? O-Oh, this? I don't quite know. It just suddenly appeared in my handbag...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it? It looks like... A seashell?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">That's what it looks like, doesn't it? I honestly don't remember owning this card... I wonder where I picked it up from...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Her not remembering something clearly? Sounds like it would be a rare occurence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Well, I must be off. I leave Mr. Engarde in your "capable" hands.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I think we've gathered about all we can...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wh-What about Mystic Maya? Is she alright...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, Pearls... She looks so worn out by all this... She hasn't slept at all, and has been walking all over the place with me today...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What's wrong, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's go back to the office for a little while. You're really tired, right?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, no! I'm OK. Really! ... I'm fine. I really am.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You don't look fine to me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">There's no one here. Everyone's gone. I wonder if the three of them went to eat together!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I don't think they'd ever do that. They're probably in yet another meeting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Detective">"Can't dig through the cereal box... Can't dig for the prize... Will lose sight of the target and ruin the cereal..."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He must be doing image training for a stake-out.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So! What now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, we did find one thing out for sure. Ms. Andrews has a motive.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You mean Ms. Inpax's suicide note...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. She was also the one to discover the victim's body. Clever...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah! Mr. Nick! The transceiver!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hello!? This is the law office of Wright &amp; Co!</line>
<line speaker="???">...Mr. Attorney, you're not answering a phone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maya! Where's Maya!?</line>
<line speaker="???">As I promised, I have not come within a few feet of her this whole time.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Phew...</line>
<line speaker="???">...Which is why, I suppose, she is absolutely famished.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="???">So I suggest you win a quick acquittal, my friend. At any cost. Wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait! Maya! Let me hear her!</line>
<line speaker="???">...Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Ask my...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya! Is that you!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Sis... Ask my sis!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya! Maya! ...Dammit! He cut me off!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mystic Maya said, "Ask my sis," didn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Sis"...? What does she mean by that...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, s-sorry... ...Ack!! Mia!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I have a message from Maya, so come, ask me anything you want about her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's going on with Maya is the most important thing right now! I should talk with Mia...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How's Maya!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">She's safe... for now. That kidnapper is one to keep his word, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm glad to hear she's safe... But Mia, how did you know...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">As soon as she was locked up, Maya called for me. I read the note she left... Then I gathered as much information about her surroundings as I could.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I didn't know you could use spirit channeling like this... Pretty smart of her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The kidnapper! What's he like!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I don't know... Apparently, Maya went to answer a phone call at the hotel and was drugged there...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">She didn't see the face of her attacker.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Sorry, but I don't have time to answer your questions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah... And we should be worrying about Maya right now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Maya is locked up in a very dark place right now. I'll tell you everything I heard when I was with her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When you were with her...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nnngh... I'm starving... I could really go for some apple pie... I mean, at a time like this, sweets are the only way to go! I have to stay positive! He promised he wasn't going to kill me! I'm not going to die! <thought>Sis... I wonder if you're with Nick right now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's this...? It feels like there are a lot of glass bottles here. And these... They feel like barrels. I'll pass... Too bad I'm really hungry, and not really thirsty.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's all sorts of things piled up here... But it's too dark to see.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Drat, it's locked. <thought>Hmm, but this door's lock seems easy enough to open...</thought> On TV, the hero always uses a plastic card or a stiff piece of cardboard... ...Then "click", they magically open the door. <thought>I wonder if there's a card like that around here I could use...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Someone dropped a card here... It kinda looks like... a business card... But there's no name on it. Hmm... It's a picture of a seashell, I think... What a strange card.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can't see very well in this darkness, but it doesn't seem like there's anything there...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If I don't do something to the door first, I don't think I'll be "moving" anywhere...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! That's it! This shell card! If I use this, maybe I can get the door open! This might be my key out of here! I had a feeling this card might be useful... I'm such a genius! Alright. Now if you'll excuse me, Mr. Kidnapper...</line>
<line speaker="Maya"><thought>I did it!</thought> OK... Now I'm getting the heck out of here! <thought>I shouldn't keep Nick waiting... Or worried.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think I have enough evidence yet... I should investigate and gather some more clues before I try again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nnrgh! I've made too many mistakes!</thought></line>
</xml>