<xml>
<title>Farewell, My Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wha...!? What have I done wrong!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...? B-But I'm just a simple defense attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Phone">... ...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hello, this is Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">You don't look so well, dude. You're gonna prove me not guilty today, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Hahaha... If you please, Mister Lawyer. Remember, it's not just me. Your precious friend's life is riding on today's verdict too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Grr...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now listen up! You'd better get Engarde a guilty sentence, OK!? If you get that creepy slimebag a not guilty, I'll never forgive you, ever!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Maya...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Phoenix... Phoenix!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mia! Maya! How's Maya!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...I don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't know...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">She hasn't tried to channel me since yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia... What... What am I supposed to do...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... Well, like I said. For a lawyer, the worst of times are when you have to force your biggest smiles.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You can't give up! There's still some hope left.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Stop it, please! There's nothing left... Not here, not anywhere...</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! It's that accursed Engarde again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WILL YOU LEAVE ME ALONE!? Look, don't call me anymore! I mean it!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">......You're really mean, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaah! Gumshoe! I'm really, really sorry! Where are you?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">They let me join the investigation team and we're chasing after De Killer, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! Then, you have some sort of lead...!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry, but right now we've got zero leads on the guy... But we're not going to give up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gumshoe...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Until the trial is over... until the verdict is handed down, we're going to do everything we can and find De Killer! If we can get Maya out, then you can get Engarde the guilty verdict he deserves, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's true, I could do that if they found Maya first...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You got that!? So you have to do whatever you can to make the trial last longer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have to make the trial last longer?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If you go at Mr. Edgeworth with everything you've got, then you two can draw it out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, now I get it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I believe in you, pal! You and Mr. Edgeworth can do it! So! Believe in us! We're going to give it all we've got, just like you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it! Thanks Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...Hey, Phoenix. You understand now, don't you? You have something money will never be able to buy. Friendship. It's the strongest weapon in the world and you have it in abundance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah! <thought>Looks like we're coming to the end... I have to make the trial last as long as I can! Gumshoe will come through, I know it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Matt Engarde.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution has been ready for a while, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, as I recall, we concluded yesterday's session with a big mystery on our hands. The mystery being what exactly was Ms. Adrian Andrews' role in this murder? That is to say, is she really connected to the crime itself? Mr. Edgeworth, if you would please inform the court of today's proceedings.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Adrian Andrews. She forged evidence that threw suspicion onto Mr. Engarde, and then proceeded to escape the crime scene by wearing a Nickel Samurai costume. The guilt of these actions are those from which she cannot escape.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, then you're saying that she is guilty after all...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm not finished, Your Honor. Ms. Andrews has nothing to do with committing the actual murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I would like to direct the court's attention to this card.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is that...? It looks like a shell...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the calling card of a certain assassin.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-Assassin, you say!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, Juan Corrida was killed by a professional assassin! And the person who hired the assassin, his client so to speak, is Matt Engarde!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What a surprising turn of events!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I would think it's become commonplace by now, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I know what's going on this time... So I know that everything Edgeworth has said is true...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">But we still have to hold out as long as we can. At least, until Maya's safe and sound.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder how the trial will turn out today...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, please call your first witness, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution calls the defendant's "mentor", Mr. Will Powers to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, witness. Your name and occupation, please.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">O-OK. I'm... Uh... Will Powers. I'm a poor, underpaid action star...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what is your relation to the defendant?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Well, that's... I guess I'm sort of a lousy mentor to him in a way. Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Um, Mr. Powers. Please... You don't need to put yourself down so much.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Oh, uh, sorry. Well, but I'm just kind of a nothing sort of guy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">On the night of the murder, you visited the defendant's room. Is this correct?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Y-Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>I... I didn't know that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">Um, but you know... I didn't actually get to see Matt when I went...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">All you need to do is answer what you're asked. Now then, I would like you to please testify about when you went to Mr. Engarde's room.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">O-OK... Sure...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">After the award ceremony, I went by myself to Matt's room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Nothing sounds out of place in Mr. Powers' testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And talking with the bellboy is no big deal...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If one assumes that the person Mr. Engarde was speaking with was an ordinary bellboy...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What are you implying?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, Mr. Wright. Let's have your cross-examination, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Looks like we're in another sticky situation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">A trap. Can't you smell it, Phoenix? But for us to find out more, we're just going to have to charge in head first, right?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">After the award ceremony, I went by myself to Matt's room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defendant's room? Why did you go there?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Well, I'm his mentor, like a big brother sort of, and I wanted to say congrats... ... ...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's wrong? Why did you stop?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">M-M-Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-Wh-What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">You... You're going to try to trick me into a corner, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I... I know I'm just a poor, underpaid action star, but... But... I... I'm not the killer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, no one said you were, Mr. Powers.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">No, please! Don't trick me! Every time you do your lawyer thing, the witness suddenly turns into the bad guy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Every time"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Witness. I will personally talk to the defense at a later time. So for now, please kindly cooperate and continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">S-Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, you went to the defendant's room. And then?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey, wait a minute! When and how did I suddenly turn into the bad guy here??</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">Matt was standing there in front of his room, still in his Nickel Samurai costume.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure that was Matt Engarde?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah, I'm sure. He wasn't wearing the Nickel Samurai mask then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If that's the case, then he really can't be mistaken...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And? What was the defendant doing, standing in front of his own room?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">He was talking with someone. At first, I thought it was the bellboy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"At first"? What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Well, he was in a bellboy-ish uniform and he had a bottle of juice on a tray.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Sounds like an ordinary bellboy to me.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Um, yeah, but... I didn't think he was a normal bellboy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And why was that?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Um... Why did I think that, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-How am I supposed to know!?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Sorry, but I can't remember right now. ...Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I'm going to have to wait patiently on this one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"At first"? What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I didn't think he was a normal bellboy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And why was that?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Um... Why did I think that, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-How am I supposed to know!? <thought>...Hey, wait a second...</thought> Actually, Mr. Powers, only a few minutes ago, you stated:</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Um... You know, I did feel something weird. I think it was because Matt... Well, he gave the bellboy a tip.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could it be that you felt something "strange" about the tip-giving incident itself...?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">... AH! Yeah! That's it! You really know your job!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This bellboy... He wasn't an ordinary one, was he...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps we should let the witness tell us.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Mr. Powers. Please amend your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">You mean about the bellboy, right?</line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"He was talking with someone. At first, I thought it was the bellboy." to "Matt gave the bellboy a tip."</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Matt gave the bellboy a tip.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So he gave the bellboy a tip. What's so strange about that?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ah, well, you see, Matt's not a poor penny-pincher like me. I was trying to figure out how much it was because the tip really shocked me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"How much it was"...?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">But that's when something even more surprising happened! The bellboy was putting the tip he got in his pocket. And that's when I got my first good look at the guy's face... I was really shocked!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I'm afraid I don't follow at all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It sounds like Mr. Powers was surprised twice by this event. I wonder which of his shocking moments I should ask about...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was so shocking about the bellboy's face, Mr. Powers?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Well, he wasn't exactly a "boy"... more like an old "gramps"...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem! I hope you know that discrimination towards old men is a no-no in my court!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">No, no, that's not what I meant at all! In the smack middle of the guy's face, there was a line of stitches!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A line of stitches...?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah! And it went straight from the tippy top of his head to the bottom of his chin! Almost like if that thread snapped, all the stuff in his head would come spilling out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Ah! <thought>He was there... At Engarde's house... He was that BUTLER!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Ah, nothing, Your Honor! <thought>So that means Engarde was talking with De Killer then. If that fact were to be exposed, Engarde would be declared guilty in a blink!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix, you have to play dumb here! Pretend you don't know anything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Chief!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You sure you don't have something you would like to say, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Umm... What did you just say, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Nothing, Mr. Wright. Nothing. We're just going around and around in circles. Now then, Mr. Powers. Please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I watched the two of them for a while, but then I gave up and went back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You saw the two of them, the bellboy and the defendant, together, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah. The bellboy just wanted to say congrats.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, while you were watching the two of them, did you notice anything strange?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Um... You know, I did feel something weird. I think it was because Matt... Well, he gave the bellboy a tip.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A tip? <thought>But that's a perfectly normal thing to do...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, how long did you watch the two of them?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ah, not more than a minute or two, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I had guests with me that night, and I couldn't make them wait for me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So who are these "guests" you're talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">You guys, of course. You and Maya and little Pearl. I thought it would be really rude since I invited you guys, if I disappeared on you... So I went back to my seat pretty soon after seeing Matt in the hallway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is like squeezing water from a stone... It's probably pointless to press further...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Do you remember this incident? Did Mr. Powers leave his seat that night?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't remember that happening at all. Maya was making such a racket in her hyper state... I ended up focusing on her.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...I see. In any case, from his story, he probably wasn't gone for very long.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defendant is a huge star. He can afford to give generous tips, wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Um, sure. But giving him that much was maybe a little too much, I think...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"A little too much"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Would you please clarify for the court, about how much would you say the defendant gave to the bellboy?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Honestly, I don't know. I can't even begin to guess.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And why is that?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Because he gave the bellboy a really, really fat roll of cash.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A ROLL OF CASH!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, well... How interesting... That certainly was a very generous tip, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A very fat roll of cash... That can hardly be called a "tip", Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The judge is beginning to look awfully suspicious of us...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defendant is a superstar! That kind of tip is typical fare for people like him!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you saying that all superstars are super-spenders!? If I could receive large rolls of cash by simply bringing people things on trays... Then why on Earth would I stand around here prosecuting!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's got a point... I don't even get paid, let alone rolls of cash for all my hard work.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's nothing I can really object to here. I mean, who can argue that a fat roll of money isn't really odd...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, so supposing that roll of cash was not a tip... Then what was it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Payment, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Payment...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Isn't it obvious? For the murder of Mr. Juan Corrida.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then... Then the bellboy the witness saw...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, he was the assassin.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">H-Hold your horses now! Mr. Edgeworth, you don't have any proof of this... do you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Have I ever been unprepared to support my claims, Your Honor? I have here, the card Shelly de Killer left at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Shelly... de Killer...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He is the person the police's special investigations team has been chasing for ages. I am certain that the person the witness saw was this very assassin, Shelly de Killer!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">R-Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? What's wrong, Mr. Powers?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">No, nothing. Something just clicked in my head and I think I just figured something out!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Actually, I saw that bellboy again later on that night!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAAAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Powers! Please testify! Tell us what you saw!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yes, sir! Right away!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">This time, I was in that hallway because I had to go to the bathroom!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thank you very much. That is all we need for now.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Huh? But I'm not done. There's still more...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let us first establish that the bellboy was truly Mr. de Killer. Then we shall see.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So the bellboy came out of the victim's room... And if that bellboy really was the assassin... Then, I think the answer is fairly obvious.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That would be correct, Your Honor. Well, Mr. Wright. I believe it's your turn... to entertain and make us laugh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha. Ha. Ha. Ha.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">This is no laughing matter!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">This time, I was in that hallway because I had to go to the bathroom!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what time was it?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ah, well, I don't remember. The award ceremony ended around 8 PM, right? ...And I went to Matt's room pretty soon after that... And then I came back... And then I went to the bathroom... ... So I guess maybe it was around 8:10 PM by that time?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're not one for details, are you Mr. Powers?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">S-Sorry... I thought I could maybe catch Matt and say my congrats...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">And that's when that bellboy I saw earlier came out of the room!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure it was the same bellboy?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And how could you tell? All the bellboys wear the same uniform, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">But, you see... Well, he had those stitches in his face.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">So I'm sure it's the same guy that was talking with Matt.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So which room did the bellboy come out of?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Of course, when I say "room", I mean Juan Corrida's room!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim's room, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah. The one with all the really pretty flowers and teddy bears. It was Juan's room alright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Words cannot describe how screwed I am...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Let's continue with the testimony, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Now that I think about it, that bellboy did seem kinda out of place!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... so what exactly was so "out of place" about him?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright, Wright, Wright. Why the insipid grin?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe because I have no idea what damaging thing he's going to say next...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">Um, well, the bellboy was empty-handed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Empty-handed?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">That bellboy was one of those room-service people, right? But he wasn't pushing a cart and he wasn't holding a tray either! You'd call that "a little strange" too, wouldn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I agree that it is a bit strange, Mr. Powers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But is it really that unusual for a bellboy to be empty-handed? What I should I do? Should I let Mr. Powers' testimony slide or...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're right. I think it's pretty unusual too.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ah, I thought you might think so!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. There's no need to say anything when the defense gives up without a fight. Let's move on.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Anyway, Mr. Powers. You thought the bellboy was a little suspicious, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is nothing strange or unusual about an empty-handed bellboy!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">But there really, really is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There really, really isn't!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you two are done being schoolchildren... Bellboys are for room service. There is no reason for them to be empty-handed, ever. Your Honor! I ask that the witness' previous statement be supplanted with this new one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grr... Edgeworth... Are you going to do whatever you can to make the bellboy look suspicious?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Very well, this court recognizes and grants the prosecution's request. Mr. Powers, if you could amend your testimony, please.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Y-Yes, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"Now that I think about it, that bellboy did seem kinda out of place!" to "I thought it was kinda strange for a bellboy to come out of a guest's room empty-handed!"</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I thought it was kinda strange for a bellboy to come out of a guest's room empty-handed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you're saying that it's suspicious for him to be empty-handed?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah, really suspicious. I mean, when I first saw that bellboy, he was holding a tray in his hand! And there was a bottle of juice and a wine glass on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Juice...? What kind of juice was it?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Um, I'm pretty sure it was tomato juice...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">If we could come up with some sort of reason as to why he would come out empty-handed, some sort of proof, then I think we can dodge the bullet on this one for now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Proof, huh? <thought>Sounds like another job for the Court Record!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah! So he had to be the assassin! I'm sure of it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please don't be so quick to judge!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ah, but it's kind of a Powers family thing. "Think of every person as a thief".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I guess a thief and an assassin are both sneaky and silent...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's not the point, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">In any case, if that bellboy was the assassin, it would be very bad for us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... he really is the assassin, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes... But. You can't give in yet. If you want to prolong this trial for as long as possible, you're going to have to pull some cheap tricks on this one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Powers.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Y-Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're easily influenced by other people's words, aren't you? As soon as you heard that the bellboy might have been the killer, you got caught up in believing it must be true.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">But... But... Isn't he really suspicious!?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">He's got all those stitches, and... and...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So? A baseball has stitches! Are you saying all baseballs are suspicious because they have stitches!?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">*gulp!* Well, there's also... I mean, what about him being empty-handed!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I would like to ask the court to please take a look here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is... the crime scene...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is a wine glass sitting next to Mr. Corrida's body. The liquid inside this glass is tomato juice. And now, if you would look at what is on top of the table in the lower right corner here... Anyone can clearly see that it is a tray with a bottle of tomato juice on it! The bellboy had just brought this to Mr. Corrida's room. He left the tray in the room, which is why he was empty-handed when he left!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Aah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But! That would mean that the bellboy had seen and left a dead body in the room!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, but can you prove that Mr. Corrida was already dead at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... M-Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I blame you for leading me down this route!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh heh heh. I'm terribly sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is with him? Why is he laughing??</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Witness. Isn't there one more thing you would like to share with us?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I-Is there?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The bellboy was empty-handed... Or should I say empty-"hand"ed? I recall you had something interesting to say about his hands...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Oh yeah! I almost forgot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Wh-What...?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">That bellboy -- he was wearing gloves!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gloves?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah, pitch black, leather ones. All the other bellboys don't wear gloves like that, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Black leather gloves... Why didn't you mention them earlier!?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">S-Sorry... It slipped my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! Boy does this make the bellboy look really suspicious... Alright, got to focus. I can't get lax here!</thought> So what if he had gloves? A lot of bellboys wear gloves!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Come on, Mr. Wright! That bellboy was wearing black leather ones!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So? A football is made of leather! Are you saying all footballs are suspicious because they are made of leather!?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">*gulp!*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But that man... He received a large roll of cash from the defendant. And then he was seen leaving the crime scene wearing black leather gloves. I don't think that even someone like myself can believe he was just another bellboy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urgh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems that we have finally come to an understanding... Now then, witness. Please continue with the rest of your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The rest...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh yes, please tell us more.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">OK!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">After leaving Juan's room, the bellboy went and knocked on Matt's door, just like that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So the bellboy, after leaving the crime scene, next went to the defendant's room...?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah. I kinda saw all that by accident...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Some accident! I'd say you saw too much! And all of it was suspicious to high heaven...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I think it's safe to say that we can no longer consider this bellboy to be "normal". Now then, let's get started, shall we? Mr. Wright, your cross-examination, please.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">After leaving Juan's room, the bellboy went and knocked on Matt's door, just like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that what you saw while you were busy spying?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">E-Excuse me!? I may be a poor, underpaid action star, but even I wouldn't stoop to spying!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I think the point is where did you watch all this from, Mr. Powers?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Oh, um, from the door of the bathroom with my left eye, in a sort of sneaky, spy-like...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I knew he was spying!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please, does it really matter if he was doing it over or underhandedly? What did the bellboy do next? That's all I care to know.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">He gave something to the person inside the room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I said, "<cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn>"</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Umm... OK.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's better! *ahem* What kind of statement is that!? Please elaborate and give us a few more details!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Oh, umm... OK...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, I should probably ask him only one question at a time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So who took this "something" the bellboy handed off?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Um, actually, I don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I'm sorry, but I only saw the person's arm.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Only an arm...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then you're saying you didn't see the person's face?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, it was Mr. Engarde's room, correct? So it could have only been Mr. Engarde himself, I'd say.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And then? What did the bellboy do after that?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Oh, so after he gave the person inside the room the thing...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He gave "something" to this person?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what was this "something"?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Hah hah hah. If I remembered what it was, I wouldn't be calling it a "something", would I?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But this implies that something was removed from the scene of the crime! Are you sure you really can't remember, Mr. Powers?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Umm... I think it was something kinda small...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is an incredibly crucial piece of information. Please, try to remember what it was.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Umm... I'll try...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In the meantime, let's talk of another point. Namely, what the bellboy did next.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Oh, so after he gave the person inside the room the thing...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think I can find out much more from Mr. Powers... I should probably move on to a different topic...</thought> So what did the bellboy do after that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I would like to summarize the testimony up to this point, if you don't mind. When the bellboy left the crime scene, he immediately went to the defendant's room. There, he handed a small item of some sort to the person inside. As for the person who received the item, all you could see was the person's arm...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yes, yes! It was just like that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth. Is all this really that important?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course, Your Honor. I think this is of the utmost importance. This is when whatever was removed from the crime scene was handed over to the client!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Mr. Powers, please, try to remember what it was the bellboy handed off.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Um... Well, let's see... Hmm... I think it was... No...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you remember, please add it to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Y-Yes, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"If I saw it again, I could say for sure, but I think it was some sort of wooden statue."</line>
<line speaker="Powers">If I saw it again, I could say for sure, but I think it was some sort of wooden statue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A statue?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah... It kinda looked like one I guess. If I saw the actual thing again, I'd probably remember, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like for this trial to proceed... I'm going to have to come up with whatever this "statue" thing is and show it to him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You're going to have to trust your instinct on this one and take a chance, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well Mr. Powers, let's continue with your testimony. What did the bellboy do after that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Powers">Then the old guy just left, without even going into the room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Where did this bellboy go after he left Mr. Engarde's room?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Hmm... He opened the door to Viola Hall, went in there, and who knows after that, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nngh... I do...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">After that, I went to the bathroom and then back to my seat.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you see anything strange, suspicious, or just out of the ordinary at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Oh yeah, I saw that one thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!? <thought>He saw something else!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">There was this jittery alien with a ray gun... It was watching Juan's door like some sort of stalker.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Um, I think we can forget about the alien...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Mr. Powers' testimony just now was just as vague as his first.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's a little troublesome, isn't it? But I'm sure if you press him enough, everything will become clearer. Although, that just makes it harder on us, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh... Talk about a lose-lose situation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What was the point of that pregnant pause!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Where did that objection come from!? Well, speak up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, it was me, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What is it, Phoenix?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have a feeling that something bad is going to happen once I show this...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! If you have something to say, please spit it out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor. <thought>OK Phoenix, deep breath...</thought> Mr. Powers. The "something" you saw... Was it this item?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Oh, hey! That's it! That's the something! Wow, Mr. Wright. You really figured it out.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm, I recall we found this at Matt Engarde's mansion...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">At the d-defendant's house!? What does this mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's simple, Your Honor. Shelly de Killer assassinated Juan Corrida in his room. And then he stole this wooden bear from the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then, the bear being found at Mr. Engarde's mansion would mean...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It goes without saying, Your Honor. Mr. Matt Engarde is De Killer's client!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! ...I said ORDER!!! Mr. Wright. This is a most unfortunate turn of events for you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... Sorry, Mia.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">No, it's alright. Your judgment was sound. Actually, I figured the bear would come up. If not now, then it would have later on. Even if you hadn't shown it to the court, I'm sure your friend Edgeworth would've.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ah, I almost forgot that he knew about it too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I think it is clear that there is no need for us to continue this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I... I can't let this happen! I have to do something... There has to be something we've overlooked!</thought> Your Honor! A minute, please!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are still a few points left that we have not fully explored!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What are you trying to pull!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh... Well, we can't have that. Alright, Mr. Wright. What questionable point would you like to explore further?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Powers' testimony, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Huh? I know that my testimony was kind of shaky, but --</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your inanity stupefies me, Mr. Wright. We have already clarified all questionable points during the cross-examination just now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wasting time like this, calling the testimony questionable... I'd say it's your head that's questionable here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I agree. The cross-examination went smoothly and there was nothing wrong with the testimony. Now then, I belive --</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Please! Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You are being very persistent today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Because I can't let it end like this!</thought> I know my outburst just now was a little... questionable.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Questionable indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But! There really are some questionable points left to discuss, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was one thing in Mr. Powers' testimony that was very unclear. And that is the identity of the person who received the bear!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">He gave something to the person inside the room.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I'm sorry, but I only saw the person's arm.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As long as we don't know who it was that took the bear, we can't be sure of...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Aaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">...............?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What is it, Mr. Powers!? If you're going to scream like that, then at least give us a good reason why!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">O-Oh, yeah... Sorry. Actually... So... I remembered. Um... I remembered who took the bear...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wha--!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I mean, I only saw his arm... But... But... The arm... It was the Nickel Samurai's arm! I swear it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you sure of that, Mr. Powers!?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah! I'm sure it was the Nickel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! It looks like you've dug your own grave... yet again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How many times is that today? ...I've lost count...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So the person who took in this little bear was the Nickel Samurai. And, as we all know, Matt Engarde is the Nickel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thanks to the defense, we've made that all the clearer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What am I supposed to do now!? Mia, help!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You don't have time to act lost. You've got to find another angle to attack this from! Hurry!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, I will bring this cross-examination to --</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Again, Mr. Wright? We've already removed any and all questionable areas of this testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's about time you were removed from this court, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to find something... Even one more little point will do!</thought> There are... There are still questions left unanswered!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think it's fairly obvious that the bear itself is very questionable!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The bear... Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This was found at Mr. Engarde's mansion. However, Mr. Engarde was arrested at the hotel that night! Which means that since the murder occurred, he has not had a chance to go home!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think Your Honor has already figured out what I'm trying to say. It is not possible that it was Mr. Engarde who took this bear to his mansion!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Why, that's very true! We didn't consider that point, Mr. Wright! There was no way, timewise, for the defendant to have taken this bear home.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">(Phew... Disaster averted it looks--</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You haven't gotten the best of me yet, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I remember it clear as day. I remember what you muttered to yourself at Engarde's mansion.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We have this area completely surrounded. There is no way for him to escape.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't believe it... That butler... All this time, he was De Killer...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">De Killer and Engarde were working together, so to speak.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">And De Killer was hiding at Engarde Mansion... as its butler.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What a... bold move...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The bear figurine was brought back to Engarde Mansion by De Killer himself. When it looked like he was about to be arrested, Engarde had him do so. I assume because it would've been bad had the police found it during their investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, Mr. Wright? You've been quiet for a while now...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is too much! Isn't there anything I can attack at all?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to try... I have to find something else!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What will you do now, Mr. Wright? Do you plan to...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I plan to expose a clearly shaky place in Mr. Powers' testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What!? There is still another one!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is indeed, Your Honor. And it's quite a questionable point!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think we've heard enough. We now know why this bear figurine was at the defendant's mansion, as well as who it was that received the bear from the assassin in his room... Everything has become very clear. The client who hired the assassin to commit the murder was Mr. Matt Engarde! ... I see no reason for this trial to continue. Therefore, I will now hand down my verdict!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thank you, Your Honor, for your understanding. You see, Mr. Wright? You could not win against the truth, could you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>I knew it would turn out this way... After all, what Edgeworth has stated is the truth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Any last objections, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, do I...? What should I do...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... The defense... rests--</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix. Are you giving up? If you do... Maya will die.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">And you'll carry that weight on your shoulders every day for the rest of your life. I don't want that to happen to you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Raise an objection, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...............</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I will now announce my ver--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There is only one way for me to drag this trial out... The only thing I have left is this one dirty trick...</thought> Your Honor. Right now, we have these two reasons to believe my client is a client of the assassin. Reason number one. He accepted the bear figurine from the assassin. Reason number two. That very same figurine was found at Engarde Mansion. However! It's possible this is all the work of a certain other person!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What are you saying...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What I am saying is, it's possible a different person is De Killer's real client!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The "real" client...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tsk, tsk. Is this all you have?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Wright. Let's hear your theory. Who do you say is the real client of De Killer, and therefore, the real murderer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You've let me down, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know you are aware of the truth. And you are free to turn your eyes from it... But at least try to make some sense while you are doing so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'll give you another chance. Don't squander it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Adrian Andrews...!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. We already know that she tried to frame Matt Engarde for the crime... By wearing a spare Nickel Samurai costume!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ah! Then... Then the "Nickel Samurai's arm" that I saw...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That could have very well been Ms. Andrews!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But what about Mr. Engarde?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you would please recall yesterday's testimony, the defendant was taking a nap during the break period.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's right... Then... finding this figure at Mr. Engarde's mansion...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was a well-laid trap set by Ms. Andrews.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth... What is your opinion on this?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I can't even begin to count the flaws in the defense's logic. Besides which, there is no evidence to support it. However... I can't fully discount its possibility either.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is to save Maya... This is to save Maya... Even if the whole world turns against me, this is one fight I can't give up on!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! All disruptive parties will be forced to leave the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor. ... For the benefit of the defense, I'm willing to play along with his "what if" game.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">His "what if" game, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution is prepared to challenge the defense's theory.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Wright. Even you must have thought it strange and wondered, "Why would the criminal want this little wooden bear...?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's right... De Killer did specially bring that bear to Engarde right away...</thought> Why do you ask? Is there something special about it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Absolutely. And I'm sure that once the court knows its significance, the true killer's identity will become crystal clear. Your Honor! The prosecution calls upon a witness who will clear all doubts against Ms. Andrews.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And who would that be!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's quite simple, Your Honor. Ms. Adrian Andrews herself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... Well then, the court will take a short 10 minute recess. The prosecution will prepare its witness in that time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Hahaha... Oh, I knew it was a good idea to hold her hostage. Don't you agree, Mister Lawyer...? But I never thought in your desperation, you'd try to pin the guilt onto Adrian!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Aaaargh! I swear this demon will pay...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Pearls? Where's Mia?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... don't know... A really strong power suddenly called her away...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A really strong power...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phone">...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, Mr. Nick! Your phone is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's from Gumshoe!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">How is it going!? Have you been hanging in there, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, sort of... We just barely found something to latch onto.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Phew. That's good, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what about you!? Anything yet!? Have you figured out where De Killer and Maya are!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, uh... We still don't have any leads, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAT!? We don't have any more time!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If we just had one! Even a single clue would be really helpful...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I was only able to come this far because I kept thinking to myself... I've got to keep the trial going until Maya's been rescued... But have I just run out of luck this time...? Is all our hope for naught...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? A tent!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mia!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It looks like Maya was unconscious until just a few minutes ago. As soon as she woke up, she called for me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So it was Maya that called you away!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">She's locked in a dusty little room right now. But I could see a circus tent outside the window about 300 feet away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gumshoe! Is there a circus in town right now!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's only one, pal! The Berry Big Circus!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya is somewhere within a 300 feet radius of the main tent!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What!? ... OK, hold on a sec, pal! Hey! Draw a circle on that map! About a 300 feet radius from the main tent! Hurry!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">And...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I could see a mailbox under the window.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gumshoe! There's also a mailbox!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm... OK! What else?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What else, Mia!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I'm sorry, but it was a very small window. I couldn't see anything else... It felt like I was in an old office building... Maybe the third floor or so...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I heard her! An old office building. Good stuff, pal! OK, just hang in there! Just a little longer, pal! Wish us luck!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good luck!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'll call you later, so don't let your battery die, OK pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia! Maya's not hurt, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">She's in a pretty bad state, Phoenix. She's being starved.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gumshoe! Please hurry!!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Looks like we're out of time. Are you alright, Phoenix?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's only a matter of time before Maya's rescued... I can do this! I just have to make this trial last a little longer!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court will now reconvene.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">De Killer, the man who murdered the victim, handed this to his client. From this, one obvious question arises. "Why this particular item?" I believe the answer to that question will provide us with the name of the real criminal. Now then, the prosecution calls the defendant's manager, Adrian Andrews, to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Currently, the witness is accused of tampering and obstruction of justice.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, you have been called to the witness stand today to ascertain... who exactly is guilty of murder.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very good. Now, have you ever seen this bear before, Ms. Andrews?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Of course I have.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You have seen it before?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's right. It's only natural that the witness has. Ms. Andrews. Could you please enlighten the court to this bear's secrets?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Alright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why... Why does she...??</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Actually, this is an elaborate puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So this figurine... it's a container of sorts, is it...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes. Looks can be deceiving, wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes. This is superb craftmanship. ...Oh, yes, I nearly forgot. You may begin your cross-examination, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It looks like there really was something to that bear after all.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Actually, this is an elaborate puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A puzzle?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... But it looks like an ordinary figurine...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>True enough... To people who don't know, I'm sure they would never guess that this was a puzzle...</thought> So what kind of puzzle is this exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">If you know the correct order, it can be taken apart one piece at a time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you can "take it apart"? And how would one go about doing that?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Well, you first turn its tail to the right and then push it in.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Oh, yes, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">After that, the arms and legs are free to move and can be removed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ooh... This is most interesting...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A boy and his new toy... It's like he's 5 all over again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">......... ......... ......... ...Oh, don't mind me. Go ahead and carry on.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think he's lost it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So what do you find after you take the puzzle apart?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">At its center is a small cavity, with just enough room to store a small item.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And how do you know about this...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I know because I was the one who bought it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It was a souvenir from when a friend and I went to Switzerland.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then, this... this was a present from you!?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">That's right. It was a puzzle in the shape of a bear, so I thought it would be perfect for Juan.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So it was a present from Ms. Andrews...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Witness, let's continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Because of its complexity, if you don't know the order, you can't open the bear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So who exactly knew how to solve this puzzle?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Only the two of us, Juan and myself. It was a souvenir from Switzerland... So I doubt there are that many people with this same bear in this country.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But this looks like it can be easily broken. Especially if someone wanted to get what was inside.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Well, it's a toy. But it can never be the same again once it's been broken.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">You really can't tell that it's a small "jewelry box" just by looking at it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who else knows that this bear is actually a small container or "jewelry box"?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I never told anyone. And as long as Juan never told anyone either, then only the two of us knew...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The two of you, huh... Then of course that means Mr. Engarde didn't know, right?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">We don't know anything about this figurine. So we should try to find out more for now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I'll keep pressing her for more information.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think this is about all I'm going to get for now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, Mr. Wright? I think even you have come to realize...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That there is one very important fact we have uncovered, and that is this: This bear is actually a "jewelry box".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now that we have agreed to this point, there is only one logical question that can come next. And that is this: What is inside this box?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's inside!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's right. That's what we are going to find out next. Witness.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You are the only one who can open this. Please...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's a painful silence hanging over the courtroom... All eyes are on Ms. Andrews now as she solves the puzzle, and takes the bear apart...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I've opened it. Is this what you wanted?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What is that? It looks like a... note...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't think we need to guess at what that is... Do we, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the suicide note.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The suicide note?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The suicide note left by Juan Corrida's former manager, Celeste Inpax. Until now, no one knew of its whereabouts... But just as we suspected, it was hidden. Hidden by the victim, Juan Corrida himself. It seems Celeste Inpax had very beautiful handwriting. And she just as beautifully signed her own name on this document. This is most definitely the note she left right before she committed suicide!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-ORDER! Witness! Did you know about this...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...Yes, I did. I heard all about it from Juan. When I discovered his body... I looked for the bear. I wanted to destroy the note before it became public. But... I couldn't find it anywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Because it had already been taken by De Killer.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Everything is going at Mr. Edgeworth's pace... So now that the suicide note has been found, what's the next logical question?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"What is written on the note...?"</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's right... At least, that's what I would think...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, I believe it is only appropriate the contents of this note be made known.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I can't stop you, can I...? I went through so much... just to get my hands on it. And I was going to burn it... for her sake.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm deeply sorry, but I can't allow you to persuade me to stop. Your Honor. If you could please read the contents of this note aloud.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The judge's voice rang loud and clear though the dead silent courtroom... In her note, Celeste Inpax left to us a record of all that had happened to her... About being used and then thrown away by Engarde... About being engaged to Corrida, and Engarde's role in destroying that... And about how she decided, in her despair, to end it all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... And that's all Ms. Inpax had to say.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is one thing I would like to say here. The prosecution has no interest in slandering Mr. Engarde.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then... What...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Our intention, Your Honor, is to establish a motive for murder. Isn't that correct, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes... On the night of the murder, Juan was going to make the contents of the note public. After the post-ceremony show... he was going to hold a press conference.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">My word...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Matt Engarde values above all else, his "refreshing like a spring breeze" image. Which is why he had to stop this note from being made public... At any cost!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is no margin for doubt here. Mr. de Killer's client's goal was to obtain this suicide note. And the only person who needed this note that badly is the defendant. Let's not forget that the bear with the note inside was found at the defendant's house!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems that we have come to the truth at last. The defendant's motives were entirely selfish. He deserves no sympathy from anyone!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk... <thought>How am I supposed to escape from this one!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Why the hesitation, Phoenix? Gumshoe hasn't called yet, so you know what you must do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I know. I have to carry on and buy him some more time! OK. There are 2 deadly pieces of evidence: the figurine and the suicide note. Maybe somehow, I can find a way out of this situation through one of those!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">The gavel is already in the judge's hand! Phoenix! Hurry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The suicide note or the figurine!? Which one of these should I pursue??</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please wait, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think Your Honor believes that Matt Engarde killed in order to obtain this note.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, that is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that seems a little strange. In fact, I think there is a contradiction here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This note was hidden by Mr. Corrida until the night of the murder. If that is the case... I say that Matt Engarde could not have known what was written on this note!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! I didn't think of it that way...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. But I did think of it that way, and I thought it was rather strange. No one in their right mind would kill for a note without first knowing what it said!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please wait, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The assassin took this with him from the crime scene after murdering Mr. Corrida. At the request of his client, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, what's your point, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think it's possible that Mr. de Killer's client was Matt Engarde. In fact, I think there is a contradiction here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can't tell by just looking at it that this bear is really a jewelry box. The chances that Matt Engarde thought the note was inside this bear... Are zero to none!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! I didn't think of it that way...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. But I did think of it that way, and I thought it was rather strange. After all, there is no reason why Mr. Engarde would ever want a jewelry box like this!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! Y-You make a valid point, Mr. Wright! Mr. Edgeworth! What is your opinion!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It was just a flash, but I think I did rather well on this one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Unfortunately... I think he believes differently.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe a show of appreciation is in order.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">H-Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The defense seems to be in love with wishing more despair upon itself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I would like to direct the court's attention to this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is that...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is a very small video camera, Your Honor. This type of camera is commonly used as a means of spying.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-Spying...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What the...!? I thought that spy camera was in my possession...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Matt Engarde and the victim both thought of the other as their biggest rival. They even went so far as to use this type of item to find each other's weaknesses!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The victim, Juan Corrida, was being spied on! His personal life was being watched by none other than Matt Engarde!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Oooooorder!! Ahem! Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You... Don't tell me you knew about your client's spying activities!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... sort of...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Sort of" is not an acceptable answer, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see you are confused, Mr. Wright. You're probably thinking, "But I have the camera that was in the stuffed bear's eye..."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But this camera that I have is not that same one. Last night, I searched the victim's house on a hunch... Using this...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gumshoe's bug sweeper...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">By the way, Mr. Wright. The defendant's fingerprints were found on this camera.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Matt Engarde's fingerprints were on there!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, Phoenix... It looks like those cameras were hidden all over the place, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What am I supposed to say to that evidence...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think this is the end. It's fairly obvious that Mr. Engarde learned of the suicide note through this. He was watching the victim all along.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He got me good this time! I don't have anything to counter that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Chief!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Have you figured out what you're going to do next yet?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What I'm going to do next!? <thought>Does running away like a frightened child work?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">I know it seems like Mr. Edgeworth is very close to putting the lid on this case. But... In his eagerness to prove his point, he forgot one very important thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, what is it, Mia!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">There is a piece of evidence that he really should investigate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something he should investigate?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">I would really hate to see the good prosecutor get scolded... For not remembering to look into the item when he had the chance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why are you speaking in riddles all of a sudden...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Alright, I think this time we finally understand everything. Well, Mr. Wright? You don't have any further objections, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is this piece of evidence that Mia is talking about...? Can I figure out what it is that still needs to be looked at, or should I let it go...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have no objections to Engarde getting his guilty sentence as he should... But I can't let that happen yet! Mia said there's still something worth examining. If she thinks so, then even if I have to force it, I must find something to bring up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I have an objection, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. That was about the weakest objection I've ever heard, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! The defense has no intentions of letting this go so easily!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You are beginning to sound desperate...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's just your imagination, Your Honor! Mr. Edgeworth. This is not like you at all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In your eagerness to prove your point, you've forgotten one very important thing.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Hey... Isn't that what I just said!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, you're telling me that I forgot something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're so close, Mr. Edgeworth... But there's something you really should examine about this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Edgeworth...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I do believe some special examination is needed... But I think the item that should be examined is the defense's grey matter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoops!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. After this trial is over, I would like to see you in my chambers. I think there are a few things we need to discuss.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. If you're going to speak, at least use your brain to make up something intelligible.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is... Ms. Inpax's suicide note, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Who knows?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I mean, sure, this "suicide note" was found inside this bear. But this bear was in my possession until a few moments ago. Which means... The handwriting on this "suicide note" has yet to be analyzed!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So! As to whether this pivotal piece of evidence was really written by Ms. Inpax or not... Has yet to be even remotely confirmed!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Wright! You can't seriously be suggesting...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Mr. Wright! You... Are you saying this suicide note is a fake!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Andrews... You were the one who tried to pin this murder on Mr. Engarde. Who's to say you didn't create a fake "suicide note" and put it into this bear!?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">H-How dare you!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor. The defense is indiscriminately accusing the witness again! There is no evidence linking the witness to the suicide note whatsoever!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But if this is a fake, then the witness is the only person who could have made it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Recall the witness' testimony concerning this figurine! The only person other than the victim who could solve the puzzle is the witness herself!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Ahh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Andrews! You wrote this note, didn't you? You wrote it so you could use it to frame Matt Engarde!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I... I did no such thing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright! If you're going to pronounce this suicide note a fake... Then show this court some evidence to support your theory!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Edgeworth! You were the one who presented this scrap of paper as evidence! That means the burden of proof lies with you, the prosecution!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Uuugn!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! Mr. Edgeworth. Can you confirm the handwriting on this suicide note...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is as the defense has stated! The handwriting has yet to be analyzed!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that's the case... It seems that yet again we have reached a point where a verdict is impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Imposs... That's impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">This isn't good, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The judge is going to carry this trial over one more day. I don't think Maya will physically be able to make it another day!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I didn't want to have to do this, but I don't have a choice. I request that both the prosecution and defense further investigate...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I think we've reached the end of the line...</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What is that sound!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's Gumshoe!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hello!? Gumshoe!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... *sigh*...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is with him!? And what's with that sigh!?</thought> Where's Maya!? What happened to De Killer!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He, uh... He got away...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm sorry, pal! I really am! I don't know what to say besides I'm sorry. I wish there was some way to make it up to you! I really do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Anyway, what's going on!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We found his hideout, pal. But... the two of them were already gone...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...This is terrible...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm going to keep looking for them, pal. Don't you worry! I just need a little more time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't tell me we don't... we don't have any more...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you hear that? They're calling for his head!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Wright... I can't... For us to come this far and... ... Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Let me talk to Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I can't do that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Would you please get a hold of yourself!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I am about to end today's proceedings. You may take your phone calls after...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hold on, Your Honor! Edgeworth! Catch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Please! You've got to buy us some more time!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Court is in session. ...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sorry, Your Honor. You were saying?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! This is a court of law!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, Your Honor! But...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I am reluctant to do this, however... It appears that I have no choice but to suspend proceedings until tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I... This time, I really can't do anything...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now adjourned for the day!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please wait, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>E-Edgeworth!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What is it, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I humbly request another 30 minutes of Your Honor's time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">For what purpose?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We can perform the necessary tests on this piece of evidence in that time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... But can you really obtain your results in 30 minutes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe we can, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But wouldn't it be better if we adjourned for today and then reconvened tomorrow...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thirty minutes. Please, Your Honor. That's all I am asking for.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please! Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">At the prosecution's request, this court will now take a 30 minute recess. But be advised that I will not allow another recess today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not sure if this is helping... or hurting us...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will now take its final recess of the day!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright! Well!? What's going on with Maya's situation!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">De Killer... It looks like he got away again. Thirty minutes...? We can't find her in that time...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Report!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! I-Is that Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We don't have time! Just spit it out!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">R-Right! It looks like we just missed them, sir. But De Killer left a few things behind by accident in his rush to get away.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A few things...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can we use any of them as evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ho ho ho. I thought you'd ask, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I've got the things he left with me right now and I'm on my way over!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's odd. Any items like that are usually sent to the crime lab first...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We don't have time to wait for those guys, sir! When those guys weren't looking, I swiped the stuff and ran!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well... I'm not a detective anymore, so I had to... I'm really sorry, sir, but I've got to put the law on hold for now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds bad... I hope he doesn't get in too much trouble over this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">With my hunk of junk car, I'd say I'll be there in about 20 minutes, sir! Don't worry! I'll be there! Wait for me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A-Alright... Just get here in one piece.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm on a mission and no one can stop me now, sir! No one! I'm pulling out all the stops and running every red light!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Items left by the murderer, huh... Maybe there's something among them that will be decisive enough to end this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hey! What's wrong!? Detective Gumshoe! Answer me!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... No one can stop... I'm...</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep* *beep* *beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What happened?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It sounded like he had an accident. I'm guessing his cell phone broke as well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What was he thinking?? We've got to hurry and call for help!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But we have no idea where he is. His cell phone is broken, and he wasn't driving a patrol car, so no radio either. Also... If we don't get to those items before they do, the police will take possessions of them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No! We can't let that happen!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, if there is a way we can find out where he is, then we stand a chance...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why, oh why did Gumshoe have to get into an accident now!? Is there any way to find out exactly where he is at this moment...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right! There is a way!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!? How!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure we can find out where Detective Gumshoe is through this...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why are you bringing up Franziska at a time like... Oh, I see! I'll try to get in contact with her. The chances are slim, but she's all we have...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Franziska... Will she even want to help us...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright, we're not in the middle of a mock trial here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess this won't work, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I guess it's up to me. Alright, I will think of something on my end. Don't get your hopes up too high, but I'll try my best.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Did I say something wrong...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh! It's no use! I can't think of anything!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... Alright, I'll try to think of something on my end. Don't get your hopes up too high, but I'll try my best.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Did I say something wrong...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't have any right to judge anyone ever again...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know my client is guilty. But what I'm doing now... I'm pinning the guilt onto someone totally innocent, and using the evidence to do so... ... It might be my turn to say, "Defense Attorney Phoenix Wright chooses death"...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright. It doesn't suit someone like you to cry useless tears. Whether you did your job well or not... That can only be seen after the verdict has been decided.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The verdict...</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Is Prosecutor Edgeworth here!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, bailiff?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">There's a phone call for you, sir. They said it was extremely urgent.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They're probably finished with the handwriting analysis. I have to go take this call. In the mean time, think hard about what it is you must do.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court will now reconvene. I assume both sides are ready?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-Yes, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I can understand the defense acting like this, however, why do you also seem distraught, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I... that is... It's nothing, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's wrong with Edgeworth...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">It looks like something unexpected just happened to him.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Edgeworth. If you could please tell the court the results of the handwriting analysis on Ms. Inpax's suicide note...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y...Yes, Your Honor. Unfortunately... We have discovered that this suicide note is a forgery.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This... This note was not written by Ms. Inpax herself! It is a fake!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! Mr. Edgeworth! Would you care to explain what is going on!? If this was not written by Ms. Inpax, then who wrote it!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We would need more time to do a more detailed analysis, however... It appears that the handwriting matches that of the victim, Mr. Juan Corrida.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. C-Corrida...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, well... It looks like Ms. Inpax never left a suicide note after all. She never wrote anything about Engarde...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However! Your Honor. Even though this suicide note is indeed a fake, Mr. Engarde could not have known that, and so that facts remain unchanged! Acting under the assumption that it was real, he had plotted to possess it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That does sound very plausible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This theory that Engarde had no idea that the suicide note was fake... Something seems a little wrong with it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense believes that the theory the prosecution has stated contradicts testimony! If everything the prosecution has proven up to this point is true... Then it's impossible for Mr. Engarde to not have know it was a fake!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Edgeworth?? Your response?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe that even more important than finding out if this note is real or not, is whether the attorney's badge pinned to that man's chest is real... That is the million dollar question!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I agree.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Me too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm going to take a wild guess and say that I messed up again...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is this little item called again...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, a video camera, Your Honor. Well, a very small one, but...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, that's right. A camera. Ah, you kids and your fancy toys nowadays...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Edgeworth! Earlier, you claimed that Mr. Engarde knew of the existence of this note because he was spying on the victim. Isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If that were true... Then this means Mr. Engarde would have known that the victim had forged the note!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aaack!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's no use... Something feels wrong, but I can't put my finger on what it is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Actually, there is something I would like to ask. Mr. Edgeworth. You had stated something earlier to the effect of the defendant had spied on Mr. Corrida's private life...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe this would mean that he would have known about the note as well...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Th-That's it!</thought> Yes, and so naturally... This means Mr. Engarde would have known that the note was a fake!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Uungh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! See here, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Um, yes Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I was the one who thought of the spying thing! Jumping in and stealing my thunder like that is simply... I can't even describe it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, yes... Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I could've even bragged about embarrassing Mr. Edgeworth to my grandchild had you not... For that, I assign you a penalty, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaaa!? <thought>If only I had kept my mouth shut...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So then, the defendant knew this suicide note was a fake. And if that's true, then the situation has suddenly changed in a very dramatic way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly, Your Honor! The prosecution's theory as to what Mr. Engarde's motive for murder was... It has suddenly disappeared into thin air!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But Your Honor! It's not as if Mr. Engarde monitored Mr. Corrida 24 hours a day! Perhaps the victim wrote the note in a place Mr. Engarde didn't know of!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, right back at you, Mr. Edgeworth! Why don't you show us some proof that the victim made the forgery at an unknown place!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! ...Mr. Edgeworth. It looks like this time, it is you who has dug his own grave.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unnnngh... As I figured...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Huh? ...As you figured...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As I figured... It came down to this after all...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth, you are not making any sense...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">When I heard the results of the handwriting analysis, I thought this might happen. The question is... "What next?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What next...??</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If the prosecution can't prove Mr. Engarde's motive through the evidence, then we must prove it from another angle.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I agree with you there...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor. The prosecution... would like to call a witness to the stand at this time...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh. Well, that's fine.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However... this witness... This witness is a little... unusual...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Edgeworth stuttering...? This is not like him at all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Unusual? Well, what sort of witness is this person, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This witness is one who is perfectly fit to answer once and for all the question of, "Who was it that hired Shelly de Killer to commit murder?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's impossible!! Who in the...!? No such person exists who can answer that question with such certainty!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes! Mr. Edgeworth! Who is this witness!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is... It's... um...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes!? Go on! Who is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The man himself... Mr. Shelly de Killer.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, Mr. de Killer. ... W-W-Waaaaait!! Shelly de Killer!? Um, you mean... The killer? Err... I mean the assassin?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He's coming here? To the witness stand...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, yes, in a manner of speaking... I recognize that this is a very unusual circumstance, so I ask for your permission.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is this alright with you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Do I have a choice here...? I can't really do much else to drag this trial out...</thought> The defense has no objections, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I wonder if it really is alright to do this...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very well then. The prosecution calls our witness to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Edgeworth... Is there no other way left to us...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, witness. ...Um, your name... and your, uh... occupation, please.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I... I say!! Wh-What is going on here!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How can you remain so calm? And what is the meaning of this two-way radio...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Actually, Your Honor, it was delivered to me just now... And it came with a condition. As long as we do not trace its source, Mr. de Killer will testify to this court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So this must be what that urgent phone call he got earlier was about...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh no, this will not do. I cannot allow this in my court. First of all, we can't even be sure this is really Mr. de Killer himself!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Witness. Please present some sort of proof that you are in fact Shelly de Killer.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...?</line>
<line speaker="???">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... I'm... sooo... hungry...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-M-Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A... A voice! Mr. Wright! Can you confirm anything from this!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense has no objections to this person! We are satisfied that this man is indeed Shelly de Killer!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It looks like we have run into yet another unexpected turn of events... Well, it doesn't seem like we have too many choices under these circumstances, so...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Now then, witness. There is one thing I would like to confirm before we speak of anything else.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">At the request of a client, you killed Mr. Juan Corrida. Is this correct?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now that we have answered that, let's move on to the name of your client!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is all just a bad dream... Yes, that's it, a bad dream...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Shelly de Killer... What is he going to say...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, Mr. de Killer seems to be a very clever man. I'd almost say he seems to be mocking us.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">While he may appear to be our enemy, Your Honor, Mr. de Killer is only stating the truth. He is no hypocrite. He has always stood by this one belief.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You mean about this "trust between his clients and himself" thing? Hmm, it seems to be a level of trust beyond what people like me can comprehend. ...Well, Mr. Wright? Are you ready to cross-examine the witness?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">There's no way to know what's coming next, so stay cool and collected, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We can hear anything you have to say later. Can you please just tell us your client's...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... S-Sorry... Go on...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, it appears this is one witness you can't badger, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's only because you don't know about Maya's situation...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The trust between you and your client...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And that is why you're testifying in this manner?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But couldn't someone stab you in the back and break your trust?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That's enough! Please, no more!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The trust between you and your client...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, but I was wondering about something you just said. You said that your client had already "broken the rules"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's why you feel you can betray this person?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just my luck... An assassin with a conscience. Who would've figured...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This case just keeps getting better and better!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Everyone understands your point, I think. Really.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You have made it crystal clear that you value trust over all else. I believe we are ready.</line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"It is my wish that you grasp this concept before I give the name of my client." to "Now then, I do believe it's about time I revealed the name of my client, don't you agree?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That seems a little strange to me... I mean, you're about to tell us the name of your client. I would think that this would be very bad for them.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Their role...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You... Who gave you the right to be so high and mighty...!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, no! No! I, uh, didn't say anything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The judge had better watch himself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We understand, so please tell us the name of your client!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Aaargh! That egomaniacal...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Somehow, that coming from an assassin makes it less than comforting...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't really care about all this extra fluff. Just tell us the name already!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Patience. Try to calm down a little. It's important to try and understand his mindset. He seems very steadfast and closed so you're going to have to work to get him to talk.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not his therapist, you know...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Umm... Now I can't bring myself to ask the client's name...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you can't ask it, Mr. Wright, then I will. Witness! What is the name of your client who requested the murder of Mr. Juan Corrida!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa</line>
<line speaker="Judge">aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Witness!! That's not who you told me it was earlier!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Whaaaaaaaat!?!? Th-This can't be! On the phone earlier...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What's going on here...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">My guess is that Mr. de Killer just stabbed Mr. Edgeworth in the back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Stabbed Edgeworth in the back...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I'm sure in order to get an audience with this court, Mr. de Killer told him a different name... "Matt Engarde", perhaps...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I knew it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This... This is outrageous! I was deceived! This witness is telling a very serious lie!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But you were the one who summoned this witness!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Grk! Grr... Y-You... Shelly de Killer...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">H... Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wow... All of a sudden, it feels like we can actually win this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The prosecution has failed to provide a motive and has instead, provided this suicide note, which is a forgery created by the victim. Furthermore, there is a possibility the defendant himself knew it was a fake. But most definitive of all, we have heard from the assassin himself; the name of his client. Mr. de Killer's client who requested the murder was not the defendant at all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...No...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">With all this evidence, it is obvious to me that this means that Mr. Matt Engarde... Is innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Please bring Ms. Adrian Andrews in immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What now? With the way this is going, Engarde will be found innocent. This may be our last chance... to save Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... But... But Edgeworth is right. De Killer is lying! And Engarde... my client... I know he's guilty! <thought>Can I live with myself if I win this!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who would've believed that the prosecution's own witness would absolve the defendant!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor! The prosecution requests permission to further question the witness! Shelly de Killer is certainly lying under oath!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It wasn't me! Listen! Everyone! Please! That testimony just now... It was all one big lie!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Andrews...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">The suicide note may have been a fake. But! That man... Matt... He's the reason Celeste died! And Juan's death... It was all because he got pulled into Matt's twisted world! That testimony just now... You have to believe me... It was a horrible, horrible lie...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... Mr. de Killer himself has testified... He has named you as his client.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">No! That's not true!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Also, there is quite a bit of evidence that points to you. The knife and button, donning the Nickel Samurai's costume...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">But that's... That's...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You even have a motive. We know that Ms. Celeste Inpax was a large part of your life. You wanted to follow her... And you wanted revenge against the two who hurt her. I would say you have plenty of reasons to want them both dead.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I... No... Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">You... You know the truth! Tell them! Tell them the real story... Who the real killer is... Tell them! Please... Help me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yes, I know the truth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe we have reached the end of this trial. Therefore, I ask the defense for any final words or opinions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>I have to decide... Do I take the not guilty verdict and save Maya... Or do I throw this chance away and wait for Gumshoe's new evidence...? What am I supposed to do!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! The defense will make a request... ... ... <thought>It's no use... I can't... It feels like I've lost my voice...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't do it, Mia... I can't accept a not guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You are a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know. But... But Matt Engarde is a killer; a murderer! I can't... I can't let him get away with this. I can't let someone else take the fall. If I let Ms. Andrews be convicted, then I am no better than Engarde. And even though I don't want to admit it, I have to face the fact that it is because of Edgeworth that I now know the real truth. He could've gotten Engarde convicted so many times over, but he never took a single one of those chances. If I take this verdict right now... I'd be betraying his trust. <thought>...His trust...? I never thought about it until now... I... I trust him...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">... Yes, you do.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Your opinion, please.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense requests that we be allowed to further question Mr. de Killer.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-Am I hearing you correctly, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... But... That witness has cleared your client through his testimony! Your job here is done!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not done yet. To see through this witness' lies and find the truth... THAT is my job, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's still more evidence to look at... And I'm sure that once those pieces arrive here in this very courtroom... a miracle will occur!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The trial will continue. Mr. Edgeworth. Please re-establish connection with Mr. de Killer.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Right away, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Before that, we would like to talk with you a little more.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well... Actually, we would like to hear everything you know about this case. This is how things are... usually done.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is he talking about? "Usually done"...??</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... What shall we have him testify about now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. de Killer. If you don't mind, please testify about your client in more detail.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... This is a most unexpected turn of events... For the... um, fifth time now...? However, this time, everything has finally been revealed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just a second, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We still have the cross-examination to do...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But you don't need to question testimony like this... Do you, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Your Honor, the defense will question the witness. <thought>As if I have a choice here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Huh!? Why!? What this witness has said is nothing but beneficial to the defense's case! If you scrutinize the testimony, then...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Then I'll expose the lies in that oh-so-"beneficial" testimony, I suppose.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't understand what's going on anymore...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That makes two of us...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I press him the wrong way, it might raise suspicions on his end... But I have to do something to waste more time...</thought> Um... Witness. About requesting a hit...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How much is your fee...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! NONONO! I'm not thinking of hiring--</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-M-Mr. Wright!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Y-You... You want to kill me... You want me dead... DON'T YOU!?!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaat!? Why would you think something like that, Your Hon--</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Guilty! MR. PHOENIX WRIGHT! You are hereby declared GUILTY!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Witness. Let's continue... Why did you disclose the name of your client? They are your client, are they not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I would think that most people wouldn't be able to overlook a person hiring another to kill.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... Yeah... <thought>Well, a change in occupation might be good for you...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That goes without saying, Mr. de Killer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you talking about the button and the knife?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, this card...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You try to make things easy...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's pretty devoted to his work...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... It's really hard to tell if he's being truthful or not without him being here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you're saying most clients wouldn't do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, no! I already told you! I have no intention of ever using your services!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why does he keep looking at me like I'm the one on trial here!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">From the very beginning?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if that's really true...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's odd...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So why do you think your client did that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, fiddling around at the scene of the crime is pretty risky. And why would someone who has requested a murder go to the crime scene anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, that is true.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If that's the case, then why didn't the person just request that you do it...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's all you have to testify?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Again"...? As in you plan to continue?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me? Ah, no no no! I'm fine! Really!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Are you really now...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder what kind of man the judge thinks I am now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">What are you going to do now, Phoenix?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All I can do now is expose the lies.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's true... However, you realize that will be very bad for our client, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nnngh... I'm so confused... But the one thing I know for sure is I can't let this trial end yet!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you so much for taking the time to testify, Mr. de Killer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When Adrian Andrews entered the victim's room, your "client" had no idea that Juan Corrida had been murdered!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But how... How do you know that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">From this wine glass, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The glass...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. de Killer's supposed client thought Mr. Corrida had only fainted. Which is why this glass of tomato juice was poured for the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... But isn't that just a part of Adrian Andrews' calculated plan?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That is not possible, Your Honor. This glass bears the fingerprints of that person. Had this been planned, they would never have left their fingerprints behind!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see your point... Mr. Edgeworth!? What is your opinion?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Strangely enough... I had the same exact thought just now. Witness! How do you explain this strange phenomenon!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm afraid you are mistaken. If Adrian Andrews really is your client, as you claim... Then your client should have had knowledge of Mr. Corrida's death. If not... Then that can only mean that Adrian Andrews was never your client at all!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix. If De Killer figures out what we're up to, we're in real trouble!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I know...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Edgeworth! I'm surprised! You know you can't say things like that without any evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah... Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Th-That sounded like an awfully weak "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>" to me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Anyway! I am positive there was a contradiction in that testimony. The prosecution requests further testimony concerning when the request was taken!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right now, I have to buy us more time... While we wait for the items De Killer left behind to get here. I just know that the very outcome of this trial lies with those items!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So you physically met your client, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... Well, Mr. Wright, your cross-examination, please.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One week ago? Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please... stop...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A specific date and time...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you ask why on that specific night?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Your suspicions, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even if I ask about them, it would only be a guess.</thought> I see... That's fine then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what are these "suspicions" you had? Why did your client request that night...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The bear...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He must be talking about this bear puzzle...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Inside that figurine was a suicide note. Naturally, the victim brought it with him to his hotel room. He was planning to publicly disclose its contents at the press conference, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I see...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright? Was the testimony just now of any importance?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The testimony just now has made one thing clear. And that is... The "client" knew the secret of the bear figurine!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...? Why is everyone so quiet...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. I think all of us already knew that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh, really?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Witness, please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What De Killer said sounds plausible, but... In the end, it's just his conjecture...</thought> No, Your Honor. I don't think it's very important.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well then, witness, please continue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you physically met Adrian Andrews, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What was that?? What was with the brief pause...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's probably just my imagination... I need to find something more definitive to catch this guy on!</thought> Can we believe that your testimony up to this point has been reliable?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Witness! I would like for you to give us a few more details.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And why is that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, Mr. Wright? Was the testimony just now of any importance?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course, it was very important, Your Honor. If Mr. de Killer had met his client before the murder, then it's unlikely he is mistaken!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So you're saying that his client really was Adrian Andrews?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... um... I guess so...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm so lost... Who the heck am I supposed to be helping here...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Calm down, Phoenix. Think carefully and relax.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, would the witness please continue?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why he meets his clients is not important. And that wasn't the point. Witness, please stop side-stepping my questions!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My question was "Did you really meet Adrian Andrews in person?"</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It's true what they say about talking face to face. Well, Mr. Wright? Was the testimony just now of any importance?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I was so sure there was something, but I can't get a good grip on what it is...</thought> Hmm, I guess it wasn't all that important.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What did you hear just now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Clean out your earwax and pay attention, Phoenix. You're letting his words slip by!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Um... I guess I missed something back there...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Witness, please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I heard what I think I heard just now... Then I think I've got him.</thought> Your Honor. I believe the testimony just now was of the utmost importance.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Huh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that's the case... Witness, please include the statement just now in your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"From the moment I saw him, I thought, "I can trust this person as a client.""</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But as we now know, that was not how it turned out, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Adrian Andrews turned out to be a client who couldn't stick to the rules, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So I would like to check one last time. Are you sure your testimony is accurate?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So your client was Adrian Andrews...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, he says the two of them met... But if they did, then there shouldn't be anything wrong with De Killer's testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, there doesn't seem to be anything strange this time around...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You have to draw more information from him, but you can't draw his suspicion. If you can do that, you should be able to find a flaw in his testimony somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Talk about a delicate balance...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I would like to go over this one more time. You met Adrian Andrews at a bar and took the request at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's when you thought "he" was trustworthy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, but that is an impossible tale.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Shelly de Killer. You have never met the real Adrian Andrews!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because you made one very big slip-up... ...about her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you had ever met Adrian Andrews in person... One look would have told you that she is a woman!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Order! Order in the court! Mr. Wright! What is the meaning of this!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This witness testified to the following: That he always meets face to face with his clients when taking their request.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But he has never met Adrian Andrews in person...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, Your Honor! That is exactly the point! That means Mr. de Killer's client could not have been Ms. Adrian Andrews!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth... I understand your logic on this one... However... Why would the assassin make such a basic mistake?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe it has to do with her name, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Her name?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Adrian Andrews is, without a doubt, a very androgynous name.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unluckily for Mr. de Killer, the entire time he was on the stand, no one had stated Adrian Andrews' gender. And so, he simply picked the wrong gender to go with.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What... What is going on...? Shelly de Killer! This court demands an explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So does that mean you remember something different now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! I know he's just going to spit out more lies.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. But this time, please give us the truth, and nothing but the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So you took this job through a letter...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He didn't mention anything about a letter in his earlier testimony... Which means he is definitely lying!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Be careful, Phoenix. If you break the assassin's testimony completely, it's over for us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know... I can't make him suspicious. But... I think we're OK; like we can do this. <thought>As long as he's standing there across from me... No matter how strong of a punch I throw, he'll counter it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, let's begin the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But didn't you just say that you always meet your clients?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But didn't you meet your client this time?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, come now. Let's stop with this game of cat and mouse.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright then, just cough it up and confess!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! You can't badger a witness with such harsh words!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're a lawyer, so behave like one and present evidence instead of mindlessly yelling. Now then, do you have any proof that Mr. de Killer met with his client?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We've come this far! I have to try to prove something here!</thought> Very well, I will show you proof.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Are you sure about this, Phoenix?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here is the proof that the witness met with his client, who wished Mr. Corrida dead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So! What do you think!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... That's right, you can't actually see the evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! How could I have picked the wrong piece at a time like this!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... In any case, let's continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, Your Honor. Unfortunately, I don't have any proof.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, I see. Then your line of questioning was just another waste of time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sadly for us, Your Honor, that is the nature of Wright and wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And why could you not meet certain clients?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Nice business opportunities?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Electronic mail? Do you have to mail that in a special insulated envelope?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... E-mail...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>In a contest of mimicry, the judge would beat a parrot, hands down...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*ahem* Anyway, so you took this job without having met your client, and...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Two or three other things...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what were these "other things"?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What should I do...? Should I let him slide with that...? It'd be really bad if I push his buttons the wrong way and he gets mad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>De Killer sounds like one sharp man... I should try to find a better way to do this without making him suspicious.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's continue with the testimony. Witness, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whether or not they're related to this case is for the court to decide.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-W-Wait! <thought>Uh oh... This is looking really bad! I shouldn't press my luck. Alright, I have to think. Is this worth pursuing...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>De Killer sounds like one sharp man... I should try to find a better way to do this without making him suspicious.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's continue with the testimony. Witness, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Witness, this is a very important matter. Please cooperate and tell us what these other "jobs" your client requested were...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The bear figurine...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And... Where was that figurine...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And then... what did you do next?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You gave it to your "client"... Interesting.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... This information certainly sounds important to me. Witness, please include what you just stated in your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"One of these was to find the bear figurine and to give it to Adrian Andrews."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I found this figurine at Mr. Engarde's mansion. If you gave it to Ms. Andrews, then what was it doing there?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That makes a lot of sense. Well, Mr. Wright? Do you have any problems with this piece of testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's no use... As long as I can't put my finger on the central problem here, pressing this witness any more would be extremely dangerous!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It appears that Mr. Wright has no problems. Well then, witness. Please continue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So De Killer says he gave the figurine to Ms. Andrews. But I know somewhere in that statement there is a contradiction... And yet... I know that if I present something trivial here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">...He will cut the connection on his end. If you want to make a strong point, Phoenix... You have to present strong evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's right. So now what, Dr. Wright!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's no use... As long as I can't put my finger on the central problem here, pressing this witness any more would be extremely dangerous!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It appears that Mr. Wright has no problems. Well then, witness. Please continue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Witness, let's go over this one more time. You gave Ms. Andrews the bear figurine. And she told you to take the bear and wait for her at Engarde Mansion. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I think maybe you might have remembered a few things incorrectly.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is a battle of wits! I can't let up on him!</thought> I don't think it is possible for Ms. Andrews to have been the recipient of this bear!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So! What do you think!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Witness!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. de Killer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you're saying that you never saw your client's face. Not even once?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Yes, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A mask?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The Nickel Samurai mask, I'm guessing...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright... What do you have to say about this? Do you have any problems with this piece of testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One thing does sort of stick out at me, Your Honor. Witness. I think you most definitely saw your client's face.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's recall Mr. Powers' testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">After the award ceremony, I went by myself to Matt's room. Matt was standing there in front of his room, still in his Nickel Samurai costume. Matt gave the bellboy a tip.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You received quite a large roll of cash from Mr. Engarde! And at the time, he was not wearing his Nickel Samurai mask!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Yes, now that you mention it, I do remember that...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sorry, but sadly, we are not nearly so generous here. If I could receive large rolls of cash by simply bringing people things on trays... Then why on Earth would I stand around here prosecuting!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, the dj vu... And isn't his salary more than enough for one man...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... And where is your evidence that the large roll of cash was not in fact, a tip...? Come, Mr. Edgeworth. Show me the money!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Whaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, no, it's not like that at all. I just think lies aren't a good thing, you know...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry! Please forgive my foolishness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... If only you were this apologetic all the time... Anyway, I do not see a huge contradiction here. Therefore, you may continue witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I can pull something out of what he said... But it would be real bad if I did something and made him mad over something trivial!</thought> There are no problems with the testimony, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">We've pretty much reached the end of our rope here...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Seems like we're still OK to me.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">And that's exactly what is so bad. At the rate we're going, we will end up completely destroying De Killer's lie. If we do that... You already know how serious of a situation that will put us in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh yeah... <thought>All I can do now is pray that those items reach us in time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Shelly de Killer. If you had really given the bear to Ms. Andrews... then this item should not have been inside it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see where you're going...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup, that's where I'm going...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Where is everyone going!? Do I need to pack a suitcase?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor. Please think back to Ms. Andrews' testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">And I was going to burn it... for her sake.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If even for a single minute, this bear had actually been in Ms. Andrews' hands... I'm sure she would have taken the suicide note out and burned it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! So that's where you two were going!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So by the very fact that this suicide note was still inside the bear... Tells us that your "client" didn't know how to disassemble the puzzle!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Which means...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It means, Your Honor, that it is impossible for Adrian Andrews to be the "client"!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O...Order! Order! ORDER!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No! That's not...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait! Please!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N...No... Please... Not that... Please wait...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nnnngh... Gnwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhh!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What in the...? Mr. Wright...? Are you...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I didn't understand this witness' outburst just now. Do you think there is a need to hear more testimony, or is this enough...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well... We should...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Edgeworth! We can't do this! If we keep this up... Maya... She'll...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">U...Ungh! The prosecution... I...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What has come over everyone? Even you are...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution... rests.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is going on around here...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution has no further questions, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh... Whaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I never thought I'd see the day. This is a most unusual situation... If the prosecution rests with no further questions... Then... the prosecution has failed to uphold its stance.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that is the case, then even though I am reluctant, I must believe that Mr. de Killer's testimony is accurate. That would mean that Shelly de Killer's client is... Adrian Andrews!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If I end the trial here, right now, then your client, Matt Engarde, would be declared innocent. And in his place, Adrian Andrews would be charged with murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>M-Ms. Andrews... would be charged with murder!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The prosecution has no further questions, so we will now hear the defense's final remarks. Bailiff! Please bring the defendant, Matt Engarde, to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The items from De Killer's hideout didn't make it in time... We tried as hard as we could, but it looks like our time has run out...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't believe it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">The outcome now lies in your hands.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Dude, did the old guy finally decide?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">To be honest, I can't think of you as a truly innocent and good person. You have done enough evil to drive a woman to suicide.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... At least on the charge of murder, it would appear you are innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... Hah...! So, I guess even the old fuddy-duddy figured me out!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Engarde...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">You were atrocious as a lawyer, weren't you? Giving your client away like this! And that "refreshing like a spring breeze" crap; it's just as atrocious, don't you agree? ... Anyway, get on with it and pronounce me innocent already. Right, Mister Lawyer!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Should I side with justice? Or should I save Maya's life?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You'd better get Engarde a guilty sentence, OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But... But if I did that... Maya will die! But if I say he's innocent... Then Ms. Andrews will be charged as the murderer! Do I say he's "guilty"... or "not guilty"...? Either choice I make, someone's life is going to end!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It all hinges on what I "choose"!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Wright. Let's hear the defense's final statements on this matter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If the person who hired the assassin was Adrian Andrews... Then your client, Mr. Matt Engarde is innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Hmph... There's no need to ask, old man. After all, my lawyer is going to say what I want... aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't! I can't do this! But I have to decide something! I can't count on the evidence to help me anymore. I have to listen to my heart!</thought> My client... Matt Engarde is...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We are waiting for your answer, Mr. Wright! Matt Engarde, your client deserves an answer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Maya... I'm sorry...</thought> Matt Engarde is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">F-Franziska von Karma!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What are you doing here... OWW!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Did you bring them? The final pieces... Do you have them?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What a filthy, old coat this is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's Gumshoe's... I can spot his tattered rags anywhere...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've fought long and hard this whole trial... All for what is inside that raggedy coat... I'm sure that inside that coat, lies a crucial piece of evidence!</thought> Your Honor! Inside that filthy coat... Are the defense's final pieces of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your final... evidence!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... This trial is already over. All that remains is for me to hand down my verdict. I do not believe that any evidence presented now, would change the outcome of this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-What!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor. It is our duty to examine every piece of evidence, down to the last. I request that Ms. von Karma be allowed to present these pieces of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I suppose you are right, Mr. Edgeworth. I grant permission to do so. However, this one obvious rule applies here; If these items do not bring up any new points, then they will not be accepted by this court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, Ms. von Karma. If you please.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... He must have been in quite a rush.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Somewhere among the evidence we're about to see... There will be something that will turn this whole situation around... like a miracle. I'm sure of it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">That is all we can hope for.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Does De Killer's pistol have anything to do with this case...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Does that pistol have any relation to this case?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's the pistol that he used to shoot you, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's the pistol that was used to shoot Franziska... It's probably not going to help us very much...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm pretty sure there was no gun involved in this case. There's no real benefit to hearing about it...</thought> Please present the next piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I bet De Killer took that from Engarde Mansion...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you checked the contents of that tape?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why would you say that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">De... De Killer went back for it...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right now, we don't need to establish De Killer's role in this case... I should be listening to information about a different piece of evidence.</thought> That's fine. Please present the next piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is that a uniform from the Gatewater Hotel...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was that used during the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's no doubt about it! De Killer was wearing this on the night of the murder!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what is that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A button...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think this is going to help us much at all...</thought> Thank you very much, Ms. von Karma. I think that's enough.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It's just as I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And... what is that, Your Honor..?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sure, were we under normal circumstances, these items from Shelly de Killer's hideout would be very important clues. However... Our question is not "Who did the killing?"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is, "Who is the client?"...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, that is correct. And these three items do not tell us anything about that! Thank you for your hard work, Ms. von Karma. You may step down now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, Your Honor! Please allow me to examine this new evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Overruled. This court already has all the evidence it needs to hand down a verdict!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Wonderful... Absolutely splendid. This judge is such a brilliant man, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is this the end...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I knew it... There's no such thing as a "miracle" in this world, is there?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I think you're wrong. I think they do exist. But you have to make that "miracle" happen. You've come this far! You can't give up now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... But... No matter how you think about it... It's... It's...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Try... For my sake. Just think about it for a second. There are two ways out of this situation for us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>T-Two!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">The first... Make Engarde wish from the bottom of his soul for a guilty verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">De Killer will always place his client's wishes first. If Engarde himself wished to be convicted, then he will let his hostage go.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That may be true, but... That's asking me to do the impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The second way... Force De Killer to end his contract with Engarde. If De Killer were to no longer think of Engarde as his "client"... Then he would let Maya go.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia! That's even more impossible! He is a man who values his duty towards his clients above all else!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... I know both of these seem like impossible feats at first. But if you could make either one happen, it would truly be a "miracle".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The bigger problem is, the judge has already said he doesn't need any more evidence! The pieces he was just shown; he's not accepting them!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix. Think things through from the other side. Isn't that what has always worked for us?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>The "other side"...? Wait, does she mean...</thought> You mean... to turn things around?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix. The judge says he doesn't need the evidence. If that's the case, then who does need it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"The person who needs the evidence"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">The defense, prosecution, and the judge... We have seen all the pieces of evidence. And that is how we have come to know the "truth". But there are people who have not seen them all. And those people do not know the "truth". That truth... It may be what will bring about the miracle in the end.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There are no objections this time, correct? Now then, I will pronounce my verdict!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Why don't we all respectfully sit back and listen, kids.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I have already told you, Mr. Wright. This court does not need any more evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I am not saying it is us that needs the evidence, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then... you want to show the evidence to... that person...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. For you to ask with such passion... I will grant you one chance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>O...One chance...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please show your evidence to who you think is the right person.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's impossible! To turn this situation around in one try...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">One try. That is all I will permit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to try to remember... Everything that has happened up to this point... Think, Phoenix! Think! There must be a way to save Maya while taking Engarde down at the same time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Wright. Let's not waste any more time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who would you like to show evidence to?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. And now... Tell this court what one piece of evidence you would like to show this person!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Well, what do you think, Mr. Edgeworth...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Uh... Um... I... don't have anything to say to this...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... How about you, Ms. von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid I cannot allow the defense to continue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No one understands what you are talking about anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait! Please! One more chance...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is enough, Mr. Wright. I will now state my verdict. This court finds the defendant, Matt Engarde...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is all. This court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Well, what do you think, Mr. Edgeworth...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Uh... Um... I think there is some merit... in showing this evidence to that witness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Bailiff! Please bring in the transceiver from earlier!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Alright! It looks like they got a hold of him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya... She's OK, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. One is all I need. I have here a video tape. It was found at your hideout.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I heard you injured three officers in your attempt to get this back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I thought so...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know the contents of this tape?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, you are on this tape.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was a video camera hidden at the crime scene. Your actions were being recorded.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is that true!? Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, the only person who could have placed a camera at the scene of the crime... would be your "client" naturally.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That was... Adrian Andrews...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Be quiet and listen... Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your "client" specified a place and time for you, isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was so they could film you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why did Matt Engarde film the crime scene...? The reason "why" he did that is my ticket out of this whole mess!</thought> There is only one reason why your "client" would secretly film the crime scene. They...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They wanted to witness the moment Juan Corrida died! Your client was going to sit on their fluffy soft sofa... Sip some coffee and pretend they were at a film festival!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Your Honor!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Well, what do you think, Mr. Edgeworth...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Uh... Um... I... don't have anything to say to this...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... How about you, Ms. von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid I cannot allow the defense to continue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No one understands what you are talking about anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait! Please! One more chance...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is enough, Mr. Wright. I will now state my verdict. This court finds the defendant, Matt Engarde...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is all. This court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your "client" didn't trust your skills! That's why, in order to monitor your work, they set up a video camera!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... Is that how you feel...? W-Well, everyone...? What do you think...? Pretty good, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Well, what do you think, Mr. Edgeworth...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Uh... Um... I... don't have anything to say to this...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... How about you, Ms. von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid I cannot allow the defense to continue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No one understands what you are talking about anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait! Please! One more chance...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is enough, Mr. Wright. I will now state my verdict. This court finds the defendant, Matt Engarde...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is all. This court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your "client" once told me something very interesting. We were talking about you, and this is what they said.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">But I'm no weakling. I don't believe anyone... least of all assassins.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Oh, come now, Mr. Wright. Assassins aren't above blackmail.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Yes, that's where the video comes in. With that, I can keep him at bay, and even blackmail him if I want.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your "client" didn't trust you at all. They were thinking of using this video to blackmail you! What do you have to say to that, Shelly de Killer!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... By a natural... That is the kind of person they are. Your "client" is a person who only thinks and plots of how to use the people around them to protect themselves from any and all dangers that may arise. That is the true nature of your "client".</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have one question for the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You told us one thing numerous times during your testimony. You said that you detest traitors most of all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But what if that traitor was your own client...? What would you do then!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. That's all I wanted to know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So the traitor becomes De Killer's next target... Ah! I get it... This is how we'll turn this case around!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...What the!? I'm not an item!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya... I thought I'd never see you again... Oh thank goodness!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Um... This trial appears to have come to its conclusion... However... I... Actually, I am sort of... I don't quite know what just happened there with the client and the witness and... Gwaaah! M-Ms. von Karma! Where did that...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">She always has you in her sights. Now! I do believe it's time to finally hand down a verdict!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Engarde. It looks like somehow, you got what you wanted. You will finally receive the acquittal you wanted so badly. You should be happy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But before that, I would like to make one final statement. Sometime in the near future, one very betrayed assassin may appear before you.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Needless to say, that man is very good at what he does. I'm sure you would understand what I mean, if you watch this video.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...H-- Help me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, Your Honor! The verdict, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-Is this alright with you, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">We have finally reached the end of a very long battle. Whether he's convicted or acquitted, there is no escape for him now. Go on, Phoenix. Plead whichever way your heart tells you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right, Chief.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Congratulations, Mr. Matt Engarde.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please make sure to savor every moment of what little time you have left. Your Honor! As always, the defense pleads not guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. This court finds the defendant, Matt Engarde...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">P-Please wait...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">If... If I get a not guilty... I'll... I'll be... killed...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">I... I'm... I'm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Matt Engarde.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even though I am a lawyer, I cannot make your crime disappear. I think a guilty verdict is appropriate here.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">M-Me!? My wonderful self...!? G-Guilty!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even if you got an acquittal, the instant you set foot outside the detention center, your life would be in danger. No matter which way you look at it... You can't run away from your crime anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... Noooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!Guiltyyyyyyy!!!!!!!!!!!!!!Guuuuuilty!!!GGG--Guuiiillltyyyy!!!GGGUUUILLLTYYY!!GUILTY!!!GuiLTy!!guIIIltYY!!Guil--guilty!guilty!GUilTY!GUILTY!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As always, it looks like we have uncovered the real truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We? I don't remember you helping out much in this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth. How is Matt Engarde?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have left Ms. von Karma in charge of his incarceration. I'm sure he's getting a full-course meal of whip leather right about now.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very good. That was a close one, wasn't it, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes... I plan to pay my debt to society for my own crime, Your Honor. ... This trial was the first time I had stood on the witness stand, and when I did... I really felt hopeless.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She must be talking about the time Edgeworth really went after her... I guess she's trying to forgive him for what he did...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This witness... How should I put this... She has an illness.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you're going to say you would "choose death", that is of no concern to me.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">But... after that, when I was alone at the detention center... That's the first time I really saw myself and who I am.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">And today... When the two of you used your combined strength to convict Matt... I... I felt like I had finally been saved.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, this is the first time I've ever seen her smile.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I am really happy that you two were in charge of this case. I really don't know how to express how I feel at this moment... This is... This is the first time I've felt comfortable with myself; with who I am. Thank you so much, everyone!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It looks like we have resolved everything at last. As for myself, there are still a few things I'm confused about... But everyone seems to be in good spirits, and that is good enough for me. That is all. This court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You were great out there, Phoenix!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What I did out there was right... wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... This is the first time you've not gotten your client off. You got them a "guilty" verdict this time. But... You have to look past all of that, to what's really important. You now realize that there is something more than just getting a "not guilty", right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, I understand now.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix, think back for a second. Think to the moments before Ms. von Karma arrived with the final pieces of evidence. Think about the incredible decision you had to make...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Wright. Let's hear the defense's final statements on this matter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>I can't count on the evidence to help me anymore. I have to listen to my heart! Should I side with justice? Or should I save Maya's life?</thought> My client... Matt Engarde is...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Is he "guilty"... or is he "not guilty"...? Those were your choices then. And your answer... Your answer spoke to what being a "lawyer" means to you...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have good news. Maya is now safe in police custody!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Pearls--</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You're telling us the truth, right Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-Yes... She's quite safe. She is on her way here as we speak in a patrol car.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Aaaaaaaaah! Mystic Maya! Mystic Maya's safe!! You did it! You really did it, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oww... She punches deceptively hard for a kid...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... I believed in you. I kept saying to myself: Mr. Nick will save her... Mr. Nick will save her... Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, um... Thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ms. von Karma...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... About earlier... Uh... Thanks... OWW!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I don't think you'll ever understand... Ms. von Karma.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't worry. She may in time. After all, I was like that myself, until a year ago...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Edgeworth...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For my own personal victories... and for guilty verdicts... I used every dirty trick in the book. And so my win record remained spotless. But... A man appeared and stood fast against that selfish me. I fought him in my usual manner, and tasted my first defeat. I felt like I had lost everything because of that. And then... It was my turn to sit in the defendant's chair. And I was saved... by that person I called my "enemy"... I couldn't forgive myself for all that had happened. So I left the Prosecutor's Office. And I left that note... "Prosecutor Miles Edgeworth chooses death"...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...But that was not what happened. After I left the Prosecutor's Office, I finally came to realize something. And it was in that moment of clarity that everything began to change.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We prosecutors use anything we can to attack the defendant. But every time we did so...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No matter how desperate the situation... instead of giving up like most people, that man would hold strong with his undying faith. And then, before I knew it... I began to trust in that man as well.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It doesn't matter how many underhanded tricks a person uses... The truth will always find a way to make itself known. The only thing we can do is to fight with the knowledge we hold and everything we have. Erasing the paradoxes one by one... It's never easy... We claw and scratch for every inch. But we will always eventually reach that one single truth. This I promise you.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">The "truth"...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. That's the reason why prosecutors and defense lawyers exist. But I'm sure you knew that already, didn't you Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's why you couldn't forgive me; this man who went into hiding. Isn't that right? This man who only had his sights set on "victory", who ran away into the night...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah! Is... Is Mr. Edgeworth right, Mr. Nick...!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You really let me down...</thought> When you disappeared, I felt... betrayed. The reason I decided to become a lawyer to begin with... Was because I believed in the things you said to me, all those years ago... And you... You betrayed your own words. That's why... one year ago, I made up my mind. I decided that the Miles Edgeworth I knew had died... ...At least, that's what I told myself.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-Ms. von Karma...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Franziska threw something on the ground just now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is... an electromagnetic receiver.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't that the thing she used to track Detective Gumshoe...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll return this to the precinct later. There's something else...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah! Isn't that Ms. von Karma's whip!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"I'll never set foot in another courtroom again"... I'm sure that's what she's saying by this action...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You should keep this, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Umm... OK.</line>
<line speaker="???">Nick!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......! M-M-M... MAYA!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mystic Maya! Mystic Mayaaaaaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, Nick! I knew you would come through! You got Engarde convicted, like I knew you would... And on top of that, you even rescued me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, of course I did! You know I would never desert you! But we sure pressed our luck this trial... You're really lucky to be standing here!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whatever, whatever. Look, it's over, OK? Besides, if I did croak, I would just come back and haunt you like a bad ghost through Pearly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Is it really that easy to do something like that...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Th-Thanks a lot... Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Don't mention it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Um... I'm relieved you're alright.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey... It looks like you've made some real progress, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Umm... Well, I suppose I'm a little different from who I was a year ago.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Heh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Alright! I think it's time we got out of this depressing place!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Where are we going!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Food, Nick! FOOD! Grub! Chow! I'm starved! I'm so hungry even you look like a nice, juicy burger on a bun to me, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You think I look like a burger...? I'm a Prime Rib at least!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Come with us, Mr. Edgeworth! Please!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Uh, um... If you insist...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright... So how about we hit up our usual burger joint...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't be silly, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This case messed up that awesome evening, and got in the way of my gourmet food. So I've decided that we have to make it up by having another feast!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Another feast...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">C'mon, Nick! FOOOOOOD!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal! Sorry to keep you guys waiting!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gumshoe! Are you alright!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, but I'm really embarrassed. I didn't think I would hit a telephone pole, of all things.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A telephone pole...? <thought>Then, it wasn't a red light that got him...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ya did it again, City Boy. I felt like my dear ol' heart was gonna give out on me! And I ain't jokin'!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah! It was more exciting than the very last episode of the Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-Thanks...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Now lookie here, mister snooty prosecutor! Don't ya reckon ya bullied Mr. Wright too hard!? If ya don't start bein' a lot nicer to him, he might just kick it... Tonight, even!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Umm... I'll keep that in mind.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well, come on now! Everyone gather 'round! Y'all are gonna get yer picture taken by a genuine professional photographer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like Lotta bought herself a new camera...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, pal... At least we can put this messy case behind us now. Come on! Tonight's all about eating, so let's go chow down, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Amen to that, pal! Amen!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">You know, when you think about it, you were the one who saved the day, Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? Me? ...You really think so?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He's right. If it wasn't for the three items you took... I think this trial would have had a very different ending.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah, well, you know... It's... Ho ho. Ho ho ho ho. Ho ho ho ho ho. ...Huh? Wait. That's odd... When I ran off with the things from De Killer's hideout... I was sure I took 4 things total, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Four?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, I'm sure I put one of the items in my coat pocket...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There was a fourth item...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Aw, come on y'all. It's over! But whoo boy, I tell ya! You really are somethin' else! Between getting' accused of murder and getting' kidnapped... Never a dull moment with you, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hahaha, you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why does she look so happy about that...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But being shut away for two whole days... Weren't you scared...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, it was really scary. I felt so hopeless. So to keep my mind off of things, I drew a picture!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Sounds like ya had it rough, gal! So where's this picture of yers?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yeah! I want to see it! I want to see Mystic Maya's picture!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Hmm... You know, I don't know where it went...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Aww... That's too bad...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-Well, it's alright! It wasn't anything important anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ah... It sure is nice to finally see them both smiling again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it, Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This thing is picking something up.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! That's! That's Ms. von Karma's receiver! Ugh. Thanks to her, I had the most awful experience of my life, sir! I can't believe she stuck a tracking device on me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's odd. Even though you're standing right here... The tracking device seems to be in a different location.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh... It's probably busted or something, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... ...Well, it doesn't matter. I'm afraid it's about time for me to excuse myself. I still have some work to do.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh!? But Mr. Edgeworth! You haven't even eaten anything yet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And you've eaten way too much, you glutton!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I had fun tonight. Now, if you'll excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I just want to say... Thanks, Edgeworth. You really saved me out there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hmph. If anyone should be saying thanks, it should be me, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I feel like words alone aren't enough here... I wonder if there's anything I can give him to express how I feel...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's this...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you... It's all thanks to you two. You... and her...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... What's this...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... It's my way of saying thanks...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I... see... Well, it's the thought that counts...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I guess I'm not very good at this showing my appreciation thing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You don't need to thank me. I was only doing my job.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It looks like Mr. Edgeworth has left, Mr. Nick. Hey, Mystic Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hm? Yes, Pearly?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I guess you two can go back to being lovey-dovey, right? You and Mr. Nick, I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">P-Pearly! Would you cut it out already!? You're embarrassing me!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Um, anyway... So, who's paying for this lovely dinner party?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">As if you need to ask! Everyone say, "Thank you" to Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah, yeah... I'm kinda at the point where I can't even buy instant noodles, pal. So I kinda already put your name on the bill.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yeah, I got me a situation just like that myself. There's this camera shop in this hotel, see... And I just bought myself this good ol' beauty here! It'd better be anyhow for $3,000!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Huh? Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Actually, I reckon ya bought it for me since it's on yer tab and all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Isn't this great, Mr. Nick!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Why do I suddenly feel like screaming?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Aww, ya don't need to hold back now, ya hear?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, pal! Time to let it all out!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">This is going to be the first time I hear the real you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Go on! It's been a while since I heard you say it. I've been busy being a hostage and all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Alright then... If you say so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You really came through for me, Nick! I had to hide that letter, but I knew you'd find it. I really feel like I've been living on the edge lately. I mean, I've escaped death three times now! Pretty cool, huh? I feel like a pro!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm so happy that you could save Mystic Maya, Mr. Nick! And I'm so happy for the two of you! Speaking of... I think this hotel is a popular place for honeymooners... So I sort of... made reservations for the two of you... Just in case...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, pal. It looks like I'm back on the force again. Mr. Edgeworth had a long talk with the Chief, and he got me reinstated for my sake! I heard he said things like, "Letting that one go is bad for all of society." I knew it! Crashing headlong into everything is the only way to live, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I, Maggey Byrde, am retiring this uniform as of today, sir! I'm going to be a waitress from now on. And bring smiles and joy to the people who come by the restaurant, sir! I hope you'll stop by sometime, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes... Are you here to visit a patient? Hmm... I'm Director Hotti... Hoh, hoh. Recently... Hmm, yes... That girl, you know... I haven't seen her around... Hmm, yes... But I remember... If I even laid so much as an eye on her, it would go, "Crack!". Hmm... ...It didn't matter if I got whipped though... Hmm... Hmm, yes... Hoh, hoh.</line>
<line speaker="Max">It's time to begin our quest of world circus domination sweetie!! And to let the world know we are serious, I plan to make a fabulous flight to Zimbabwe!</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Hey Max! What do you think Zimbabwe is like? Do you think there are castles made of cake, and bunnies who can talk...?</line>
<line speaker="Max">I think if there are any talking bunnies, even they won't laugh at Moe's jokes!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I'm ready! I'm ready! There's no way these jokes are gonna fall on deaf ears. I'm going to be more contemporary with my humor! Moe Curls, R-R-R-Represent!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">We've got our new act all worked out! Prepare for the "Hallelujah Chorus"!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Say something will you! You're supposed to start this off! Get on with it...!!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">...What's this!? Drat, it's just an ordinary electric razor recharging on its stand! I can't believe this. Really! How long do they plan on making me do this!? Ah, but it's Edgey-poo's idea, so that means it must have a deep, hidden meaning. But... Why do I get the feeling... They wouldn't forget about me, would they? Ah, it was never like this in the old days! Everyone thought the world of me! They used to call me Queen Wendy, and treat me like royalty, and any man who hasn't heard about this is going to feel the pain of my heel, yes they're going to feel the burn, and speaking of burn, playing with fire is very dangerous and because of that, three of the warehouses where they stored the scenery were burned right down and that caused a huge stink that</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I appreciate everything you and Mr. Edgeworth did for me from the bottom of my heart. Oh, that's right. I received a letter from Ms. von Karma. She said that after I get out, I should feel free to consult her about anything at all. I'm really thankful to have met everyone!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">With this.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I heard you were planting things on a certain person. Things like tracking devices in his coat, for example.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh, that's right... Speaking of that man... He told me something very interesting.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">When I ran off with the things from De Killer's hideout... I was sure I took 4 things total, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems he put the last one in his coat pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... What are you going to do now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you running away?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... You may not be a genius like your father... But... You are a prosecutor. You have been and always will be.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Speaking of that... Wright gave me this to hold onto. <thought>Wright... You knew something like this would happen, didn't you...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm going to say this again. We prosecutors do not fight for personal honor or pride. I hope you will think deeply... About what you should be striking down with that whip.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... Wright... You were supposed to give me the whip!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe you can. Just like how Adrian Andrews did.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You were going to use her during the trial, right? But you... You were "dependant" on your father by using his tactics. Isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Today, you chased after me, after I had left you behind all these years. And that's why we're standing here now, side by side.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But I have no intention of stopping. If you say you are going to quit your walk down the prosecutor's path... ... Then, this is where we part ways, Franziska von Karma.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't sound very sure, Mr. Wright. Objection denied.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection denied. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This evidence clearly reveals the contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are the evidence and the statement just now related?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They aren't, are they...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Wright, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness's statement is clearly faulty, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry, but I can see nothing faulty. Unfortunately, I will have to penalize you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh, I must be on the wrong track...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! This court sees no reason to further prolong the trial. Nor is there any need for more time to decide the case against the defendant. This case is extremely clear. I see no room for misinterpretation of the facts. This court finds the defendant, Matt Engarde...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accused will surrender to the court immediately, to be held pending trial at a higher court within a month from today's date. That is all. This court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>