<xml>
<title>Farewell, My Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mystic Maya... M-Mystic Mayaaa... *sniffle, sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There, there, Pearls...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... I can't take it... anymore... ...Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">L-Look! It'll be alright! Everything may still work out.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hm...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The condition was that we had to get a "not guilty" verdict. And so far, the kidnapper has kept his word and hasn't hurt Maya. And he won't because Mr. Engarde hasn't been given a "guilty" sentence yet!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Unngg... Nnmff... *sniffle, sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Cheer up! We don't have time to stand around crying! We have to get going!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... Y-You're right...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mystic Maya is in much more pain than I am!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, that's right. So...</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey! You guys! Glad I caught you, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-Mr. Scruffy Detective...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Oh boy. Looks like Detective Gumshoe... has been dubbed "Mr. Scruffy Detective" in Pearls' book now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's just plain ol' "Mr. Dick Gumshoe" now, and I came to talk to you, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But we're kind of busy right now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, it's wilting a little!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'll... I'll give it some delicious water, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, it's OK... I already did that...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...The watering can... Where are you, Mr. Watering Can...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Did he just call the watering can, "Mr."?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">This is the... uh... Nickel Samurai, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! Please take care of Mystic Maya, and be her "Nickel Samurai", alright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Difficult-looking legal books stand in a formidable row. They mock me.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! Do you need to look something up in one of these law books, Mr. Nick!? Wh-Which book is it!? Which book do you need!? ... Umm... I can't read those hard books, and... um... I can't reach them either...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">B-But I can read AND I'm tall, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Please stop competing with an 8 year old... It's disturbing...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My desk. Since I don't have time to sit, it's unusually clean...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! I cleaned it up even more for you last night!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">B-But I can get it even more cleaner, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Aaah! That's... That's for the toilet!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What a mess. Literally...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what are you going to do from now on?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whadaya mean, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, you've been fired, right? So, do you have a new job lined up yet?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, that! A-Ah... What am I supposed to do now, pal!? I... I don't have anything coming in at all until my next payday!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What are you talking about!? You don't have another payday!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... I guess that means I'm just gonna half [sic] to work here at your place, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-SAY WHAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You'll be searching for things that will prove Mr. Engarde's innocence all day, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well... yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So yeah! I'm going to help you, pal! I've got lots of experience in investigating, and watching over people's places! And I'm great at making really simple meals, pal! I'll take care of it all!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Come on, Mr. Nick! Let's let Mr. Scruffy Detective take care of things!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Ah... OK... By the way, what's your best dish?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Instant noodles, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why am I surrounded by people who only eat cheap, unhealthy foods...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...That was the first time I've ever seen Mr. Edgeworth act like that... Never thought he'd say something like, he didn't care if Ms. Andrews killed herself...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">H-He said that!? That's horrible...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But because of him doing that, we got the truth finally.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...The truth... <thought>Ms. Andrews' last testimony; I wonder if that was the truth...?</thought> I'll give you that there was nothing strange in her testimony itself. But... I still think there is something fundamentally wrong with the whole thing.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You mean about "that" thing, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why would she want to -- no, I mean, almost "need" to frame Mr. Engarde... I couldn't figure that out from anything she said all day!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Then... Then you're saying that testimony... was a lie...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not a lie, per se... It just feels like there's more here than meets the eye. Or that's what Edgeworth would like us to believe...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Th-That's such a dirty trick! Even that woman prosecutor was better than that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Franziska von Karma...</thought> Speaking of Ms. von Karma, do you have any more information on her condition? Wasn't she shot this morning!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ms. von Karma was shot today on the way to the trial by a pistol, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But she's going to be fine, right? I mean, Edgeworth said she was in "stable condition", but...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, she was shot in the shoulder, so she's OK and still hanging in there. They should be done taking the bullet out, so she's probably resting at the hospital.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which one...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What? Are you going to visit her, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No... Well, I was kind of thinking about it...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! You've actually got a heart, don't you!? She looked like she was being tortured to death not being able to go to the trial today, so maybe it'd be good for her if you went and let her whip you for a bit, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Let's go let her whip us, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now I'm DEFINITELY not going.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um... let's see... The name of the hospital... Oh yeah! The "Hotti Clinic"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That name sends a chill down my spine... Well, I guess it can't hurt to stop by and say hi...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, it's my attorney's badge.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! It's a little tarnished, don't you think, pal? Don't worry! I'll make it all sparkly shiny again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I... I'm really touched...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Have you heard anything from the kidnapper...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...No... not yet.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm sure once he hears what happened at the trial today, he'll call, pal. But remember! You can't provoke him when you get to talk to him!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">When I saw that button, I thought to myself, "This is gonna prove Mr. Engarde's guilty!"... But it looks like there was a lot more to it than I thought, huh pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're a pro. You should know better than to say something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">W-Well, I'm not a cop anymore. Just a regular helper around the office now, so...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if he misses working down at the precinct...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Who would've thought that this knife Mr. Engarde used to eat his dinner steak with...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Go on...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...That it would be stabbed into the victim's body by Ms. Andrews, of all people. I guess she just hated the victim that much, huh pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The question isn't why she hated the victim to that extend, but rather why she tried to pin the murder on Mr. Engarde.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I wonder if she really hates Mr. Engarde?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So this "Nickel Samurai" was really Ms. Andrews, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. This is either when she went to Mr. Engarde's room to get the knife... ...or when she was done with the foul deed. But I guess we'll never know.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It'll be OK! You'll see her again, little missy!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Y-Yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's really important that you don't give up!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">O-OK!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess a big voice really does give you a sense of presence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... I won't give up. Ever!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Cheer up! You can't give in, missy!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Y-Yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! I know! I'll show you something cool! How's this? It's a real, genuine pistol... ... I... I don't have my pistol or my police badge anymore...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Cheer up! You can't give in!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What are those two doing...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">People are jealous of my roguishly cool "detective look", pal. It's because of this look that I passed the detective's test, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But you know, people can't coast through life on their looks alone, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, you can't count on your looks alone.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow... I learned something new today...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is she alright...? After being shot, I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Her wound isn't that bad... Well, the gunshot wound anyway... But the wound to her pride, now that's a different story, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The wound to her pride?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, until now, she's always upheld the "Von Karma Creed", but since she came here, well, you've given her pride quite a beating, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I mean, she may act all grown-up, but she's really still just an 18 year old. ...Quite frankly, I worry about her, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's the first time I've seen that side of Mr. Edgeworth, pal. Forcing people to say what he wants them to during testimony... I want to know what in the world happened to him all this time he's been gone...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't believe it. Maya getting kidnapped all because of this guy... I mean, what kind of person is the real murderer anyway!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Maybe they're a big fan of Mr. Engarde?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But the kidnapper's voice... He sounded like an old man to me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">My impression of her has totally changed, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... So, where is she right now...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm sure she's being questioned down at the precinct. At the very least about messing with the body, and obstructing the investigation. And she'll probably be staying over at the detention center...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The detention center, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She was Ms. Adrian Andrews' mentor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Because of the suicide of the mentor she depended on, Adrian Andrews tried to follow her in an attempted suicide... Now the question is, who is Ms. Andrews relying on now...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you please take a look at this...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um... I can't think of anything to say about this, pal. ... Wh-Why don't I make us some instant noodles, instead?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That's OK... Really.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>From what the guard told me... It sounds like along with Mr. Engarde, Ms. Andrews is also being detained here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Then we should talk with them since we're here...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, but both of them are still in questioning.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hmm... And we don't have time to waste.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, visiting hours are almost over...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Smile, you're on candid camera.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitor's the visitor's room. Catching a few z's while he's standing; now that's a good way to spend free time.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Alright now, Mr. Nick! Let's go look for clues! We have to, for Mystic Maya's sake...</line>
<line speaker="???">You shall not pass!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*gasp* Ms. Oldbag!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Don't devalue my name and turn it into a gasp, you spiky-headed poof! Because of you, I've been made to look like the bad guy again! Although, I did get a piece of gum from Edgey-boy, just as he promised... But what I really wanted was something much more valuable! I wanted Edgey-poo's heart! I want it all for me! It's all your fault! You've awakened the wild beast inside of this Oldbag! Grrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Aah! Ms. Oldbag!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Keep your hands off of me! This helmet is airtight! No air's gets in and no air gets out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... What does your helmet have to do with anything?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hmph! Don't think you can get me to move with silly questions! You're going to have to defeat me if you want to get by!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not hearing this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hey! I said no restless loitering and no touching! You're interfering with my watch, and that's a no-no!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh. Looks like in order to search around here... I have to first get this kooky "alien" to go away...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Ray Gun">*rata-tat-tat-tat-tat...*</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hah! You're a million light-years too early to be asking ME questions, whippersnapper!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh. Looks like the only way I'm going to get any investigating done... is to first do something about this kooky "alien"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Could you please take a look at this...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hmph! Sorry, sonny. I can't see it very well through this helmet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh. Looks like the only way I'm going to get any investigating done... is to first do something about this kooky "alien"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I see that look in your eyes! You stop thinking I'm an alien from outer space this instant!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow. Everybody looks really busy with something or another...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... They're probably strengthening the evidence for tomorrow's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Detective">Hey! Hurry up with that, will ya!? Pass that victim's list around! ...Now you're speaking nonsense! There's more than 100 people on there!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, Mr. Nick...? Is Mr. Engarde a really bad, terrible criminal...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Actually, Pearls, never mind. It sounds like they're working on a different case...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Detective">"...Very well. Now why do you want to work for our company?" "Well, that would have to be because I feel I would like to help this company grow."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He must be doing image training for corporate interviews.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be the chief of the detectives here. He's glued to his computer screen.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">WHAT!? Prosecutor von Karma was shot in front of the courthouse!? Wh-Who did it!? Who shot her!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have a sneaking suspicion that even Gumshoe could do this guy's job...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Never thought I'd ever come back to this place...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Hmm, yes... Are you here to visit a patient? Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, hi... ...Wait a second! You're...!</line>
<line speaker="???">Hmm, yes... I'm Director Hotti... Hoh, hoh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why are you still here!?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes... What is it? Hmm... Can I help you? You can tell me... Hmm, yes...</line>
<line speaker="???">Director Hotti!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes... I'm Director Hotti... Hoh, hoh. ...Oh, you're the man from this morning. Hmm, yes... What is it?... Uh huh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Director. Franziska... How is Franziska von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm... You don't need to worry. Hmm, yes... She's in good hands... Because, you see... I'm personally taking good care of her... Hmm, yes... Hee hee. Hmm, yes... and that thing... that surgery... It went well.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You have my gratitude.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looks like Edgeworth doesn't know about this "Director" and his secret...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hotti">She looked so pitiful; absolutely terrified. Hmm, yes... But I understand, hmm... Hmm, yes... Her opponent was a gun, after all. Uh huh. And when I snuck up on her real secret-like, she would scream really loud. Hmm, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see.</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Ah, but she's really cute too. When I'd do that, she'd whip me with her whip, uh huh... Boy did I cry like a baby. Hmm, yes... But I think I could get used to it. Hmm... Hmaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">You're so mean, uh huh... So mean... my frisky Friska. But that's good too-- Hmaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah! OK, OK... I... Hmm, yes... It's time for my IV drops. Hmm, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! I knew I shouldn't have come here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be the waiting area. It's got the feeling of one and there are sofas lined up... but I don't see all that many patients.</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes... well, visiting hours are over. That's why... Hmm... It's time for nightly consultations to begin... Mine, that is... Heh heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Isn't there anyone keeping an eye on this guy...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder where that door way down there leads to...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Oh, that's the X-ray room. Hmm, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-H-How did you know what I was thinking!?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes... Well, it's... Because that's the X-ray room... Uh huh, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There is something very peculiar about this guy... Because I know it's not me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This patient is undergoing rehabilitation.</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Wasn't that patient standing in the same spot the last time you came to visit? Doesn't look like they've moved any closer to the reception desk, huh? Is this clinic really doing anything!? Is that patient really getting better!? Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! Don't just cut into my monologue like that! I'm explaining things here!</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Ah, sorry. Hmm, yes... Most sorry... Yes... Uh, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the clinic's reception desk, but it doesn't look like there's anyone at the counter. On the wall is this month's "Word to the Wise": "Put your best foot forward." Putting this up at a general clinic like this is doesn't really mean much, does it...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But! But that would've been too much!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah! You looked like you were deathly scared until only a few minutes ago...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was the only logical course of action given the bullet was still lodged in your shoulder. But with me doing so... I found myself having to clean up after you and that irresponsible deal you made.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I know what "deal" he's referring to...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. von Karma. You made a deal with Ms. Andrews yesterday, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In order to make sure you got your guilty verdict on Mr. Engarde, you told Ms. Andrews to not testify in court today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You're denying it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All while hiding Ms. Andrews' own crime?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess that's all I get...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ms. von Karma. Adrian Andrews believed you when you said, "If you don't tell the truth of what really happened, then Engarde will be found guilty."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because of that, she is now in danger of being found guilty herself! All because she believed in your words until the very end...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you had to know she was... OWWW!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What's wrong? Why did she suddenly cut you off...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Probably because she thinks I had the advantage in that argument... ...Edgeworth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What happened today at the trial, Edgeworth? That was not like you at all...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I mean, I know you knew about Ms. Andrews' condition. You could have made her testify as many times as you wanted, but to go that far...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Ah, but she wouldn't testify about THAT until I said something. Listen, Wright. The courtroom is a garden of judgment. I am putting myself on the line when I stand in there. And that's why I made the witness do the same... It's only natural.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By the way, Edgeworth... You were really angry in court today... That's rare for you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Witness! That card... Give it to me! Hurry! Do you have any idea what you have stupidly, yet inadvertently done!? This... I can't believe you hid this from me all this time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That card... What in the world is it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... You mean this...? ... Listen, Wright. This is top secret information. You absolutely cannot leak this. A special investigation team has existed for a number of years, but few know of it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Their task is to find the "owner" of this card... A man called Shelly de Killer. And just as his name states, he is a "killer", an assassin. The best, at that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>An assassin!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So who is this "Shelly de Killer"?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"De Killer" is the name of a long standing line of assassins.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Long standing?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The name first appeared about 100 years ago, I hear. Shelly is the professional name of the third heir to the De Killer name.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So because his professional name is "Shelly", he leaves cards with a shell on them...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He has a habit of making sure to leave a card by the body of his victims.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Why would he do something like that...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We think it is a part of his duty to his clients.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His "duty"?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If he leaves a card, then his clients can be assured it was he who killed the victim. It also serves as insurance against any charges being pushed onto his clients.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I see...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">De Killer values the trust between his clients and himself above all else. It seems that this is one honorable assassin with a moral conscience.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess that even honorable assassins can exist...</thought> So, you think this assassin... You think he's the one who did the killing in this case?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would appear that way. The discovery of the card basically confirms it, wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Shelly de Killer, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I've been put in charge of this case. So I can't give you any help with reagards to clues or evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You sure are hardnosed. Totally different from Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...And that is why he was fired.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's got a point...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I noticed something at the trial today. You were behaving in a very strange manner. ...Is something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess... I should just tell him.</thought> Maya... She's been kidnapped.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">K-Kidnapped? What does the kidnapper want!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An acquittal.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I see. I had no idea. ... I will prepare a rescue team as soon as possible, and resolve this by tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">R-Really!? Did you hear that, Mr. Nick!? M-Mr. Edgeworth is going to...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Stop trying to console me, Edgeworth! I don't need your pity!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no way you can find her. We don't have even a single clue to go on.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's only one way to save her. I... I have to get an acquittal somehow! It's the only way!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Wright. Listen, you need to know something. Juan Corrida was killed by Shelly de Killer. And the client who ordered the job... is Matt Engarde... Your own client.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please, stop! ...I can't listen to you. I can't believe that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I see. Well, if you want to continue your investigation, you will need this.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The hotel right now is restricted to police personnel only, as we are looking for any clues that might lead us to Shelly de Killer. If you take this with you to the hotel, I'm sure they will let you enter.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...In any case, I must attend to the preparations for Maya's rescue team. We'll meet again, if anything should happen. Now if you'll excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick? Do you... Do you think... Mr. Engarde hired an assassin...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No way! <thought>I mean, he doesn't have a Psyche-Lock...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Y-Yeah, I guess not...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya... Please... All I ask is you make it home, safe and sound!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Heh heh. I guess even kidnappers can be a little clumsy. Clumsy enough to drop a card like this for me. And even though he said he was an "assassin", I bet he's just making that up, like how Nick does with everything in court. Anyway, let's try out the card trick with this card I just found...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sounds like I got the door open... OK! Time to go take a look around!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I've unlocked the door with this card... I should probably go and take a look around...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-What is this place...? I've got a feeling I'm not in the hotel anymore... Are those videos over there? ...Well, I'll worry about that later. For now, I should be looking for clues. That way, I can show them to sis and maybe get out of here!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, I've never seen a TV this big before. Now where's the power button... Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Phooey. It's busted. I would so die a happy Samurai fan... if I ever got to see the Nickel Samurai on a TV like this. ... Ack! I can't believe I just made a joke about dying, all things considered...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What is this thing? An antenna... I guess? And this is... a VCR? There sure are a lot of electronic gadgets here. But what is an antenna doing here...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, hey. It's a computer. I've never really used one before. ... Um... I have no idea where the power switch on this thing is... Drat. There goes my plan to use this somehow to get out of here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's a framed picture sitting on this coffee table. It's a picture of a woman... She's kind of pretty. Hey, looks like something's written here... Let's see... I think it says, "With love... Celeste" I bet this could be a clue...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...That's weird. What's a figurine doing on a sofa in a place like this...? I think it's... a bear. Aww, how cute! But it's got a lot of cuts and slits on it... I wonder if it's some kind of puzzle or something...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's so dark in here that I can barely see, but... these kinda feel like... video tapes... All of them... Just what kind of room is this...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Unngh... Locked. Of course. And it doesn't look like I can use the card to open this door. There's a little hole at the bottom of the door. If only I was a little skinnier. Then maybe I'd be able to crawl through there...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can't see very well in this darkness, but it doesn't seem like there's anything there...</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, this simply will not do... I cannot have you wandering around at will.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eeeeeaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="???">...It seems... that your Mr. Wright is truly concerned about you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He is...?</line>
<line speaker="???">For now, I would suggest you remain cooperative. If you cannot, there are ways in which I can help you...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ways... You mean...</line>
<line speaker="???">"Dead men tell no tales" is how the saying goes, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"D-D-D-D-Dead"!?</line>
<line speaker="???">I'm almost certain I told you on our first meeting. I am... an assassin.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-No way... You're lying... I mean... An assassin...?</line>
<line speaker="???">...People are not always who they appear to be.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Niiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiick!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm? O-Oh yes, Pearls? <thought>Got caught up in my thoughts about Maya's situation...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Edgeworth has left, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess for now, I have no choice but to believe in Mr. Engarde. But I think I should listen to his story one more time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright! Let's get going too.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">OK!</line>
<line speaker="Jailer">I'm sorry, but visiting hours are over for today.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Aw...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh... I have too many questions I need to ask...</thought> I-I'm sorry, but I'm Phoenix Wright, a lawyer for one of the...</line>
<line speaker="Jailer">You're Mr. Wright, you say? Oh, yeah, there's a message here for you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A message...?</line>
<line speaker="Jailer">It's from Matt Engarde. ...Ah, here you are.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What did he write!? Is it something really important...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know. Well, let's see what it has to say... "To the lawyer dude. I've got something really important to tell you." <thought>Why do I feel uneasy all of a sudden...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... ... Oh, Mr. Wright. So actually... I have a favor to ask of you. I have this cat named Shoe. I didn't put out a lot of food when I left the house, so he's probably pretty hungry. You think you could drop by my house and feed Shoe for me, dude? My house is just a little ways down from the hotel, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Th-This is terrible! Let's hurry! We have to feed his cat! I'm sure poor Shoe's stomach is growling by now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, I guess...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A client's request is a request... Guess I should go check up on his cat.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Maybe if I show her this letter I got from Edgeworth...</thought> Um... Ms. Oldbag... If you would look at...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What!? You want me to look at this worthless piece of... .................. ...Edgey-pooooo...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... Is that her perfume, Phéromone d'Amour, I smell...? *shudder*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Let's see here... "Would you please allow this unsophisticated young person to conduct his investigation? Yours truly, Miles Edgeworth"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Y-Yours truly"!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hmph, that man's good at flattery. Fine. But only because Edgey-poo said so, you understand!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I just thought of something I have to do. Remember, no messing around! You do anything bad and I won't let you off the hook!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It looks like she has strong feelings for Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That may be, but you know nothing's going to come of it.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That's so mean, Mr. Nick! Feelings are meant to be told and shared!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Owww... <thought>Every time we talk about love, I always end up with a handprint on my face somehow.</thought> Um, so anyway, let's continue our investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">OK!</line>
<line speaker="Ray Gun">*rata-tat-tat-tat-tat...*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! What!? What now!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">One little thing, before I forget. You can't go into Engarde's room today.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Why?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">The police's main investigation team is going to be in there all day, you hear?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if they're the team in charge of investigating "De Killer"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">So don't go in there! Set one foot in there and you'll face the wrath of Wendy Oldbag!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the stage they were going to use for the post-ceremony stage show. After the show, there was supposed to be a press conference, but...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But that press conference...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was really the victim, Juan Corrida, trying to disclose something about Mr. Engarde.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But they're both heroes... Why would they do something so un-heroic?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They may look like heroes on the outside, but on the inside, they're only human.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, sure is dark...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'll go turn on a light!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow... So this is what a star's house looks like. Must be nice to be rich.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Come on, Mr. Nick! Let's find Shoe, the kitty-cat!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Shoooooe!</line>
<line speaker="Shoe">Meow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So I guess this is Shoe.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah, what a lovely cat. ...Hello, Shoe.</line>
<line speaker="Shoe">Meow.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Tee hee.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The cat seems to like Pearls.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Pardon me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">!</line>
<line speaker="???">May I help you with something, Mister...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, uh, we're lawyers. Actually, I'm Mr. Engarde's lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="???">The master's... Then, you must be Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes.</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, it's a pleasure to meet your wonderful self.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">I am the family butler, John Doe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nice to meet you.</line>
<line speaker="Shoe">Meow.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! There's a giant cooking hearth here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's actually a fireplace.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">How are they different, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>You know, I've never actually seen a hearth before, come to think of it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You should come and visit Fey Manor, then. I'll show you one when you do.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">A... A giant bicycle is flying through the air!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... That bicycle, Pearls, is one where you don't have to pedal, and it moves on its own.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Really!? Wow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But sorry to disappoint you, it can't fly.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Oh. That's too bad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a very comfortable and spacious lounge set. I wonder if famous stars drop by and sit around and have a good time. ...In any case, I don't really belong here, do I? ... Argh. What is with me and feeling inferior today...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah! There are masks here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. That one in the middle is the Steel Samurai. The ones next to that are the Pink Princess and the Evil Magistrate. They fought many battles against the backdrop of Neo Olde Tokyo.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow, you really know a lot about the Steel Samurai, Mr. Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>I don't know whether to laugh or cry that I know more about that show than a kid...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's another door over there.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You shouldn't go wandering off over there, Mr. Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes, Pearls. <thought>Now I know how Maya feels when I tell her to stop playing around...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">There's a small door at the bottom of this bigger door, Mr. Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet it's for Mr. Engarde's cat to use.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, you mean Shoe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The door... It's locked tight. Well, I guess that's to keep nosey people like me from entering it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You must know all sorts of things about Mr. Engarde, right?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Honestly, sir... I don't believe my master is capable of such a foul deed as murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Doe">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And, uh, anything else?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">No, not especially. It is not appropriate for a lowly servant to speak of the master or his affairs.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... How typically "butler-like", as it were...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Doe, how long have you served at this residence...?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Well, sir, I would have to say... maybe about one year?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Doe">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And, uh, anything else?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">No, not especially. It is not appropriate for a lowly servant to speak of himself and his affairs.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You know, I would've thought Mr. Engarde the kind to have a "maid" over a butler...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a very cute cat you've got here.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">It is my duty to take care of him. The master rather fancies Shoe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Doe">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And, uh, anything else?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">No, not especially. It is not appropriate for a lowly servant to speak of the family cat.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Well then. I guess I don't need this piece of scrap paper anymore.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You must know all sorts of things about Mr. Engarde, right?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Honestly, sir... I don't believe my master is capable of such a foul deed as murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Doe">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And, uh, anything else?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">No, not especially. It is not appropriate for a lowly servant to speak of the master or his affairs.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... How typically "butler-like", as it were...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was wondering if you wouldn't mind taking a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">I'm afraid I cannot offer up anything special about it. It is not appropriate for a lowly servant to speak of evidence for a trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Polite yet snotty with a touch of rude. He's the stereotypical butler alright.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you happen to know who this person is...?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">No, I would not. It is not appropriate for a lowly servant to speak of the master's acquaintances.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Then what in the world CAN I talk to you about!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-Mr. Nick! Being angry is bad!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">...Well, I'm afraid I must take my leave of you now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, we should probably get going ourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Ah, so young and yet already so accomplished. A master of law...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But there is also a lot to be proud of in being a butler, in charge of the house and all.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Thank you for the compliment, sir. ...People are not always who they appear to be. ...Now if you'll excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Shoe">Meow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like we're the only ones here.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">And yet... the hotel seems so busy somehow...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Probably because the police team is scouring for clues about "De Killer"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I want to eat a meal with Mystic Maya again...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, me too...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Whenever I watch Mystic Maya eat like she does... It makes me happy about eating, and then I can eat a lot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, then... How about after we wrap up this case, we all go out for a huge twenty-course feast!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">OK! Let's work really hard, then!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey, City Boy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">L-Lotta... You're still here...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Reckon course! An investigative photographer eats or starves on her ability to snap up the scoop, yeah!? And this hotel just has that "aura of mystery". Ya know, like something's always about to happen.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But... Do you have a camera?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Reckgiven!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">A photographer's gotta have cameras out the ear like corn to be a real pro, ya know!? So I'm hangin' around here... ... ... Speaking of cameras and feedin' the mouth, do ya have mine, ya bread-thief!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why can't you drop that "thief" thing already?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Aww, how lovely! The teddy bear looks happy to be surrounded by so many beautiful flowers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Pearls really seems to like teddy bears a lot.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... I wonder if... Lotta also...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I didn't touch them! Wasn't me, I tell ya! I give ya my word!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I get the impression Lotta helped herself to one of them...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Compared to the flowers on the other side of the hall, these are much more gorgeous. Although, other than sunflowers and tulips, I have no idea what any of them are.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, Mr. Nick? What's this flower called?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a sunflower... I think.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">This flower over here is pretty too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a tulip, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Callin' everythin' a sunflower or a tulip; don't reckon even little kids'll fall for that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a piece of paper taped to the door that says, "Matt Engarde's Room".</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">The old lady told us about this, didn't she? That we can't go in this room tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if an investigation briefing is going on right now inside... Without Detective Gumshoe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I want to ask you about the night of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">What? Ya really gonna shell out the bucks for the info I got!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lotta, you were loitering in this hallway the night of the murder, were you not?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well, kinda... But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Brace yourself, Wright. Here it comes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I didn't exactly hang around here the entire time, ya know. Followed a few stars around... got a few autographs, shook a few hands, had a soda-pop with a few of 'em too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like she wasn't here the entire time, that night...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">The security lady also wasn't in this hallway the whole time either.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess this means there's no one who can tell us who came and went that night...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, about the note that was inside your camera case.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Oh, that ditty I wrote?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... Can I believe what you've written?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ya mean the stuff about Engarde shovin' his manager lady onto Corrida?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ah, well, I reckon ya best not be believin' that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Look, I sorta wrote that on a whim, ya know? Writin' whatever came to mind.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">"Whatever came to mind"...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yeah, when ya get down to it, it's just a lotta random bull dooders.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey, what's with ya!? Why ya starin' at me like my grandpa used to!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey, and why do you look like you suddenly got older too!? Or am I just shrinkin' here!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ah! My baby! My $1,600 baby! What's with that red-coated prosecutor anyhow!? The guy told me it was "evidence" and refused to give it back to me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, that's kind of how it is...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey, hey. Yer that red-coat's friend, ain't ya? So put in a few good words for me and git me back my camera.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You want me to do what!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Listen, nag the guy real good fer 'bout five hours and I guarantee he'll give it back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why don't you do your own dirty work...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, would you please take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Nope. Sorry. No can do. Only thing I wanna see is a steamin' hand towel.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, what? A steaming hand towel...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Need one for my eyes. Today just ain't a good day for my eyes to be lookin' at stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How convenient! Maybe I'll have to use that one next time you show me something!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">... Well, I reckon it's time for me to get going. A tabloid photographer without a camera is just a "tabloid", huh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Yeah, I guess so.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Keep yerself together out there, ya hear!? I'm comin' to see ya in court tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-OK, I'll see you then...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">And you too there, little 'un. Keep up the good work, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">OK!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Don't be picky about yer food, now.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">OK!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">And make sure ya do all yer homework, ya hear?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">OK!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">And if you happen to find yerself a camera, make sure ya bring it right to me, ya--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you please just leave already!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a piece of paper taped to the door that says, "Juan Corrida's Room". <thought>I wonder what EXACTLY happened in the room behind this door...? Even now, no one really has any idea...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">... Ooongh... Oooonnngh... Ooongh... Oooonnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-M-Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What is that otherworldly, ghastly moaning...!?</line>
<line speaker="???">... Ooonnnn... Oooo... Nnnghff... Ghfff...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... I hate evil ghosts... Waaaaaaaaaaaaah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think it's a ghost... Maybe it's a demon!?</line>
<line speaker="???">E-Excuse me!? Watch who you're calling a demon, brat!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Aaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Zoinks! It's the alien!!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Who are you calling an alien!?</line>
<line speaker="Ray Gun">*rata-tat-tat-tat-tat...*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, it's just you, Ms. Oldbag. What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What is wrong with young'uns today!? I came down here to pay my respects to my poor Juan, and you're disturbing me!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So that's a bed...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup. It's big, but it's a bed.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Aaah! Mr. Nick! It's sooooo soft!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How easily children are entertained.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Bottles of cosmetics are scattered all over the floor. This is probably where Mr. Corrida fought his assailant.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">These glass shards...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They're probably from the glass vase Ms. Andrews knocked over.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So, the Nickel Samurai's costume was in here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I can't believe Mr. Corrida went so far, just to say bad things about Mr. Engarde...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well, it was a "press conference", so he had to go in costume.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But weren't Mr. Engarde and Mr. Corrida friends?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They weren't friends. They couldn't be friends because they were rivals.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So, a "rival" is someone who is a "strong enemy"!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Pearls is really fired up over this... And I don't have an answer for her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a beautiful wine glass, and there's... tomato juice in it.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ewww. Tomato juice. I don't really like it much.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a bottle of it on the table over there. That's probably where this came from.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please talk to me about the night of the murder just one more time.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I talked about it plenty at the trial! I was fooled, tricked... DECEIVED by that fraud of a photographer and her note! She was loitering around here with that imbecilic look on her face!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">"With that imbecilic look on her face"... OK, got it.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">N-Now hold on a second there you little pipsqueak! If you're going to take notes, at least make me sound better than that!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, alright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now I've seen everything...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">But you know, I was working that night too, doing my job, minding my own business. So it's not like I had time to waste standing around here the whole night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was wondering if you could tell me a bit more about Mr. Corrida.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">He was the most popular star, you know... Especially where it counts -- in my book!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I heard that he was lagging behind in the polls against Mr. Engarde...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Um, w-well, that's just a recent thing. Bad luck and all that, you know. But! He was going to become an even bigger star than he used to be! Look! Just look at this mountain of presents! It's a show of the mountain of feelings all his fans had for him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, the mountain is pretty big, and certainly nothing to shake a stick at.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm? What is it, Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">The presents. They're all bears... right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's got a point... There isn't a single thing here that isn't a bear...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All of Mr. Corrida's presents from his fans seem to be... bears...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, that's because you can't think of Juan without thinking about bears!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Bears...? Why bears?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">You don't know!? When my dear Juan was training, he fought barehanded with a bear. He refused to give in and let the bear win, but after the fight, they became friends.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow... What a heartwarming story.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Look, it's just like in those young people's dramas. I can see those two tuckered out, down by a river going, "Heh... You... You sure can fight..." "You too, bub. You too."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Did all that really happen?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">It's in his biography, bub.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What a load of crock!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">So ever since then, fans have been giving him bears as presents.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... Nice... Bears...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-Wh-What is that infernal racket!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">It's one of the presents going off. Sounds like it's already 8 PM. Way past your bedtime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk... That startled me! I thought I was going to die for a second...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Eight PM... That's the time when the award ceremony ended that night, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Time sure flies... Hard to believe it's been two days since the ceremony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The transceiver!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hello!? Hello!?</line>
<line speaker="???">...This is not a phone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya! How is Maya!? You haven't hurt her, have you!?</line>
<line speaker="???">...It seems you were not able to fulfill your end of the bargain, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="???">I have heard the news. So it would seem my present did you no good...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">N-Noooo! Mystic Maya! Mystic Mayaaaaaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One more day! Please! All I ask is for one more day! I... I'll get a not guilty verdict for sure this time! Please...</line>
<line speaker="???">... I suppose if I must. I need that acquittal more than anything else, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Please... Please let Maya say something! I want to hear she's alright!</line>
<line speaker="???">Alright... hissssss... then... hisssssss... ssssssssss... ssss... a little... sssssss...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is with this static all of a sudden...!</thought> Hello!? Hello!?</line>
<line speaker="???">It seems... ssssss... hisss... sssss... bad... sssssss... hisssssssssss... ssssssssss... connect...sssssssssssss...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Dammit! Did the transceiver just suddenly break...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">ssssssssss... 'll excuse me... hisssssssssssssssss...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wh-What happened...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know. All of a sudden, it became nothing but static.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Aaaah... Mystic Maya! Mystic Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why did the transceiver suddenly break like that...? I should probably have an electronics expert look at it... The sooner the better!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! Welcome back, pal! I thought I'd make you a little something for dinner.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th...That's nice... Thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's a rich-man's luxurious full course meal... out of a can, that is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry you went through all the trouble to cook, but I don't have the time to eat.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, hey... You don't have a can opener here, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You've got to be kidding... And here I thought he had already whipped something up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, I know! There is one way I know how to be helpful! Ask me about anything you want, pal! Go ahead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, since he's here and offering... I wonder what I should try asking him about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The transceiver...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, Mr. Nick! You should ask Mr. Scruffy Detective about that thing.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What thing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh yeah! This thing just up and broke all of a sudden!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It... It broke, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When I was talking to the kidnapper, it just suddenly broke into static...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, it sounded like this.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't hear any static, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Huh??</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Maybe it fixed itself?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's strange... I'm sure it was making a loud static noise.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm... Maybe...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe what?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Maybe it was "electromagnetic interference", pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Electromagnetic interference"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh yeah! Do you know about this card?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Card?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth, for some reason, went pale the instant he saw this card.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, I know what this is, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You do?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No matter what way you look at it, I'd say it's a picture of a shell.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, that's it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh yeah! That's right! Mr. Edgeworth really likes those cooked snail things. Um, what are they called again...? "Escargot" or something like that...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! I think we just solved the mystery of why Mr. Edgeworth's face turned pale, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>As I suspected, Gumshoe has no clue...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... So what is "electromagnetic interference"...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's something that happens when a radio wave gets mixed up with another signal, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, when you put it that way...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I don't understand what you're talking about...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Like for example, when a cell phone goes off next to a computer screen, the stuff on the screen gets kinda fuzzy and starts acting funny, right?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Huh? ..."Kom-pu-ter"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Um, it's like when you use the dryer next to the TV, and the screen starts looking weird.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">O-Oh, yes, the TV does do that! Hmm... Oh, so that's what you're talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She seems amazingly happy at being able to understand this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So the room you were in when that interference to the transceiver happened... There's gotta be something there that's sending out very strong radio waves, pal! Something like... Hmm... Like a listening device or something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, speaking of that! Where were you when it happened?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">We were in Mr. Corrida's room... The scene of the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What!? That's it! I'm going to sneak into the precinct and get a bug sweeper! I'll meet you at the crime scene later, alright pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, wait! Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh yeah, baby! It's investigating time! I'm on fire, pal! My fingers are itching to go! Yeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeah!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">We should be going too, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright, let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My desk. Since I don't have time to sit, it's unusually clean...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! I cleaned it up even more for you last night!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! You're finally here, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry to keep you waiting.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Do you have the... um... "bug sweeper"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, well, you see... I got busted trying to sneak in, pal. Then suddenly, I'm staring at the precinct doors. ...From the outside, I mean. So yeah... I couldn't get one of the police bug sweepers...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... What do you mean you couldn't get it!? We need that item!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, hey, calm down, pal. I didn't say I didn't get one, just not the police's.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow... So this is a "bug sweeper"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks a little... broken.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, this was made when I was in elementary school, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? By who?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Me, of course! Ah, seeing this sure brings back memories...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, don't look down on it, pal! Sure, it looks a little run down... But I put my heart and soul into building this puppy here!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Your heart and soul...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It'll work! Trust me, pal, it'll do the job! But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But you can't set the sensitivity... So it's going to beep at anything that gives off electromagnetic waves.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But isn't it better that way?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho! Well, anyway, since I brought it all this way, might as well give it a whirl, right pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm getting that sinking feeling again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OK, now I'll tell you how to use this baby! There's a listening device or some other sort of bug hidden in this room, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So we're going to find it, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Right. Now, first, let's turn the sweeper on. Next, touch the sweeper and take a real good look around the room with it, pal. You can see how strong the radio waves are in an area by looking at the CHECK gauge. Once you find something that's giving off strong waves, the gauge will change... And when that happens, touch the gauge to really give the thing a long hard stare. There's a lot of things here that's going to give off radio waves, so let's take a good look at anything and everything that seems suspicious, OK pal!? Alright! I'm going to go stand outside and keep an eye out. Give me a yell if you find the bug. Got it, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a plain old calculator.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It says "50" on it. Maybe he was calculating his allowance?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A whole 50 cents?? Um, maybe if he was a spirit medium...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it certainly looks like an alarm clock.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What's wrong? Why do you look troubled?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I just can't imagine the listening device being inside this alarm clock. It just, um, sort of reminded me of something that happened a long time ago...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, anyway, it looks like the listening device isn't in here.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow, there's a really delicious loaf of bread in here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like it's been on "keep warm" all this time since the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Well, Mr. Scruffy Detective always says, "Got to keep the trail and crime scene warm."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think the "keep warm" in that case is a little more metaphorical...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a small video camera. ...No listening device in this gizmo.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Everyone's trying to make everything smaller and smaller lately, aren't they Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what it seems like.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But! I want to grow bigger and bigger!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, eating only vegetables isn't going to help you there. You have to eat meat too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the TV's remote control. But it doesn't look like the listening device is in here.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, so I was thinking... I wonder if a TV remote works on other things... Like... Could I make you change your expressions like TV channels? Zap!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Hey! <thought>Hmm, but if I could... Ooh, the people I would give the ol' mute button to!</thought> Well, I don't think it's going to work on me... Why don't we try it on Maya tomorrow, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... OK!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no listening device in that notebook computer, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Umm... What's a "notebook computer"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Do you know what a "notebook" is?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes! It's a small book with paper that you can write on! ...So?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, that thing is like a notebook in a way. It's basically a small laptop.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Umm... Mr. Nick... What's a "laptop"...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">This is a... a refrigerator, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I really don't think the listening device is in something like this.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Because it's filled with nothing but healty vegetable juices, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, yeah, sure. <thought>What does that have to do with listening devices?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What's this? It sort of looks like a hot water pot, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, well, it's kind of like a hot water pot, I guess. But instead of hot water, coffee comes out.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Really!? Th-This pot can do that!? ... Um, is there a pot that orange juice comes out of...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think there's anything like that, Pearls. Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, the water in this hot water pot has run out! I'll go get more water for it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-OK. Sounds good. <thought>Looks like she's forgotten all about looking for the listening device...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, the listening device isn't in the air conditioner.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Aah! Yuck! This air filter is covered in dust and dirt...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... Come on, Mr. Nick! Let's wash it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if being a neat freak makes even the tiniest dust bunny look colossal...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh, nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't really think the listening device is in the TV of all places.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Looks like the TV was left on, and it's now showing an old samurai movie.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. This channel plays all sorts of international movies, as well as domestic ones.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You know, every time I watch one of these old movies, I always think, "Wow, these Japanese stars are really good at English!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Um, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">When I grow up, I want to study Japanese!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should probably keep my mouth shut here, and not destroy her dream...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lamp, check. Listening device... nope.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">There are a lot of lamps in this room, aren't there Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">And they're all on. You shouldn't do that, Mr. Nick. Don't you know that's wasteful?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ah, yeah... I'll be more conscientious from now on. Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A cell phone... Nope, no bugs in here.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">A "cell phone"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What!? Don't tell me you don't know what a cell phone is!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...I'm sorry. I've never seen one before...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that she mentions it, my cell phone couldn't get any reception while I was staying in Kurain Village... And Pearls has never lived outside of that village, so... Well, I guess I can't say it's impossible to live without one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, the phone is the most common place for a "listening device", I'd say. But, let's take the receiver apart first before we get ahead of ourselves here.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow, you know a lot about electronics, don't you Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I know tons. Especially when it comes to taking them apart. It's my specialty. <thought>I'll leave the fixing part up to Gumshoe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So...? Is there a "listening device" in there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...No. <thought>And I really thought it had to be in the phone too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah, what a lovely bear...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">AAAAAAAAAAAAAH!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, this must be one of those fancy bear-shaped toy robots.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I-It's a robot!? It's a REAL robot!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, it's a real one.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">H-How many horse-powers is it? How many horsies!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Horsies...? ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Well, look, it's a bear, so... uh...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">The radio is on and playing something. Oh! It's "Kids' Question Corner"!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... Yes, why is it, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Why don't you listen to the radio program a little more, Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">There doesn't seem to be anything giving off radio waves there, Mr. Nick. Keep a careful eye on the CHECK gauge, and let's try again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This sweeper isn't exactly the best... Well, make do with what you have, right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">This is... This is just a giant stuffed teddy bear, right? It's the biggest one I have ever seen!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! So did you guys find it yet? The listening device, I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">No, not yet. But this bear's eye is...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Let's see, let's see... A perfectly normal stuffed bear with some really strong radio waves... Sounds like you found the device to me, pal. Let's dig this big fella's eye out and see what we've got.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">N-No! You can't! Such... Such a violent act...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oomph! *rip!*</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Noooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That's!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's a miniature camera... And it looks like there's more. There's a... transmitter, and a timer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A whattawhatta-mitter?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A transmitter, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh... Is this more of that "high tech" stuff...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this tiny thing is a camera...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup. It's a pinhole CCD camera, pal. It's a small, high-grade video camera mostly used in security systems.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So it's a video camera...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It runs on a battery, which comes with it in a set.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... there's no video tape in this camera...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is only the camera part here, pal. The tape recorder with the tape inside it is somewhere else.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Somewhere else?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The footage is changed into radio waves and then it's sent to that recorder.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So... It's sort of like a TV broadcast, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, you know, you're right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... what is a "transmitter"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's a device that sends footage the camera took to a specific destination. It's like a video version of a listening device, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like it's attached to a small, clock-like thing...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, that's a timer, pal. You can set it to turn the camera on and record at a certain time with it.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You can set it for a certain time...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup. Let's see... This looks like it was set to start at 8 PM and go for one hour.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eight PM? <thought>That was the time the award ceremony ended!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's no date set, so it's been recording every night, I'd guess.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-Mr. Detective! How long has this bear been here...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, I'm pretty sure it's been here since the night of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Then... Then maybe...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Maybe this camera caught the murder on tape!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And if you think about the angle the bear is at... It's bound to have had a clear shot of the whole crime, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So there was a camera... in this bear's eye...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And it was disguised as a present.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And I'm sure it was here on the night of the murder, pal. It's pretty big, so it stands out pretty well in my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... who gave Mr. Corrida this present?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I, ah, don't know, pal. But! This means that someone out there's got a video of what happened here that night!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Isn't there any way we can find out who that person is?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's impossible, pal. Radio waves can be sent almost anywhere, so there's no real way to find out...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh... *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is there really no way to find out...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So... the assassin's name is Shelly de Killer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And because he's "Shelly", that's why he leaves a "shell" card?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Ho ho ho ho! Oh, that's great. But you know, no matter how strange I may seem, at least my jokes don't make you cringe. Right, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Umm... Yeah, you keep on thinking that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It's a really tiiiiny camera.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A camera this size lasts about 3 hours with a fresh battery pack, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But what would something like this be doing in...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I'd say taking a secret video of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Which means... Someone knew there was going to be a murder here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This device looks like it was made by the criminal themselves. If it's only sending images, then I'd say it'd last about 80 hours, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You know a lot about these things, don't you Mr. Detective? Is spying on people a hobby of yours...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, no... I mean... You're making me embarrassed, putting me on the spot like this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why should he be embarrassed? Is there something I'm not getting here...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">The bear is really lovely, isn't it? It's so soft and fuzzy, and the face is really well-made...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I guess when you compare it to all the other presents, it is well-made.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, but I don't think the bear itself is a clue to this case at all.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... ...I got it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal. Let me borrow this mini camera for a bit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What are you going to do?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm going to go around to the electronic shops and see if I can find out who bought this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But that's impossible! I mean, it's already 9 PM!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Leave it to me! Even if I have to search all night, I'll find your man, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh yeah, baby! It's investigating time! I'm on fire, pal! My fingers are itching to go! Yeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeah!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...He's gone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But Mr. Scruffy Detective sure is a nice man. He's pushing himself so hard, all for Mystic Maya's sake...</line>
<line speaker="???">...You always manage to do things in the most ineffective ways.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ack!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You'll have to excuse me. I heard your conversation just now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Edgeworth! What are you doing here!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A rescue team has been created and deployed. I can't say I'm optimistic... but we have to move forward, one step at a time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I see... Thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't thank me yet. We still have to find her.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... So, there was a spy camera hidden inside this stuffed animal, huh? You are one lucky man, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you know this stuffed bear, little girl?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... I have no idea!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Of course not. The maker of this bear is a very expensive, luxury brand from overseas. It's completely hand-made and there are very few that are exported here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The camera and transmitter that scatterbrained detective took with him are dead ends. Things like those can be bought anywhere... However, this bear is different. By tracking how it got into this country, this bear can tell us who the buyer is.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">C-Can you really do that!? Mr. Nick, can he really?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well, I guess so...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It's 9 PM. I think I can still make it in time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll be taking this for now. I'm sure you have other things you have to do.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">See you soon, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why are you doing this...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I have no interest in explaining myself to someone who cannot comprehend. But besides that, Wright. Until court reconvenes tomorrow, you should concern yourself with this question: "Who was the person that murdered Juan Corrida?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The "real killer"...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you really still think it was Adrian Andrews?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To be honest... I don't know anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... You still have a little time left... Find the truth, Wright. Everything begins with the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Juan Corrida's real killer... Ms. Andrews' past... The kidnapper whose sole condition is an acquittal for Mr. Engarde... And... this card. Shelly de Killer...</thought> ...Maya. The only way I can save you now, is to find all the answers to this case tonight! I don't understand what your real intentions are, Edgeworth... but as you said, all I can do for now is find the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It's past 9:00 PM already, isn't it? I wonder... I wonder if Mr. Edgeworth has already found Mystic Maya...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>These things take time. I'd say probably not...</thought> The police are professionals, Pearls. They'll find her, so don't you worry. And if we can win a not guilty verdict tomorrow... then everything will be OK.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Y-You're right... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the real person who killed Mr. Corrida was...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That assassin... Mr. Shelly de Killer, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the card Ms. Andrews found at the crime scene seems to be proof of that. But if that's the case, then a new question comes to mind. Who was the one that hired De Killer to begin with? Who is his client?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You mean... Who asked for the murder...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That person didn't want to dirty their own hands in blood, but whoever this client is, they're still a killer.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Who... Who could have hired the assassin? Do you think it was Ms. Andrews...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder... But if she was the client... then why go through the effort to stab the knife into the corpse herself...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But if Ms. Andrews wasn't the client... Then... No, it can't be...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Matt Engarde himself...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">If Mr. Engarde really did hire the assassin...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then he is not innocent at all. Far from it, he would be guilty of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">B-But it can't be Mr. Engarde, right!? I mean, when we first talked with him...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Mr. Engarde, I'd like to ask you one more question. Did you kill Mr. Juan Corrida?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... Alright. Just so we're clear, dude, I didn't kill anyone, and that includes Juan Corrida, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I didn't see any Psyche-Locks at that time... Actually... That reminds me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Did you remember something, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, something Ms. Andrews said at the trial today. She said something interesting.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... So what is this "interesting thing"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, that's right. You didn't hear it, did you Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Juan had bet everything on the Jammin' Ninja this year. And if he lost the Grand Prix... He was going to make sure Matt was going down with him. That's what he thought anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It looked like somehow, Juan had in his hands a secret so powerful... that it would destroy Matt's acting career had it been revealed!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Engarde's "secret"...!? Wh-What is this secret...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know yet. But for now, let's think about it this way. Mr. Corrida was going to reveal this "secret". That means... Mr. Engarde had plenty of motive to have Mr. Corrida silenced. ... <thought>Which means we have to meet with Mr. Engarde. There's no way around it now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... I believe in your lawyer powers, Mr. Nick. I know you can bring us a miracle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm guessing by "miracle", she means a not guilty verdict... And she wouldn't be wrong either. It will take a miracle to pull this one off.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Why... Why did the kidnapper have to take Mystic Maya...? Why couldn't he have taken me instead!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Stop it, Pearls! Don't say things like that! If that had happened, then Maya would be hurting, I'm sure of it. Just like how you are hurting now, Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Y-You're right...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">One more day...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... If we can bring the trial to its end, she'll be back. Don't worry.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I decided I won't cry anymore, Mr. Nick. You're so brave and holding strong for Mystic Maya, so I have to do the same.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">If only I had studied harder during my training... I could be a bigger help to you, Mr. Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, don't worry about it. Really. Pearls, you're doing a great job...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! Is there a waterfall around here!? I feel that I must be made new under the rushing spring waters!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, Pearls... The only body of water around here is a lake.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh... Thanks anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">This is the first time I've ever met someone who loves to eat instant noodles.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something tells me Gumshoe isn't eating them because he genuinely likes them, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">He's working so hard, all for Mystic Maya's sake... I'm going to get him lots and lots of instant noodles as a thank your present!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... Is it really that important to be the Master of all the Stars? So important that you try to find your friends' weaknesses, and then expose them...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I wouldn't know...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I-Is it really alright for us to trust him? This person... Mr. Engarde...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>I-I don't know... I can't even answer that for myself. We have to go see him one more time! That's the only way to know for sure!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... I was wondering if that old lady is really a person from Earth. I mean, maybe she's really from waaaaaay out in outer space...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, actually, I was thinking the same exact thing. She's too strange to be from Earth.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Why did Ms. Andrews... Why did she frame Mr. Engarde, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She has some sort of grudge against Mr. Engarde... But why is that? That's something we still have to figure out...</thought> Let's go ask her, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">This person was Ms. Andrews' mentor... And she... killed herself, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right. And Mr. Corrida hid Ms. Inpax's suicide note... So to get it back, Ms. Andrews got close to Mr. Corrida... But the thing is, where is that suicide note now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow, it's really getting late, isn't it Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. It's past 9:00 PM already. But we still have some things to prepare for tomorrow's trial. <thought>There's still the matter of this "secret" Mr. Corrida held about Mr. Engarde... And Ms. Andrews' real intentions. These are two things I must know tonight!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But aren't visiting hours over at the detention center?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... I'm sure we'll think of something, Pearls. Don't you worry.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What is it, whippersnapper!? All I know is nothing that has anything to do with you is ever good! Like just now. I was handed this strange device for who knows what reason. And I was told to use it to search the whole hotel.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's... the bug sweeper, isn't it? <thought>The one Gumshoe made...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I don't know and frankly, I don't care. But the request came from Edgey-poo, so...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">And he said,</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"If you feel angry, direct your anger at that unsophisticated lawyer."</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">So, I'm going to feel free to direct all my anger towards you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... Gee, thanks a bundle, Edgeworth! What a pal you are!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They haven't cleaned up all the food yet.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Don't you touch it without permission! I brought a lunch box today, so I could pack it.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... But... Hasn't the food been out for two days already?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">When it's in your stomach, it's all the same!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, the digestive powers of an alien are wondrous...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I want to eat a meal with Mystic Maya again...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, me too...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Whenever I watch Mystic Maya eat like she does... It makes me happy about eating, and then I can eat a lot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, then... How about after we wrap up this case, we all go out for a huge twenty-course feast!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">My mind's like a steel trap, so I'm going to hold you to that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I was NOT talking to you!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">This is absolutely top secret, so you had better keep it to yourselves! I heard they found a spy camera hidden in one of the presents!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, very interesting.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I'm sure it was... you know... It was to catch poor Juan in the middle of a scandalous "meeting"!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">"Scandalous"...? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">It means... Well, you know, that gossip that's been going around about my dear Juan.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... You mean that thing about Ms. Andrews. <thought>But I'm sure she must've had some reason for getting close to Mr. Corrida...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I'll let you in on another secret, young'un. I know who planted that spy camera! It was that obnoxious, puffy-haired photographer girl! The nerve of some people! Spying on people by herself! As if I wouldn't want to see it for myself too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow! The alien actually admitted her true intentions for a change!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I don't know what you're thinking exactly, but I can bet that it's nothing good!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But I didn't say anything...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">So you want to know about Juan and that manager, right? Actually, as I hear it, they were something of a refreshing pair, those two.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I tell you, Juan really welcomed that manager with open arms, I heard.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That "manager"...? Who are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">You don't know? That manager woman Juan had. It's a shame she killed herself, though...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, you're talking about Ms. Celeste Inpax... Ms. Andrews' mentor, right?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Yes, yes, that's the one! That Celeste girl. She was supposed to get married, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Married? You mean... to Mr. Corrida?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">*sigh* Really, you young kids today don't know anything, do you? That girl Celeste killed herself three days after their marriage announcement!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Three days after their marriage announcement!? What in the...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Why would Ms. Inpax want to kill herself!? She was going to get married!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, that's because... she was thrown away, you see, by Juan.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">B-But... They were going to get married, right? They promised each other, right?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">They held a grand announcement session... But... Three days later... Juan suddenly cancelled their marriage.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-Is that true?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">It was in the weekly magazines.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">B-But why!? Why did he do that!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That was not in the magazines, unfortunately.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I see.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That night after Juan called off the wedding, that manager, Celeste, killed herself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How terrible...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I wonder what happened between those two...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On that night, there must've been at least a few hundred people here. Hmm... I guess the police are done with their questioning and investigating. It looks like things here in the lobby have finally calmed down.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A lobby with a grand staircase always feels enormous. When the murder happened, it was abuzz with people running back and forth... But now since things have quieted down, it actually feels more eerie than before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like no one is around...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, what happened to that person with the stuffed teddy face...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, she must mean that butler with the stitches in his face.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Shoooooe!</line>
<line speaker="Shoe">Meow.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, there you are. I guess you're still awake, huh Shoe?</line>
<line speaker="Shoe">Meow.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hee hee, come on, let's play.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if that butler, Mr. Doe, is already asleep or not...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It doesn't look like Mr. Scruffy Detective is here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, he's out there with that camera asking around at all the electronic stores.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Then, I'll make some salad for him for dinner.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looks like Pearls really appreciates what Gumshoe is doing for us...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Um, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm? Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Where is the lettuce?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I don't think I've ever bought lettuce before.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... Aww, I guess I have to give up on making a salad, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess the lack of lettuce is kind of a problem.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! I'll water it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, it's OK... Gumshoe already gave it more than plenty earlier...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...The watering can... Where are you, Mr. Watering Can...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Pearls gets too wound up if she's not doing something to distract herself... I hope Charley can withstand Typhoon Pearls...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My desk. Since I don't have time to sit, it's unusually clean...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, I'll wipe it some more and make it super shiny! ...The wiping cloth... Where are you, Mr. wiping cloth...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's fine. Really. If you wipe it any more, it'll be so shiny I'll be using it as a mirror.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Visiting hours ended a few hours ago. Looks like we're not going to get a chance to talk with Mr. Engarde tonight...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">B-But... Isn't what we have to ask very important?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, but I don't think that matters to the guard...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Visiting hours ended hours ago, so what's the camera watching over now?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Maybe it's watching the Mr. Policeman who's standing over there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Somehow, I don't think that's it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Visiting hours ended hours ago, so what's he watching over now?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Maybe he did something bad and he's standing there as punishment.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Somehow, I don't think that's it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It feels sort of tense in here, doesn't it Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, it does. I wonder if something happened...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Chief">You're Mr. Engarde's lawyer, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, yes sir.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Well, we've finally found just the person we've been looking for. A real decisive witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A "decisive witness"? You mean for Mr. Engarde's case?</line>
<line speaker="Chief">We're taking the witness' statement right now. Gotta hand it to Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's Edgeworth up to now...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wh-Who is this witness?</line>
<line speaker="Chief">I think you know this person quite well, Mr. Lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-Mr. Nick...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Between the kidnapper's demand and now this... I can't see any way to win here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Chief">Oh, yeah... Mr. Edgeworth wanted me to tell you something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He did?</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Even though visiting hours are long over at the detention center, he wanted me to grant you special permission, so there you go.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Eh!?</line>
<line speaker="Chief">I've already called them so they know. Go on, go talk to your heart's content.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you very much.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">This is such good news, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Go talk to your heart's content"? It sounds like the police are pretty sure they have tomorrow's trial in the bag.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Detective">"It seems as though my true face has been revealed... I was an elite businessman who made deals with the entire world! I was the young successor and CEO of a colossal corporate conglomeration! But my real self is that of a regular everyday policeman!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Stop doing image training, and get yourself out there in the field!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be the chief of the detectives here. He's glued to his computer screen.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Whaaat!? "The real killer in the Corrida murder is an assassin..."!? This must be someone's idea of a joke. I can't believe this garbage!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Have a little more faith in your own subordinates!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Chief">This mascot here is the "Blue Badger". I made him, you know. I'm finally gonna show him off to the Chief of Police tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow, that's really something.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">You have no idea how much time and effort I invested into him to get this far... But my hopes for this little guy go far beyond just this precinct, yessiree. I'll get him deployed to every precinct in the nation. Just you wait.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I wish you luck, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm sure they must have transferred Ms. Andrews here by now... So that means that both Mr. Engarde and Ms. Andrews are in this detention center. Now then, whose story do I want to hear?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Dude! It's Mr. Wright! I hope you can get me off the hook tomorrow. I'm counting on you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... hope so too... <thought>Edgeworth just dropped a bombshell on me and said... that Juan Corrida was killed by an assassin, and that assassin's client is... this man... Matt Engarde...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Mr. Engarde. There is something I must know with one hundred percent certainty.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Hmm, you seem kinda different. You're totally not like your usual lawyer dude self.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitor's the visitor's room. He's sleeping standing up. The night's pretty long, and he probably got tired. Hmm... I hope he doesn't fall over...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, about the "press conference"...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">You mean the one where Juan was gonna dress up as the Nickel Samurai?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. I heard a little more about it from Ms. Andrews.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It looked like somehow, Juan had in his hands a secret so powerful... that it would destroy Matt's acting career had it been revealed!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you please fill me in on what this "secret" is? Please?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I knew this was coming...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick? D-Don't tell me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A Psyche-Lock...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">You said a "secret", right? But you don't have any idea what it is, do you dude...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is a very important matter! Please! You must tell me! What is this "secret"!?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Hmm... Well... Hold on a sec. I'm gonna consult my lawyer, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phone">............</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Hello? This is Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Oh, hey Mr. Lawyer dude. Sorry, but you know dude, you totally don't have any idea. And I really didn't care at all about what Juan was up to, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">So, it's like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Looks like I have no choice but to remove those Psyche-Locks...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you know about Mr. Corrida and Ms. Andrews' relationship...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Well, it's all over the tabloids, dude. Ah, but I don't know any of the details, if that's what you mean. Look, how many times do I have to tell you? I don't care what Juan did with his life.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Andrews... She had a purpose in mind when she started seeing Mr. Corrida. Her mentor was Mr. Corrida's manager... and Ms. Andrews was going to get Ms. Celeste Inpax's suicide note from him.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Celeste...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Does that jog any memories...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... Dude, I suddenly just got totally hungry. You up for a pizza? My treat.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... ...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... Mr. Nick? What's a "pea-za"? Is it a kind of pea, like green peas?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's go eat one later, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...Argh, I got cut off by the pizza dude at the shop.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's too bad...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Well, how about we get our minds off of this topic and talk about something else, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mr. Engarde... Are you connected to Ms. Inpax's suicide in some way...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">That Juan... Posing as someone else and trying to hold a press conference...! And the person who set it all up was Adrian, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what I heard.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Argh... I can't believe... Why would she do such a thing, dude!?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">That's a very nice transceiver, dude. I'm kind of an expert in gadgety things...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why does what he just said give me a sinking feeling?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">His signature item was a guitar. Hah! I mean, dude, what kind of ninja carries a guitar!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, I'm not someone who would know...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Dude, it's such a kid thing to do. I mean, just my opinion and all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Isn't your show a kid's show too?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">He was a bit of a talentless hack when he was alive... But who knew he could play dead so well? Wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well, that's because he really IS dead!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">And quite pitifully indeed, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">That Adrian... I never thought she'd go this far to frame me for the crime... I mean, what does she have against me? Dude, I don't get it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's something I would like to know too. Do you have any ideas at all? Even the slightest clue?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Huh!? What!? Me!? D-Don't be silly, Mr. Lawyer dude! How am I supposed to know something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Mr. Engarde?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Dude, I know I asked you to be my lawyer and all... But I don't think I have to tell you anything and everything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">It just means I don't have to tell you anything and everything, dude.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, about this...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-Mr. Nick! You can't!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ms. Andrews said she doesn't want anyone to know about that, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, this? Um... Nothing. It's nothing, really.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>... I'm kind of scared to show him this card...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">What's wrong, dude?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, um... So about this picture card... Have you ever seen this before?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...? Nope, never saw it before in my life, dude.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think he's lying... Or is he...? Then again, he looked like he gasped just now... Maybe I'm seeing things...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">It's true we debuted at the same time... so that's why people were always comparing us. But I totally didn't care what people were saying because he wasn't even close, dude. I mean, I won every contest we ever had, hands down!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">I don't get it... Why would she want to frame me...? I mean, I've never done anything to her, dude...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mr. Engarde sounds pretty sincere and he seems trustworthy... So I have to find out what Ms. Andrews' real intentions are!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About this person...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...H-He's...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">He is your butler, Mr. Doe, right? We met him at your mansion.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Oh... Yes, that's right. He's a pretty cool dude who can do lots of things. He takes real good care of me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you please take a look at this...? I know it may not seem important to you...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Well, if it's not important, then I'd rather be in bed. If I don't get my 12 hours of beauty sleep, my skin's gonna wrinkle up like a prune, dude.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You know, he's right Mr. Nick. Your skin's kind of drying up here and there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I swear... After this case is over, I'm going to get lots and lots of sleep...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">..Oh, it's you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry to be visiting at such a late hour. But there are a few questions I absolutely have to ask you tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Me? I thought your client was Matt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm sure Ms. Andrews knows something... She can't be clueless about this "secret" Mr. Corrida had on Mr. Engarde...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd like to ask you about Matt Engarde, if you don't mind...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Mr. Wright... You still don't know, do you? The real him, I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... You seem to bear a lot of resentment towards Mr. Engarde. If that's the case, then why did you become his manager? And why would you become intimate with his rival?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... That... has nothing to do with this case. Nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About Ms. Celeste Inpax...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I had finally put her death behind me... And now, thanks to you, it's all come back to the surface.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes, I was shocked by her suicide. And it's true that when I heard the rumor that Juan was the one who had hidden her suicide note, I began to draw close to him. I wanted to get her suicide note back... and to burn it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You wanted to "burn it"? But why?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I didn't want it to spread like just another piece of gossip. But... I never held any murderous intent towards Juan. I would never do something so stupid.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The suicide note, huh...? I wonder what it said?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did you try to frame Mr. Engarde?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">That's simple. Because he's the killer, that's why. Isn't it the duty of every good citizen to inform the police?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">B-But... there had to be another way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The police are excellent at doing their job, so they'd figure it out, right?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes, they're so good that they couldn't figure out the real truth behind Celeste's death.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ms. Andrews...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, um, I know you're not the type of person to do something without a reason, so please, tell me why you did what you did...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...Revenge.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Huh...? Did you say something just now...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A Psyche-Lock, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Don't you understand yet? You're not my lawyer. To be honest, you're more like my enemy.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm sure I just heard Ms. Andrews say, "Revenge".</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did you frame Mr. Engarde...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Hmm, I wonder why...? I don't really know myself. When I realized what I was doing, I had already stabbed the knife into the body.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm almost sure that just now... Ms. Andrews muttered, "Revenge" to herself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I was the one who organized the whole press conference. Juan wanted to deal the most damage possible to Matt's career. And that's why he was killed. It's quite simply a story of cause and effect, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It appears to me that rumor was started by Juan himself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Corrida...? But...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I'm Matt's manager, remember. I think he wanted to embarrass Matt through his relationship with me.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But... But didn't Mr. Corrida like you...!?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">There weren't any feelings of love between us. For me, it was about getting Celeste's suicide note... For him, it was about wounding Matt's pride. That's all it was.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That's... That's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Pearls is in shock. She sees just how cruel the world can really be.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So there was a Nickel Samurai costume inside of this case, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes, there was. I even personally carried it here from the studio. I always thought it was such a childish thing to dress up and wear a costume like that, but I never thought that I would wind up using it myself that night.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">When I was pouring that glass of juice... I honestly had no idea that Juan was dead...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I really am a terrible woman, aren't I? One moment, I'm thinking of looking after him, and the next, I'm stabbing him in the chest with a knife.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About this photo...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">The person who stabbed the body and opened the guitar case was me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that was so you could get the Nickel Samurai's costume out so you could wear it...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I thought I had executed that part quite well. But you showed me differently. You are a formidable lawyer, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">You know... There was only one thought running through my head at that time. "With this, I can finally expose Matt's true nature to the world."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>His "true nature"...? I wonder why she's saying that, but not telling me what his true nature is? If it were me, I think I'd be happy to finally get that kind of thing off my chest.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I don't care what the reason was... It's unforgivable that he hid Celeste's suicide note.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you don't have any proof that she left a suicide note behind, right?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Celeste... She always believed there was a right way and a wrong way to do anything. She would have left a note. I... I wholly believe that.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">S-Stop it! I don't want to remember the hopelessness and the despair I felt back then!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hurry up and put that away, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm so sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It was near Juan's dead body. I... I noticed it when I went to fill the glass. And then when I realized that Juan was dead... I completely panicked. That's when I must have unconsciously picked this card up and put it into my pocket. As for why...? I simply don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">That's Mr. Will Powers. He's an actor contracted with Global Studios. He's a very nice man. A man with a good heart. ...But that's all he is and ever will be.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Urk... What a horrible thing to say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...Society doesn't care about genuinely nice people, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">He is a very prideful man... Or rather, was. He absolutely had to compete with Matt in everything, no matter what it was. He really was such an idiot.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ms. Andrews...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Well, I guess maybe all stars are like that. Never giving any thought to other people's feelings.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ms. Andrews...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">That things have come to this... I have nothing left to say about that man. Not one word.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I hate talking about myself. It's a trifling matter, that's why.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Celeste... was my mentor. She was a strong woman... She wouldn't kill herself over any old trifling matter...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">S-So... You have some ideas of why she killed herself...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes, I suppose...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, I'd like to ask you about this...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I told you. I hate trifling matters. It's a waste of time to show me things that are of no relevance to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow... This is the first time I've been shut down this badly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Oh! Mr. Wright! Please, you have to help me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh...</thought> M-Mr. Powers!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What happened? Why are you here?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I-I... Uh, you see, I got roped into this somehow...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What??</line>
<line speaker="Powers">And now I'm going to testify at tomorrow's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So the decisive witness... is Mr. Powers?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">I was talking with a detective until a little while ago, and I was on my way home... When all of a sudden, "You there! You're under arrest!" And I was brought back here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">They said my face and whole self in general looked "suspicious" or something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Well, I guess I can see how they thought you looked suspicious...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">*sigh* I'm just a normal guy on an exercise show for kids... Is that a crime??</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Detective">"...I... I'm sorry, everyone. I've lied to you all... I... I'm not a detective. I'm really... I'm really... I'm really Global Hero Onyankopon!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I think he's lost his grip on what's real and what isn't...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, about this "testimony" you're giving. What are you going to talk about?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ah, I really don't know yet... But it sounds like I saw something pretty important from what they tell me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You saw something important? What was it?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ah, well, the detective told me not to talk about it. "You can't tell anyone, and especially not that lawyer," he said.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Who do you think is "that lawyer" the detective was talking about...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm going to take a wild guess and say it's me.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">...Y-Yeah, you got it.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! Mystic Maya and myself are your only two allies in this whole world, but it's alright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ouch... I don't really have a lot of friends, do I...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">This is going to do a lot of damage to Matt, you know. Because he's got that "refreshing like a spring breeze" image going.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But what is he really like?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Well, let's see. Matt's always been kind of a "player" with women... He would never really turn a pretty face away, if you know what I mean... He'd always say, "It's just a game" to justify himself.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What!? H-How horrible! That's unforgivable!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Oww. S-Sorry. Didn't mean to offend you. But you know, he said once that, "There's only one person in the world who won't swoon over me."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One person who wouldn't swoon over him?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">His manager, you know. Ms. Adrian Andrews.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why is Mr. Powers suddenly looking kind of... energetic?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ah, you see, I'm actually a sucker for gossip. I mean, celebrities and their world have this dazzling sort of image, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A dazzling sort of image? But aren't you a part of that dazzle, Mr. Powers?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">No, I'm more of a hairy, sweaty, smelly, brutish kind of guy, you see. But it's OK, really. I get to hear plenty of gossip about a lot of the other stars around me as things happen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Oh, hey! So did you hear about this yet? About Ms. Andrews' mentor and her suicide...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean Ms. Inpax?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">We heard something about how her wedding was cancelled...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Yeah, that's what I'm talking about! I thought about it a little the other day! About that mysterious death! Hey, Mr. Wright! Why don't you ask me about that!? Go on, go ahead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mr. Powers is so charged up his skin is practically glowing with electricity...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">Hey, so have you heard this? Celeste left a suicide note! And they say that Juan went and hid it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We heard about that in court today. <thought>But there wasn't any actual proof that she had left a note...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">Well, this is what I think. I think that something bad was written on that note. Something bad for Juan, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Something bad for Mr. Corrida?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why do you figure so?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Well, before she died, Celeste talked with a few of her friends. And she said, "It looks like I may have been caught by an insidious man..."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An "insidious man"...? Did she mean Mr. Corrida by that?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Well, there's no one else that fits the bill, right? And that would be reason enough for him to hide the suicide note!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... Well, that's some good info. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Y-You're welcome!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mr. Engarde and Ms. Andrews; they're both at the detention center right now. There are still things I don't understand or know about, I'm sure... I have to get the two of them to tell me everything!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">Um... That kidnapper... Has he said anything since then...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... He tried, but there was a lot of interference.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That radio interference... Who would've thought it was caused by a spy camera?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">Hey! That article! Is that from "Gossip Land"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, I guess so.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ah, you too? I absolutely love this magazine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... "You too"...?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Oh, they wrote a little something about me once! "Steel Samurai's Midnight Dine and Dash".</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Dine and dash...?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I bought ten copies of that issue, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Do you think we could somehow get back to THIS article...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">The Jammin' Ninja made me want a bright red guitar, you know. I wanted to be cool like him, so I went out and bought one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... That's nice...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Ah, but you don't understand. I can't get a single sound to come out of it. Because I sort of tripped on it and crushed it... the day after I bought it.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">I can't believe Ms. Andrews tried to frame Matt... Those two have such a strange relationship with each other, don't they?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like Mr. Powers is just as in the dark about things as I am. I guess I don't have a choice other than to go talk to the two of them myself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">Hey, that's Ms. Andrews! She's Matt's manager. Actually, I was interested in her for a little bit. Just a little...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... So Mr. Powers likes this type of woman...</thought> What do you know about Ms. Andrews...?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Well, see... Here's the thing. I don't really KNOW her know her... you know? Ah! If you're interested, I can give you a little bit of the details!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's so happy, he looks like a lion that's just found his next meal...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Powers">That's Juan's former manager, right? Celeste Inpax... She was with Global Studios for a while way back when... But some things happened and she ended up moving over to Worldwide Studios.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">"Some things"? As in?</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Well, there's no one left around who knows the details, you know. Only rumors are left now.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Umm... I'm honored you're asking me, I don't know anything special about this person... Umm... Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, it's OK. You don't have to apologize so much.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">S-Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! Your phone!</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Hey, that's the Steel Samurai theme song, isn't it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't like the sound of this ringtone right now... It sounds kind of ominous.</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Y-Yeah, I know.</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hello--</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We're in trouble now, pal! I'll... I'll be back at the office really soon!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What's wrong!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Something really unexpected just happened! Mr. Edgeworth... He...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Edgeworth...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Anyway, hurry up and get back to the office, pal! I don't know what's going on anymore! It's no good! The end! I --</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Hello? He got cut off.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wh-What's going on, Mr. Nick!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gumshoe said we need to go back to the office right away.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Th-Then we should hurry back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'm scared to go back.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What are you talking about!? Mr. Nick! Pull yourself together!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Powers">Maybe it'll be good news!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Somehow, I doubt that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal! Mr. Edgeworth's already back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well? What happened?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We got 'em! We know who bought that spy camera!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Eh!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-This quickly?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And this bear's what gave them away, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The bear...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I figured it out, pal! I figured that we should've been looking into the bear instead of the camera!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... Wasn't that Mr. Edgeworth that figured...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Shh, Pearls. ...And? Go on.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's only one person who bought one of those bears who's related to this crime!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wh-Who is it!? Who would be so rude as to spy on another person in their room...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Matt Engarde.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Matt Engarde. Your client, that's who, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And here I thought things couldn't get any worse...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure you heard right!? That the person who bought this bear was...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I heard it from the department store clerk, pal. This is the credit card receipt for the purchase. It's for $3,800, pal. That's an exact match to the price of that stuffed bear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A receipt...? That's all you have?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nah, it's not just the receipt, pal. The store clerk said so himself. He told me, "I'm sure I sold the bear to Mr. Engarde." I mean, the clerk even got Mr. Engarde's autograph out of it, pal. So I'm sure the person that bought the stuffed bear was Mr. Engarde himself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>My... My sight is failing me... Th-This can't be!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what about the spy camera we found...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah, that was a dead end, pal. I mean, you can get this kind of thing from anywhere. But for now, I guess I can give these back to you for you to file away into evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Have you heard anything from the kidnapper...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nope. Not a word since we were cut off by the radio interference.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, we know his goal is to get an acquittal for Matt Engarde... So, I don't think he'll hurt Maya, because that's not going to help him at all. Come on! We can't lose hope, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Y-Yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That Engarde... What was he thinking?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean setting the spy camera up in the victim's room...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah! And it was recording at the time of the murder too, pal. Don't you find that just a tad suspicious? It doesn't sound like a coincidence to me...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! I mean, don't mind me! I didn't mean it that way, pal...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Then what "way" did you mean it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">My impression of her has totally changed, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... I wonder what she is doing right now...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm sure she's still being questioned. She sure got herself into quite a big mess trying to frame Mr. Engarde. She'll probably be spending the night at the detention center...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, that's right. She's still at the detention center.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I know you don't want to give up, pal...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I never thought... I didn't think it was possible... The person who put the spy camera in Juan Corrida's room was Matt Engarde!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Why... Why would Mr. Engarde do something like this!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I bet it was to catch Ms. Andrews and Mr. Corrida in one of their rendezvous.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"I bet" is not good enough for me. I have to know the absolute truth behind this camera.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Are you going to see him? Mr. Engarde, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm... I'm scared, Mr. Nick. I wonder... I wonder what we will find out next...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm scared myself, but I have to put on a good face for Pearls... Matt Engarde! What in the world have you done!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I've learned a lot of things during this case. For example, if you want to spy on someone, there are devices like this you can use.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it's not really a device for the purpose of spying. The way any device is used is decided by the people who use them.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Poor teddy... I feel bad for it. Its eye was... It was... And all for the criminal's mean plan...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This bear... It's an expensive luxury brand from overseas.</thought> But it's OK, Pearls. Now it's helping us by giving us a clue... It's telling us who the real culprit is so we can get some justice.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">You're working really late, you know. It's already past 10:00 PM, dude.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think it's time you told me the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... Relax. Don't you know that "ignorance is bliss"? But if you really want to know, let's talk.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, let's hear what this "secret" of yours is. What if Mr. Corrida had been successful in his plan? What would he have disclosed...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">I told you before, dude. I don't know! I don't know anything about Juan, OK? Look, Mr. Wright. I can keep on saying it until I'm blue in the face, but... I totally didn't pay Juan any attention the whole time that night! I mean, come on! I was in the middle of a nap!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't lie to me.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know you paid close attention to Mr. Corrida, especially on that night!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Someone used this camera to secretly film Mr. Corrida's room the night of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">..."Secretly film"...? What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And then sent the images the camera took with this transmitter.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Wow... But dude, where was this camera you're talking about hidden?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The spy camera was hidden in this bear's eye!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A bear that was supposed to be a present from a fan!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Mr. Lawyer dude, I'm really tired...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">But dude, you look even more tired than me. Why don't we call it quits for today and get some sleep? How does that sound?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What made you say that all of a sudden?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Well, you're here showing me stuff that doesn't make any sense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, oops. <thought>I guess I really must be tired...</thought> But I'm not giving up just yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This bear was in Mr. Corrida's room on the night of the murder. A bear that was supposed to be a present from a fan!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">So? It's a present, dude. It actually looks kinda classy, if you know what I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, I hear it's quite expensive. Which is why it is very odd that this gadget was found inside this bear!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is a very small video camera. And it was hidden inside this bear's eye.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...Maybe it's a really curious bear...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, whatever this "bear" saw was sent somewhere using this transmitter. Which means... Someone, on the night of the murder, was secretly filming Mr. Corrida's room!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Mr. Lawyer dude, I'm really tired...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">But dude, you look even more tired than me. Why don't we call it quits for today and get some sleep? How does that sound?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What made you say that all of a sudden?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Well, you're here showing me stuff that doesn't make any sense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, oops. <thought>I guess I really must be tired...</thought> But I'm not giving up just yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Mr. Engarde?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Hold on a sec. I'm gonna consult my friend, OK? ... ... He said I should snort while I give a good laugh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">OK, here I go. ... Aha ha ha ha *snort!*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't believe he can be so flippant at a time like this...</thought> Um, Mr. Engarde... I don't think you need to snort while you laugh. Really.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...Hmph. I guess Juan had a few of those kinds of fans too, huh dude?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, I wouldn't say this bear was a present from a "fan".</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... Hmm... You sure, dude? Who else could it be from?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The person who gave this bear to Mr. Corrida was...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Mr. Engarde?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Hold on a sec. I'm gonna ask my mom, OK? ... ... She says that I can't be friends with someone like you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Go home! If you don't go away, I'm gonna call the police on you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...That's strange. I thought the answer was right there in front of me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Engarde. Don't you know this bear from somewhere...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">I don't think I've ever met Mr. Bear before, dude.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aww, but he says he knows you. How could you forget such a great friend?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... What else did the bear tell you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He says that the one who put the camera in his eye was you, Mr. Engarde.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... If I didn't know how you work in court, I'd think I was in some serious trouble. Come on... This is all a joke, right dude? You're just pulling my leg.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like you're not ready to give up your secret yet.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Well, do you have any proof you want to show me first?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here is proof that it was you who put the camera inside the bear:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, come on, Mr. Engarde!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Hold on a sec. I'm gonna ask my grandma, OK? ... ... Did you know? It's bad to whistle at night, dude... Because snakes will come out if you do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">My grandma, she knows all sorts of stuff. I think you'd better learn from her example, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is he telling me to think carefully before I speak...? Argh! So close and yet so far!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have here, one credit card receipt, Mr. Engarde. It's from when YOU bought that stuffed bear!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Dude, all you can tell from this is that I spent $3,800. I go to that department store all the time, OK? This $3,800... This could be the toothbrush I bought that one time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-A THIRTY-EIGHT HUNDRED DOLLAR TOOTHBRUSH!?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...It's ivory... And it's got elephant hair for bristles...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Eww... Elephant hair? Is that what rich people use nowadays...?</thought> Anyway! The store clerk clearly remembers you and your purchase. After all, you even gave him an autograph, did you not!?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... Dude... You should've said that earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... Um, so can I ask you one thing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">You're my lawyer, right dude? So, if you are, then why are you looking into stuff like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because if I don't know the truth, I can't help you.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Sounds more like stupid lawyer talk to me... Hey, let's stop talking about this, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, not yet. I haven't asked why you set the camera up yet.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what your "secret" is. Of course, it would be strictly confidential...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">So...? What are you going to do now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm going to find out what I want to know... because I must. The reason you hid this camera in Mr. Corrida's room and filmed it in secret is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Adrian Andrews?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is a rumor going around... That Ms. Andrews and Mr. Corrida were having secret meetings.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You, who was keeping tabs on Mr. Corrida... You were going to reveal this as fact, and turn it into a scandal. Isn't that right!?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... ...Dude, you can be such a moron.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Oh man, Mr. Lawyer dude, that kind of scandal... That's the good stuff! That's what we in the industry call "juicy"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...The "good stuff"...? "Juicy"...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Look, we can get publicity without spending a penny with that kind of stuff. I mean, if people stopped paying attention to us, then it'd be the end, dude.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Too bad, that wasn't your intention.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wish your reason for spying was something so innocent. But it wasn't. You didn't spy on Mr. Corrida because of Ms. Andrews... Then there's only one reason I can think of for you to do such a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The real reason you set up that camera in Mr. Corrida's room was...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...If I really wanted to set up a spy camera... I wouldn't have set it up in Juan's room. It would be in your office, dude.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? My office...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Well, dude, you're always saying really absurd things, right? It'd be like getting the comedy channel for free!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! I'm so close! I can feel it!</thought> I-If you're done laughing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Engarde?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Dude, how about you take that bear home with you and talk to it? I'm sure Mr. Bear will talk with you about as much as I will, which is not at all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... <thought>I have to somehow get it through his head I'm not giving up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">So, is it time to throw in the towel yet, dude?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but no.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Wh-What is this card...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe he doesn't know about this card...</thought> This is a certain man's "calling card"... The man's name is Shelly de Killer... and I'm sure you know of him, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Shelly... de Killer... Th-Th-That's ridiculous! Wh-Why would I know some shady scumbag like him...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you really don't know him, then why are you acting so jumpy all of a sudden?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Umm!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is it! I'm finally starting to get to the truth! I can't afford to make any more mistakes now...</thought> Mr. Matt Engarde. I know why you know Mr. de Killer. It's because...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's because you're the great hero of justice, the Nickel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Duuuuude!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You spied on that room to do one thing and one thing only! To expose Shelly de Killer's fiendish plot!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...I... ...Okay... If that's what you think, then whatever, dude.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>I get the feeling that wasn't quite it...</thought> S-Sorry. Slip of the tongue...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's because you're a star!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Duuuuude!? What in the world are you talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, you're a star. And stars never need a logical, or sane reason for anything!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...I... ...Okay... If that's what you think, then whatever, dude.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>I get the feeling that wasn't quite it...</thought> S-Sorry. Slip of the tongue...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Since you're the one who set up that camera... That means you knew... You knew exactly what was going to happen in that room!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... How? How would you know something like that...? It's because you're his client. That's why. You hired Shelly de Killer to assassinate Mr. Juan Corrida! The real mastermind behind this whole murder is... You, Matt Engarde!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... ... ... ...*sigh* And here I was, trying to be a good boy for you, dude.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">I thought if you didn't know, you'd be able to do your job without feeling bad. Well, that's what I thought, anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mr. Engarde... You really did hire...!?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Hold on a sec. I'm gonna consult myself, OK? ... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Consult... "myself"...??</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">...Well, I guess it's probably about time anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About time for what?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">I think it's time for you to meet him now, Mr. Lawyer dude.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">How do you do... Mister Lawyer? I'm Matt Engarde.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Well done, Mr. Wright. I bet it wasn't easy to gather as much information as you have.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You really... So you were Shelly de Killer's client!?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">You don't really think I would dirty my own hands in this, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wh-What do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">And that woman... Adrian was quite brave herself. Trying to stick the crime on me -- I didn't think she had it in her. But all I care about is that Juan is dead. Isn't that right, Mister Lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Th-That's... You're lying!! What a terrible...!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">It's way past your bedtime... little girl. Go on, and let us grown-ups talk about more... adult things.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But why!? Why did you hide the video camera and...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">... A weakling soon believes the words of others... just like that pathetic Adrian.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He knew about Ms. Andrews' secret...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Engarde">But I'm no weakling. I don't believe anyone... least of all assassins.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Oh, come now, Mr. Wright. Assassins aren't above blackmail. They turn their clients into cashcows by holding the sinful deed over their heads. And a superstar like me, how much do you think I'm worth? Care to guess?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">And... And that's why...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Yes, that's where the video comes in. It's got his face and the crime scene recorded on it, preserved for all time. With that, I can keep him at bay, and even blackmail him if I want. That's right. That video is my "insurance"... Isn't that what they call it, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Why would you do something so wrong...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Because I'm a grown-up, and I can. Good enough of an answer for you, little girl?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Why!? Why would you kill Mr. Corrida...?</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Because he was about to sling so much dung onto my beautiful public image. Scandals are a little annoying, aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is all because of that press conference, isn't it...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">If Mr. Corrida had been able to give it, then Mr. Engarde's secret would've...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Ah, well, that's what we call "taking advantage of the situation", you know? I had no interest in doing it, really, but bit by bit, it crept up on me. And then the situation just presented itself perfectly... "How beautiful," I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">And that's... That's how Mr. Corrida ended up dead...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Let me tell you something. I'm not like Adrian. I don't depend on anyone. People are simply things to be used. Used and thrown away. Put on a sweet, innocent face, and people will swallow anything you feed them. Adrian fell for it. The assassin too. Oh, and how can I forget. Even you fell for it, Mister Lawyer! Everyone, all working their butts off for me, Matt Engarde!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Aww, did that leave you speechless? What a shame.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">I don't care what you show... I think you've gotten enough out of me, don't you? Enough freebies for today. The rest is up to you, isn't that right... Mister Lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">What's wrong, Mister Lawyer? You've grown awfully quiet...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-How could I have been so deceived by you all this time? When we first met, I asked if you had killed Juan Corrida... And you answered very clearly that you hadn't killed anyone.</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Hey now. I never told you any lies. The person who did the killing was that De Killer guy, right? All I'm guilty of is taking a catnap in my room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You... You... You killed Mr. Corrida!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Hahaha. I dare you to say that in court tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Grr...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">Aww, but too bad. You can't. You're my lawyer, after all. Aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">You could always drop my case and refuse to represent me. How does that sound? Aww, but you can't, can you? That would be the one thing you absolutely can't do.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-Mystic Maya...!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">You wouldn't want to test De Killer. He's a man of his word, or so I hear. You could end up getting a certain friend of yours rubbed out if you lose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Y...You... scoundrel...</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">So if I were you, Mr. Wright, esquire, I think I would give it my all tomorrow. Remember, everyone likes a happy win-win resolution.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I'll get you for this!</line>
<line speaker="Engarde">That's such a cliché phrase. Juan said something just like that, if memory serves. Of course... Well, we all know how well things turned out for him, don't we? Good night, Mister Lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya... Maya, what am I supposed to do!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">... And now... Now you've finally found it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The starting line of this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't care for the horrid atmosphere here. Let's return to the precinct.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, Wright? What are you going to do? If you plan on changing your defense...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">N...No! We can't do that...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's right... He's holding Maya hostage...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... What... What should I do...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... That's not something I can answer for you.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright... Only you can decide where to go from here. One year ago... At that time, I didn't truly understand what a "prosecutor" was. And that is why... I had to leave the Prosecutor's Office. I felt that I couldn't stand in a court of law until I knew what a prosecutor really was. And now, Wright... It's your turn.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My... Turn?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is this thing called a "lawyer"? What can you do as one? You must find the answer... And you must find it on your own.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm a lawyer... But to fight for someone who is clearly a killer... Matt Engarde... That man is really... Argh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It doesn't matter who, every person deserves a proper defense and a fair trial. Isn't that the basis of our judicial system?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Proper defense"? But what exactly is that? Is it where a lawyer forcibly and blindly gets an acquittal through shouting and trickery?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...*sigh* Ironic that you of all people should say such a thing. Isn't that exactly how you have fought for your clients up until now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... W-Well, that may be true, but... But that's... That's because I've believed my clients to be innocent from the bottom of my heart! But if I were to get Engarde an acquittal... That... That isn't a proper defense at all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I became a lawyer because I thought... I thought I could save people who were suffering and in pain...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... When I look at this mess we're in... I can't even protect the person closest to me. Even if I win the case, I still lose in the end... I just don't know what to do!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Wright. Would you get a hold of yourself? You have it all wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We aren't some sort of heroes. We're only human, you and I. You want to "save someone"? That's something easier said than done, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Th-That's...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You are a defense lawyer. You can't run away from that. You can only fight. That's all you can do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now's not the time to talk about evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">People like you and Franziska von Karma are always using all you have to pin me down. You fight to the very end, even when you know the truth is not with you. But I'm not like you. I can't fight for a false verdict -- for a man I clearly know to be guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Franziska... She fights for herself. The only thing she fights for is her perfect win record. That's all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And!? Isn't that the same as you!? Isn't that why you ran away a year ago? Because your precious win record was destroyed!? You are so petty!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I see... Now I understand why you despise me so. However, you are mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thanks to you, when you sealed off my path to a perfect win record... I began to realize the error of my ways. I realized that things such as a perfect record were meaningless.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Eh!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't believe you. Are you saying that is why you left the Prosecutor's Office? But then, why? Why are you here now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The answer to that... is something you will find out on your own. I have faith you will see it before the verdict is read tomorrow. But if you can't, then you will be powerless to change the ending of this story.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-Mr. Nick! The transceiver!</line>
<line speaker="???">I'm sorry for what happened earlier. Well then, Mr. Attorney. Do you wager you can obtain an acquittal tomorrow?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="???">My, my. What is the matter, Mr. Attorney? I don't sense your usual anger this time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Tell me. Please. Why are you holding Maya hostage for Mr. Engarde's sake? Why are you... Why are you doing this for that cold-blooded killer!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright...</line>
<line speaker="???">... Please don't misunderstand things. He is my client.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't toy with me! A man who hires an assassin is just as much of a killer himself!</line>
<line speaker="???">... ...I believe you were asking me for a reason as to why I am doing what I am...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Y-Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="???">This is what I like to call my "aftercare".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What the heck is "aftercare"?</line>
<line speaker="???">My name carries a certain amount of honor and dignity, Mr. Attorney. I take great care to insure that no suspicion falls upon my clients for my handiwork. That is what is called "client relations" and it is a part of an assassin's duty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An assassin's... "duty"...?</line>
<line speaker="???">We were unlucky this time and my client was arrested as a suspect. As a result, I did what I had to do to enlist your expert help, Mr. Attorney. And to ensure that you would do everything in your power to the very end.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What is your name!?</line>
<line speaker="???">I believe I told you once before, however...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You did... But...</line>
<line speaker="???">My name is... De Killer. Shelly de Killer.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-You're Shelly de Killer!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Aaaaaaaaaaah! Noooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mystic Maya! Mystic Mayaaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I... I don't know what to say...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you hear that? At the end of that transmission...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Huh? Oh, that... It sounded like a cat.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...A cat?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It can't be... that cat... Can it...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What is it...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think... I know where Shelly de Killer is holding Maya hostage! Edgeworth! Have all police units head for Engarde Mansion immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...! Alright. You hurry over as well, then!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't lose hope yet, Pearls! The fight has only just begun!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Y-Yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now then, whose story do I want to hear?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jailer">I'm really sorry, but... Matt Engarde is refusing to meet with you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I guess I don't really have anything left to talk to him about anyway...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Shall we listen to what Ms. Andrews has to say...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Please answer us! Mystic Mayaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We have this area completely surrounded. There is no way for him to escape. Assuming he's still in the area...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't believe it... That butler... All this time, he was De Killer...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He and Engarde were working together all this time. I'm sure they had worked out a contingency plan ahead of time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the first time I've seen such a large fireplace.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't particularly care for large fireplaces. They remind me of my youth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder, if memory serves, if it's because of that rich aunt he had?</thought> Don't tell me you're still stuck on that incident...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't take this personally, but I really do not wish to remember anything from that time in my life.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems that Engarde was quite famous, even as a motorcycle racer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Generally when a star like him tries to do something like that, they fail, but...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems Engarde is no ordinary man.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That Engarde... This is probably where he conducted business with De Killer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Shelly de Killer values his client relations more than anything else. So I'm sure he must meet with his clients in person to talk about any transactions.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's Engarde's personal collection. I'd say it's a hobby of his to collect prop masks of shows related to his own.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You seem to know all sorts of details about Matt Engarde... Almost too many details...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He's the defendant in this case. Of course I would know about him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah... I guess that makes sense...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like there's another room in the back.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Leave that to us. I'm sure the investigation team is already doing its job in there.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">There's a small door at the bottom of this bigger door, Mr. Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet it's for the cat to use.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, you mean Shoe.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, it's a figurine of a bear! But there are a lot of cuts in it for some reason...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A bear...? Isn't that more of a thing for Mr. Corrida? Why would something like this be here...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright, look down. There's a little pet door installed here.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah, I'm sure that's for Shoe...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you think that this... came through that little door...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Umph! This door... It's locked!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I'm pretty used to breaking doors down by now. Let's go, Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh! There's no one here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">From the looks of this room, I would say this is Engarde's private lounge. ...Look at this, Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An antennae for sending and receiving radio signals and a VCR... Check inside the deck! If there's a tape, it would be an important piece of evidence! <thought>If we're lucky, it'll have the moment the crime was committed recorded on it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I'm sorry, but... The tape deck is empty. There's no tape to be found.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">No...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But there's no mistake that someone used this to record something. It looks like someone took the tape we're looking for, and escaped with it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A huge television and speakers loom largely here. I'm sure if Maya saw this, she'd say,</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"I would die a happy Samurai fan if I could see the Nickel Samurai on a TV like this!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, that's what she'd say... ... Ack! I can't believe I just made a joke about Maya, all things considered...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a VCR and an antennae. The footage that the spy camera took at the scene of the crime... was beamed here and recorded on tape.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">If only we had that tape, it would have been really helpful...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's Engarde's computer. Maya... Why couldn't you have used this to get help?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-Mr. Nick! Where's... Where's the power switch!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Oh, I get it... So that's what happened. She couldn't find the power switch...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a very small table. I bet we could barely squeeze 3 Pearls on there.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But I wouldn't sit on a table to begin with, Mr. Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What a spacious sofa. I bet 10 Pearls would fit on here.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, I don't think 10 of me would fit, Mr. Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't read all the labels, but this is a very large collection of video tapes. Looks like Engarde taped all of his own shows...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">There's a little door for Shoe in this big door.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure Maya used this door to shove this out there... I'm sure it was her! <thought>Every time you give me some piece of evidence, it's always the most crucial piece. This time too, I'm sure...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>We've searched all over, but it looks like he got away...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sorry. It looks like he slipped out of our grasp this time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And now... we've lost our only lead.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't give up yet. That little girl is looking to you to be her pillar.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We're close, I can tell. We've already set up checkpoints along every route leading out of this district. Leave the rest to us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow... I've never seen so many bottles all in one place before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I guess when you're a star, you have so much money you can buy anything you want.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The light doesn't filter in all the way, so it's hard to see. It looks like there are crates and cardboard boxes tied up with wire here.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It's a pretty heavy door, isn't it? I can't open it by myself. Please don't shut me in here by accident, OK Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I were locked in a place like this... I'd be plenty scared too. Trust me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This looks like a picture of Ms. Inpax... <thought>"With love... Celeste"</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ms. Inpax? You mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Mr. Corrida's former manager.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Why would a picture of Ms. Inpax be here in Mr. Engarde's mansion?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And why does it say, "With love"...? Hmm, this might be a clue...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's wrong, Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">P-Please let me see that picture frame!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? What's so special about the frame?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">On the back... There's something written on the back of the frame! ..."Maya" It's Mystic Maya! She left us a message!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I thought you'd come. I knew you would. Now listen up! You'd better get Engarde a guilty sentence, OK!? If you get that creepy slimebag a not guilty, I'll never forgive you, ever! I'm fine, so you don't need to worry. ...There's so much I want to write, but I don't think I have a lot of time left. Pearly, you're there too, right? Make sure you help Nick, OK? Someone's gotta watch out for the helpless lunk. ... Um... That's it for now, Nick. I guess I'll talk to you guys later.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...That's... I... Nooooooooo! Mystic Mayaaaaaaa... *sob*</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's wrong? Why the blank stare?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, um, nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We've searched the house, and this is the last room. It looks like he eluded us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As far as clues go, I think this is about all I'm going to get.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I'm still short one last thing...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what is that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ms. Andrews' Psyche-Lock... If I could just find out what secret she's holding... Then I think I stand a chance in court tomorrow... To blow this case wide open and expose the truth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think I know what you're thinking. I'll contact the detention center.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Thanks, Edgeworth. Well, let's go Pearls. It's time to open that last lock.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Good evening, Mr. Wright. ... What's wrong? You look ill...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Andrews. I have come to remove your Psyche-Lock.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Psyche-Lock...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I want to know, and you will tell me... ...your secret.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Fine, go ahead. Try to break me, if you can.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you please tell me why you framed Mr. Engarde for the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I've already told you countless times. It's because I thought Matt was the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No, that's not it! I know you have a personal reason to dislike Mr. Engarde.</thought> Ms. Andrews. You may think I didn't hear it, but I know you said something earlier. You said, "Revenge."</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">So you are saying I was taking my revenge out on Matt, and that's why? Wh-What an absurd idea. I... I don't have anything I want to take revenge for.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ms. Andrews... A woman who lives by being dependant on another person...</thought> <thought>There is something or someone in her past that would make her take revenge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Are you trying to help or hurt Matt with what you're doing...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? What am I doing?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">This random, haphazard throwing out of evidence you're so fond of doing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That's not what I was trying to do at all!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Then refrain from doing it anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I screwed up big again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">C-Celeste...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is only one catalyst that could cause such strong feelings, and even revenge. And that is Ms. Inpax's suicide.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Wh-What are you trying to say? Celeste was Juan's manager.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">On top of that, the one who hid her suicide note was also Juan. What does all this have to do with Matt?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're right. You haven't mentioned him... Yet. But for you to hate Mr. Engarde... It would mean that he must have had some relation to Ms. Inpax and her suicide.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Can you explain to me this "relation" between Celeste and Matt!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">That's it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">And what sort of relation is this supposed to explain?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well, Ms. Inpax and Mr. Engarde's...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Before you start, Mr. Wright, perhaps I should first request to see proof that your brain is wired correctly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh. I can't afford to mess up something as big as this! I need evidence that clearly shows a connection between Ms. Inpax and Mr. Engarde. If I can find that, I can finally get the real story!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I wonder if you'd like to try again, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This... This is a photo of Ms. Inpax, correct? She looks younger than when she passed away though.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...W...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"With love... Celeste". This is Ms. Inpax's handwriting, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... Where did you find this...? No, that's alright. It was a rhetorical question...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, it is. I found this at Mr. Engarde's mansion.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... ...And after all this time... My last remaining secret has been revealed...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Celeste... She was supposed to get married to Juan.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... But I heard that it didn't work out.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Because Mr. Corrida didn't want to get married to her anymore, right...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes... Because of Matt.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">B-Because of Mr. Engarde? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I can see where this is going.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Celeste... She was Matt's manager a long time ago. She was the happiest woman in the world at that time. I was working part-time back then, and I often saw the two of them together.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that's why... "With love... Celeste" is written on the frame of that picture.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">They were a couple, weren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It wasn't anything as splendid as that. Celeste was being used; toyed with until she was... thrown away.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That's so horrible...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Matt's entire image is built around how nice and wonderful of a man he is. A scandal would have destroyed that. Which is why Celeste, in her kindness, moved over to Worldwide Studios. And that is where she met Juan. She seemed really happy with him; even happier than when she was with Matt. Celeste and Juan were such a good match that they were even planning to get married. And then it was suddenly called off. On the night Juan called their marriage off, Celeste... She killed herself. And that's why I framed Matt. It was revenge for Celeste and for myself.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I'm sure even you can guess why Juan called the wedding off, right? Matt "confessed" to Juan... about his relationship with Celeste.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... So that's what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But... Then why did Mr. Corrida have to call off the wedding!? I don't understand at all...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It was probably because of his worthless male pride. Juan and Matt were always fierce rivals. Matt waited for the wedding announcement and then unleashed the truth on Juan. He was aiming for when it would hurt Juan the most.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Poor Ms. Inpax!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...That wasn't the end of it. That day, I'm almost certain that Celeste left a suicide note behind. And in that note, she left a detailed account of Matt's various misdeeds, and... So that she would never again be hurt by Matt, she chose... to die. Then, when Juan discovered her body, he hid her note.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">B-But why would he do that!?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It's simple. Juan realized that note was a powerful weapon against Matt. And it would be especially damaging to his "refreshing like a spring breeze" image. In any case... With his pride hurt, Juan sought revenge.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Revenge... There's that word again.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Juan wanted to publicly disclose the contents of that suicide note. At a time that would cause Matt the most damage, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that was at the press conference after the stage show...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I know all about it, because I heard it all from Juan. It was so I could find out about all this that I drew close to Juan to begin with. They're quite a pair of hideous monsters, aren't they? Even Celeste's death was something for them to use in their game. That night, when I found Juan's body, it was only natural that I thought the murderer was Matt. Those two were always spying on one another, after all. As for me, I was frantically searching for Celeste's suicide note. I wanted to destroy it before it ever went public. I was going to burn it. I had even brought a lighter. But... I couldn't find the suicide note... And that's when revenge crossed my mind. Yes, I was going to bring to them my own kind of cruel revenge. Celeste was killed by those two monsters. So when I stabbed Juan's body with that knife... I didn't feel a single shred of guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... And that's all I have to say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Well, Mr. Wright? Even knowing all this, are you still going to help that... "man"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I... I'm a lawyer...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I see. What a foul profession.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Thank you very much for your time and for talking with me.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It was no big deal. I couldn't sleep anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't sleep either... Not with Maya's situation... or with what I know now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think I have enough evidence yet... I should investigate and gather some more clues before I try again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nnrgh! I've made too many mistakes!</thought></line>
</xml>