<xml>
<title>Festival Fever</title>
<line speaker="Maya">Woooooow. Check it out! The centre's totally filled with people.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mmm, that's right Maya. The town is getting ready for the annual fire festival.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-did you say fire festival? Seriously? You guys are STILL doing that?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, but it's all right. This time around, no one faints whenever they hear the bell ring. The town now has fresh water coming from the English mainland. No more biological hazards here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-if you say so...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I must say, Espella, Labyrinthians certainly are quite resilient.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">And the best part is, this year people from the mainland will be coming to town to see the festival for themselves.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Woah, that's awesome.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Labrelum Inc. held a competition, of which the winners will be brought here to participate.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh, I saw posters for it all over London: "The Labyrinthia Fire Festival! This is one party that's too hot to miss!"</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, it's certainly quite the...intriguing competition.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? Look over there, by the bell tower... It's the Vigilantes!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Right you are, Luke. Although I would have thought there was no longer a need for such tight security...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Well, well, well! These are faces I've not seen in quite some time!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">My, if it isn't the captain of the Vigilantes himself. Mr Boistrum, was it? A pleasure to see you again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, they've still got you patrolling the bell tower, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">SIRS! Never before have I felt such a sense of justice, duty, pride, honour and fulfilment! I am burning with purpose.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Burning? I'd say you're practically on fire.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">The upcoming fire festival will be exhilarating, fun-filled, filled with fun, fantastic! You might say it will be funtastic!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...I see. You must be here to oversee the festival's fun levels, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Indeed! Hence why you find me in such an extremely busy state of affairs!</line>
<line speaker="???">...Umm, Captain!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Ah. It's you, Balmung. ...What do YOU want?!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">Sir! I've set up my postcard booth and the beverage stalls, but...I am reporting a severe lack of space for the barbecue!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Hmm...in that case, place the barbecue over THERE and relocate your postcard booth over HERE!</line>
<line speaker="???">...A moment of your time, Captain.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Wh...what now? Ah, it's you, Lyewood, my trusted right-hand man.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">I think the barbecue should go HERE, sir. And the postcard booth would be best over THERE.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">S-silence! I have SPOKEN! You have your orders, now get to it!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">But, sir...wouldn't it be better if the smoke from the barbecue pointed AWAY from where the Miss Bezella contestants were gathered? I'm sure they'll be VERY thankful, sir... They'll probably even say, "Oh, that Captain Boistrum, isn't he just the best."</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">............ Very well! The barbecue will go HERE. And the postcard booth will go across the way over THERE!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">WHAAAAAAT?! But, sir! I worked REALLY hard on those postcards... No one is ever going to see them way over there...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">SILENCE! My mind is made up! Now go, Balmung, before I make you!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">Uuuuuuuh...y-yes, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Poor Balmung... Dreams today, crushed tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Hail, everyone. Long time no see. Remember me? Lyewood?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah, yes. You're the...fourth Vigilante, if I'm not mistaken. Hmm, for some reason I seem to remember that... you became aware of your unconscious desire to usurp Captain Boistrum of his position, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Heh...I guess I did, didn't I? ...You know, my mind still goes there sometimes.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Just thinking about how easily I could be pulling the captain's strings... It's more exciting than being captain myself.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Guys, remind me to never let Lyewood stand behind me in line.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Listen to Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil! Bein' ah Vigilante is serious business, lass!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Umm. Did anyone else see what the heck just flew up into the air?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All those hamburgers have finally gone to your brain, Maya... Then again, it does seem extra lively all of a sudden.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes. They've also started setting up for the Special Judgement tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh?! Espella, did you just say..."Special Judgement"? Th-then that means...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">No, no, Luke. It's nothing like the witch trials. It's going to be the main stage for the Miss Bezella Pageant.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm...the Miss Bezella Pageant?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That's right. The one who most embodies Bezella will be crowned Labyrinthia's Miss Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-I see...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Again, I must say... Labyrinthians really are quite resilient.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, Espella, seeing as you actually WERE Bezella...you're a shoo-in to win this thing.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, I suppose so. But I'm actually not allowed to participate...since I'm considered to be a hall of famer, of sorts.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-right... <thought>Next you're going to tell me you have your jersey in the "Witch Hall of Fame"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Ahem! Good afternoon, everyone.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, hey! Good afternoon to you, too... uhh...whatever your name is...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">............ Yes, you're right. I get it. I'm more plain than butter on toast. ...In fact, you could say there isn't a single distinct thing about me and I'd completely agree with you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no, listen. We didn't mean...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">I am nothing but a cheap, inferior version of the others! A hopeless, empty shell destined to disappear...into obscurity!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Well, that's not quite as passionate as Boistrum, but you get an "A" for effort, I guess?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I believe you must be the second Vigilante. Mr Lottalance.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">Heh... Oh, I rid myself of that name a long time ago.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Really...?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">See, I thought it was missing a certain... kick to it. I needed a name...MUCH longer. Something ridiculous, outrageous and absurd!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Hey! Doon'cha even think about swipin' me neam, ye' sappy tin can!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, I SWEAR something keeps flying up into the air.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, Lottalance...in the end, what name did you decide on?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">It took all the brain power I could muster. But after hours of careful thought, I decided my new name should be... Lonloncelcellotlot! So? What do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Lonloncelcellotlot... I like it! It's like a roller coaster for your mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">Yet...everyone keeps telling me it's too long or that it's too much of a tongue-twister.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, you know what they say about guys with long names... They're difficult to pronounce!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">...That's just the problem. It's so difficult, no one even tries. They've all gone back to calling me Lottalance, for the sake of ease...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm, well...I guess it is a little less... confusing. Oh, hey... I definitely remember you. Mr Shakey, right?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">I-i-i-it's a pleasure to see you again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you're still doing the whole "gonna keel over any minute" thing, I see. Uhh...are you sure you're all right?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">Y-yes. I-I...actually feel pretty good today... Th-the sun is shining... Th-the birds are chirping... M-my body is ready...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">...Hey there. Am I late to the party?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Umm...who was this guy again?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I know! This guy's really Lonloncelcellotlot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think he's Lonlocello...urgh... Maya, you bring new meaning to the phrase "the gift of the gab".</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">Heh, heh... Allow me to remind you. If it's my name you're after... then talk to the back!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Mr Servius, wasn't it? I see you've not changed much.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">That's right. I still spend my every waking moment basking in the unbridled avarice of being under her heel.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">Why, hello there. You guys sure do know how to keep a girl waiting.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! Hey there! You're looking as "divine" as ever, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">I'm the steel angel gracing the Vigilantes with my sweet presence. My name's Foxy. Don't you dare forget it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Trust me. With an intro like that, how could we ever forget?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">You all have impeccable taste, right? Of course you do. That's why you're going to cast your vote for me tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Cast our vote, Miss Foxy?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">In the Miss Bezella Pageant, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y'know, if we're talking about someone that most embodies Bezella, I'd say Foxy's got this thing in the bag. She's got that sorta...witchy vibe going on, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I dunno about "witchy", but she's definitely giving off some kind of vibe, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Well, actually...the current favourite to win this year seems to be Aunt Patty.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Each candidate is ranked according to their flammability factor. The higher the factor, the more likely they are...to win.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I see... <thought>This pageant sure is...something.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">By the way...I just noticed something rather odd.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">And what's that?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Miss Foxy, may I be so bold as to ask... what exactly are you sitting on?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">............ Come now, isn't it obvious?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">It's ME!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">AHHH! Foxy! Don't look now but, there's a guy under your butt!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Y-you must be...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">That's right! Vigilante number 8, Treddon at your service...err, well, at HER service!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">T-trust me...there's no way we'd forget you. <thought>I think "human chair" falls under things you want to forget but can't...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">...Let me ask you guys a question. Have you noticed... that there are two kinds of people in this world?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">There are those who sit and those who get sat on.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-whatever you say...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">So? What do you say? Wanna try seeing the world from a whole new perspective?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ It would seem Miss Foxy, too, is enjoying the world from a much higher perspective. I must say, it is quite fascinating.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">Mmm, I'm so glad you noticed. By the way, you know what? They won't just let anyone into the contest. There ARE try-outs.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Did you say there are try-outs...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Miss Foxy, do you perhaps mean...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">You got it. The try-outs are puzzle try-outs.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...! If that is indeed the case... then allow me to throw my hat into the ring. Figuratively speaking, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">Well now, that didn't take long. Seems I've stumbled upon some stiff competition.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">C-competition...?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">Exactly. This pageant is FAR from over! I don't plan on losing to anyone. And I mean ANYONE! Not Patty...and certainly not you!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm, help me out here, Nick... Is the professor silent because he's insulted? ...Or is he actually proud?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, you're asking me about the professor here. This guy's like the biggest puzzle of them all...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You know... it's quite exhausting trying to remember each and every one of the Vigilantes' names.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll say. I think that's all of them, though... <thought>Hmm... Why do I get the feeling there's still someone missing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Vigilantes! Assemble! Today's security exercise is now complete! The perimeter is secured and the bell tower has been locked!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Ah locked eht good, Ah deed!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Now! Vigilantes! Sound off! ...One!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">...Two!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">...Three!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">...Four!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">...F-f-f-f-f-five!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">...Six!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">...Seven!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">...Eight!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">...Nayn!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Oh? It would appear there is one Vigilante missing...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, who could that be...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you think...maybe they're still Dzibilchaltunchunchucmilled up in the tower...?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">HEY! If anyone's up there, please answer!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey! I can hear a voice!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">YOOOOOO! Speak up! We can't hear you!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">............ ...I say...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-are you kidding me? If anyone would be stuck up there, it had to be HIM...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, then... It would appear our friend has managed to find a new napping spot.</line>
</xml>