<xml>
<title>Flour Everywhere</title>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey...it's Patty's shop! Maaaaan, this place really brings back some memories!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mmmm... I recognise this yummy smell!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I want to surprise Aunt Patty today, so I've kept our visit a secret.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah, Mrs Eclaire's bakery... It has been a while. I hope she's as jovial as ever.</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof! Woof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, look! It's Constantine. I wonder what he's doing here.</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Grrrrr...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Check out those pearly whites. He looks really happy to see you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Happy to see me? More like happy to have his favourite blue chew toy...</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meow...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh, look! Eve's here too. And looking as cute as ever!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder if Constantine and Eve are friends now... Hey, Luke. Why don't you ask and find out?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Umm...okay. But you do realise these things are pretty personal questions, Maya. Even for a dog... So, Constantine... Are you and Eve on friendly terms now?</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof! Ruff...woof!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">He said: "Friendship has no place on the battlefield! 'Tis nothing more than a fool's errand for a dog of knightly honour!"</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Affectionate as ever, Constantine! Not sure I'd call this place a "battlefield", exactly...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did anyone else notice that Eve is chewing on an éclair?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, Eve... You can't go eating Aunt Patty's pastries like that!</line>
<line speaker="Eve">...Meow.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Just a moment, Espella! Eve said that the éclair was a present from Constantine!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Really...? Luke, do that "animal whisper" thing again, and dig up some more dirt!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Uhh... Okay, Maya. You've really taken quite an interest in their personal lives, haven't you? Is it true, Constantine? Did you give Eve that éclair as a present?</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Constantine said that he doesn't recall having given anyone a present.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hear that, Nick? Constantine gave Eve a present. You could learn a thing or two from him...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...? What could I possibly learn from a dog?!</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Grrrrr...rrrrr... Ruff ruff ruff...woof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AAAAAAARGH! AAAAAAHH! Why me?! Why does he always bite me...?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps he's merely expressing a fondness for you... Now then, shall we all go on in and see Mrs Eclaire?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow...the smell of freshly baked bread!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This must be the work of a true artisan, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="???">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... It would appear we have found a baker quite proficient in the use of cutting-edge methods, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...He has such a fearsome expression as he's kneading that dough.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Rather than "kneading" the dough, I'd say he's "punishing it into submission", Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can almost hear the agonising screams of that poor, defenceless dough...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. I bet the poor lump is wishing it had never been made...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Um... Excuse me...Mr Barnham. ...The guests have arrived.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Hm...? Well, well, well... If it isn't Sir Blue Knight, the daunting defender of justice! ...And the intrepid Sir Top Hat, no less! I welcome you back to Labyrinthia, and insist that you enjoy your stay.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd appreciate it if you wouldn't "insist" while drawing your sword and waving it in our faces...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Ah, the witch trials... They seem like but a dream from long ago... 'Tis hard to believe they truly happened.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, it is. Especially given how peaceful the town now seems.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But then... Why are you still wearing your armour, Mr Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">According to the mistress of the bakery, a baker's apron is his armour. Thus, I choose to wear my armour as my apron, while doing battle with the dough both fairly and squarely.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I've gotta admit, I'd expect nothing less from "Ex-Inquisitor" Barnham. He's baking Barnham-style, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're not wrong, Maya... But I've gotta say...I never pictured you becoming a baker, Barnham.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Well, actually, Mr Barnham is only a part-time baker.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Just a little side job, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">He's kindly agreed to stay here for a while and help out in the shop.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I, err...have recently found myself in need of some extra coin. What little I make here helps out a bit. And living here also means that Constantine gets to eat all the fresh éclair he desires.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that "present" to Eve was a leftover...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Anyway, how come you need money so bad? Are you paying back a loan on that armour or something?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">As fearlessly direct as ever, Miss Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Well, in truth...I am planning to use the extra money to buy something special. You could say...a gift, of sorts...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?! Did you say "gift"? So, who's the lucky lady, Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...L-lucky lady? Assuming it IS for a girl, I wouldn't get your hopes up, Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">........................ I-I have just noticed the dough for the bread rolls is now prime and ready for the flames! I-if you will excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Barnham...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Soft doughy rolls, delight of Labyrinthia! May the fire's embrace bake you!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor! There goes that agonising scream from the dough again...and it's intensified!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, my boy, I'm sure it's all part and parcel of the roll-making process.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But I wonder... is Patty even paying him for any of this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well...since he's staying at the bakery too, I guess he's like a live-in apprentice.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">An...apprentice? Is that normal for a bakery?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... Well, the apprenticeship system has been around since the Middle Ages...albeit not generally in the field of bread-making.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Anyway, worst-case scenario, I guess she'll at least be paying him in bread, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I suppose bread would be better than nothing...</line>
<line speaker="???">Hold it right there... Did my ears deceive me...or did you just say "worst-case scenario"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-that voice... I know that voice...</line>
<line speaker="???">And what's more... ...I could have sworn I just heard the words "better than nothing".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-b-b-b-b-b-b-boss!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">YIKES! I mean...h-hey there, Patty!</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Now, I'm sure you both know what happens in MY bakery... when you belittle the importance of bread, do you not?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No... Not the rolling pin! Quick, Barnham! Help us! H-he's gone!</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Right, you two... Prepare yourselves... Because there's no backing away now... from this delightfully challenging puzzle that has absolutely nothing to do with bread!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Really, Espella... You should have let me know in advance that you were planning to invite everyone here! If I'd known, I could have prepared a big batch of my best hot buns!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm sorry, Aunt Patty... I wanted to surprise you.</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Phoenix, Maya, how have you both been? I bet you're really rolling in the dough these days, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, we can't complain, I mean, we make enough to get by. Unless...I wonder if we're talking about the same thing here...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I, uhh...don't think it matters either way, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Phew...looks like that puzzle helped calm Mrs Eclaire down a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, Luke. I'm delighted to see that friendly smile once again.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh! I almost forgot...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's up, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I need to prepare a present too...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Really? You too, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So...who's your present for, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's for Eve... Her birthday's coming up soon.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, no kidding? ...Eve's birthday, huh... ...Wait! Didn't Barnham say something about a super-special gift?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't mean...he's been baking a present for Eve's birthday?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Now that's a surprise! Do you think maybe Mr Barnham has a soft spot for Miss Eve?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I must confess, this is rather intriguing.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww! That's so romantic! Wouldn't you say, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, y-yeah... I guess so.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">........................</line>
<line speaker="Maya">........................ Boy... Like master, like dog...</line>
</xml>