<xml>
<title>In a First-Class Cabin</title>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's almost two weeks now since we left Japan. I can't believe how quickly time has gone. So...our next port of call will be Shanghai.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Who's there? <thought>Who could it be at this hour?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...A detective.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">'A detective'? Who?</line>
<line speaker="???">...A great detective.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><thought>...I don't get it. What's a great detective-</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">If you would just be so kind as to open the door?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Oh, yes, sorry. Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Is something wrong, detective? Are you investigating a case?</line>
<line speaker="???">Wherever a great detective goes, great cases occur. Indeed, I am the root of all evil.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">S-Sorry? <thought>Then I don't think I want you in my cabin.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Under our very noses on this steamship, a terrible theft has just occurred.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What?!</line>
<line speaker="???">You noticed, I presume, the brief power failure a short while ago?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Oh yes. The power couldn't have been out for more than ten minutes, though.</line>
<line speaker="???">Indeed. Yet that was ample time for this wicked crime to be perpetrated.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I see... Well, clearly it's a case that needs investigating.</line>
<line speaker="???">Precisely. The culprit ran away in this direction. Down the first-class cabin passageway here.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Really? The thief came this way?</line>
<line speaker="???">I'm quite sure of it, It may have escaped the attention of the dim-witted crew, but not of the great detective. To that end, I would be obliged if you would allow me to investigate here in this cabin.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...! Um...well...</line>
<line speaker="???">How curious. Is there some reason why it would inconvenience you to have your cabin searched?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><thought>Inconvenience me? Well... I'd be lying if I said no. After all... ...there's a stowaway in that wardrobe right over there!</thought> It's just me in here, you see. No one else. So you might perhaps want to focus your attention on one of the other first-class cabins.</line>
<line speaker="???">As it happens... ...you are the only first-class passenger at present. The other cabins are vacant.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="???">Did that rather tragic rumbling of the stomach arise from within you, my good fellow?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...Of course. As I said, I'm the only person in here. It's not long until dinner time now, so...perhaps we could do this afterwards?</line>
<line speaker="???">I do apologise, sir, but it is of the first importance that the investigation is not delayed. Now...if you'll excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><thought>Wait... Where did he go? How did he suddenly move all the way over there?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Yes, without a doubt. If the culprit were to be hiding in this cabin... ...it would have to be inside this wardrobe. I shall need to examine this wardrobe thoroughly. I presume you have no objection?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...I'm sorry, but I'm going to have to decline. Really, you won't find any-</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="???">Did those two rather tragic sneezes...arise from your good self?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Of, of course they did! As I said, I'm the only person in here!</line>
<line speaker="???">You have a curious knack of talking while sneezing, then? Twice, no less.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...! <thought>This is going to be a tough one to argue...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">I was watching you quite intently, sir. And I assure you I saw no signs of a sneeze.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><thought>Argh! Couldn't Ryunosuke have held his nose?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...As I was saying, I shall need to examine this wardrobe.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><thought>We've had it now then. The game's up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Hm...nobody hiding in there, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Wh...WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="???">You seem surprised.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">No! Not! At all! <thought>YES I AM! He was in there, for sure! I shut the doors on him myself!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><thought>More visitors? Who's this now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">Excusing me!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Oh, Seaman Strogenov?</line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">Sorry for disturbing, but crime has been committed on board ship.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, I heard. A terrible theft, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">How do you know this?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ah, well, the detective here just informed me, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, I assumed you must have asked him to investigate. Detective, could you...? <thought>Wh-Where did he go?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">I must ask you to cooperate with investigation into this crime. Fully.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><thought>Uh-oh, he's glaring at the wardrobe already.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">Aaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah ha ha ha ha hah! Well done, you found me!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Wh-What are you doing hiding in my wardrobe?</line>
<line speaker="???">My good man, I was merely assessing the practicality of concealment in such a place. And I would say that, at a push, a human could survive for up to five minutes in that cramped space.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><thought>Ryunosuke's been in there for a fortnight. ...Is he not human?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">Who are you?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ssh! This is the moment of truth! The great detective is about to unveil the sordid details of this wretched crime.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You, you mean to say...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Yes, there can be no doubt that the culprit of this terrible theft... ...did indeed conceal himself within this wardrobe!</line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">But, but that's impossible! He couldn't have done. <thought>Because my best friend was in there the entire time. Or at least, I thought he was...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">How can you be sure of this?</line>
<line speaker="???">Elementary, my dear fellow. The criminal left behind the most revealing evidence. How else could you explain...these three bones?!</line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><thought>What the...? He's right. look at those gnawed bones in there. And three of them...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">Argh! The kriminal has escaped this time! But I will find him...and crush him!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...Um, could I ask you something, detective?</line>
<line speaker="???">Why yes, of course. I am always delighted to answer an enquiring mind.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In this 'terrible theft', what exactly was stolen?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah-ha! What else...but some steaks on the rib bone!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Huh? Did...did you say, 'steaks on the rib bone'?</line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">For this evening's dinner. Three rib steaks were stolen from ship's kitchen only short time ago. There was malfunction with generator and ship was without lights for ten minutes. Chef who saw kriminal said that he ran away down first-class passageway. And now I am on his tail!</line>
<line speaker="???">I'm afraid to say, dear fellow, that your man is no longer in this cabin.</line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">But...how?</line>
<line speaker="???">Through the cabin door, no less. Having devoured his haul in this wardrobe, the culprit discarded the bones... ...and concealed himself behind the cabin door as you came inside. Then... ...when attention was turned to the wardrobe, he seized his chance to escape through the open door!</line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">What?!</line>
<line speaker="???">Make haste, my good man! After the culprit! I shall follow presently.</line>
<line speaker="Strogenov"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="???">...Something troubles you, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">I think maybe...kriminal is not running away at all!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...! What are you suggesting?</line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">Now I know where the dog is buried. ...Mr Asogi.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">M-Me?</line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">Da! When I think that you are culprit, everything is falling in places.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...!</line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">The kriminal that disappeared in first-class passageway... The bones in the wardrobe... All clues are pointing their fingers at you!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">D-Don't be ridiculous! I would never...</line>
<line speaker="???">Yes, yes, of course. I established at once that you couldn't be the perpetrator of this crime.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You did?</line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">Why? How are you so sure?</line>
<line speaker="???">My dear fellow... ...there are but two things in this world on which one can rely with total certainty.</line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">What two things?</line>
<line speaker="???">The first, is the word of a great detective. And the second...</line>
<line speaker="???">The second is the tragic rumbling of an empty belly.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ah! <thought>Not again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">When I first entered this cabin... ...there did arise from this gentleman a belly rumbling so odiously tragic, that it confirmed beyond all doubt... ...that the man had not eaten a single rib steak in some time, let alone three!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><thought>Why do I have to suffer this humiliation? When I've done nothing wrong!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Strogenov">......... Curses! I will catch this thief! He cannot have gone far!</line>
<line speaker="???">Indeed. Assuming he decided against a post-meal constitutional swim. Well, if you will excuse me now. My apologies for upsetting your evening.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Detective! One moment, please.</line>
<line speaker="???">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">That was...a most remarkable deduction. Perhaps you'd be kind enough to tell me your name?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, it quite slipped my mind. You have been talking with the one and only...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Herlock Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I see. Well, I'm Kazuma Asogi. I'm a student, on my way to Great Britain.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Pleased to make your acquaintance, Mr Asogi. Oh, and before I forget...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...I feel I should warn you. Live cargo is strictly forbidden on this vessel. So you would do well to conceal the stowaway currently lying low under your bed as carefully as possible.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Oh... <thought>Under the bed...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I bid you farewell then...Mr Asogi.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><thought>He's uncovered our secret! I supposed I should have expected nothing less...of a great detective.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Now then... ...when did you move in under the bed? I thought we'd had it when he opened the wardrobe door.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, well, it was thanks to that split-second chance you engineered.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">That I what?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You distracted him for a moment, remember? When you suggested that he investigated the other cabins instead.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Oh yes. He turned to look towards the corridor, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I couldn't see what he was doing, of course. But I thought to myself, 'It's now or never!' and the next thing I knew, I was under the bed!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You really know how to give me a scare, don't you? Anyway... ...what's all this about the rib steaks, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...sorry about that. I've, I've just been so hungry!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ever since we left Japan, stuck in that tiny wardrobe... Well, you should know! You've been splitting all your meals with me, You must be starving, too, surely?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">*Grooooan* <thought>Right on cue...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And there was that power cut before, wasn't there? For about ten minutes.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So it was then...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I caught a whiff of the most delicious smell. And I thought to myself, 'It's now or never!' The next thing I knew, I had the steak in my hands.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><thought>This man just can't help getting himself into trouble.</thought> Well alright, you were hungry. But three steaks? Thanks to you, three crewmen are going to go without tonight, I imagine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, it was just the one.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I only took one rib steak from the kitchen, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">But...I don't understand.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hey, I'm not that selfish! If I'd stolen three steaks, I'd at least have tossed one your way.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...I'm not your pet dog. Well in that case...who stole the other two?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Ah! Do you think...? C-Could there be a g-g-ghost on board? A m-m-meat-loving g-g-g-ghost?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><thought>There can only have been a single bone in the wardrobe when Ryunosuke moved to hide under the bed. Which means that the other two bones can only have been put there by one very flesh-and-blood person...</thought> ...Haha...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wh-What's so funny? We're on a h-h-haunted g-ghost ship!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">A great detective...or a great mischief-maker? <thought>Either way...I think I'd like to spend a little more time getting to know that man. The great Herr Lock Sholmes...</thought></line>
</xml>