<xml>
<title>In Mr. Natsume's Room</title>
<line speaker="Susato">So...Mr Natsume... ...are you really returning home? To Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Yes, indeed I am. Everything is arranged already.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">We'll be sad to see you go. And after Runo worked so hard to prove your innocence as well. What a shame. It feels like it was all a wasted effort.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">DON'T SAY THAT! I, I know what you're suggesting!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Now calm down, Mr Natsume. It's all fine, really.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You are in good company here, sir. If you fear the Reaper, you needn't hide the fact.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I am a proud citizen of the Empire of Japan! I'M NOT A SCAREDY-CAT!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Talking of cats...Mr Sholmes just casually threw one among the pigeons there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">A man like me belongs in Japan, not here. That's what I've come to realise!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm, I wonder. A moustache such as yours is eminently suited to London, I would say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>There goes Mr Sholmes throwing another cat in!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">The moment I arrived in this city, I noticed. Everyone in London laughs at me behind my back! Like hyenas!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm, I'm sure that's not true, Mr Natsume.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh but it is. Whenever I turn around and peer down the fog-filled streets, all I see is foreigners everywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, there's you, Runo and Susie in here, so that's three foreigners out of five people... I take your point!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Only the other day, I was taking a stroll through the fog as usual, when a young man approached me from ahead. He was pale and gaunt, his back arched like a cat. Observing his wretchedness moved me so deeply. 'Ah,' I thought to myself, 'I'm not the only one suffering in this hell!' But...do you know what? Can you imagine?! It was just my own reflection in a shop window.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Don't forget 'Slap in the face'.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Everyone started laughing at me. Gentlemen thereabouts, ladies passing by, even the man in the shop window!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah yes. And a certain great detective would like to be included among the mirthful.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">ARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Mr Sholmes is really going for Soseki-san today!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, I for one think you're a very handsome man, Mr Natsume.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There, did you hear that? This ten-year-old girl thinks you're handsome. Isn't that wonderful?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... That makes me feel suspiciously warm inside.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He looks genuinely delighted.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">The point is...we Japanese are HUMBLE and MODEST! Studying on foreign soil, surrounded by foreign people... How could anyone POSSIBLY enjoy that?! No one could! It's impossible! ...If you're a genuine Japanese!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hm, if you say so...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Actually, it would appear...that there IS someone. A Japanese man who studied in a foreign country and seems to have thrived on the experience.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">There is?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Ogai Mori. I believe he studied in Germany.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Mori? Pray, tell us more of the fellow.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well today, he's a very successful author in Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, I've heard of him. He's the professor who wrote 'Mai-hime', isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">My...heemeh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I suppose in English, the title would be...'Dancing Queen' maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, I see... A tale of a woman who waltzed her way through the world, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You really needn't make up a silly translation, you know. It's already officially called 'The Dancing Girl' in English. It seems Mr Mori greatly enjoyed his time in Germany. He became close with a local lady while he was there.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">C-Close, you say? With a l-l-local lady?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...I suppose your experience of studying abroad depends to a large extent on your character.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Ugh. As they say...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Mori has an open mind. Mr Natsume, a closed one.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Possibly a slightly black-and-white view, do you think, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well anyway... ...if that's how you feel about being abroad, why did you choose to study here?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wasn't it to further our nation's understanding of the English language or something?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Yes, yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So what were you doing in Japan before you came to Great Britain then?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I was a school teacher. Of English, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">A bit cursory, perhaps, but I've managed to discover some information about Mr Natsume's teaching days.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That's just a little outside the field of law, isn't it, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, let me pose you a question, Mr Naruhodo: If you had to translate the English phrase 'I love you' into Japanese, what would it become?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's easy. 'Aishiteru' or 'Suki desu'.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Wrong! ...According to Mr Natsume's teachings, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Would you like to explain, Mr Natsume?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Yes, yes, of course. Your research was very thorough. I always used to tell my students... ...that we Japanese don't express ourselves that way. Rather, we might say, 'Tsuki ga kirei desu ne.'</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear Mr Natsume, I must interject! 'Tsuki ga kirei desu ne' would translate as 'The moon is beautiful, isn't it?'</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I KNOW THAT!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The point is that we Japanese are reticent when it comes to expressing our emotions. We prefer to show our feelings of adoration - our 'suki' - by approaching the beauty of the moon - the 'tsuki'.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, using the 'tsuki' to express 'suki'! It's an amusing play on words, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">No! ...Or in language YOU might understand better: BAD SHOLMES! It's not a play on words! It's subtle. It's humble. It's fleeting and beautiful. It's ART!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Isn't it just...being shy?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow, the foreign 'dancing girl' will forever be out of your reach with such an attitude.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Imagine how the great Mr Mori would act. He would win the lady's heart in a flash with a well-placed and unrestrained 'I love you!'</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">ARGH! That smooth Mr Mori! Am I destined to live in his shadow forever?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Just what sort of man is he in that imagination of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">The fact is, I just can't settle in this foggy London town with all its foreign inhabitants. I've lost count of the number of different lodgings I tried before I found myself here. As it happens...I even lived on Baker Street at one time.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">No! Really?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">A Sao scholar lives near there. A man by the name of William James Craig. His knowledge of Sao is unsurpassed. He's been a great inspiration to me over the-</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Forgive the interruption, but...am I supposed to be familiar with this 'Sao' of which you speak?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">It's Shakespeare, of course, Shakespeare! But in Japanese, we write it as 'Sa' and 'o'. It's a phonetic representation using kanji characters. So, 'England' is 'I-gi-risu' and 'America' is 'A-me-ri-ka'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Come to think of it, we use the same character as 'ri' in one word and 'risu' in another. Talk about confusing!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm, so Shakespeare is 'Sa-o' in Japanese... Presumably the 'Sa' is a brutal attempt at the first 'Sha'. In which case, where is the '-kespeare'?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'd never thought of that. We only have the 'o' left...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Which could, even in the most charitable interpretation, only be a brutal attempt at 'old man'.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It seems to me that whoever had the job of deciding on the characters for his name got bored very early on.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Complete Kanji Character Catastrophe!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So then...on to the burning question! What about me? How do you write my name?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Herlock Sholmes, my dear fellow! There must be Japanese characters for my name!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... I am sorry, Mr Sholmes, but none exist that I'm aware of.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">WHAAAAAAAT?! Am I really NOTHING to you Japanese? In that case, it is a matter of paramount importance. You must construct my name in kanji at once!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Erm...well...we could use a kanji that's pronounced 'So' to start with, and then use one more to give... ...'So-o', perhaps? I think that would be about right, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But...that's almost the same as Sao, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes! You employed the dreaded 'o'! I don't want people to confuse me with an old man who died centuries ago!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'm sure the world's greatest literary figure would rather not be confused with you, either.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well the world's greatest detective is still youthful and full of vigour. So how about 'So-handsome'?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes, that sounds wonderful! I'm sure EVERYONE will be calling you that a hundred years from now!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>How can she say that with a straight face?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">What about me, then? Iris. Perhaps 'Ai-hime'...since the second character doesn't seem to matter?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ai-hime? Oh yes! 'Princess of Love'! That's an adorable name for you, Iris!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">STOP! PLEASE! With a name like that, Mr Mori is likely to turn up at any moment and rashly declare 'I love you!'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This Mori-san has become quite a character in Soseki-san's mind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And you, Mr Naruhodo. Might I venture 'Kuro-bozu' as a fitting name for you? As in 'the dark monk'.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, that's very good. It describes you perfectly, Runo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you think I'll be wearing this black varsity uniform for the rest of my days, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But Mr Naruhodo already has a Japanese name. I don't believe he needs another.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well anyway... ...we were talking about your life here in London, weren't we, Mr Natsume? You should just get out and have fun!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Ugh...the landlady has said as much to me, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mrs Garrideb?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">But it wasn't fun at all. It was frightful.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Whatever do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">A CYCLE INCIDENT!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">An incident? On a bicycle? Oh, yes, come to think of it... ...there's an old bicycle parked just outside, isn't there? It's in a sorry state, though.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I tried to say 'no' to her, but she insisted I took it for a ride. Perhaps my pronunciation was wrong... So I took my life in my hands and attempted to ride the steel, spider-webbed stallion to a nearby park.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I really don't think there's anything wrong with your pronunciation, Mr Natsume.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Joan Garrideb just isn't the kind of woman to take no for an answer...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">If you're going to die, you might as well die in beautiful surroundings. So the park was my first thought. After a whole day of dicing with death, I emerged with only relatively minor bruises.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you got the knack of it?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Don't be silly! Dying...isn't something you can learn to do!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Um, Mr Natsume, you keep talking about dicing with death and dying and so forth, but... ...riding a bicycle is supposed to be fun.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh no, that's just what people tell you. But it's an old wives' tale.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Is it?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I mean, just consider the real name of the vehicle... It's not called a die-cycle for nothing! How anyone expects to use such an aptly named vehicle to move forwards is beyond me!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I didn't think it was possible to get worse with practice.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I'm lucky to be alive! Although, I must say... ...after looking death in the eye for a whole week, I did at least manage to mount the steed reliably. And notwithstanding a few wobbles, I found I could make progress in the forward direction.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...what a triumph...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Deduction is much the same. When first presented with a problem, the mental exertion of trying to solve it leads only to bitter disappointment. But after a week of picking one's way carefully along the path of reasoning and thought, one begins to see results.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...is that why all of your off-the-cuff deductions always seem half-baked?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What a wonderful insight into your extraordinary mind, Mr Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Unfortunately, after wobbling down the street, I noticed there were little stones everywhere. Deathtraps. 'Not that way!' I said to myself. But the wild vehicle wouldn't listen... It wobbled me on and on down the street... So OF COURSE! I hit one of those DEADLY stones, and the crazy colt threw me! It's just my luck. Die-cycles are the epitome of my pitiful life...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I...wish I could disagree...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">On the same subject... ...I'm sure there's a famous American author who's written about having a similar experience.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes. I've read that essay, too, Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Some of us are better read than others.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Well no more die-cycles for me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Mr Natsume, at least you have an interesting anecdote to take with you back to Japan, if nothing else.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You always manage to put a positive spin on things, don't you, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Personally, I haven't mounted a bicycle for some time.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">No, me neither.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">That's good.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So how about a jaunt? We shall all ride out together!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That sounds great. I'll perch behind Miss Susato.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">But...but...THE SUN IS GOING DOWN! It will be pitch-black before long!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">London's streetlamps are very bright, you know. And the fog isn't too thick today.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">AND MY BELOVED RIDE IS ALL BENT OUT OF SHAPE!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow, if you are bound to topple the vehicle anyway, it's fitting that it's already bent out of shape.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It's settled then! Come along, Mr Natsume! Shall we go?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... Tsuki ga kirei desu ne.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Don't tell me that's his translation of 'No, thank you', as well?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed, Mr Natsume. The moon is at its most beautiful at precisely this time in the evening!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">We're not Japanese. You can't beat around the bush with us!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">.........</line>
</xml>