<xml>
<title>In Sholmes's Suite</title>
<line speaker="Susato">Good morning, Iris. Good morning, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, morning, Susie! I'll get breakfast on the table for us all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...Mr Sholmes... Morning...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Come now, why the long face?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, um...sorry. The thing is... ...I just had a rather strange envelope posted under my door this morning. With some rather strange things inside.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What strange things?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ooh, what is it, Runo? Do I catch the scent of mystery in the air?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Nothing so exciting, I'm afraid, Iris. It was just five orange pips. I can't imagine what it could possibly-</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Whaaaaaat?! O-Orange pips, Mr Naruhodo? And f-f-five of them?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's the matter with you? That's a bit of an overreaction, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">An overreaction?! Mr Naruhodo, you, you don't understand! It's a warning. A notice of imminent danger...to your life!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">WHAT?! To, to my life? What's the meaning of all this...Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow...why do you make such an enquiry of me?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Because the name of the sender was written on the envelope. And it was yours.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You're right, Runo! It says, 'Sent by: Sholmes, Envoy of Hell'!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah ha ha ha ha hah! So, my little ploy has been exposed. Well, so be it. Cast your mind back, if you will, Mr Naruhodo, to the time of our dining last night.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes... Miss Susato cooked Japanese food for us.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed. In particular, you may recall the final norimaki sushi roll that I was about to savour. That is, before you swooped in with your clacking chopsticks and filched it from under my nose!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! I, I assumed because you'd left it that you didn't want it.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'd left it, my dear fellow, because I had planned to enjoy it as my very last mouthful. Surely you must have noted my intent by the subtle dilation of my right pupil?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Perhaps a clearer sign would be helpful next time. Just an idea.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In summary, the post you received earlier is a notice of impending revenge. You should be quaking in your boots!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Really? Because I went straight out into the garden and planted them. I'm hopeful we may grow some exotic fruit!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">There's no point sending a 'notice of impending revenge' if the person you send it to doesn't know what it is.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, I knew, of course. Because I've read this book. 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes'... On sale now in all major London bookshops and receiving rave reviews!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes, of course. It's finally been published, hasn't it? I hear it's selling very well.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It is! Twelve short stories in one volume... I've earnt a lifetime's spending money already!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And it has further bolstered my name. In fact only the other day, a Bohemian king sought to engage my services.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? That's...extraordinary.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Of course, the gentleman persisted with some pretence about being a fishmonger for the duration.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But only a fool would presume to be able to deceive my eyes with such a charade.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So how did you know he was a king then?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Why, there is no mystery, my dear fellow. A distinct smell of fish accompanied the man's lowly apparel. And though he tried to hide it, the left side of his moustache quivered in a quite manifest manner.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Mr Sholmes... That's simply brilliant!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Having neatly resolved the case for the man, I was sent a quantity of fresh cod as a mark of his appreciation.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I think perhaps you shouldn't discount the possibility that he actually WAS a fishmonger.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">......... Ah... Is, is that...? Can anyone else smell burning?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes, you're right. And look...smoke! I, I think maybe...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Fire! Fire! There's a fire, everyone!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really?! A fire?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">We must all leave at once! Everyone out of the building!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No! Wait! I... I have to go back to my room first!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Are you deranged? If you're not asphyxiated by the smoke, the flames will burn you to death!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But my daruma doll! I, I can't let my daruma burn! It means too much! Argh! Drat! Sorry, but I'm...I'm going to make a dash for it upstairs!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hahahaha! Oh, Runo, you're so funny!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is no time for jokes, Iris! Go! Quickly! Get out of here!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But...there is no fire. Is there, Hurley?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah... What a delight to see that ploy enacted in the flesh! I wouldn't have dared to dream I should be so lucky!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">M-Miss Susato...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah ha ha ha ha hah! Indeed, indeed! Indeed it was a ploy. A devilment engineered by my puckish spirit!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It was all a trick? But WHY?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It is a simple experiment of the mind, Mr Naruhodo. When his life is threatened... ...a fellow is compelled instinctively to protect that property to which he attaches matching importance.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And after your own life, Runo, the most important thing to you seems to be...your daruma doll!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Let's not dwell on that, shall we, Iris? So...you knew all along, Miss Susato? That it was a trick?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, of course. The very ploy is described in this book. 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes'... On sale now in all major London bookshops and receiving rave reviews!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Not again...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I have used that device quite satisfactorily in the past to solve a case.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh yes, it was a great success, wasn't it? But then it became something of a habit, didn't it? You started yelling 'Fire!' at every crime scene. In the end, people started to pay no attention to you at all.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, that's true. There was a time when I was known as 'the Sholmes who cried wolf'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I think there's a lesson to be learnt in there somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But sadly my little ploy failed to yield results this time. Iris was utterly unmoved.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, I was anticipating that Iris would immediately expose her secret hiding place. The location of the nest egg she must have cached somewhere in this room.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Nest egg? You think Iris has some secret savings?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Why naturally! The book is selling like hot cakes, after all. It is a simple deduction indeed to conclude that the profits must be concealed here within these walls.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh Mr Sholmes...are you in need of money?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah! I bet I know what it is! It's that new microscope that's gone on sale, isn't it, Hurley?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What else?! I have such a strong desire to own one, yet my purse is one pound too light. And as no offer of a loan has been forthcoming, I have been forced to resort to an alternative stratagem.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hee hee, sorry, Hurley, but I'm not falling for that. Not coming from the Sholmes who cried wolf.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Agh! How vexing!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You really shouldn't be trying to steal a ten-year-old's savings, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">My book is full of little tricks like that, you see. The armoury of the great detective!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Except that in this case, both the orange pips and the fake fire fell a little flat, didn't they?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Oh, I have plenty more tricks up my sleeve. Take, for example, the case of 'The Boscombe Valley Mystery'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'm already filled with dread, just from the title.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It is a tale of extraordinary skill on the part of the great detective. The skill of tracking.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Tracking?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">When I arrived at the scene of the crime in the eponymous valley, there were footprints everywhere. But my eye was immediately drawn to one set in particular!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh Mr Sholmes! Your detective instincts are truly remarkable!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As you know, my dear madam, no detail, no matter how small, escapes the scrutiny of these eyes. So, I tracked my quarry, following the trail of his footprints all the way to the man's place of residence!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It led you directly to the culprit's house? What a triumph!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You misunderstand. It led me directly to my own house, my dear fellow.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">For the footprints were...in the final analysis...those made by my own shoes.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hurley had left here for Boscombe Valley as soon as he received the telegram about the case, you see. And then he followed his own trail straight back here to Baker Street.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Now Iris, please. You make it sound almost humdrum. But I assure you, it is no easy feat. Tracking of this nature is a skill possessed only by the great Herlock Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're right. It really is...extraordinary.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Quite so. Extraordinary is the word. And let it be the last on the subject. Anyway, needless to say, I subsequently went on to solve the case with various other deductions.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, it's the 'various other deductions' that I'm interested in.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, well, you shall have to read the book then! I'm sure Iris has penned it with her usual flourish.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, absolutely! I've put an ingenious spin on the great detective's exploits.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It must have been very ingenious to make this man sound even remotely credible as a detective.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">......... Wait... Is that...? Does it smell like something's burning again?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We've had enough devilment for one day, Mr Sholmes. Put your puckish spirit to bed.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I assure you, this has nothing to do with me or my spirit!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no! The, the smoke is getting thicker!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean...it's not a trick this time? There, there really is a...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Fire! Fire! There's a fire, everyone!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">AAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Susato! Where are you going?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Stand aside, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh! Easy, Mr Sholmes! What are you...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes?! <thought>Why did he just chuck that bust of Napoleon on the floor?</thought> Oh! <thought>Look at that! In amongst all the broken porcelain...</thought> Coins! Sovereigns, in fact! Worth a whole pound each!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Come, everyone! We must leave at once! Evacuate the building!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">......... Hehehe! You fell for it, Hurley. Hook, line and sinker!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait, you mean... Iris!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I certainly wouldn't have guessed that's where you'd hidden it.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Do, do you mean to say that this smoke was...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">My own puckish spirit needs to come out and play sometimes too, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, of course! I know what it is, Iris! It's that indoor herb garden set that went on sale last week, isn't it? That's what you're after.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I want one so desperately! But I'm four pounds short. And even though you told me you didn't have any money to spare before... ...I knew you had a secret nest egg somewhere in this room!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Argh! You've outwitted me again!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You really shouldn't let yourself be outwitted by a ten-year-old child, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">So, thank you for the loan, Hurley. Oh, but wait...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Where's Susie? She's disappeared.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Oh yes, that's right. She ran off up the stairs before, didn't she?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Hahh...hahh...hahh...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! What are you all still doing in here? We have to evacuate! It won't be long before the fire is...is...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">.........</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Sorry, Susie. Children will get up to mischief once in a while, you know. But it's all perfectly harmless!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Harmless, maybe, but oh so devious!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh well...at least nobody was hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Apart from Napoleon. And my secret hoard. Now, tell us, Miss Susato. What is it that you went so fleet-footedly to fetch?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Sorry? Oh! No, nothing. This is just... No, this is nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Susie! That's... That's your notebook detailing all of Runo's trials, isn't it? It's bulging at the seams!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah... a testament to the various people you've helped over the past months.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Susato, I...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, I am your judicial assistant, after all. I would do anything to ensure the safety of these records. Even risk my life, if necessary. I mean, it's very important to me. It's like a diary of everything we've achieved together.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>I'm getting all teary-eyed now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, in stark contrast to a certain someone who would have fetched his daruma doll, I must say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Uuuuuugh...</line>
</xml>