<xml>
<title>In the Defendants' Antechamber</title>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Just look at my priceless treasure now! Myself, I have scrubbed and scrubbed... ...but the repellent odour of meat will never be repelled from its resplendent surface again!</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">But you have it back in your possession, at least. You should be grateful, old man.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">How dare you?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, excuse me, but...I'd just like to get at that zabuton cushion there if I could...</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Hm? Ah... Rest assured, you miserable military malefactor...this is not over! Incarceration awaits those who would defraud a senior citizen for his priceless treasures!</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Watch your tongue, old man! Mark my words, I won't-</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry, Sergeant, but...could I just get at that zabuton cushion there as well...</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Hm? Oh... I won't go to jail! Never! Imagine if I did... ...the very next day, my boy would starve without the chain of command in place to provide for him!</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Hmph! Using the child to protect yourself? Myself, I call that absonant cowardice!</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Oh really? And who just employed the old poor, defenceless 'senior citizen' tactic, hm? The only way to fight an enemy who's using underhand tactics is with a tit-for-tat strategy!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, sorry to interrupt again, but...I just need to get at that Western-style cushion there on the sofa...</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Enough of this insubordination! What do you want, man?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, please, don't mind me.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Ah-ha! Do my eyes deceive me, or is this the wide-eyed criminal from the trial before?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Wide-eyed, perhaps, but criminal...no.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">What is this unhealthy fascination you exhibit with the seating arrangements of others, hm? Why were you peering under the cushion of this upholstered seat?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, well, the thing is-</line>
<line speaker="???">Any luck? Did you find it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, sadly not. I don't think it's here, Kazuma.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Tsk, you really are a liability, Ryunosuke.</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Report! At once! Have you lost something, is that it?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes. We were just on our way to a party to celebrate my friend's victory here, when...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I realised that my university pin badge was missing.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">A university pin badge, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. From my collar here, you see?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Affirmative! Uniforms must be kept in prime condition at all times! A missing badge is unacceptable!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I thought if I looked around, it would probably turn up somewhere. Like the old tale of the koban coin and the steak.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">A parable of which I am acutely aware.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But I've exhausted my search now, really. The only logical conclusion...is that someone must have stolen it.</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">...Don't look at me! I don't just find any old metal objects irresistible, you know! Imagine what would happen if little trooper Aido here swallowed something like that!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I'm afraid we'll have to give up, Ryunosuke. Still, if you tell the office your student number, they should be able to issue you with a new one.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What's the matter? Don't tell me...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I don't remember my student number.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I don't believe it! I mean, this is the second time you've lost your badge, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Third, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">If you didn't think you could remember it, you should have made a note of it somewhere. I told you that until I was blue in the face the last time this happened!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...yes, I do seem to remember someone telling me something along those lines... It was you, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...You can't even remember who told you that you needed to remember it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, student numbers are six digits, Kazuma... Who could remember six whole digits?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yumei isn't exactly a long-established university, you know. All of our numbers are still rather low. In fact, they only use the last three digits.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...that might help, I suppose...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">That MIGHT help? Ryunosuke, it's only three digits you needed to remember! Just three!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Sorry my brain is such a disappointment.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Yes, well... Anyway, young man. Myself, I was greatly impressed with you in the courtroom today.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Oh, you mean me?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">A lawyer already, before you've even graduated. And such a loyal friend to this...one.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This 'one'? What's that supposed to mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Oh no. I still have much to learn. In fact, that was brought home to me in no uncertain terms only last year. My Achilles' heel was spectacularly exposed...by my best friend here.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Indeed?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? By me? <thought>This is the first I've heard about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, by Ryunosuke Naruhodo... You can't have forgotten, surely? It was last summer. At the speech contest.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The speech contest? ...Oooh. That.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Contestants had to take to the stage and deliver a public address on any subject they chose. We were competing to give the most compelling and powerful speech.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And yours was great. It made a huge impression on the audience.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Obviously, since I was a budding student of law, I was determined to win. And sure enough, one by one my opposition fell. When I reached the final at last...I came up against you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, so you did.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Not being rude, but when I first laid eyes on you, I thought to myself: 'This cheeky, wide-eyed no-hoper is out of his depth. He's going to be a pushover.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That's your version of not being rude, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well, I paid for my complacency. Because it brought on that humiliating defeat.</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Defeat?! How were your ranks compromised?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">My speech was going very well. I had the audience in the palm of my hand. They hung on my every word. And then...when I came to the very last line...</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Yes? What happened at the very last line?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It was supposed to be a climactic end. Unfortunately, I completely fouled it up.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Never!</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">You mean, you stumbled on your words?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Spectacularly. Even now, I can't believe I ruined it!</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Well...what on earth did you say, man?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... Ryunosuke, you'd better say it. I still can't get my tongue around it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sure, of course. I can still recall it perfectly. What you said at the end of your speech...or rather... ...what you intended to say at the end of your speech... was this:</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">And what went wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Hm, what indeed? Myself, I see no problem with the pronunciation of these paltry words.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In that case, old man... ...I invite you to say it yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Very well then, I shall. Ahem, ahem... 'So arise, ladies and gentlemen, and applaud our forefathers' plight and the flight...the fight for flilial pile...' It's impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The 'arise, ladies and gentlemen' part, I delivered perfectly. But the next part had me floundering for a whole five minutes. By the end of it, I was on my knees in front of the podium, a blabbering mess.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And that's when the audience started to heckle you. 'Arise! Arise!' they were shouting.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">...Hell on earth.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">But then of course this man went and delivered his word-perfect speech, with a perfect ending. How did it go again?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, let me see... 'So, my dear fellows, the message is simple: treat your father and mother with respect!' ...Something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I mean, talk about stating the obvious. But the fact is, I lost to that speech.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Hmmm... Tongue-tied is the only way to describe it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, it is quite tricky to say, I agree. That final 'fight for filial piety' especially.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And ever since that day, I've had this question whirling around in my head. Why did our forefathers choose such an awkward phrase? Was it to mock their children? I mean, it should never have been called 'filial piety' in the flirst pace... AAAAAARGH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...At least you're going to Great Britain soon. It might not come up much there...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well anyway... Having lost that accursed contest, I came after you to ask you a question. 'How is it that you never trip up on your words?' I enquired. And you just gave me a broad smile and said... 'Speaking fast is my hobby.' ...I mean, really? What kind of a hobby is that?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Do you think you could take your hand off of your sword? Besides, it's just a way to pass the time...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">After that, you started talking at me ten to the dozen. Like you were possessed, almost. Honestly, you can't imagine the shock I suffered that day, you really can't.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're right...I really can't.</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Speaking fast is just the sort of hobby I'd expect a civilian like you to waste his time on.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well you have to practise, of course. But there are some simple things to start with. Like this famous one, for example: Swift samurai swords swipe silently sideways.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Ah yes, even a decrepit tongue in an ailing frame such mine can find its way around that one.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I've no doubt. It's just a bit of fun, really. I can't imagine anybody would struggle to say it. Isn't that right, Kazuma?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... Swift swamurai swor- AAAAAAAAARGH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>A blabbering mess by word two.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nosa">It's not just the samurai. Every good soldier needs to be able to handle a sword. That's why I've been busy teaching Aido the finer points of swordplay! None of this wordplay nonsense, private!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Come to think of it... ...not long after that, we started to attend lectures together, didn't we? And we got into that debate about family values at the sukiyaki place on campus. Do you remember?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes. Your argument was full of jokes and puns and wordplay as usual. I remember it well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In any case... ...I swore that I would never let myself forget the shock you gave me back then. And as a symbol of how seriously I took that oath, I decided to wear this: my red hachimaki headband.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">.........</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...sorry, Kazuma...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You've lost me there, I'm afraid. I don't see the link. What does your red headband have to do with your oath?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Because! It will always remind me of that smug look on your face as you uttered those tantalising words.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What words? You mean another tongue twister?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I practised and practised until my tongue bled. But in the end, I mastered it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Mastered what?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well, I think it's time you heard this, actually. Listen carefully now. Here goes... 'Red headband, lead headband, dead headband.' ...There! Word perfect, see?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">.........</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'd actually been meaning to ask you about that. About the story behind your headband, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well, now you know. So that I'll never forget the shock and humiliation of that day. That's why I wear this red headband every single day without fail!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Well, I don't know exactly how much of a shock you think you had back then, but... ...it can't be more than the shock you've just given me now.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I'm sorry to have to tell you, but... ...the tongue twister I said didn't go the way you seem to have remembered it.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's just as famous as 'swift samurai swords', so I can't believe you don't know it, really. It goes: 'Red bread pan, lead bread pan, dead bread man.'</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Wait, what? Bed red pa- Ugh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...It seems I've knocked some wind out of that headband of yours.</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">It's not too late, private. You could always start wearing a red bread pan on your head instead.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Your youthful vigor is manifest, young man. Your cheeks are glowing redder than your hachimaki.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">URAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!!! Why do so many words have to be so similar?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... So, looking forward to Great Britain, then? Where you'll have to deliver speeches in court in English.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...I suppose I can always shell seasells on the sheashore.</line>
</xml>