<xml>
<title>In the Bailey</title>
<line speaker="Judge">This court is now in session for the trial of Mr Herlock Sholmes. This is a most extraordinary case of murder. Counsels, I assume I may proceed?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, My Lord. The defence is ready.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">At your discretion, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. I hereby call on the prosecution to introduce the case.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The incident in question took place two days ago, late at night, when the ground was blanketed with snow. The location of the incident was the residence of the accused, Mr Herlock Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed? The now famous address of number 221B Baker Street, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The address may have enjoyed fame once, My Lord, but will henceforth endure infamy for this grim crime.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Y-Yes, sir! Well put. The victim, a certain Madam Rosie, was found asphyxiated on the accused's sofa.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">My word...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But it's unclear as to whether the victim was actually killed in the defendant's suite or not! After all, when Mr Sholmes left the room for only a brief moment... ...Madam Rosie somehow vanished herself out of his room completely!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Vanished herself, Counsel? The victim?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Quite true, My Lord. There is but one adjoining door between my drawing room and the kitchen. Yet having brewed some tea in the kitchen, I returned to find the room completely empty.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There was nobody else present?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ordinarily, my fellow lodger, Iris, would have been at home. However, on the day in question, she had been invited to a meeting of a scientific society in the city.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid you have a propensity for exaggeration, sir. You claim the victim 'vanished herself', but really... ...it seems to me entirely plausible that she chose to leave via the main entrance to your suite.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">As it happens, My Lord, the door to the accused's room was locked at the time, from the inside.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Very true, Inspector. As such, I can say with considerable surety that the victim did not leave via my front door.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but what about...um... Ah-ha! Yes! She could have snuck out through a window!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">However, there was snow all round the buildin' outside, and not a patch of it had been disturbed.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Would my learned friend care to explain how the victim could have left without leaving a trail?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So the victim, Madam Rosie, somehow vanished from the scene before she was killed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Argh!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Naturally, I was alarmed by the sudden disappearance of my guest. So I summoned this gentleman, who resides in the attic room above my own, and we took a cab to Scotland Yard.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can confirm that the defendant called for me, and I saw his suite on my way downstairs. And yes...I'm quite sure it was empty, just as Mr Sholmes has said.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">When we reached the Yard, this very detective happened to be there.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Ah, well, yes, you see...I was just in my office for a while havin' got back from some, er, important business.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And then, having explained the situation to the inspector, we travelled back to Baker Street together. At that time, there were no footprints in the snow around the building other than the ones we'd made.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do I take it then, Counsel, that you personally witnessed the scene where the incident took place?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, My Lord. I went straight up to bed in my own room in the attic.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Inspector Gregson, however, was met with a most blood-curdling sight: On Mr Sholmes's sofa...the vanished Madam Rosie. Motionless.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm. So the victim was already dead when you discovered her, Inspector?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">No, My Lord. Not dead. But not far off it. She mustered all her remainin' strength to say these dyin' words: 'That rotter... Sholmes...will be...the death of me.'</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah yes, I overheard that remark at the time, too. Delivered in a rasping voice, full of malice.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Those words indeed proved to be her last. The victim expired moments later, there on the sofa. The cause of death was identified as damage to the respiratory tract as a result of strangulation. ...Pray, does the accused dare to contest the inspector's account?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Certainly not. In fact, the inspector has done an unusually fine job of summarising the salient points.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">'Sholmes will be the death of me.' ...Damning departing words indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">In her final moments, the victim named her killer. You! Mr Herlock Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But the defendant had no reason to take the victim's life! Perhaps you could tell the court, Mr Sholmes, who exactly this Madam Rosie was?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah yes, of course. ...Did I never mention her to you? I'd extended an invitation to her that evening. Though she is loquacious in the extreme. The most trivial of matters quickly becomes a quarrel. I was only too pleased to leave her presence to make tea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Great...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It would appear then, that the accused did in fact have a motive for silencing his eristic guest...permanently.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Putting that tenuous motive aside, what about the other mysteries surrounding the case?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... I'm inclined to agree with the defence. There remain a number of inscrutable details. The victim's alleged disappearance and subsequent reappearance leaving no trail of footprints, for example.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right! The crime described by the prosecution... could never have happened!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yet the victim named the accused in her dying breath. It seems to me, that my learned friend has overlooked a significant detail here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Nonsense! ...What have I overlooked?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The man in the dock - the so-called 'great detective' - all too frequently makes the following bold claim: 'There is no crime beyond the realms of possibility. No mystery beyond my powers of reasoning.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">So, Mr Sholmes...you will have no difficulty in explaining how the crime thus described could have taken place. Therefore I propose a toast. To the great detective upholding his name!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... But of course. Were I to put my mind to the matter...the crime would immediately appear to all present to be entirely feasible.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Please, Mr Sholmes...whose side are you on? All you need to say is: 'No, even I can't think of a way that a crime like that could have been committed!'</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Let the accused's admission be noted by the court. Though the crime may appear impossible to us mortals of inferior mental capacity, this man alone... ...claims to know exactly how it was done!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Now hold on! That's a very fragile argument!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, Counsels. I believe I've heard more than enough to proceed to my adjudication. The accused 'great detective' did, in some inscrutable manner, wilfully murder the victim, Madam Rosie. I therefore find the defendant...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let this man be taken from this courtroom and, in some equally inscrutable manner, be sanctioned for his crimes! Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My Lord...please... The truth about the mysteries surrounding this case... ...are known to another besides the great detective.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">'Pon my word, Mr Naruhodo, you are coming along wonderfully. You've deduced a fundamental truth about this case, I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Which would be...detective?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">That the truth to this case is known... ...only to the true culprit, obviously. ...Is that not so, Gregson?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Eh? What? Well, um... I s'pose...yes...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You don't mean...! Are you suggesting, Mr Sholmes... ...that you have an idea as to what actually happened that night?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">An idea? My dear fellow... ...I could explain the entire incident from start to finish with not a single detail omitted!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Pray, Mr Reaper...which of us has truly failed to grasp the situation, I wonder?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Then answer me this: You claim that prior to the incident the victim suddenly vanished without a trace from your room. If so... ...how exactly did Madam Rosie disappear?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Why, naturally, via the window. It was ajar after all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But that can't be! The room is a whole storey above street level, and anyway no prints were found in the snow!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">There are any number of ways one could avoid leaving tracks in the snow, surely?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">S-Such as...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Such as...flying, for instance.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">A fatuous notion! And to where do you propose the victim flew, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Is it not entirely plain? To the culprit's abode, of course. For, having left my suite, that is clearly where Madam Rosie was murdered. ...Take a moment to consider the cruel irony, if you will. By her own volition, she flew directly to her death.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">No doubt because her killer carried her back there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but what about the lack of footprints in the snow again, then? There just weren't any. Other than our own, from when we returned home ourselves!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">If by 'our' footprints, you refer to your own and mine, you are quite right. But there were those of another. On the night in question, there was one other person who could have conveyed the victim to my sofa.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious! To whom do you refer, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">A man whose somewhat unavailing presence at the scene of the crime would be questioned by no one.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Unavailing? ...Ah! You, you don't mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed I do. A man who hastened to the scene directly upon learning of the incident at Scotland Yard. Namely... ...you, Inspector Gregson.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Eeeeeeeeeh?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">When you arrived at my address on Baker Street, you were carrying the half-dead Madam Rosie with you. You waited for a suitable opportunity, and then laid the victim on my sofa.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He did...WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But we were with the inspector when he arrived. How could he possibly have been carrying the victim? We would have noticed!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow, a most obvious answer presents itself, does it not? The inspector is rarely, if ever, without his overcoat. The victim was simply conveyed in one of its many pockets.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I fail to see what makes this detective great. But I can say one thing with great certainty: A human body cannot fit into the pocket of an overcoat.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... I believe you may all have fallen foul of a rather significant misapprehension.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Madam Rosie...was not a human.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I beg your pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...Mr Sholmes...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, Mr Naruhodo? Something troubles you, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Whatever gives you that idea? Exactly what sort of creature was Madam Rosie?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Is it not apparent already? A parakeet, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">A most self-conceited specimen, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A parakeet?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">She was an incessant talker, I must say. Her manner was quite intolerable at times. Wont to turn every conversation to a quarrel. I thought to strangle the creature on more than one occasion.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You had a quarrel...with a parakeet?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But of course. Why else would she have chosen to fly from my window so uncordially that evening? To the abode of the inspector here beside me no less!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">To Inspector Gregson's abode? But...why?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Because that was the parakeet's home, naturally.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">What are you...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The inspector was called away from town for some days, so it was arranged that I would look after the bird. But it would appear that she was overcome with a sudden yearning for her keeper. Thus prompting her flight from my comfortable suite to the inspector's office at Scotland Yard.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, Gregson? I believe it's high time you explained. Give us your account of what happened that night. Sparing no details, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Inspector Gregson?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">......... It...was an accident.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I got back from bein' away that evenin', you see. I'd just walked through the door of my office. I never imagined Madam Rosie would be on her way back to the Yard as well. I slammed the door shut behind me...just as she was tryin' to fly through it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So Madam Rosie...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">She got sandwiched between the door and the frame and fell to the floor... ...never to move again. Because of me.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well I never.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I had to do somethin'. And just when I was tryin' to think of a plan... ...you fellas arrived talkin' about some incident at Baker Street.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I had to hide Madam Rosie in a hurry. So I stuffed her in my coat pocket and got in the cab with the pair of you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What could possibly have motivated you to behave in such a manner, Inspector?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">......... Lord Stronghart, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...? Lord Stronghart? Please tell me I didn't hear that right.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">It was the Lord Chief Justice who asked me to look after the bird in the first place. She'd been livin' with the pigeons at the Supreme Court until then. But apparently the, erm...other birds had...started to pick on her. So for the past six months or so, I'd been carin' for her in my office at the Yard.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">If anythin' happened to that bird...! Just imagine! No pay and no time off for the rest o' my career! You mark my words, that's what's gonna happen! That's why I... Well... .........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But the victim's dying words, Inspector... The court heard earlier that Madam Rosie spoke the name of her assailant on her deathbed.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">'That rotter... Sholmes...will be...the death of me.'</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed she did. Quite uncalled for, wouldn't you agree? But those words...are your true feelings, are they not, Inspector?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Ugk...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Clearly you speak of me often at your office at the Yard. In this disparaging manner. A manner that the merry parakeet took much delight in mimicking.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Well, come on! I mean, have you read this month's edition of Randst Magazine, eh? I'm...I'm... ......... ...SOOOOORRY!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">This is all... ...absolutely TRUE?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Somethin' wrong, Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Hm? Ah...no... Nothing. <thought>...I almost drifted off for a moment there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">It's hard not to drift off...when you've been kept waitin' three hours already.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks"><thought>I wonder if we'll manage to meet with Lord Stronghart at all today. We may have to deliver the report on the Windibank case that he asked for on another day.</thought> Tell me, Inspector, what became of that bird?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Ah... Madam Rosie, you mean? She had a narrow escape, but...she's still alive. I delivered her back here not long ago, actually. On Lord Stronghart's orders. He's hopin' the pigeons will accept her now.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...It was something of a shock to hear that she'd been crushed in the doorway of your office. Especially as we were all under the misapprehension that Madam Rosie was a person.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Uh...um...sorry about that. It was Lord Stronghart's demand that-</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah good, you're here.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I apologise for my tardiness. I'm exactly three hours, twenty-four minutes and...fifty-seven seconds late.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Oh no, My Lord! No no, please don't trouble yourself. Nothin' gives us greater pleasure than standin' here doin' nothin' for hours on end! </line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...Heartening. So, let's hear it then. Your report!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks"><thought>The Windibank trial is concluded. ...But this is far from over. It seems that dark, Far Eastern lawyer and I have some shared destiny... We will meet again. Of that I have no doubt.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Did you see that, Lord van Zieks? Did you? Madam Rosie went flyin' off among the pigeons there! Happy as Larry, she was!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Really, Inspector? You must be...relieved.</line>
</xml>