<xml>
<title>London <thought>episode</thought></title>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow! It's been ages since we were last here, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh...I think I remember this place. Isn't this...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's right. This is where we came right after you were snatched away by witches. In fact, it's where our investigations began.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There seem to be a lot of people around, given the time of day.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I've seen a bunch of other people wearing top hats just like you, Professor. Has there been some kind of English top hat revival?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Not of note. Perhaps there was a wedding... At any rate, I thought I'd introduce you to some places related to last year's incident.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, that sounds like fun! Right, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well then, without any further ado, shall we make our way to the next location?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Ah! This is where we ran into the "Great Witch", isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Hee hee... Eve was really on top form that night, wasn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You said it! That scene was super intense... My eyes were totally glued to the screen!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Our next stop is a famous London park.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, you mean the park where Carmine and I were trying to escape from the witches in his car?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be where that crazy crash happened, right? After that, Carmine took his leave for the rest of the game...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">If we're lucky, the park should still be open at this time. There's something I'd like to show you all, but I better go on ahead and get it ready.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, check it out! It's that Walled In puzzle. If you solve the puzzle, you get to enter this spooky secret room!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah yes...that puzzle was a little arduous, as I recall. Moving all those heavy blocks around was quite the physical challenge.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">There's a bit of a crowd around it, so I'm not sure we can get much nearer.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup... Tons of top hats here, too. I can't even see the pattern on the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Not to worry. Let's head towards the park, instead. Although now that the mysterious accident has been cleared away, there's nothing particularly eye-catching about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, makes sense...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What the...?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Woah! No kidding! I didn't know cars could fly like that.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This is most peculiar... I'm quite certain that accident had already been cleared away.</line>
<line speaker="???">Layton! What brings you here this evening?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, if it isn't Inspector Chelmey.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, the famous Inspector Chelmey! Pleased to meet you, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">I can't imagine what you're all doing here... That mysterious incident has long since been cleared up.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You say that, Inspector, but there would appear to be something rather out of place up in that tree, would there not?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Hmph! Well, needless to say, Scotland Yard has no intention of divulging any such information to the likes of you lot.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">............ Then again, I suppose it can't hurt to fill you in on the basics... That vehicle is what you might call... a game-set-piece tourist attraction.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Game-set-piece...?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">All on account of your game being such a big hit, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-how flattering...I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Ever since your little collaboration was released, this right here's become a popular spot amongst fans. Tour guides are dressing up as the main characters and leading fans around on tours of the city.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah... That would explain it, then... Namely, the reason behind our seeing so many top hats around this evening.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Spot on, Layton. Believe it or not, those people are dressing up as you.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">How intriguing... I imagine I must look like a fan as well. You might even say I'm impersonating myself...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Say, what about the car up there? Was that reconstructed for the tour?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Hmph! As I said before, Scotland Yard has no intention of divulging any information on the matter. None!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">............ Well... I suppose just a little scrap of info is only fair. That vehicle is what you might call the main tourist magnet of this whole bleedin' park.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Tou-rist-mag-net...?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">You heard me right. They felt something really memorable was needed at the end of the tour, see... So some bright spark decided they'd call on a bit of audience participation to recreate the accident as the tour's "grand finale".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait...recreate the accident? As in... "Hey, let's throw this car into a tree again" recreate? No way...</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">I tell you, some of these game fans are brave as a bobby. First, they drive along a predetermined course... then that stone statue over there gets up and chucks the vehicle and its occupants up into that tree, as precisely as possible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was kinda hoping you'd say something a little more reassuring... Like, with flawless precision...</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">You know, that there vehicle was thrown into the tree just a moment ago.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm astonished that such a plan could manage to obtain approval.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Well, you know Londoners... They're all daredevils at heart. It's pretty popular with the folk over at Scotland Yard, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmmm... But...doesn't it strike anyone as a little weird?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">...Weird? What do you mean by that, missy?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That statue was supposed to have been moved by witchcraft, wasn't it? But there's no such thing as witchcraft here in London!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That's right! How do you explain that, Inspector?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Listen, you lot! How many times do I need to say it? I have no intention of divulging that kind of sensitive information!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">............ Hey-ho... I suppose just a little hint wouldn't be out of order. ...But this is the last time, you hear me? Now, anyone who's cleared this game already knows that magic isn't the real deal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Exactly...</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Well, truth is, that stone bloke over there is in fact a robotic bloke, created with the very latest ultra-advanced technology.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Ro-bo-tic...?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">It just so happens that research has been carried out day and night over at Labrelum Inc., in order to make magic a reality. ...That "statue" is a prototype that came about through their research.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... But what's a prototype like that doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Well, seems Labrelum were rich enough to buy up that part of the park.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-but why would they go placing a statue like that in the park?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">There's a good reason for that. You see... when that upstart detective took Espella and fled Labyrinthia, they needed some way of grabbing his car and lobbing it into a tree.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-that's so improbable, it's ridiculous...</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Funny you should say that... Labrelum's corporate slogan is: "making the impossible improbable".</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If I may interject, why exactly is that sta- ...that robot picking up tourists' cars and throwing them into that tree?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Peh! Why not investigate that yourself, Layton? ............ Well, apparently, the president of Labrelum is no longer in need of magic, so he's donated the statue to the people of London.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Inspector Chelmey, do you mind if I ask you something?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've been telling us since the start that you have no intention of divulging any information... but now it kind of feels like you've told us everything.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I mean... Why make a big deal about "divulging" things if you're just gonna tell us anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">............ ............ Do you have any idea what you've just said?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Don't you lot understand the whole fierce authoritative hierarchy going on between Layton and me?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Au-tho-ri-ta-tive-hi-er-ar-chy...?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">I always have to say something like: "Keep your nose out of police affairs, Layton." Even though everyone already knows from the start which of us is more talented...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Right, I guess...</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">To be downright honest, I'd be more than happy to tell Layton everything I know. But I can't just do that, now can I? ...No, that would be too simple. I've got to stand firm under the steely gaze of all the players and put on an air of superiority. That's my sad fate, as Layton's rival!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No kidding... Well, sounds like that's a weight off your shoulder, Inspector.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's good to vent a little, once in a while. I mean, this is a Special Episode, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Inspector, you needn't think about things so much... It's certainly not something worth worrying about. In truth, I have never once considered you to be my rival.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">............ ............ ............ What the devil is that supposed to mean? Tell me...what are you getting at?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ My dear Inspector Chelmey, it simply means that I see you not as a rival, but rather as a friend.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">As...a...friend, you say? Well, yes, that's...just what I was getting at.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is it me, or has anyone else noticed those looooooong, awkward pauses between Inspector Chelmey's answers?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd abandon that line of questioning if I were you, Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Normally, of course, that kind of free-flowing information only comes from Constable Barton.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Constable Barton, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">He's the one who gives too much away, meaning I have to say something like: "Oi, shut it, Barton! I'll do the talking." But he isn't around today, which is why I felt the need to pause. Hence all the uncomfortable silences before I answered...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Now that you mention it... Constable Barton is rather conspicuous by his absence this evening.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Um... Speaking of being absent... What about Luke? We haven't seen him since he left us and went on ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, that's right! Luuuuuke! Heeeeeey, Luuuuuuuuke! Don't tell me he's been abducted by a witch! Not after all we've been through!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Fear not, Miss Fey. I can assure you, he's quite all right.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">What do you mean, Mr Layton?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If you're concerned about Luke's whereabouts, then I have something that may be able to offer some clarity.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh...? Does that mean what I think it means?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Quite right, Miss Fey. It's time for a puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Again with the puzzles...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would appear that before Luke went on ahead, he left us a message. If we can solve this puzzle, we'll no doubt gain an important clue as to his current whereabouts.</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So..."Layton loves his afternoon tea" is meant to be some kind of clue...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Way to state the obvious, Luke...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes...we all know Mr Layton loves his tea.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">I'd hardly call it a revelation.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ho ho, indeed. It would seem there was no clue to be had after all.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Where in the blazes has Barton got to, anyway?! I could've sworn he was here when that youngster arrived...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh...so, Luke did come to this park after all?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And, guys, remember what he said? "There's something I want to show you all, but I've got to jolly well get it ready first, guvnors"... Or something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To me, that "something" sounds like it can only be referring to one thing...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Remind me... What was it that you said a moment ago, Inspector? Something about that attraction being popular amongst your colleagues at Scotland Yard...?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Well, yes, I remember saying that, all right. But what are you suggesting?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you think the "something" he wanted to show us and this "attraction" could be the same thing?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You mean... Luke and Constable Barton...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, no! What shall we do?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Luuuuuuuuuke!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Luke! Are you in there?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Oh! I think I hear something coming from the top of the tree!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, at least it seems like Luke is okay... thank goodness.</line>
</xml>