<xml>
<title>Making Money</title>
<line speaker="Birdly">And now, without any further ado, behold my latest song...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wooooooh! Here we are in the latest episode, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yep, and it sounds like Birdly is in top form today.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, that was pretty funny! Here you go, Birdly! A little something for your song.</line>
<line speaker="Cracker">Thank you...thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">Thanking you... Many thanks to you..</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey... Isn't that Mr Bardly dancing and singing way over there?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Do you think he and Mr Birdly are working on some sort of collaboration...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps so... Although, I'm not sure it's one entirely of mutual consent.</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">I wrote the lyrics, he stole my song. I'm over here...something's gone wrong ♪</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Did you hear that, Nick? That doesn't sound fair. Maybe we can do something for Bardly. I wonder if there's someone we can lodge a formal complaint with...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lodge a complaint? Yes, Maya... I'm sure Labyrinthia has a customer complaint line you can call...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I did like the song, though, "The Ballad of Emeer Punchenbaug I: The Man with the Golden Dream".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">More like: "The Man Who Takes People's Gold to Buy His Dreams"...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, what's the matter, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I think we've been overspending a little... We're a bit low on pocket money.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Oh dear... It could be that we've exceeded our Adventuring Allowance this time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess I'm partially to blame for that... Sorry, Professor! Better find a way to come up with some quick cash...but what? Hey, I know! We could try going to the pawnbroker and selling something valuable.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ I beg your pardon, Miss Fey, but... would you kindly stop gazing at my right arm in such a manner? It's making me feel rather uneasy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay... Well, scratch that idea.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure there must be other ways of making money here in Labyrinthia...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">HEEEEEEEEEY! I've got it! In cases like this, there's only one answer! We have no choice but to use the powers of you know what!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">The powers of..."you know what"?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">C'mon, it's obvious! I mean the powers of alchemy...duh!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um...Maya, you have a bit of a sinister look in your eyes right now...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's settled, then! So what are you guys waiting for? To the alchemist's place!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Lest we forget, Miss Fey, it has already been proven that neither magic nor alchemy actually exist here, has it not?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I believe in Greyerl! I know she can exceed the limitations of "scientific knowledge" if we ask her to.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Exceed the limitations of scientific knowledge"... In other words, turn something into gold for us.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">C'mon, c'mon! Let's go already! It's time to dive into the wild and wonderful world of alchemy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just follow the smell of gold...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Let's go! It's been a long time since we last saw Miss Greyerl.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes! Let's all go and see her!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'd like to remind you one more time... this right arm of mine is staying firmly where it is.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow! Sir Belduke's residence hasn't changed one bit, has it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It looks as "alche-misty" as I remember... This place could really use a gardener or something, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Siiiiiiiirrr!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uuuuurgh... That voice is as piercing as ever... Feels like a needle to the brain.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! It's Lettie Mailer!</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">What's this? Are you all here to see Jean? Hey, Jean...you've got visitors!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Hello, everyone. Allow me to welcome you all.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah! Miss Greyerl... It's good to see you again.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">It's so nice of you all to come and visit. This is quite the pleasant surprise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's been a while. Last time I saw you, you'd only just revealed that you're actually, y'know...a girl.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes... Ever since the incident in court, I've been able to lead a much more relaxed life.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's marvellous. I must say, it is refreshing to see that smile of yours, Miss Greyerl.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">I totally disagree!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Eh...?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Personally, I'd be happier if Jean had stayed male. Y'know, at least for a while longer. Here, look! These are letters, from the girls in town. And not just any letters. Half this satchel is full of Jean Greyerl fan mail!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Lettie, please... I-it's embarrassing...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Hee hee. But you're so popular, Jean.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Well...I better get going. These things need to find their recipients! The letters, I mean. See you later, Jean!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Okay, Lettie. Be sure to stop by again for a cup of tea.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Siiiiiiiirrr!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, at least Jean seems to be making new friends all around.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So...Jean, how have things been going for you recently?!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That's a somewhat open question... I'm not really sure how best to respond.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, okay... How's the whole alchemy thing going? Cooked up any alchemically awesome concoctions lately?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Ah...yes, well... In all honesty, I've recently taken to thinking about what Sir Belduke said regarding "the rules of nature". At the present time, I've decided to hold back on alchemy and devote my time to medical science instead.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">WHAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Is that so? Well, I think that's wonderful.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I'm pleased you agree. There are too few doctors here in Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Your smiling face says it all, Miss Greyerl. I think you've found your true calling!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Thank you, I appreciate the encouragement. Thanks to all you've done for Labyrinthia, each and every day feels more fulfilling. I have my parents living here with me now, too, so we're finally able to enjoy family life together again.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's...just...wonderful, Jean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like you can kiss goodbye to that gold, Maya...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">As it happens, I've just been out in the woods collecting medicinal herbs.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">..."Woods"? I guess you must mean the Eldwitch Woods, right?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh...Mr Wright, allow me to explain. You see, after all that's happened, they decided to change the name of those woods.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">They're now known as the Nulwitch Woods. Although I'm not exactly sure why...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Null-witch Woods, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I guess there must be some kind of meaning behind it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-who comes up with these names, anyways...?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Oh! I just realised, it's nearly time for my teachers to arrive.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You have teachers...?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That's right! There's so much to learn... So many subjects to study... And yet, so little time... Devotion to the pursuit of knowledge is a challenge to be relished.</line>
<line speaker="???">That's the spirit, Jean Greyerl...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">M-Miss Primstone! And...Miss Mystere, from the library.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Ridelle Mystere, at your service. I trust you are all keeping well.</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Oh dearie, dearie me! If this isn't quite the touching reunion. But there's one thing I would like you to consider...so if you would all pay attention! Ms Primstone's lesson number six! "Reunion leads to nothing but trouble". After a sprinkling of nostalgia, the ashes of the past will once again burst into flames... This is of the utmost importance.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">As always, Ms Primstone, your teachings are as full of wisdom as they are pertinence. [sic]</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I think you might want to consider getting another teacher...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Jean, while knowledge is important...the fruit of one's knowledge is also essential in deepening one's understanding of puzzles.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Of course, Miss Mystere.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Then let's not beat around the bush! It's time for a puzzle! Here we go then, Jean... Which of the following is the odd one out?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Why, surely that must be... Phoenix, Miss Mystere.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Correct! Peerless precision and punctuality. The perfect puzzle solution! It's only natural. After all, I am Master Belduke's apprentice!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey...th-that's my line!</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Now, now... There's no room for complacency just yet! When it comes to puzzles, one is never enough. Be prepared for puzzle number two in this series.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I'm ready, Miss Mystere.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Here we go then, Jean... Which of the following is the odd one out?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Why, once again it must surely be... Phoenix, Miss Mystere.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Correct! Shrewdness and swiftness were key in this scintillating solution!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoooooa... Amazing, huh, Nick? Looks like we have ourselves a good ol' student-teacher face-off!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Personally, I'm more concerned that the odd one out is always Phoenix...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Ah, if it isn't... Professor Layton. As always, it's an honour and a pleasure to see you, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The pleasure is all mine, Miss Mystere. I must say, you seem as radiant as ever.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">We follow the same path, you and I... a never-ending path of perplexing puzzles. I trust that you, too, have been honing your puzzle-solving skills since we last met.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Always, Miss Mystere.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Then I'm sure you'll have no trouble at all... with this puzzle!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Ah...as perspicacious as ever, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Being chased by a big monster and hurling bombs around...I can't decide if that puzzle was super scary, or super fun!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm just bummed that the gold bomb had to get destroyed... We'd be loaded if we could've sold that to Price!</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Oh dearie, dearie me! I've never in my life seen such splendid puzzle solving. But there's one thing I would like you to consider, if you would all pay attention! Ms Primstone's lesson number ten! "Puzzles lead to nothing but trouble."</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">What are you saying, Ms Primstone?! That's a step too far, even from you!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I have to agree! The exhilaration felt from solving a puzzle is like a beam of light in the mind.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...It is the light of the future. The intellectual illumination within our lives.</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Oh dearie, dearie me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... How should I put this? The only thing I've learned today is... "Ms Primstone's lessons lead to nothing but trouble".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup... And I know a certain spirit medium, who shall remain nameless, that causes all sorts of trouble wherever she goes.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey... What's THAT supposed to mean?!</line>
</xml>