<xml>
<title>Mysterious Labyrinthia</title>
<line speaker="???">............ ...Luke... Wake up, my boy.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Uh, umm... Eh? Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Good. I'm glad to see you're awake.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ugh...yeah. Glad to be back...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Are you feeling all right?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um, yeah, I'm fine. A bit drowsy though... I guess I just fell asleep all of a sudden. ............Ah! Wait, now I remember! Professor, what happened with the witches?! And...where exactly are we?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, Luke, I've only just woken up myself. We've been here in this horse-drawn wagon since I awoke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">H-how did we end up asleep in a wagon?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That is something we must now find out. First of all, where are we? And secondly, where are we being taken? There's another passenger over there. Let's start by asking her.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Good thinking, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Vegetables. They're all quite big and tasty looking.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps it is a vegetable cart? No, I don't think it is.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We're not in London any more, are we...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks pretty drab. If this is a sightseeing tour wagon, the tickets had better be cheap.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is not the most comfortable, either.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There's one more passenger, so I think it's not a freight wagon, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Judging from what I can see, we're crossing a forest.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A forest? This can't be London. Where on earth are we?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There is not a trace of other people or even cars. We must be somewhere deep in the countryside.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Excuse me, but I wonder if you could tell us where this wagon is heading?</line>
<line speaker="???">Where it's heading? ...That really is a meaningless question. It goes without saying, since there's only one place we could possibly be heading.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...I'm not sure I entirely follow.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um... What do you mean by "one place"?</line>
<line speaker="???">............ If you really want to know, why don't you ask the wagon driver? Although, whether you ask or not, we'll be arriving at our destination soon anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">If that's the case, surely it wouldn't hurt to just tell us...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Luke... Let's take her advice. We may have better luck with the driver.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">All right...if you say so.</line>
<line speaker="???">............</line>
<line speaker="???">............</line>
<line speaker="Wagon Driver">Hee-hee, so you finally woke up, did you? I was wondering what to do with you both... I was starting to think you'd never wake up.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">E-excuse me, but... where is it that we're going?</line>
<line speaker="Wagon Driver">Me-oh-my! You didn't get into this wagon without knowing where it's headed, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, in truth, we only just became aware that we were in here. Until just a moment ago, we were at Tower Bridge, in London. I'm afraid we have no recollection of having boarded this wagon.</line>
<line speaker="Wagon Driver">Hee-hee, you certainly say the strangest things. You're both still half asleep, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Half asleep...? Of course not!</line>
<line speaker="Wagon Driver">As far as I remember, you've both been in this wagon from the very start.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There's no way that's right! And besides...</line>
<line speaker="Wagon Driver">Now, now, don't get so worked up, sonny. You'll upset the other passengers. I know nothing about the two of you, except from what I've seen. My job is just to carry my passengers... ...to that town.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A town, you say...?</line>
<line speaker="Wagon Driver">Well looky here, it's just come into sight! Why not take a peek out, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Captain! All present and accounted for, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Ahem! I want you to keep it in mind, men, that the peace of this town is in your hands. Never forget that no matter what happens, the people look to you to keep the peace! We proud knights of the order will always protect the people!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Yes, sir! For honour and glory!</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Captain, Captain!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Hmm...? What can I do for you, my little ones?</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">I want to join the order of knights and patrol the streets like you!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Ha ha! That's an upstanding ambition, lad. Perhaps, when you're a little bigger...</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Yes, sir! I'll do my very best to grow up as soon as I can, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Hmm. I like your spirit, young man! Be seeing you.</line>
<line speaker="Petal">Oh, you look so pleased with yourself! You don't really think a weakling like you could join the order of knights, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Hey, that's not a nice thing to say. Every boy wants to be a knight...</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">Oh, what can he do, For one sweet as you? This bardly bard called Bardly♪</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">Could you sing me a wittle song? Something womantic, to melt my heart?</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">Oh, fair maiden, the pleasure is mine. A worthy song, for a love such as thine♪ Oh, the love in your heart, And the love in your head, Is full and warm, like freshly baked bread♪</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">...Sweeeeet!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">P-Professor! Look at those people over there! They're all wearing period costumes. I've never seen that in London!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...you're right, Luke. This town would appear to resemble the one we saw pictured in that book... Although I'm somewhat puzzled as to how we have ended up here...</line>
<line speaker="???">There is nothing strange about any of this...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah! You're the passenger from the wagon.</line>
<line speaker="???">The fact that we are here now is a predetermined turn of events.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wh-what do you mean?! We were just brought here from outside...</line>
<line speaker="???">This "outside" of which you speak... Just what exactly are you referring to?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? Well, I mean London, of course...</line>
<line speaker="???">There is no such place. Nor is there any such thing as an "outside". Not here...not in Labyrinthia...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............! Labyrinthia...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wh-what?! You mean this is really Labyrinthia? Even so, that doesn't mean that London doesn't exist! If we went back the way we came, we'd be bound to come across it eventually!</line>
<line speaker="???">If you don't believe me, then why don't you take a look with your own eyes?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ahh?! Professor! The gate is gone!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The gate we came through was right behind us, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...yes, it certainly was there.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So if that's the case, why does no one around here seem surprised? Seeing such a big gate disappear like that...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This is most perplexing...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What's going on here...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If this really is Labyrinthia, then... Could it be that we have somehow ended up inside that book...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You mean the book Espella was showing us, don't you? The Historia Labyrinthia...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's right, Luke. Do you recall what happened to us at Tower Bridge?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, I remember when that book started glowing. But after that, I'm totally blank...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor...you don't think we've somehow been pulled inside that book, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's a bit early to be drawing conclusions just yet, my boy. There are quite a few people around here. Let's start off by asking a few questions.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The flag bears some coat of arms, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Knights, coat of arms... This really seems like the past...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Look at all this fresh produce, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It seems people here do not need to rely on barter. They have their own currency.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They're selling various equipment. Swords and shields are lined up on the display counter.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The variety of items on display suggests these people's civilisation is quite advanced.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">You've finished patrolling this area, then?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Yes, sir! Nothing to report at present, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Hmm, we must be even more on our guard than usual today.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Yes, sir! Oh, by the way, Captain...</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">I don't mean to alarm you, but there appears to be a couple of unusual characters approaching our vicinity, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">What?! Oi there, you two! What business do you have with the order of knights?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh, er...well, um...we just wanted to ask a few questions about the area... Um, about the order of knights... Are you really...real knights?</line>
<line speaker="Captain">What's that?! You're not poking fun at the order of knights, are you?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That was certainly not our intention. We were merely noting that your appearance is somewhat unusual...</line>
<line speaker="Captain">You're saying we're unusual, are you? Well, that's an unusual thing to say... We usually patrol Labyrinthia, doing our usual duty of keeping the usual order. Tell me, what's unusual about that? If anyone's unusual here, it's you two! And I find it quite unusual that I've never seen either of you characters before. Which part of the town are you from?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We, um...just came here in the back of a wagon, through the gate over there. But then we noticed the gate has vanished. You didn't see anything, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Gate? What gate?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But, there was a gate... We just came through it, from outside...</line>
<line speaker="Captain">...Outside? Now I've been patient with you two, but nothing you're saying makes a lick of sense.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">My apologies. I'm afraid it has been a while since we've been here on the main street. And I seem to remember there having been a gate of some sort around here...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But, Professor...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Luke, I think it would be prudent to play along here.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">There's definitely something fishy about you two...</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Captain, I don't suppose these two are...</line>
<line speaker="Captain">No, I doubt that. Although they do look and act strangely...</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Maybe, we could test them to see if they really do live here?</line>
<line speaker="Captain">A test... Yes, that might be a good idea. I know a good way of deciding whether you two are dubious characters or not.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wh-what are you going to do?</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Well, it's very simple. If you really are upstanding members of this community, then you'll be able to solve this.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Solve? Solve what...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm. Luke, it appears this town has puzzles similar to those of our own world.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">What are you mumbling about? Are you ready? Then here we go!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">35</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Mmm...truly impressive puzzle solving! Of course, any member of our community could solve it... But those who can solve it with this level of insight are few and far between. You are no longer under suspicion. Although I must advise you to speak and act with more caution henceforth. Today being a special day, we are on an even higher level of alert than usual.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It seemed a bit touch and go for a moment, but I think we've convinced him.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Not only that, but it seems that puzzles are a familiar concept here. Which means that if we run into trouble, we should be able to overcome it through our usual puzzle-solving approach.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's good to know! That puzzle was a bit different to what we are used to, though...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It seemed to be a puzzle rather unique to this town. And all the more worth solving for it, wouldn't you say, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Too right, Professor! So what's our next step...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, my boy, first and foremost... I suggest we take a look around and investigate this town of Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">All right, let's do that! But where should we start...? We know next to nothing about this town...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's true, Luke. Although, if you recall, we do know somebody who has been here before us.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah! You mean Carmine, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Precisely. It appears that Carmine was able to leave this town and return to London. However, it would also appear that he was unaware of how me managed to do so...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So you mean, Carmine's activities here may be our only clue to getting back?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm afraid so, Luke. First things first, let's see if we can find any signs of his presence here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are, Professor! Let's start investigating!</line>
<line speaker="???">...Hmm... ...Enjoy yourselves while you can... ...for you will no doubt soon realise... ...the role you have been chosen to play...</line>
<line speaker="Petal">I haven't seen you two around here before! Do you know where you're standing?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, I might be wrong...but I think we're in Labyrinthia...</line>
<line speaker="Petal">That's not what I mean! You tell 'em, Cecil.</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Me? Uh, well... It's just that this is OUR territory, you see?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Your territory...?</line>
<line speaker="Petal">That's right. You two just went and walked right into our territory.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh, I get it. You mean we walked into the area you always play in, right? Sorry, we didn't realise... Do you mind if we join you here for a while?</line>
<line speaker="Petal">You heard 'em... Whaddya think?</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">I guess it'd be all right. The more the merrier, I say.</line>
<line speaker="Petal">Fine, here's what we'll do. If you can solve this puzzle, then you can stick around.</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">It's our initiation test!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">20</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Petal">Hey, you're pretty good.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That was a piece of cake. After all, solving puzzles is my speciality!</line>
<line speaker="Petal">Yeah, me too. It'd only take me ten seconds to solve a puzzle like that.</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Really? I didn't know you solved puzzles.</line>
<line speaker="Petal">You...just keep out of this! Nobody asked you! Anyway, you're now an official member as promised. From now on, you're number two.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Number two?</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Yep! I'm number one!</line>
<line speaker="Petal">You should feel proud. As number two, you can walk around the town freely. Not only that, but I'll let you in on a secret. If you check those green flags over there, you'll find something I hid there.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um, okay, thanks! Somehow...I get the feeling that even if I hadn't become number two, I could have walked around the town freely...</line>
<line speaker="Petal">Hey, number two! There's something else you should know.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Petal">I've hidden treasure in some other places all over our territory. For example, that flag over there. Try examining it and see what you find. You'll find something amazing that I hid! There's treasure hidden in a whole lot of other places, too.</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Just help yourself to whatever you find!</line>
<line speaker="Petal">As the boss, it's my duty to take care of my number two!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Thanks! I'll be sure to search all around for the treasure you've hidden.</line>
<line speaker="Petal">Make sure to check every nook and cranny!</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">It would be great if you found all of it.</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">Ho-hum, ho-hee! I'm just so happyyyyy!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Why are you so happy?</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">Well, that should be obvious! Today I get to gaze upon Inquisitor Barnham in all his spwendour!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Inquisitor Barnham? What's he like?</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">Are you sewious?! I can't bewieve there's a young boy who doesn't know all about Zack Barnham! He's so spwendid and handsome and kind... He's just amazing!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I, um...I'm surprised anyone could be that wonderful...</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">Oh, you'll understand when you see him! He'll be making his appeawance soon, over on Nowth Pawade Avenue. Ho-hum, ho-hee, I'm just so happyyyyy! I have to go now and see what I will seeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">She seems to have headed north.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">She said North Parade Avenue, didn't she? Do you think some sort of event will be taking place there?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I can't say for certain...but wherever you look, the townspeople certainly do seem excited about something. It could be that some kind of special social event is being held today.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Sounds exciting! Let's hurry up and see what's going on!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is a very detailed statue portraying a knight.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, is this town ruled by knights?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A cat! I like looking at animals almost as much as solving puzzles.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's asleep. I am relieved to know that even in this world cats can safely nap in the sun.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Gusts of wind are rattling the shop sign. It seems they're closed today.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The number of shops indicates the town's prosperity.</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">Oh, what have we here? A man and a lad! Like two lost sheep, It makes me so sad...♪</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow, are you singing for us?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah, how fascinating! This man is clearly a minstrel.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Minstrel? There were around in the Middle Ages, weren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. In the Middle Ages, minstrels were a kind of professional musician or poet. Although I do find it a little embarrassing to be referred to as a "lost sheep"...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, at least it's better than being called a little lost lamb, right, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">Little lost lambs, please have no fear! The bard, your shepherd, Is standing right here♪ Labyrinthine town, so your ways be known, I shall give the lambs a map, Of their very own♪</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You're right, Luke...I did prefer sheep. But it is most kind of this gentleman to provide us with a map of the town.</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">It is my pleasure, it is my delight! I am only doing, what is right♪</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Thank you, minstrel! This map will come in handy.</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">The sheep are happy, the bard is pleased, But sadly that map, is a bit of a tease...♪</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">Actually... the map I just gave you... is all in pieces...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Whaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Minstrel?</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">You did it! You fixed the map!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Please, think nothing of it. I'm just glad we have the map in one piece.</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">Now, let me tell you about our proud town! The first thing you should know, Is that it is round♪ Right is a baker, selling bread for your meal. Left is a weaponsmith, sharpening steel♪ In the north of the town, People gather and wait. And I must go soon, before it's too late♪</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There definitely seems to be something big going on to the north, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, it would appear so, Luke. Let's make sure to have a look a little later.</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">Now let me tell you, about our proud town. The shape, you see, is perfectly round♪ Right is a baker, selling bread for your meal. Left is the weaponsmith, sharpening steel♪ In the north of the town, People gather and wait. And I must go soon, before it's too late♪</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Okay then, let's make some room there!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow, would you look at all these people! And look over there! Those knights we saw are here too. What do you think's going to happen?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I don't know, Luke. But whatever it is, it must be something of great importance to this town. Everyone appears to be waiting for something.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">I'm afraid you cannot go beyond this point. The street ahead is closed.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I guess this is as far as we can go. I wonder what's up ahead...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I suppose there's nothing for it. For the time being, we'll just have to look around for a little while longer.</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">What a day! What a day! I've been waiting so long for this day that my beard has grown this far!</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">Me too. I've been so excited that he's popped up in my dweams more times than I can wemember... And the wainy weather we had till yesterday has compwetely cweared, so we'll be able to see evewything, even fwom afar! Oh my... I can hardwy wait for it to begin!</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">Without a doubt, it must be soon now.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would appear they have been kept waiting for quite some time.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Everyone else here seems to be growing restless too.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Let's come back later. It shouldn't be difficult to tell when it's getting under way.</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">Oh my, why won't it start?! I don't think my heart can take any more!</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">You and me both. If it doesn't start soon, my beard will grow even longer!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, what's that tall building over there?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I cannot see it well enough from here, but it certainly is tall.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Lots of dressed up people around here.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Also, many knights are patrolling this area. It must be very important.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The architects in this town must be extraordinary.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Buildings like those would fit in snugly in London, too.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There's some milk in it.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm. There must be a dairy farm somewhere in Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's the fishmonger. They're selling uhm...saltwater fish.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That means this town must be close to the sea.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The bakery. Labyrinthians do not seem to suffer from food shortages.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It can't be a bad place if there's so much food to go around!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow, a bakery! And it smells so good...</line>
<line speaker="Petter">If it's the bakery you want, they're out at the moment. But they should be back soon.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's too bad...</line>
<line speaker="Petter">But don't you think the taste of the bread has changed a bit recently? And the people working there seem somehow different, too. But then, I also feel like they've always been working there...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Do you mean to say you're not certain?</line>
<line speaker="Petter">No...I'm not. It's just that somehow I have the feeling that there are more people working there now.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There is something I would like to ask you. How knowledgeable are you about the people of this town?</line>
<line speaker="Petter">The people? Well, I have lived here all of my life, so I guess I know most of them. Why do you want to know?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I would just like to know if you have ever met a man called Carmine.</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Carmine? Hmmm... Sorry, but no. I've never seen nor heard of anyone by that name.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You've never heard of him? How curious...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Do you think he was just going under a different name here?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Petter">More importantly, shouldn't you two be on your way? Everyone else is already heading there.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Is there something else we should be doing?</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Are you kidding?! With all the townspeople getting so excited like this? You two must be waiting as well, right? Why not kill some time with a puzzle?</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Pulling the strings is far better than having your strings pulled, don't you think? Bravo, brilliantly solved.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Thank you. So something really is about to happen?</line>
<line speaker="Petter">You seriously don't know? Ha! Amazing! To think that there could be anyone in town who could be so clueless... Well, if you don't know... Why not come and see for yourselves? As they say, seeing is believing. Or should it be, "a picture is worth a thousand words"? I'm sure you get what I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">He could have just told us... This is all a bit exasperating.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, it looks as if we'll just have to go and see for ourselves. As soon as we've finished looking around, let's head for North Parade Avenue.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Sounds good, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Petter">The bakery is closed. Shouldn't you two be going to North Parade Avenue too?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's a sundries shop but no one's here now.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Each item has a price tag attached, but what currency is this?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Swords, shields, spears, helms... they're not just for show. They're genuine.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This is a smithy, after all. As far as I can see, the blacksmith knows his trade.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Cobblestones. They remind me of some areas of London.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The roads in this town are very well maintained. I wish I could say the same about London.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">This is definitely the best weapon shop! I could blow a month's pay in this place! This sword, this axe and this mace... And that new shield over there... What more could a knight like me ask for?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">They all seem to be painstakingly crafted. But I can't help but wonder how a knight would be able to move with all this equipped.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">A soldier unable to wear this equipment is not fit to be called a knight! What's more, this amount of equipment is but the bare minimum required to effectively oust wrongdoers. Such a knave might come at me just like this...</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">20</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Yow saw right through that shadowy deception with consummate ease! Such powers of observation are outstanding! If you notice anything untoward, be sure to let me know immediately.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Certainly, we'd be pleased to help. Unfortunately, villains tend to be careful too.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Hmm...recently I've heard many tales about badly behaved youths. It seems there are two in particular who are up to no good together. I intend to deal with them before any of the townsfolk fall foul to their misdeeds. So I must remain on my guard at all times, in case they suddenly appear!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">He's definitely a knightly sort of knight! But these streets seem so peaceful, it's hard to imagine any "villains" around here. It's a shame...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, we must hope they apprehend those individuals soon. Let's offer our support too, where we can.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">We must choose our weapons well, so as to be ready to fight at any time!</line>
<line speaker="Price">I say, sir, that's a delightfully elegant hat that you're wearing there! If you were willing to part with it, I would pay a fair price.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...I don't see any hats for sale on your shop front.</line>
<line speaker="Price">Ho ho! You obviously don't frequent this part of town, do you? I'm Price, the pawnbroker. I deal with anything from heirlooms to hats. You can't beat Price when it comes to price.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah, so you're a pawnbroker. I'm afraid I'm a little too attached to this hat to let it go. After all, it is the mark of a gentleman.</line>
<line speaker="Price">Very well, I can see it's a treasured item, and rightly so. Never mind, then. But if you're not selling, then how about buying something?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hmm, I wonder if the money we have on us would pass as currency here...</line>
<line speaker="Price">What's that, you're currently short of funds? Then here's what I'll do... As today is a special day, I'll let you have a little something for free. That is, if you can solve this puzzle... Now, I'll bet this young man excels at puzzles like this one...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? You mean to say you're even selling puzzles?!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Price">Just as I thought, a bright young man!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I pride myself on my puzzle-solving skills.</line>
<line speaker="Price">Then your future is assured! A sharp mind is essential for success. With a mind as sharp as yours, you could even take over my business some day!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Just imagining you as a pawnbroker is certainly an entertaining image, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I've always been the professor's apprentice, and I can't imagine doing anything else.</line>
<line speaker="Price">Whether you're buying or selling, you won't find a fairer pawnbroker anywhere!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The centre of the town is certainly bustling. Something looks set to start at North Parade Avenue.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Everyone's heading that way... Come on, Professor, let's go with them!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I was staring at that flag for so long that I started to make out a face in the pattern...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The coat of arms is unlike anything I have seen in books on the topic.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Those flags are all over the place, so they've got to be important, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They're selling fruit and veg. Good place to get your five-a-day.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">They also have fish on the other side. It's a grocery stall.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The open market is much more fun than shops in the town centre.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I am not averse to admiring implements of this sort.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">These things don't have anything to do with witches or magic.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Archaeologists learn about ancient cultures by examining sundries like these.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's a statue of a knight. We've got them in London, too.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is a magnificent statue. We can deduce from it that knights are very respected in this town.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The water's so pure and cold.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's comfortably asleep. Just like in our world, cats take it easy here.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Cats used to be valued for catching mice. I wonder if they're kept here for the same reason?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This kitty likes sitting on top of barrels.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The cat seems determined not to get down unless someone makes it an offering of delicious fish.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The shop sign looks very peculiar. What do they sell here, I wonder?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The shop's not open yet. The door's locked.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Where do the wagons with milk come from?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I haven't seen any cows or goats around here, but there may be a farm outside the town?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Someone left their wagon unsupervised.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So many types of fish! Is there a river or a lake nearby?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Interesting. I, too, wonder where they obtain so much fish from.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The fish are very fresh. Some are still alive, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mmm...there's a delicious smell coming from the bakery.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There is only one bakery in this area, it would seem.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So many types of bread! Sweet, savoury...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A sundries shop. Pots and vases of various sizes are lined up on display.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm not sure if you could call it a sundries shop. It looks like they specialise in earthenware?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps it is an antique shop. Although I am not sure if the concept exists here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The wares he's peddling look pretty heavy. I can't believe he can walk carrying all that.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">He looks athletic, but what is physical strength compared to the power of witches?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The trade with the knights seems to be flourishing.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The middle of the road is paved with white cobblestones.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">These cobblestones surround the shopping district. This must be the main street.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">If you follow the white line, you won't get lost.</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">This is it! He's about to appear! This is the moment I've been waiting for ever since I began queuing this morning!</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">I can hear their footsteps! He'll be here any moment now! And that means Inquisitor Barnham will be with him! Oh, I just can't wait to see Zacky-wacky up cwose!</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Come on! Come on! We're waiting! Once it's over, I have to get back and finish my deliveries... Come on!</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">We people have gathered, In the street we all wait. Waiting to see him, to learn of our fate♪</line>
<line speaker="Allan">Dearie me... Look at them all, clamouring for a peek! It's as if this has never happened before... It would be more fitting and proper to wait with calmness and solemnity, to show our respect. I always have trouble mingling with the common masses...</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Now, now, out of the way! Let a lady and her goat see!</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaa!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Attention, you rabble! Keep that line straight there!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks like it's beginning at last, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, you appear to be right, my boy. The level of excitement is remarkable.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Hey, you! You with the tall hat! I can't see a thing!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I beg your pardon, madam. What might be the occasion?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">What are you saying?! I've never heard such nonsense... And to think that he is about to appear!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Sorry, but when you say "he", who exactly do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Surely you two can't be serious! Why, it's him, of course! The town's creator...the Storyteller himself!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The Storyteller...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh?! The creator of Labyrinthia?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow, Professor, this is amazing!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And that must be... this town's "creator"...</line>
<line speaker="Woman">Thank you, Storyteller! Thank you for granting me this lovely baby girl!</line>
<line speaker="Man">Look at my mother! She was ill in bed, but now she's as fit as a fiddle!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">People of Labyrinthia! Behold your new Story!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow, that was amazing, wasn't it, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. But, something would appear to be amiss...</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">Eeek! This stowy is too howwible!</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">Without a doubt, this is terrible...</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Th-this...doesn't look good. Today, I'll finish up my deliveries and go home early!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Up until a moment ago everyone was so excited... But now that the parade has passed, the mood here seems totally different.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">They all seem to be afraid of something.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yes, it's very strange... Ah! Professor, there's one of those sheets of paper over there.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That must be one of the sheets that the knights were throwing to the crowd. The problem seems to be related to what is written on those sheets of paper.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hang on, I'll pick one of them up. This doesn't look like a typical letter or anything like that...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's hard to imagine what could be so terrible... Let's start by giving it a read through.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Okay, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What could that mean? A witch again?! And what about where it says, "their lives were consumed in the flames"?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Luke, let us cast our minds back to what Espella said in London... I seem to recall her mentioning that those witches had followed her from Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So that would mean...that the witches we saw in London really were from this town... The witch in this story... Do you think she's the one from before?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's still too early to say. But at any rate, this seemingly prophetic story, is rather disturbing...</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">I onwy came here to see Inquisitor Barnham! And this...this stowy is what I get! Oh my, what bad wuck this is!</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">Oh no-no-no! Things had been so peaceful, and now the witch is to strike once again... What a fearful world we live in.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">What a horrible story! I can't stay here any longer. I'm heading straight back to the market stall, where I can be with my lovely little goats!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, it seems that what's written here is indeed the reason for all this unrest.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's definitely a little ominous... But it's only a story, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">It's pwecisely because it's the Stowy that we're all so afwaid! Don't you even know that much?</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">Without fail... Whenever a witch appears, somebody dies!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Even if what you say is true, there's no reason to be afraid. After all, it's just a story. It's hardly going to become a reality...</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">...What are you saying?!</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">Yes, what do you mean by that?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">You're not impwying that you don't bewieve in the Stowy, are you?!</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">No-no-no...no-no-no... Nooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">You'll get your comeuppance for this!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Hmm? Hey, you two! What's all the fuss about?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Us? Um, nothing...we're not making a fuss!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">What is it? Is something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Captain! It's these two, sir! They're creating a bit of a disturbance...</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Well, well, it's you two... Causing trouble again, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">Ah, Captain! These two here are claiming that the Story won't become a reality! How can they say such a thing?!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">What's that?! This simply can't be... You claim that you don't believe what the Storyteller writes? ............! Could it be that you two...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">P-Professor...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This atmosphere is somewhat unsettling...</line>
<line speaker="Captain">It appears my original instincts regarding you two were indeed well founded! You're clearly suspicious! Men, surround them!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Uh-oh...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Easy, Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">P-Professor! This isn't good... Perhaps we should make a run for it!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Agreed...but running off blindly in any old direction is unlikely to prove successful... We're too unfamiliar with the streets of this town.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Oi! I wouldn't think of running if I were you! Just give up peacefully.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="???">...Mr Layton! ...Luke! Both of you...over here!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............! That voice!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hang on, isn't that...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The voice came from that back street over there... Come on, Luke...let's run!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Okay, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Oi, wait! Stop! Come back here! After them, men! They're getting away!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Yes, sir! Captain!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">As I thought... It really was you, Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But...why? Why are you...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Shhh! I'll explain later... Please, just wait here quietly.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...R-right.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Where are they?! Which way did they go?!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">C-Captain, we seem to have lost them...</line>
<line speaker="Captain">What?! They must still be here somewhere! Find them!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It appears we've managed to elude them... But what now?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We can't stay here... They're bound to find us sooner or later.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Let's move elsewhere. If we keep to the back streets, we should be able to reach the square without being seen. Follow me!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Okay. We're in your hands.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Come on, this way! And keep quiet...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That was rather too close for comfort. It seems you rescued us this time...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It was nothing. I'm just glad you were both able to get away safely. But...what are you both doing here in Labyrinthia?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We'd like to ask you the same question! What about you, Espella? What happened after we were separated in London? I remember you jumping aboard that cargo vessel... Did you have any trouble getting away?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Well, I...uh...that is, I...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Easy now, Luke. We mustn't bombard Espella with questions like that.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I-I'm sorry, Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">No, I'm the one who should apologise. I'm afraid it's just not very clear...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You have no reason to apologise, Espella. But when you say it's "not very clear", what do you mean, precisely?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Well, to be honest...I seem to be unable to clearly recall what happened...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...is that so...? After we put you aboard that ship, we should have followed after you... But at any rate, I'm relieved to see that you're all right now.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, I am. Thanks to you both. It's good that we could meet again like this. I'm so happy to see you here!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Too right! We're both very happy too, aren't we, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We certainly are, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Let me guess... You both came here to solve the puzzles of Labyrinthia, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um, well, yes...something like that. Right, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Actually, the truth of the matter is, we don't really know why we're here.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Eh...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It seems as if... Well, it's almost as if we've been sucked right into that book's story.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Sucked into...the Story?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If it's okay with you, Espella, I'd like to ask you some questions about Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We can't really settle down here for a chat, can we? Those knights might find us again! We'll need somewhere to lie low for a while.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ Ah, I know! If it's all right with you two...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">For now, Mrs Eclaire, the local bread maker, is kindly putting me up in her shop. If you don't mind, you're welcome to come to my room. I'm afraid it's only an attic room, so it's a little small.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Really? I mean, are you sure that's okay? If they were to find us there, wouldn't that mean trouble for everyone at the shop?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Not at all! You shouldn't even think like that. After all, it was you two who rescued me in London, wasn't it? So if there's anything I can do... You must let me help in whatever way I can!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Espella... Thank you. Allow us to graciously accept your kind offer.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Okay! Let's make our way there, while keeping an eye out for those knights. The bakery is on the eastern side of town.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm. The door and windows on the ground floor are shut. Could this be so for safety reasons?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">If this was my house, I'd keep the windows open during the day to let fresh air in.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">The townspeople are afraid of witches, so they bolt the doors and keep the windows shut tight.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's a water fountain. The water looks very clear. It may be suitable for drinking.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There must be a spring somewhere nearby.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Many people come all the way here for water.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A pile of discarded wooden crates.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They're just crates. Nothing to see.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh dear! It's a scorpion! Behind a crate! Aaaaah! ...Oh, it's just a piece of wood.</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Boo-hoo...*sob* *sob*...</line>
<line speaker="Petal">That's enough already! Won't you ever stop crying?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Why are you crying?</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">The witch...the witch is coming!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah...so you both read the story too, right?</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Boo-hoo! I'm a-afraid...of the w-witch! Save me, sis!</line>
<line speaker="Petal">You wimp! You're a boy, aren't you?! It should be the other way around! You should be the one saving me! You're the one who wants to be a knight!</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Boo-hoo... I can't beat a witch... ...I'm toast!</line>
<line speaker="Petal">Will you just stop crying! What about me, huh? How d'ya think I feel?</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">I'll never be a knight... ...boo-hoo!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Don't worry, you just have to be brave. You can still be a knight! And you can look after your sister, too. Here, it's just like in this puzzle...</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">20</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Wow, that's amazing! He really made it to the princess!</line>
<line speaker="Petal">At last, the crying stops!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You must remember to be brave, even when you feel afraid. Sometimes even I feel scared if I'm alone. I believe that if you're with someone you care about, you can overcome any fear!</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Got it! Thanks! From now on I'll take care of Petal.</line>
<line speaker="Petal">I...really don't mind one way or the other. But I do wish you'd stop your crying...</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Yep, ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Even if the witch comes, I'll protect my sis!</line>
<line speaker="Petal">Uh-huh... Even though I'm stronger really...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Look at that bench, Professor! Wouldn't it be nice to spend a whole day on it, reading in the sunshine?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Luke, we are carrying out an investigation. This is not the time to be lazing about on a bench.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes...we should be on our way.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A single bell hangs in the belfry. Perhaps it is sounded on special occasions.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's one huge bell.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Some knights are standing guard at the entrance. I guess we can't go in.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is plausible that the guards are there to make sure no one goes to ring the bell without permission.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It is forbidden to enter the bell tower. Everyone in this town knows about it.</line>
<line speaker="Nozey">This is not good, not good at all. And to think, I was so looking forward to the Storyteller's parade.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You've seen the story too, I presume.</line>
<line speaker="Nozey">Of course I have. But luckily there's only one of me, so I won't become a victim. I still don't see why the Storyteller can't just write happy stories, though... I imagine you feel the same, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes...yes, I suppose so.</line>
<line speaker="Nozey">Oh, Espella... Well, the shadows are growing longer... It's time I was off home!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Eh?! But it's only just after lunch time.</line>
<line speaker="Nozey">My home is far from here! So, er... Be seeing you!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What's got into him?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Nozey">I suggest that you all head home early too.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I was staring at that flag for so long that I started to make out a face in the pattern...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The coat of arms is unlike anything I have seen in books on the topic.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Those flags are all over the place, so they've got to be important, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">The owl symbol is very important to us Labyrinthians.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They're selling fruit and veg. Good place to get your five-a-day.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">They also have fish on the other side. It's a grocery stall.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The open market is much more fun than shops in the town centre.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Maybe I should get something for Aunt Patty?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I am not averse to admiring implements of this sort.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">These things don't have anything to do with witches or magic.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Archaeologists learn about ancient cultures by examining sundries like these.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's cheaper here than in the town centre, so I sometimes do my shopping here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey, Professor, the minstrel is singing a song again.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I believe you're right, Luke. Let's go and listen, while taking care not to disturb him.</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">The crowd, they thronged, In the afternoon sun! The Story was told, And the Creator was done♪ Oh what a tale, the Story's so fearful! Oh what confusion, no one was cheerful♪ Oh, this bardly bard named Bardly, Must tell you without fail, as it is his duty, To relate to you this tale♪ In the darkness of night, When the sun has gone down, The shadow of the witch shall appear...♪ And the unfortunate couple, Walking in the darkness, Shall come unerringly to the witch...♪ And bathed in the witch's fire, Their lives will be consumed by her flames♪ Oh, the story you hear today, Is terrible, I have to say...♪</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">Oh, this bardly bard named Bardly, Must tell you without fail, as it is his duty, To relate to you this tale♪ In the darkness of night, When the sun has gone down, The shadow of the witch shall appear...♪ And the unfortunate couple, Walking in the darkness, Shall come unerringly to the witch...♪ And bathed in the witch's fire, Their lives will be consumed by her flames♪ Oh, the story you hear today, Is terrible, I have to say...♪</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's a statue of a knight. We've got them in London, too.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is a magnificent statue. We can deduce from it that knights are very respected in this town.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The water's so pure and cold.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Knights are indispensable to this town. They protect us from... witches.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's comfortably asleep. Just like in our world, cats take it easy here.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Cats used to be valued for catching mice. I wonder if they're kept here for the same reason?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This kitty likes sitting on top of barrels.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The cat seems determined not to get down unless someone makes it an offering of delicious fish.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">My cat also spends most of the day napping in a warm place.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The shop sign looks very peculiar. What do they sell here, I wonder?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The shop's not open yet. The door's locked.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">This shop was selling medicines made by the town alchemist...</line>
<line speaker="Price">Hello, sir. Did you gentlemen see the parade?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We certainly did. The turnout was most impressive. It seemed almost everyone in the town was present.</line>
<line speaker="Price">Well it's always a good turnout. But more to the point, what do you make of the Story? The very idea of a witch appearing makes me shudder... I'm thinking of closing up shop and heading home early today.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">So do you believe it will be safer to stay at home tonight?</line>
<line speaker="Price">That's exactly what I believe! But that's not all... Just look at the weaponsmith over there. His weapons are selling like hot cakes.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Why are weapons selling so well?</line>
<line speaker="Price">Well, lad, I should have thought that would be obvious... It's because the knights are buying them! They're replenishing their stock of weapons on account of the witch. As a merchant, I'm rather envious. He'll surely make a fine profit this day. Meanwhile, I'm but a pawnbroker, getting almost no custom at all.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hmm, that's too bad...</line>
<line speaker="Price">You gentlemen should also consider going home before it gets dark.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We thank you for the warning.</line>
<line speaker="Price">They're all buying weapons in preparation for fighting the witch. Well, that's what my neighbour says. I'd like to be making as much profit as him.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A sundries shop. Pots and vases of various sizes are lined up on display.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm not sure if you could call it a sundries shop. It looks like they specialise in earthenware?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps it is an antique shop. Although I am not sure if the concept exists here.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">This shop has the best earthenware in town! It's very durable.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The wares he's peddling look pretty heavy. I can't believe he can walk carrying all that.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">He looks athletic, but what is physical strength compared to the power of witches?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The trade with the knights seems to be flourishing.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Apart from swords and armour, he also repairs broken pots and tools.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The middle of the road is paved with white cobblestones.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">These cobblestones surround the shopping district. This must be the main street.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">If you follow the white line, you won't get lost.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">This street surrounds the shopping district, so the cobblestones are different.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Those two characters were slipperier than I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">It seems they have left this area, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Shall we head back, Captain? The men should return to the guard post.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">What...?! This is a disgrace...letting those two slip away from under our very noses like that! Let's take another look!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Sounds like we shouldn't be hanging around this area too long...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. Let's head for the East Shopping Area before they find us.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I agree. If we lay low for a while at my place, perhaps the knights will give up and go home too.</line>
<line speaker="Allan">Did you two see the latest story?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">When you say "latest"...am I to assume that these parades are held on a regular basis?</line>
<line speaker="Allan">You mean you don't know that? People these days... No one knows a thing... Never mind. I'm a forgiving sort. I suppose I should fill the gaps in your knowledge.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's not very polite...</line>
<line speaker="Allan">Ahem... The Storyteller appears in a parade before the common people whenever he writes a new story. It would be no overstatement to say that I spend every waking day looking forward to the stories that he provides.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So you look forward to stories in which witches burn people?</line>
<line speaker="Allan">What are you saying?! That only happens to be the Story this time! Usually the Storyteller writes the most wonderful stories. That's why I thought he would give us a wonderful chapter today, too... Instead, I found myself caught up in the crowd. My glasses were broken, and I was bitten by a dog...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Don't feel down. Every cloud has a silver lining, so they say.</line>
<line speaker="Allan">Don't feel down? Don't feel down, you say...?! Do I look like I am feeling down? Bah! No way am I feeling down! If my unhappiness is recorded in the Storyteller's pages, then so be it! Oh, sorrow... A part of me is such sweet sorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It seems that not all stories are born equal...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Why do I feel that a person's character might have something to do with it?</line>
<line speaker="Allan">For certain, the next story will hold something good for me.</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">Ah, it's you two... You were causing quite a bit of a commotion earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We weren't causing a commotion!</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">The Storyteller's Story is always right. And I cannot abide anyone saying otherwise.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Then you believe that a witch will appear and commit some foul crimes?</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">Of course I do! The Storyteller decides everything that happens in this town. Whether folk meet with good fortune or ill, all that comes to pass is already decided by the Storyteller. Whoever the victims are, they're probably up to no good on a regular basis. I spend every day as an upstanding citizen, so even if a witch does appear... I have absolutely nothing to worry about. ...Nothing to worry about...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............?</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">Mmm...mmm... Argh!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">It's no use pretending! I am afraid of the witch! Argh...... It's over for me!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Maybe you ought to go home as soon as you can...</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">The witch is coming! The witch is coming! It's all over for me...... Argh!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The atmosphere of gaiety has dissipated. That Story has fearsome power over the people here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Shopkeepers and customers all look so grim.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The person who was waving up there is now gone.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The townspeople were overjoyed to see the Storyteller at first, but now...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Ah...we're here. This is the bakery!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mmmm...I can smell the bread baking!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">There are some excellent bakers working here. Come on, I'll introduce you!</line>
<line speaker="Petter">So, did you both read the Story?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, we did. It said a witch will appear and two young people will be burned...right?</line>
<line speaker="Petter">It's a terrible story. There will be a feeling of dread hanging over the town tonight...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Aren't you afraid? You seem so relaxed.</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Well, I'd be lying if I said I wasn't afraid... But what's written is written, and there's nothing we can do about it. The Story can't be changed once it's been written...so no use moaning about it now.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Don't you feel there's even a possibility that the story may not come true?</line>
<line speaker="Petter">That sounds a bit deluded to me. You know, you should be careful... The story was of two young people, and I'm thinking that matches you two perfectly... Aren't you afraid?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Afraid...us? Nah! And anyway, we're a group of three at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Hello, Petter. Have you come to buy bread again today? I think there's some freshly baked bread about to come out of the oven.</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Ah, yes, maybe I'll do that. Thanks, Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............?</line>
<line speaker="Petter">All you can do is pray that the Story's not referring to you two.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So many types of fish! Is there a river or a lake nearby?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Interesting. I, too, wonder where they obtain so much fish from.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The fish are very fresh. Some are still alive, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I tried to bake fish bread one day, but it didn't turn out too well.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mmm...there's a delicious smell coming from the bakery.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There is only one bakery in this area, it would seem.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So many types of bread! Sweet, savoury...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I help out at the bakery, too. Nowadays I hardly ever burn anything.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ahhh...Professor, it's the smell of freshly baked bread!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, Luke. It's certainly whetting my appetite.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I bet the staff here are really talented!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Talented...and highly enthusiastic, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...He's kneading the dough pretty hard, isn't he...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I would rather liken the motion to "pounding", myself.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, um... Mr Wright, these gentlemen aren't customers...they're my friends.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh...really?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Espella, welcome home!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Hello, Maya. Um...where's Aunt Patty?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The boss? She's gone to the market. She should be back at any time now. Sorry about Nick here, he didn't realise you weren't customers.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Not at all. There's nothing wrong with such sincere dedication to one's job.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright, Maya, meet my friends, Mr Layton and Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A pleasure. My name is Hershel Layton.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">And I'm Luke Triton. Nice to meet you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm Maya Fey. And this is Nick...my assistant baker!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix Wright, pleased to meet you. How come I'm the "assistant"?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Phoenix Wright and Miss Maya Fey. ...Somehow not quite the kind of names I'd expect to hear around here. Have you both been working here long?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup! Must be going on five years now. Isn't that right, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Ah...yes, I suppose it must be.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Say, you know what? Seeing as you're both friends of Espella, I think we can give you guys a little something... On the house, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow, really?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, why not? I actually just took some freshly baked walnut bread out of the oven, so...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Cor, so that's what that great smell is! I bet it's delicious!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If you think the scent is good, you should try TASTING it. You too, Mr Layton. It's so good, it'll knock your hat off!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'd be delighted to. That's most kind of you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, that's that then! Go ahead and help yourselves...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Maya">How many times do I gotta tell you, Nick?! You're supposed to say "here's your order"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, uhh...yeah... That's right. I forgot... I don't know why, but... I just get the urge to point and shout like that sometimes...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Bad Nick! Bad! You can't keep shouting at the customers like that... The boss'll be all over you like butter on toast!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That baker...he's...quite a character, isn't he, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, indeed. There's something curious about both of them... They both seem somehow...out of place in "this world". Most intriguing...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">My room is upstairs. We can get there from behind the counter. Feel free to take something to eat.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Noooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wh-what's wrong?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">She seems to be upset about something... Let's ask her if there's anything we can do to help.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry if I came across as rude earlier...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Please, pay it no thought.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's just that sometimes I get carried away when I'm pounding the dough like that.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, it was kind of surprising to hear a big thump like that, even if you were just kneading the dough... And when you said "<cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>>", my heart nearly stopped!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When I bake great bread, I guess I just feel the need to present it to the customer like...that.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A large variety of bread. One could have a different type every day of the week.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They're all baked to perfection, and the smell is making my mouth water.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah, the smell of freshly baked scones. They would go very well with some tea.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">We also deliver bread to other parts of the town.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So hot! That's where bread is baked, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's a sturdy-looking wood-burning oven.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You can bake many batches of bread at the same time in an oven this size.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Baking bread requires more physical strength than most people think.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What's the matter, Miss Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's these loaves of bread... And after I'd arranged them all so nicely, too... Grrr! It's all Nick's fault! His pounding messed up everything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me? But I was only kneading the dough...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What am I going to do?! I have to fix this before the boss gets back!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmmm, that's most unfortunate. Perhaps we can lend you a helping hand.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">REALLY?! Thanks a lot! You'd be doing me the BIGGEST favour in the world!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya...you could try to show a little restraint sometimes, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Not at all. Helping those in need is the duty of any true gentleman.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Not only that, but if we all chip in and help, we'll soon have it sorted out!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Totally! We should all help each other out in times of need, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">40</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Perfect, that's exactly how they were before! Thank you so much!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, thanks! You really saved my bacon!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's no more than any young English gentleman would do!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You said..."inglish"? What's that? And where have I heard it before...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! Maya! The boss is back!</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Hello, everyone! Just as I was wondering what the commotion was all about, I see you're back, Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Welcome home, Aunt Patty.</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Were Maya and Phoenix doing a proper job of minding the shop while I was gone?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">O-of course we did!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Naturally! You know you can count on us!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They may be calling her "boss", but she seems like such a warm and friendly person.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">She certainly does, Luke. And she has a heart-warming smile, too.</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Oh, such flattery! You're just trying to make me blush! By the way, Espella, are these two gentlemen customers of ours?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">These two are friends of mine. They kindly helped me out once, in the past. I was so happy to see them again that I invited them here.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Pleased to meet you, madam. My name's Hershel Layton.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">And I'm Luke Triton, the professor's apprentice!</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Is that so? It seems Espella is indebted to you both, so it's certainly a pleasure to meet you both. As a thank you from me for helping Espella, please feel free to stay for as long as you like. We just happen to have an empty room that you're welcome to use if you wish.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Thank you for your kind offer, madam.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Ah, yes. I imagine you must both be feeling hungry.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well actually, I'm more than a little peckish.</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Ah, you don't say! Well, in that case, let me offer you something special... My very own creation!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Aha! Wonderful! And that face baked on the surface... a masterpiece!</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Yes, I'm proud of it. I use a secret technique to make it extra fluffy!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Only the best for our special guests!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This is great!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Still, we don't really have a whole lot else to offer...only bread.</line>
<line speaker="Patty">............ ..."Only" bread?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh...I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-hey...Espella! Uh... Shouldn't you show our guests to their room? Let's just forget the bread.</line>
<line speaker="Patty">"Forget" the bread...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">M-Mr Layton, Luke. Let's go upstairs, now!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? What's going on?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Just trust me, come on!</line>
<line speaker="Patty">"Only bread"..."forget the bread"?! What kind of attitude is that? You two really expect to become fully fledged bakers some day?! Any more of this half-baked attitude, and I'll throw you in the oven until you're both well done!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I, um...didn't expect that.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm sorry, she's usually so kind and gentle. But when it comes to bread...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I suppose it shows just how dedicated she is to her craft.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I guess it must be fun to live in such a lively place, though.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, it is. It's thanks to them that I enjoy living here as much as I do. Mrs Eclaire is always so cheerful and kind to me. And Maya and Mr Wright are so energetic... Maya, especially.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's certainly an interesting group. Particularly those two... But, Espella, what about your family?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I, um... It's a bit complicated...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Sorry, I didn't mean to pry...</line>
<line speaker="???">Meeow!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Ah...Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meeow!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">What's the matter, Eve? Are you hungry? Sorry, it's my cat. It must be supper time.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah, I see. Please, go ahead. Don't mind us.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">...Meeow.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So Espella has a pet cat... Its name is Eve, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A finely groomed black cat, I must say. I'm sure Espella takes excellent care of it.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Roof windows make this room very bright.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is a very pleasant room. You can see the blue sky through the windows in the roof.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Aunt Patty chose this room for me.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Thick volumes are lined up on the shelf.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Labyrinthian books...interesting. I would like to read some when we have time.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They're all very thick. It would take you some time to read them, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I like reading before going to sleep. I've read these books many times.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Jars with...jam, perhaps? They all have vibrant colours.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They look scrumptious.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I am sure this jam would be even more delicious on Mrs Eclaire's freshly baked bread.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I made all this jam myself. You can try some if you want.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's such a cute cat! So well behaved and clever, too.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Thank you. Eve is a real friend...</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meeow...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, I'm sorry to have kept you waiting. Mr Layton, you wanted to ask me something, didn't you? What was it that you wanted to know?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, there are a few things... Perhaps I'd better ask them one at a time. It may take a little while, if you can spare the time.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, of course. Anything I can do to help.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Thank you, Espella. Well then, first off... <thought>What I want to ask Espella about, is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Could you tell us again what happened, between the time that we were separated in London and your returning to Labyrinthia? You said you can't clearly recall what happened to you, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">No, I can't. When I came to...I was back here in Labyrinthia. I can remember everything up until I boarded that cargo ship... But after that I just can't seem to remember how I got back here. It seems the townsfolk didn't even notice that I'd been away... I almost thought the whole thing must have just been a dream, until the two of you appeared here in Labyrinthia. It seems I wasn't dreaming after all...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, indeed. It all really did happen. You came to my office, and then the witch came for you.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So, does that mean that the witch brought Espella back to Labyrinthia?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Well, I suppose so... But... Why was I in...London in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Why did I meet you two gentlemen...? And why was the witch after me...? I just can't seem to remember why...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Espella, you and Carmine were running away from the witches, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Carmine...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Do you mean to say that you don't remember being in London with Carmine?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Carmine took you with him and tried to escape from this town.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Carmine...took me with him and tried to escape...? ............ I'm sorry...I do have a vague memory of Carmine, but... Why was I in London? ............ I just can't seem to remember...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Why would witches be chasing me in London......? I do remember meeting you, Professor, and you, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Do you remember this letter, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">A letter...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes. Carmine gave you this letter and instructed you to bring it to me. You followed his advice and brought it to me in my office.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That letter...could I take a closer look at it?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Do you remember anything?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I don't remember the letter...but this writing does look somewhat familiar... I do have a feeling...that there was someone there next to me... ............!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Espella, are you all right?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I...I think I remember... I remember Carmine.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">You're right, I do know him... I definitely know Carmine. Carmine was here in this town. In fact, he was in this very shop.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ In this shop, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But according to the townsfolk, they've never even heard of him...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes...yes, that's right. What they say contradicts what I remember. That's why I'm finding it so difficult to trust my own memories...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Please, don't let that deter you. We'd be grateful to hear what you know.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I can't accurately recall what happened in London, but when you showed me the letter... I remembered Carmine being here in Labyrinthia. I remember him quite clearly now. How...how do I have this memory...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Please, do let us know what you can recall.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">According to my memory, Carmine was working here in this bakery.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Eh? But there are already two workers in the shop, right? Mr Wright and Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Those two have also been working here making bread for some time now. Or at least... I'm quite sure...that must be the case... Mrs Eclaire and anyone else around here would soon tell you so. That's why I put no faith in my memory.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...this difference in perception is certainly intriguing. And the fact that Carmine worked here has me somewhat curious.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Do you think all the townsfolk could just be pretending not to know? I mean, maybe Carmine really was here and they're acting like they don't remember. After all, he did mention in that letter that he wrote... that he escaped from Labyrinthia. How about we go and ask a few people around the town?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">No, Luke, I don't think that's a good idea. As you are no doubt well aware by now, a single word out of place can be enough to bring in the knights against us.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Not only that, but I really cannot believe that Mrs Eclaire would pretend not to know him. She's always so straight with people... She's never two-faced.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps, Luke, we should be thankful that she took care of him.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yes, you're right of course, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">By the way, in that letter, Carmine claimed that this town held a mysterious secret. He implied that he wanted me to solve Labyrinthia's mystery. Do you have any idea what that mystery could be?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Labyrinthia's mystery...? I'm sorry, but I've never even suspected that this town holds any secrets.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Then what might it have been that Carmine was investigating?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">What was Carmine investigating...? ............Ah! I think I might know what it could be. One time, Carmine asked me this: "Why is it that whatever is written by the Storyteller in the Historia Labyrinthia always becomes fact? If that puzzle can be solved, then we will unravel the mystery of Labyrinthia," he said.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So Carmine didn't believe that what's written must always come true either...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Well, I'm not sure, but...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But what?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's only natural that what's written in that book must come true. And it's hard for me to believe that both you and Carmine could doubt this.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, speaking for myself, I can't just believe it so easily!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Nevertheless, to the people of Labyrinthia, it appears to be a matter of common sense. Which is why those knights treated us with such suspicion.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's true, but...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Are you saying that... in your London...there's no Story?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, there are certainly none that come true, as the Historia Labyrinthia does. In the world as we know it, such a notion is inconceivable.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">As I suspected... Carmine is from the same London as you two... So I suppose it makes perfect sense that you should all think in that way.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Incidentally, what action did Carmine take after he came to suspect the story?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Um...well, Carmine often visited the Great Archive.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The Great Archive?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, that's where all the volumes of the Story are kept.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You mean to say, all previous volumes too?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, every volume of the Story so far. All of them.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I see... In other words, he wanted to confirm the authenticity of the story.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But, Professor, surely he wouldn't be in trouble with the witches just for looking at some books?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">As I recall, in the letter he sent to me, he wrote:</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I believe that was it. Which probably means it wasn't just ordinary books that he was investigating. It's quite likely that the books had something to do with the witches.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">So you mean...Carmine came close to unravelling Labyrinthia's mystery... And therefore became the witches' target... is what you are suggesting?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I believe that would be highly probable.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">But, why did the witches... ............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um...Espella? Have there been other stories involving witches before this?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Ah, yes. There have been many stories about them. All of these stories are also being kept in the Great Archive.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Carmine seemed to doubt these stories. Which is why he visited the Great Archive so many times.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Stories about the witches are no doubt a source of considerable fear for the townsfolk. So why is it deemed necessary to keep such stories in the Great Archive?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">They are an important source of information for the Inquisition. Their prime objective is to capture witches and protect the people of the town.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">So you're saying that in order to fight the witches, it is essential to read about them and learn their ways?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, that's right. Stories involving the witches are under the authority of the order of knights. And the order of knights was established to protect the town of Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Undoubtedly, it was the order of knights keeping peace during the parade we saw.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That's right. The Storyteller holds those parades from time to time. He gives the townsfolk the Story that will determine their fate from that time onwards. The Story this time involved a witch, which explains why the knights were on such high alert. I wonder what spells will be used this time... If only we could check in that book...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">......! Just a moment, Espella. What was it that you just said? Do you mean to say that there is a book about magic?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Y-yes, there is...in the Great Archive. It describes all of the spells that provide the witches with their wicked power. It is a special book, used by the Knights of the Inquisition, to aid them in their investigations.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's it! That must have been what Carmine was so interested in. He was investigating the witches' power. Of course, it's possible that he came upon a secret that he shouldn't have known...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">And that's why the witches attacked him...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, Luke. That may well be the reason. The Story, so respected by the people, and the witches whom they fear... There could be a certain secret connecting these two in some way.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Thank you, Espella. It seems we now know where to begin with our investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">So you'll be visiting the Great Archive?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, indeed. The book about magic that resides there, may well provide a valuable clue towards unravelling the mystery of Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We'd better get going with our investigation straight away, right, Professor?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Absolutely, Luke. We must solve this puzzle for Carmine's sake, as well as for our own.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Um...Mr Layton? ............ Please... Please take me along with you!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...I'm not sure that's wise. It might put you in more than a little trouble. It is likely that Carmine's investigations are what led to him being pursued by witches. And if that's the case, the path we tread may well be fraught with danger.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Even so... I really would like to help you. Talking with you both like this... I, too, have come to believe that there must be a secret to this town. I want to help you find the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, Espella... I suppose that settles it. From here on in, let's all do our very best to solve this mystery together.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, together!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm the professor's apprentice, so if there's anything you need to know, just ask!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Ha ha, thank you, Luke. I'll be sure to do that!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well then, without any further ado, let's follow in Carmine's footsteps and visit the Great Archive. I'm quite certain that's where the clues are waiting to be found.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meeeow!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Not you, Eve...I'm afraid you'll have to stay here until I get back.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meeeow?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh! My pendant. I almost forgot it.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's a lovely pendant, Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's very old. I can't even remember how old I was when I started wearing it. Right. Sorry to have kept you. Shall we leave for the Great Archive now?</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Oh, Espella. Are you off out somewhere?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes. I'm taking Mr Layton and Luke to see the Great Archive.</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Is that so? Well, you might want to hurry... it looks like it might rain at any time. Ah yes, that reminds me. Could you get me something while you're out? Just on your way back would be fine.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, of course. What can I get for you?</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Some goat's milk from Mary. I forgot to get some when I was at the market.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Okay, I'll drop round to Mary's farm on the way back.</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Would you? There's a milk bucket ready round the back.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Milk, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Naturally, our bakery uses only the finest goat's milk for our milk loaf. It's so fluffy and white, it's delicious!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Cor...sounds great!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Let's be certain to try some later, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm totally up for that!</line>
<line speaker="Patty">So you two are good at problem solving, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, actually, more like puzzle solving than problem solving, really.</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Is that so? Well perhaps you could help me, then. Someone came to me for help, and it's a little difficult for me to solve.</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">40</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Well, I never! You've really solved it, haven't you?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If you have a puzzle to be solved, you can always rely on us!</line>
<line speaker="Patty">What a gentleman! I'll have to bake you something extra special later, to show my appreciation!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm already looking forward to it!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Patty">You both take good care of Espella for me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So you're both friends of Espella's? I'm glad to see she has friends like you.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks like the knights have given up searching for us, thank goodness.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, it seems you're right, Luke. From the look of things, we should be safe to explore a little more before making our way to the Great Archive.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Here we are, this is the Great Archive.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow! It looked impressive even from a distance, but now we're here up close, it's huge! Just looking up at it makes my neck ache.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It must have taken considerable time and manpower to erect a building of this size.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, it did. This building has become something of a symbol for the town.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? Hey, look at that roof over there... It looks like it's suffered considerable fire damage at some point. Was there a major fire or something?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Ah, that... That was...</line>
<line speaker="???">I've been listening for a while, and must say, you two really are strange.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh, it's you.</line>
<line speaker="Petter">That roof has been like that for some time. It's certainly nothing new.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">R-really...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If it's all right with you, could you tell us a little about it?</line>
<line speaker="Petter">You two never cease to amaze me, with your incredible lack of knowledge. Well, I guess it couldn't hurt to tell you. That damage is from the Legendary Fire.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The Legendary Fire?</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Yes. Long, long ago, there was a huge fire that engulfed almost this entire town. The damage there occurred at that time. You can see other traces of the fire around the town too, here and there.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The entire town was engulfed in a huge fire?</line>
<line speaker="Petter">All of the townsfolk know about it. You're probably the only ones that don't.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Thank you for filling us in. That's certainly cleared up a few things.</line>
<line speaker="Petter">No problem. It so happens I had nothing better to do. It wasn't such a bad way to kill time. Anyway, I'll see you around...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">To think that even a building this size could be affected by fire... The fire that spread through the town really must have been "legendary"...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You're certainly right about that, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............? Espella, is something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Oh! Um, no. Nothing at all. Shall we make our way inside?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............?</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">It just won't do. It's compwetewy unacceptable.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What's unacceptable?</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">There's no one in the world more spwendid than Inquisitor Barnham. And yet, evewy time it's that woman who gets to stand awongside the Stowytewwer. It's so unfair.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You mean the woman who was distributing the Story to the crowd, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">To be honest, I found her a little scary.</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">I'm sure it's all some pwan of hers. I just feel sowwy for my poor Zack-ums. Oh...if onwy I could get cwoser, I could offer my support...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would certainly be difficult to get close with that bustling crowd all around. Perhaps even dangerous.</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">...I'd fwy.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">I could fwoat down beside him fwom one of the fwuffy cwouds in the sky. I could fwyyyyy!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wh-whaaat...?!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, I don't think she's coming back!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We can only hope that she manages to reach the man she's after...</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Uh-oh... Not good! What shall I do?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What's the matter? Is there something troubling you, madam?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Oh, yes! Something certainly is! Troubling me, I mean. Today's scary story, it's just so frightening! I may be afraid... But I have to do it! I have to finish my delivery! See this? A whole satchel full of letters! A letter-fest! And I have to deliver them all.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, my...that really is a lot of letters! If you'd like, I could help by delivering a few of them for you.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Oh...Espella! No, no... It's all right. After all, it's my job! And anyway...you look busy right now yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Well, a little. But we should always help each other out in times of need.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">I-I'm okay! Don't worry about me. I've got it covered! Right, I'm off! I can do this... I can deliver them all! The letters, I mean. Nothing can stop the Labyrinthia courier!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah! She's gone! She really was in a hurry, wasn't she? But is she really all right? She seemed a bit...flustered.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I think she's just very, very busy. Come on, let's head to the Great Archive.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks even taller when you see it up close! I can't even see the top!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It requires a lot of architectural knowledge to construct a building of this size.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It makes me feel giddy just looking up at it!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Seeing it like this, you get an idea of how monumental the Great Archive is.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This whole town had once been burned to the ground. It's hard to imagine damage on that scale.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The entire town had to be restored afterwards. It might have looked very different from what it is now.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The symbol from the flag can be found throughout the town.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's an odd symbol. Maybe it's unique to this town.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The quills seem to resemble the Storyteller.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's his crest...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Labyrinthia seems surrounded by cliffs and woods. In the distance there's nothing but fog.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The fog is so thick, I can't see far.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This place looks so mysterious, surrounded by the misty forest.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">The mist here never clears up.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow! There are books crammed in here from floor to ceiling!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Truly remarkable... Are all of these books "stories"?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, they are...all of them. It's said that these were all written by the Storyteller.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">All of these books? But there are so many!</line>
<line speaker="???">Excuse me! Beg your pardon! Look out! Gangwaaay!</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">I've got 'em, don't worry. P-p-piece of caaake! Phew...told you! No problem.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's all right. It's lucky that you didn't drop any books.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I don't think I've ever seen anyone carry so many books at once. Aren't they heavy?</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">I love books, so I feel like a mother carrying her baby. If you love books too, why not carry a few with me?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I do love books, but I don't think I could carry that many...</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">You obviously don't understand the true enjoyment of books. Embracing books, being buried in books, the feel of books, the smell of books... Listening to the sound of the pages turning, gazing up at books piled high... Being surrounded by books and playing with them... That's how to enjoy books!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm not sure I totally agree...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Um...Dewey?</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">Eh?! Th-that voice... That's Espella, isn't it? Uh-oh! H-here we go again!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Please, remain calm. You wouldn't want to drop those books.</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">Just leave it...to me! See, all under control.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Sorry, I didn't mean to startle you like that. Dewey, we've come here to find a book about magic.</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">M-magic?! I should have known... That is, I, uh...never mind.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............?</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">Well, if it's magic that you're interested in, then might I suggest the Grand Grimoire?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The Grand Grimoire, you say? We'd like to borrow that book, if we may.</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">Well, you'll need Miss Mystere's permission. Are you sure you want to borrow it...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Absolutely! We're very interested in magic.</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">Friends of Espella's...interested in magic...? So these two must also be... Uh-oh...whoops! Nooo! I-I'm losing them!</line>
<line speaker="???">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Silence in the library!</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">Only Miss Mystere can give permission to borrow the Grand Grimoire. But I doubt she would allow it...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There are two identical statues, one on each side.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The statues portray people reading. Maybe that's supposed to motivate those who come here to read more.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">The statues look much bigger when you get closer.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This appears to be documentation on accidents and criminal cases.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There's nothing on magic or witches in here.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">An owl statue. This is a frequently used motif in this town.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah, that's right! The flags also have an owl symbol on them!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A candle chandelier. How do they light the candles?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I would venture a guess that they light them from the second floor, with the aid of a long stick.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Reading by candlelight can ruin your eyesight.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, I remember seeing very bright street lights in London. They were so strange.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">The Great Archive was founded for those in the noble pursuit of knowledge. I must ask you to be a little quieter, please. Dewey, as a budding librarian I would have thought that you would have known better...</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">I'm sorry, Miss Mystere. But these people say they want to borrow the Grand Grimoire!</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Did you say...the Grand Grimoire? .........! You're... ...Espella Cantabella. You of all people must know the significance of the Grand Grimoire. It is an important piece of literature which can only be viewed by learned persons of significant status. It's not like I can just give my permission to whoever asks for it, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I understand that, but this man...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">I'm sorry, but rules cannot be changed.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The request is all mine. That book could prove indispensable for my investigations into magic.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">And you are...? Excuse me, but may I ask your name?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm Hershel Layton. I'm investigating this town... You could say I'm a traveller, so to speak.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">A traveller? I'm afraid I have never come across such a profession... Well, I suppose we can return to that later. My name is Ridelle Mystere. I am a librarian, as well as curator of the Great Archive. And I am therefore responsible for all pieces of work here, including the Grand Grimoire. I'm afraid that no matter what your profession or who you are, it is beyond my authority to lend you the Grand Grimoire... It is simply against the rules.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The rules...? Can't you make an exception for us?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Luke...please, leave this to me. I can understand that you are unable to show this book to just anyone. However, as you yourself said just a moment ago, the Great Archive was founded for those in the noble pursuit of knowledge. And I am currently very much in the pursuit of knowledge regarding magic. Perhaps you would consider letting me at least peruse the Grand Grimoire?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Only learned persons of significant status, and in particular, inquisitors, are permitted to refer to the Grand Grimoire.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Inquisitors...?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Those who administer justice in this town. Knights of wisdom, as they are known. Only somebody with equal status to that of an inquisitor, or with the same level of wisdom, would qualify.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">So if I could demonstrate the required level of wisdom, then I would qualify?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">You certainly are a persistent gentleman. Very well, let's see what you make of a trial. This trial has been used in the past to test the ability of aspiring inquisitors. If you are able to clear this trial, then I will acknowledge that your wisdom matches that of an inquisitor. If you can achieve this, then as curator of the Great Archive, I will lend you that book.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Splendid! Then by all means, do begin.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">You certainly have some confidence. Let's see if you can live up to it. Do you think you can pass this trial, at which so many hopefuls have stumbled? See what you can do with this!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">20</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Unable to quit puzzle</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">............! How can this be? That hardly seemed a challenge for you. Who are you...and how did you do that so effortlessly?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">More importantly than who I am, there is one thing of which I am certain, and that is that every puzzle has an answer. So do I qualify?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">............ Not so fast! Do you really believe that my permission can be obtained as easily as that? That was no more than a preliminary trial, to separate the wheat from the chaff. Now for the real trial. Even a man of your calibre should find this challenging. This trial will have your eyes rolling and your head spinning!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............!</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">Miss Mystere, I've never seen you get this excited!</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Silence! Be quiet, Dewey!</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">...Sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I assume it's safe to predict that this will not be quite so simple...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Ahem! This will put an end to that overconfidence! Prepare to lose your mind in this mind-bending puzzle!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">40</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Unable to quit puzzle</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">Before starting puzzle:</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Before I forget, I must warn you... You no longer have the "luxury" of undoing a move. One teeny, tiny miscalculation... and it's game over. I do hope you don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">H...h...how...? My mind-bending puzzle! You didn't lose your mind...on the contrary, you found the solution! It's...that's...just impossible! Oh! My glasses! My book! Don't...look... Don't look at me! My glasses, let me put them on... Just a mo...ment!</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">That's better. I apologise...for a moment there, I lost my composure. But to see my trial cleared like that... It seems I underestimated you, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It was a fascinating puzzle. No more than I'd expect from the curator of the Great Archive.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">I find your confidence rather disconcerting... I hope someday to have the pleasure of showing you a puzzle that will make those little round eyes of yours spin in your head! But nevertheless, a promise is a promise. I hereby grant you your permission. The special viewing room containing the Grand Grimoire is located on the first floor. As I'm sure you are already aware, that book is of unparalleled importance. By no means may it be treated with anything but the utmost care.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Of course, Miss Mystere. Thank you for granting me permission.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Well then, shall we proceed to the special viewing room? I shall have to accompany you, since the room is locked.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You did it, Professor! You cleared both trials in one fell swoop!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That was amazing, Mr Layton! It's well known that Miss Mystere is an avid collector of puzzles. And I've heard that the puzzles she presents are always very difficult to solve!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I see...so there are collectors of puzzles in this place, too...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">......? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Oh, nothing important. Right then, no use in waiting around. Let's go and take a look at the Grand Grimoire!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">That was really amazing, overcoming Miss Mystere's trials like that! That reminds me, I have a puzzle of my own that feels right at home here in the library. A puzzle for true book lovers!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">20</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">Just what I'd expect from someone who sailed through Miss Mystere's trial. I must polish my own puzzle-solving skills...</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">That's amazing! Just what I'd expect from someone who cleared Miss Mystere's trial! I must polish my own puzzle-solving skills...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">This is the special viewing room. I'm sure a gentleman such as yourself will understand... but seeing as this is a special room not open to the general public, I must insist that you all be on your best behaviour.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow...this room feels so grand and elegant.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's my first time in here too... I must admit, I feel a little nervous.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It certainly does give some indication of the importance of the book being kept here. That book in the centre must be the Grand Grimoire.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">This tome is the Grand Grimoire. Please treat it with care.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh, these colours and the brush strokes...this wasn't painted by some amateur!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">An abstract painting in soft colours. It reminds me of a meadow in spring.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? If you look at it from a distance, it resembles an animal.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Look, there's a title: "A Very Happy Cow".</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's locked. I can't even peek inside.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A cabinet that cannot be opened... This smells like a puzzle to me.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It won't open no matter how much I push or pull. Maybe it's locked with a puzzle?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">There is no keyhole. How can we open it?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Oh, it appears we could not open it simply because the door was not fitted properly.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A lively picture of children playing.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There's a woman in this picture. Is this someone famous in Labyrinthia?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The author's signature is on the bottom. It seems to be a self-portrait.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">The woman in the picture is the Court Illustrator.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks like candles are the only source of light at night in the Great Archive.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The quiet Great Archive, bathed in warm candlelight, looks very peaceful.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks very nice, but I wouldn't want to be the one who replaces all these candles when they burn out.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This is incredible! It's crammed with information about magic.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">People say it's the magic used by the witches.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">If that's so, then the magic we saw in London must be in here somewhere too.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That may well be true, Luke. A tome as thick as this must surely contain such information.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Finding it is a bit daunting, though... Huh, what's this? Professor, this page is different from the others...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What is this...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This page isn't about magic at all... Something about it makes me feel uneasy.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............! Luke, this page...it appears to be addressed to someone, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh... You mean like a message...? Let's read it, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wh-what is this?!</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">How...can this be? Why is this in here...? How did something like this get into the Grand Grimoire?! It's just not possible... I can't understand it. No one entered the special viewing room before you came here... And whenever someone enters this room, I always accompany them in this way.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">So...that means that the page must have changed at some point...doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Could that really be possible?! Perhaps with some kind of device...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Unthinkable! There is only one key to this room, so no one can enter without being granted my permission. I assure you it's true, on my honour as a curator.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But then...how can anyone have done this?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Luke, I believe we both know who might be capable of such an act.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Eh...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">You mean, witches...don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">W-witches...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ We don't know yet who changed that page, but the more important matter... is what's written here. The "infinite vault of books" mentioned here presumably refers to the Great Archive. Which implies there is a secret of some sort hidden within the library.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, what about this part: "a person of pers, perspi...perspicacity"...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, I believe that could be referring to Carmine.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">He came here regularly to investigate.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">So it's certainly somewhat likely. Which means our next objective... is to find the answer that he was looking for.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's a bit of a spooky message... But if we can open this "door to the past", then we'll surely be one step closer to solving this mystery!</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Just a moment, please... I'm the curator here. And I won't be allowing you to investigate anything without my permission.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">S-so you mean we can't investigate...?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Not at all. I'm simply insisting that you allow me to accompany you. There should be no doors in this library that I don't know about. And even if there is something hidden somewhere, as suggested by this message, it is my duty as curator to know what that is.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I completely understand, Miss Mystere. We can only benefit from your presence. Now then, how about we all make our way back to the entrance? Let's think about where this door could be from there.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But, Professor, supposing there is a door, that message is such a puzzle in itself... don't you think it'll be difficult to find?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">You may be right. And this library is so large... Finding anything will surely take a good deal of our time.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">No, I think not. You're both missing something here. I believe I may well know what is meant by the words in the message.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Eh? Really, Professor?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes. If you'll just remember the wording...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If you'll both take a look around this room, you'll notice we are surrounded by books. There is probably nowhere else in the library with more books than there are right here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There are books extending all the way up. We're completely surrounded by them.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And the key to opening this door is in the "sun and moon watching over the sage".</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But what could that mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">There are no windows, so no light can come in from the sun or the moon.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Precisely! Which means it is not the real sun and moon that are being referred to here. And they are located where they can "watch over" the sage. In other words, behind. Perhaps you have already realised to whom "the sage" is referring...? Right then, let's find this "sun and moon watching over the sage" and open the door!</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Dewey? You haven't, by any chance... entered the special viewing room without my permission, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">Of course I haven't been in there! What are you saying, Miss Mystere? You always say that if anyone goes in there without permission, they'll have to solve 100 of your puzzles as punishment! If I had to solve that many puzzles, I'd go insane!</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">That's pitiful! If you ever even considered becoming a librarian, I'd expect that much of you.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It feels so sophisticated! I bet we'll find something here!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But the riddle mentions the sun and the moon. Where are they?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, maybe I was wrong then...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There are so many books stored here - I suppose that's why they call it the Great Archive.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Well, anyway. Luke, I'm sure there are clues to be found here!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Maybe the owl is supposed to be the guardian of this door.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I...I was thinking the same thing.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I wonder if this has got something to do with the sun in that message we just saw.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">But there's nothing remotely resembling the moon in sight.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah! What's that...?!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's a sun and moon construction... Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So the "sage" must be...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's right, the sage of this library refers to the curator. And this sun and moon construction is located right behind her seat... So that's what the "sun and moon watching over the sage" was referring to.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">And when the sun and moon swap places, their true form will be shown... and the door to the past will open. So all we need to do is work out what that means...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">But what does it mean by "their true form"?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...well, if we interpret it at face value, it would suggest that we are currently seeing their untrue form. ............Hmm? Have a look at this. There seems to be some sort of mechanism in place.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah! Professor! If you look closely, there seems to be a puzzle hidden here.</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah! Professor, there's a stairway!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Who would have thought there could be anything like this hidden here?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">"The ancient flame has been locked in an infinite vault of books"... I wonder just what we'll find down there...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">A-an entrance...to a basement below the Great Archive?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Am I right in thinking that you knew nothing of this stairway's existence?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">That's right... And if I, the curator, knew nothing of it, then surely no one else could. It's hard to believe that a secret such as this could have been hidden here all this time. Who could have possibly left such a message...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ Hmm...it might be wise not to let anyone see what has been revealed here...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">I agree. I'll be back as soon as I have asked the other visitors to leave the building.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well then! Are you both ready?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You betcha! Let's go, Professor! You too, Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Okay then, Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This place...appears to be some sort of historic site.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's amazing to think a place like this could exist under the library.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I wonder when it dates from...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Ah! That mural... ............It can't be............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A dragon breathes fire, setting the town ablaze...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There is a woman in the mural. The dragon's master, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Why is a nasty mural like that in this secret room beneath the Great Archive?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Something is written here...but the letters are too worn away by time to be legible.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">These letters have a funny shape. Maybe it's some ancient script?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I am intrigued. If we could only know what is written here...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I am not familiar with this script either... I'm sorry that I cannot help.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The ceiling around here caved in...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The walls have gone brittle, too. It may be dangerous to stay here too long.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I hope this cellar isn't going to collapse...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This wall painting is a bit scary, isn't it? A monster attacking a burning town...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There's also a woman hurling fire. I suppose she must be a witch...?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">That woman is the Great Witch.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Miss Mystere?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">This certainly doesn't bode well, a painting of the Great Witch here...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Do you know anything about the witch in this painting?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">You don't know of the Great Witch? But how can that be possible for a man of your learning?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, that's...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Never mind. I'm sure you must have your reasons. I don't wish to pry.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I appreciate that. Would you mind perhaps telling us a bit about this witch?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">The woman in this painting... is the Great Witch Bezella. And this painting depicts the infamous Legendary Fire that she caused.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The Legendary Fire...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">She is the witch in charge of all witches, whose very existence poses the greatest threat known to Labyrinthia. The Great Witch Bezella cannot be considered the same as other witches... She is the root of all Labyrinthia's woes.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ The Great Witch Bezella...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">The reason for all of Labyrinthia's suffering at the hands of witches, lies in the very existence of the Great Witch Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Would you mind elaborating...?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">The Great Witch Bezella is the source of all the other witches. As long as she exists, there will be no end to other witches. While the Great Witch Bezella is with us, the townspeople will forever live in fear under the shadow of witches.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So you mean that if there were no Great Witch, there would be peace?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">No Great Witch? That's easy enough to say... But while all of the knights have been searching for Bezella, nobody has ever been able to find her. There are very few clues, and no one has ever seen her in person. Nevertheless, the Great Witch Bezella is undoubtedly present in Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">How can you be so certain?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Because her deep claw marks can still be seen throughout the town.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">"Claw marks"...?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">You must all have seen them too. The traces of that fire, when you entered this library.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah, yes. There was a part of this building that had suffered noticeable damage.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Bezella is a fearful witch, who has all other witches doing her bidding. Long ago...this town was reduced to ashes as a result of her fiery magic.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Reduced...to ashes?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">That must have been...let me see...a hundred or so years ago. It was on the evening of the fire festival, held every year in honour of the Great Witch Bezella. The Great Witch's fury was unleashed without warning, as the entire town burned.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's terrible...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">That was the Legendary Fire... Every person in this town knows about it.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The Legendary Fire...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">The rebuilding of the town was a long and arduous process. And all the while, Bezella must have been watching and laughing from the shadows.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's awful...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Even now, the legend of long ago... continues to cause real suffering amongst the townsfolk. To think that a painting of that fearful witch could be right here in the basement of my beloved library! What is it doing here, of all places?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">There's nothing for it...I'll just have to have this room sealed shut. Please, let's keep the existence of this room strictly between ourselves. For the good of the people. As for me, I shall do my best to forget all about this hidden room... ...I'm afraid I'd rather not remain in here a minute longer. ...It's time I started closing up the library for the day.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I can't help but feel we've done something wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Luke...do you recall the words towards the end of that message?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Do you mean "until then I will wait"...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's right. When we opened this door... or rather, when we were guided towards opening this door, I could sense someone else's will at work. It's almost as if our following Carmine and coming to this library, had all been planned out in advance.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Surely you don't mean...that we were beckoned here by the Great Witch Bezella?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............Bezella............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Is something the matter? Are you feeling all right, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, I'm fine, really.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um, Espella...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Ah...I, uh...yes? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's just that...well, you've been so quiet...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, it's nothing... It's just that, this room... It's a little chilly, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The atmosphere is a bit sinister. Not to mention that scary picture... Maybe it's about time we made a move from here?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, indeed. ............ Those words at the end of the message... ............"I will wait"............ What if...we weren't meant to be the ones being called here...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Phew, it's much more relaxing here, isn't it? It felt so intense and claustrophobic down there.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, it certainly did... Today has been full of surprises. Not only did I meet up with you two again, but we also found that mural in the library. It seems that this town really does hold a mysterious secret, doesn't it? What shall we do now?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...I'd certainly like to learn more about this magic. We've been in here for quite some time. It must be getting late. It's probably best if we wind up our investigating for today and take a rest. You must both be feeling tired.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, I suppose you're right. I'd be happy to do a little more investigating with you two, but I have an errand to run before it gets too late.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm still up for investigating further! Whatever the puzzle, I'm ready to solve it!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Ha ha! Luke, I could hear your tummy rumbling from here just now!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, I can't pretend I'm not a little hungry...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">If you haven't arranged accommodation yet, why don't you both stay at the bakery? There is a room free, so I'm sure it'd be all right. And Mrs Eclaire would love to have you. What do you say...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, if you put it like that, we'd be delighted to stay. Thank you, Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">And there's all that delicious bread, too! Mmmm, I'm looking forward to it already!</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Professor Layton, do you have to be going?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes. Sorry for all the trouble we put you to.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Not at all. Although I still can't get used to there being a secret room under the library. It's been a while since I last met someone capable of solving my puzzles. And as I promised, you have my permission to borrow the Grand Grimoire. If you have any need for it in the future, please do drop by and let me know.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Thank you very much, Miss Mystere. It's been a pleasure.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Oh...there is just one more thing. I have all of Labyrinthia's puzzles stored here in this library. As you continue with your investigations here in Labyrinthia, there will likely be puzzles that you cannot solve or which you do not find. Such puzzles will come to me. Any time you wish to solve such puzzles, just visit me and I will show them to you.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Puzzles that we cannot solve or do not find, you say? Very well. Then I look forward to seeing you again.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">I'll be waiting. Please take care on your way home. It's already become dark out there. And...if I remember rightly, the Storyteller's latest story did mention the evening...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ You take care, too. Until we meet again, Miss Mystere.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow! It's already this dark out here... I didn't realise we were in there so long.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It looks as if it must have been raining up until a moment ago. The ground is still wet.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yes, and that reminds me of what Mrs Eclaire was saying before we left... She said: "you might want to hurry... it looks like it might rain at any time." Let's get a move on! You too, Espella...... Hey, where is she?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's strange...she's not here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I wonder where she could have gone...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps she's still in the Great Archive...</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">Slowly does it, step by step... Oh...are you two still here? Can you let me through? I have to lock up.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hello, Dewey. Have you seen Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">If you're looking for Espella, she left while you were still talking to Miss Mystere.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Eh? I wonder why...</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">She said something about having to buy some milk. Even though it was still raining...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah, yes. I do remember Mrs Eclaire asking her to get some milk for the bakery.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It was raining...you said?</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">Yes. It started raining about the time you all went down into that library basement. When Espella left just now, it did look as if the rain was about to stop. Ah, yes! She left a message for you. She said to go back without her.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But she didn't have to go alone! Especially in the dark...</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">I'm sure she'll be fine. If it's only milk she needs, then she can get it at the market. It's not far, so she should be back soon. If anything, I'd be more worried about you two being the ones in danger. You, know, in the Story, it said there were "two companions".</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">If your work here is finished, then I suggest you both go home. I don't want to get caught up in anything!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Luke...why don't we head back to the bakery and wait for Espella there?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I suppose so. I guess she'll be all right...right?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks even taller when you see it up close! I can't even see the top!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It requires a lot of architectural knowledge to construct a building of this size.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It makes me feel giddy just looking up at it!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This seems to be related to the mural we saw in the Great Archive cellar.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The librarian said the fire was caused by a fire dragon summoned by Bezella, the Great Witch.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Those symbols were in the Great Archive, too.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">These flags serve to constantly remind the townspeople that their creator is watching them.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's a bit unsettling, although I can't really say why.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Labyrinthia seems surrounded by cliffs and woods. In the distance there's nothing but fog.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The fog is so thick, I can't see far.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This place looks so mysterious, surrounded by the misty forest.</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">No-no-no, no-no-no. It's...pitch black! I can't go home when it's so dark!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I don't think it's so dark, with all these lights around.</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">Lights...yes, that's right. The lights... I'm having trouble with the lights in my house. It's sooooo dark in there!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Now you can return to a brightly lit house!</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">...If it's as bright as this, then I've nothing to worry about. So bright that I can even tell it's my house from afar... Shining so very brightly... No...no-no-no, no-no-no! It can't be sooooo bright... If my house is THAT bright, it's bound to get noticed by the witch! ...And then I'll be doomed!</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">The witch will appear... I'm doomed!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's bright here even after dusk.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps the light helps dispel Labyrinthians' fear of the witches.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Is it just my imagination, or are there fewer people around? Have they all gone home because of that story?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The opposite side is not very well lit, so it's hard to see anything from here.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The Great Archive, towering above us against the dark skies, looks truly imposing.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">At night, it looks more like a place to test your courage at rather than read books.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Unlike in the other parts of the town, buildings here are tall and magnificent.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks quite posh.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Many of the houses have shops on the ground floor and living quarters above.</line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">Francesca, Anna, Lillian... My dear friends. I am ever so sad... Soon, the four of us will be forced to part ways.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...? This is the pawnbroker's shop, isn't it? What seems to be the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">Oh, my. Is that concern in your voice, oh gentle sir? If you have but a moment, allow me to explain my ever so woesome woe... The family coffers are not brimming with coin as they once were, I'm afraid...so I've come to sell my ever so dearest friends.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Sell...your friends?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, and lifelong friends at that!</line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">Oh, indeed, gentle sir. However, my friends are ever so picky about where they stay. ...Pray, would you be able to put them into their proper rooms?</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">25</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Now I get it! The friends you were referring to are your dolls.</line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">Oh, thank you, gentle sirs! With my friends all in their place, I'm sure to get ever such a fair price... And I'm sure they will be ever so happy in their new homes.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wait, did we do that for your friends, or for the price...?</line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">Tell me, Mr Pawnbroker, will you take ever such good care of my friends now?</line>
<line speaker="Price">Madam, I realise you have brought your friends a long way to visit me, but I'm afraid a dolls' house like this... is a little out of my line.</line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">........................</line>
<line speaker="Price">Okay, okay, you win! I'll take them off your hands!</line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">Hee hee! Wonderful! Thank you ever so much, Mr Pawnbroker.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">She might be laughing, but I could certainly sense the tension in that transaction.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A haughty laugh of authority, perhaps...</line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">Because of your help, I can now afford to buy brand new friends to keep me company. Keeping up with the fashion scene for dolls is ever so difficult when one is so far away from the rich comforts of the castle.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Few lights are on at night around here, giving this place a very different atmosphere.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">These are some fancy street lights. What's that burning inside?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">London street lights used to be powered by gas, but that is not the case here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You can hear hammer strikes even at night.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">He may have received an urgent order. You can tell from the sound that he's very keen on the work.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The town feels somewhat desolate at night, so seeing shops like this brightens up the mood a little.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The fountain looks marvellous illuminated by the lights.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">They don't seem to use electricity for light. There must be torches on the inside of the trough at the base.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The statue has a different air about it at night.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The cat that was here earlier has gone off somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It might have gone for a patrol around its territory.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Cats sleep so much during the day that they're full of energy at night.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It doesn't seem to be open for business at night, either.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The lights are on upstairs, but maybe the shopkeeper's unwell?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We should put our time to better use than waiting for this shop to open. Let us go back.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Uh-oh... Not good! What shall I do?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What's the matter? Is something troubling you, madam?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Oh, yes! Something certainly is! Troubling me, I mean. Today's story is just so frightening!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You mean the story with the witch? So you're afraid too?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Well, duh! Of course I'm afraid! But...I'm the courier. And that means one thing! My post will ALWAYS be delivered! No exceptions. No matter what.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Courier...I guess that's like a postwoman, right?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">I wouldn't know about that. I just deliver these letters. To the townspeople. But now, everyone's afraid. So no one's going out. And so...there are way more than usual! Letters, I mean. Letters that need delivering!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We'd be delighted to offer our help. Is there some way that we could lend you a hand...?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Thank you for the offer! But there's nothing you can do. Delivering letters is my responsibility, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow, that's impressive. Even at a time like this, you're putting your work first.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Well, I suppose. But you know what? I can't help but think... If only there were something I could ride... That would make it so much easier! The delivery, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">20</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">If only I had a cart like that... I could deliver all the letters! I'd just drop them down from the sky.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Put one foot wrong and you'd fall out! You'd at least need a seatbelt...</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">A "seed-bolt"? What's that? Anyway, I'd better go. Can't keep talking. Got letters to deliver! And remember, let me know if you have anything to deliver! Letters, I mean. Bye!</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">If only I had a cart like that... I'd be able to deliver so many more! Letters, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The shop's closed. The owner must have gone home already.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The shop staff may have just gone to purchase fresh produce.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It doesn't look as inviting after dark.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's a bit dark here, so mind your step.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's dark inside. I don't think anyone's there, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There is something unsettling about the sight of the tall bell tower, piercing the dark skies.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Flickering lights reveal guards standing at the entrance.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Is this an important building?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The windows are closed, but the first floor lights are on.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Very few people are out and about at this hour. Streets empty out as night sets in.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Witches found their way even into the professor's office! Doors and shutters won't keep them out.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's a water fountain. The water looks very clear. It may be suitable for drinking.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There must be a spring somewhere nearby.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A pile of discarded wooden crates.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They're just crates. Nothing to see.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, I smell freshly baked bread! I wonder if that could be Mrs Eclaire's work. Let's go inside!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...yes, we could. Although we could also take a walk around the town at night... If there's nothing else you'd particularly like to see, perhaps we should head back in.</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Evening, gents! Isn't Espella with you?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Do you know Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Do I know her? There isn't a person in this town who doesn't know Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I didn't realise she was so famous...</line>
<line speaker="Petter">I've known some ignorant people, but you two really do take the biscuit. If you knew her better, then I doubt you'd be spending so much time with her.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What's that supposed to mean? Espella is a lovely person... I don't know how you can say that.</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Personally, I don't enjoy talking about her in that way either...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Personally, I don't enjoy talking about her in that way either... It's just that I wanted to warn you to take care when associating with her.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There's a butcher next to the fishmonger. It's still open.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Extended opening hours? That's convenient. Do you think they take pounds and pennies?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I think we've all got a bit hungry. We seem to be noticing only food.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ooooh! Phosphorescent anglerfish!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And that would be octopus over there. It looks belligerent and ready to spray the potential buyer with ink.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They've sold out of most of their products today.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This is the entrance to the bakery. Shall we go in?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Let's stay the night here and resume our investigation tomorrow morning.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Calming moonlight is pouring into the room through the roof window.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It must be very nice to lie down in bed with a view of the starry skies above!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Thick volumes are lined up on the shelf.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Labyrinthian books...interesting. I would like to read some when we have time.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They're all very thick. It would take you some time to read them, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Jars with...jam, perhaps? They all have vibrant colours.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They look scrumptious.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I am sure this jam would be even more delicious on Mrs Eclaire's freshly baked bread.</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Aha, welcome back! I've prepared the evening meal already.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow, it looks great!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hang on...where's Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm afraid we were separated when she went to get that milk. Has she not come back yet?</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Oh, dear. Maybe I was asking too much of her...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">My apologies. I should have stopped her, had I had the chance.</line>
<line speaker="Patty">It's nothing you need to worry about, Mr Layton! That girl knows her way around. I'm sure she'll be back soon. Let's go ahead and eat while waiting for her.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I love it when we all get to eat together. Meals are much more enjoyable that way!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I've never had bread and jam that tasted this good before!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I hope Espella gets back soon...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, yeah! You guys went out to the Great Archive with her, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you find what you were looking for?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well...it's a bit of a mystery, really.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">In truth, we went there to investigate the mystery that is Labyrinthia. However, what we found instead was quite the puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right... A "puzzle", huh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, I get the impression puzzles are pretty popular in this town. Do you not know what a puzzle is, Nick?! Not that I know exactly...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, we spend all our time baking... It's not really the kind of thing we're supposed to know about, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, it appears the two of you are a little unsure about the concept of puzzles.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Say, Mr Layton... Do you think you could give us a little "Puzzles 101" crash course? I'm kinda curious.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would be my pleasure, Miss Fey. But rather than explaining it in words, I believe actually trying your hand at a puzzle would be far more rewarding. Here, I'll give you both a simple example to think about. Now then, here we have two long loaves of bread placed side by side. You'll notice that they form the number 11. Do you see what I mean?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, yeah... I get it! So that's what a puzzle is!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Not quite, Miss Fey. The puzzle is what follows next. What I'd like you to try is... I'd like you to see if you can change this into a number lower than 11.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A lower number...? So how about if I take one of the loaves?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">However, the one condition is that you must add another loaf of exactly the same type.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You need to add... another loaf?! Even though we add a loaf, the number has to be lower... I think I'm beginning to see what you mean by "puzzle"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Wait, I think I've got it! I may just be a baker, but I bet I have the right answer! If I place the extra loaf sideways like this, then one minus one equals zero!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh gimme a break, Nick! That's totally the letter H. We're trying to solve a puzzle here, not win a spelling bee!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, c'mon...I can't be the ONLY one that sees one minus one, right? ...Right?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Turning it into a matter of arithmetic is certainly an interesting approach.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You, uhhh...think so?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Most certainly. That's precisely the kind of flexible thinking needed for solving puzzles. Now, let's think again.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Take a seat and leave this to a pro, Nick. How about...this?! You just take this new loaf and...TA-DA! Now THAT's one minus one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! Eating is cheating!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? Because it feels more like winning to me.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You're full of surprises, Miss Fey. I didn't expect that kind of innovation.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I solved the puzzle AND enjoyed the bread! Win-win, baby!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... didn't Mr Layton tell us at the start that we need to add another loaf of the exact same type?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Seriously?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's right, unfortunately. I'm afraid I can't accept this as a solution to the puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, all right, but... Is there really another better solution?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, what do you think? Can either of you think of a different solution?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm drawing a blank... I guess this kind of thing just isn't for me.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You both came up with such creative answers, I'm sure you'll be solving puzzles in no time. But now, it's time for the solution. The important thing in this puzzle's solution, is the angle of the loaf that is added. If the new loaf is placed upright, like so...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I get it! It's the number 1.1, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, that's right! That's a lot lower than eleven...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Exactly. When solving puzzles, there is never just one correct method. It's essential to think flexibly and try many means to solve it. Sometimes critical thinking is the key to success.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Right. I see what you mean. These puzzles are really something else.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well...if I see another puzzle like this, I'd still rather eat my way to the solution...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... You know, I don't think I'm cut out for brain-busting bread puzzles like this. I'll stick with good ol' regular bread, thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's because we're ace bakers! I guess we're better suited to using our hands than our heads...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Is that so? In truth, I can't help but feel you're both a little out of place as bakers, if you'll pardon my saying so. Naturally, I won't force puzzles upon you, but if either of you should be interested, I would heartily recommend giving puzzle solving a try.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, right now there's something else we all need to try... Mrs Eclaire's freshly baked bread is getting cold! And I'm sure it tastes better hot!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Oh dear, so it is. You know how I can get when it comes to puzzles...</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Well, young man, I must say it's a pleasure to have someone show such appreciation for my baking.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">When it comes to your bread, Mrs Eclaire, there's no limit to how much I could eat!</line>
<line speaker="Patty">............!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">L-Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You...shouldn't have said that!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............?</line>
<line speaker="Patty">My my, aren't you a darling! Well then, in that case, I suppose I'll just have to bring out my special reserve... Hold on a moment, I'll just go and fetch it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-right, er...I think it's time I started preparing tomorrow's bread...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, y-yes, me too! I'm sure it must be that time already...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, wh-what was that all about?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm not entirely sure...but I do seem struck by a sudden sense of impending doom...</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Sorry............ to have............ kept you............ waiting! There you go! Have at it! But be warned... I won't take kindly to any leftovers...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Whoa... Th-this loaf! Wait...where did those two go?! Miss Maya! Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Luke, it would appear that we have been left to tackle this particular task alone...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Phew...I'm stuffed!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...I believe this must be the most bread I have ever eaten in my life.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wait a sec... I've just realised...we've finished eating, but Espella still isn't back yet.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ She went to the market, didn't she? Perhaps we ought to go and...</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Oh, my. Customers at this late hour...? I'm sorry, but we're closed!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">That's him! That man over there!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">So he's the one, is he...?</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Just a minute! What do you think you're doing barging in here like this?!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Stand aside, madam! This is a matter of urgency!</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Wh-what are you going to do?!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">You there, porcupine head! You're coming with us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? P-porcupine head...? You don't mean...me, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Who else in this room fits that description?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Certainly, you would appear to be alone on that particular front...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh...I wish I had a top hat too right about now.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Enough of your idle chit-chat! Time to get going!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Well, it should be quite obvious. You're coming to the court, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The...court?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Whaaaaaa?! Mr Wright, what did you do?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, Nick! What did you do?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I didn't do anything! The only thing you could accuse me of is making bread that's TOO good to eat!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Ahem! This man is not the one who's on trial.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">In that case, why is Mr Wright being made to go to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Captain">That's simple! Because the girl has requested him, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Girl...? What girl?!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Naturally, the girl facing trial for this evening's crime... That heinous witch... Miss Espella Cantabella, no less!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">You're telling me you can't solve this?! Then you are definitely worthy of suspicion!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, I don't like the way he's looking at us...</line>
<line speaker="Captain">As things stand, I'm afraid I can't allow you to walk freely around the town. I will even consider having you both thrown into the dungeon if necessary.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">No way! That's way too harsh!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Let's try the puzzle one more time, Luke, before he becomes aggressive.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Any true citizens of our community should be able to solve this puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Petal">What's this, you can't solve the puzzle? Then you don't belong here with us!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Not that I mind about being accepted, but... it's so frustrating! To think that I can't even solve a puzzle given to me by a toddler...</line>
<line speaker="Petal">It's a musical box puzzle. If can you [sic] solve it, you're in!</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">It's an initiation test!</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">Oh, what to do? Oh, woe is me! I stand here with my failure, Like some dry withered tree...♪ I cannot proceed, when the map I so need♪</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Weren't you able to fix the map yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">Oh, the map is in pieces! What can we do? A map such as this one, Will not help these two...♪</line>
<line speaker="Petter">What's that? You don't like having someone pull your strings? Just joking! You really should be heading towards North Parade Avenue, you know. I'll be hanging around there a little too.</line>
<line speaker="Petter">While we're waiting, how about this puzzle?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">So you weren't able to solve this? If that's the case, I'll just have to equip more weapons to confront my foes!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">We knights have to be prepared for such eventualities.</line>
<line speaker="Price">So...you've given up on the puzzle? Then payment, please...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Price">Well...either pay up now, or come back and try your hand at this puzzle again. Today is a special day, and I'm feeling generous.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ph-phew... I thought for a moment we were going to get a big bill.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It seems Mr Price is a puzzle enthusiast too. Let's come back and try again later.</line>
<line speaker="Price">So tell me, young man, who do you think is the culprit? Get it right and I won't charge a penny!</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Boo-hoo...boo-hoo!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh dear! That didn't go too well...</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Boo-hoo...there's no way... I'm going to be a knight... boooh-hoo-hoo...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's going to be okay! Really, you just need a little courage, like in this puzzle...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm, what should I do...? Maybe I can pin this whole thing on Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">These loaves of bread are in total disarray... If I don't do something before the boss gets back...I'm toast!</line>
<line speaker="Patty">It's as difficult as I thought, then...</line>
<line speaker="Patty">It's my friend, a dressmaker, she came to me for help. Maybe you could solve this for me.</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">Would jumping this high be enough...?</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">There is a way I can get cwose to that man... I can fwoat down beside him fwom one of the fwuffy cwouds in the skyyyyy!</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">What's this? Can this really be the man who cleared Miss Mystere's trial? Everyone has their off-days, I suppose... Why not try again later?</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">Why not try your hand at this book-related puzzle?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Are you giving up, Mr Layton?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I don't think we can go on until we've solved this puzzle, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Please, no need to worry yourselves. We can take a short break and come back to solve this puzzle later.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The message on the page inserted into the Grand Grimoire mentions the following:</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">What am I to do?!</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">I can't go home when it's so dark... Show me how I should turn the lights on!</line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">Without your aid, I'm afraid my friends will have no place to stay. It would be ever so tragic... Oh, dear... My poor friends.</line>
<line speaker="Cinderellia">Oh please, gentle sirs. I beg of you... Won't you please help my friends? There is naught I can do without your aid.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">You're, um... Not afraid, are you? Of heights, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">M-Me? No way!</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Like, some sort of cart. On wheels. That I could ride though [sic] the sky on a little track... Wouldn't that make it a piece of cake?</line>
</xml>