<xml>
<title>On a Dark and Stormy Night</title>
<line speaker="Man">If anything happens to me, go and see this man. He should be able to help. Agh! Blasted witches! No! That's impossible! Go! Go without me! Quickly, get going!</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Hmm... Heh?! Well, what do we have here?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">What the blazes...?! How on earth did a vehicle end up on top of that tree? Blimey... This is going to be a tough nut to crack. Hmm...there is one man I know who could get to the bottom of this...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Did you say "witches", Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's right. People in the Middle Ages very much believed in their existence. That is the reason why they had "witch trials". Do you see?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Witch trials...? Did witches...really exist in those days?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, my boy, witch trials certainly existed, although nobody ever truly used magic. Witches were nothing more than superstition and legend.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Look! It's really London! C'mon, Nick! Take a look!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know you're excited, Maya...but can't a guy get a few last Z's in?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is no time to be sleeping! You won't win in an English court of law with that attitude!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This trip is just an exchange visit courtesy of the Legal League of Attorneys. I won't be defending in court officially.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww... Well that's no fun... You know you're always at your best when working under pressure. But who can say how things would go over here...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wish you wouldn't talk like that... You'll only jinx the whole thing.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The rain doesn't seem to want to stop... It's a bit unusual for this time of year, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mmm, I agree, Luke. But I believe it is easing off a little now, so it should clear up soon.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I hope it does clear up soon... especially the lightning.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ha ha ha. Afraid of lightning, I take it?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Of course not! I'm not a little kid, you know! It's just that I hate how it flashes suddenly and takes me by surprise.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Then let's wait a while for it to settle. Luke, I have just the thing to take your mind off it. Take a look on the bookshelf.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The bookshelf? What's on the bookshelf?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You'll know when you find it. Do you recall our usual method of investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Of course I do!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ho ho, I expected as much. But just to be sure, let's have a refresher. We use a magnifying glass for investigation. This will appear automatically. Slide the stylus along the Touch Screen to move the magnifying glass around. The secret is to slide the stylus as if drawing a line. While moving the magnifying glass, it will sometimes appear orange. When this happens, give the Touch Screen a light tap. Doing so will investigate the point in question. In addition to important information, there are also puzzles and hint coins waiting to be found. Hint coins will become invaluable later on, when tackling difficult puzzles. Okay, let's give it a try.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Touch and slide on the Touch Screen, then give it a light tap to investigate. This technique can be used to investigate points of interest, right? Now, let's investigate the bookshelf.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It doesn't look as if the rain will cease any time soon.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You can even hear thunder in the distance. The weather's unusually bad today.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It may be best to wait until the sky clears up a bit before leaving my office.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I wouldn't call it comfortable, but it will suffice for a quick nap.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Napping on the couch is bad for you, Professor. Your neck will hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">When I think about the paper I need to finish writing when I go home, staying here seems very appealing.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Your tea is extraordinarily fragrant, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You have a discerning nose, Luke. I got this special Darjeeling blend from the university chancellor.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A gentleman's love for tea is pure, strong and everlasting, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This spiky fossil looks somewhat cool.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's a rare, valuable fossil, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, please take me with you next time you go exploring ancient ruins!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Isn't this a picture book? Wow... I wouldn't have expected you to have a picture book, Professor! Wait a second...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's right, my boy... There's a puzzle hidden within that book.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I should have known! You even have puzzles hidden in your books.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">All right then, Luke, why not see if you can solve this one?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Naturally. After all, I am your apprentice!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">20</line>
<line speaker="Notes">No penalties for incorrect submissions</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well done, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That was a piece of cake! I can solve harder puzzles than that!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm pleased to hear that, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It was a charming little puzzle, though. Like straight out of a fairy tale. If only the witches of the Middle Ages were as jolly as the ones in this picture book...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, indeed. Well, it looks as if the rain is about to stop. Shall we prepare to go home?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Okay, Professor. Now...where did I put my umbrella? ...! Professor, I think we have a visitor.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">At this late hour? I can't say I've been expecting anybody.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'll go and see who it is.</line>
<line speaker="???">Are you...Mr Hershel Layton?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, indeed I am. My dear young lady, how may I be of assistance?</line>
<line speaker="???">I have been asked...to give you a letter. Please, could you read this?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This letter...it's from Carmine.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Carmine? Who's Carmine?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">He was a student of mine a number of years ago... And if I recall correctly, he's now a detective.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow, a detective?</line>
<line speaker="???">Um... About Carmine...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="???">I, um... Well... ...I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It appears there may be a matter of some considerable importance within this letter.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Let's read it right away, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, I never...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">P-Professor...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Am I right in assuming that you are the Espella to whom Carmine is referring?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Y-yes. Yes, I am.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Tell me, what on earth happened?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm afraid...I'm not entirely sure. It seemed as if we were being chased relentlessly... They caught up with us, and we were attacked. As a result, Carmine was injured.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I see. I'm sorry to hear that...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">He bravely did his best to ensure that I escaped safely. I beg you, please help him! Please help that brave man!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You mustn't worry about him, Espella. Knowing Carmine as I do, I'm sure he'll be all right.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">But...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ever since I've known him, he's always been in some difficult situation or other, and he's never failed to win through. More importantly... At the moment, I'm frankly more concerned with your safety, Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">You're concerned...about me?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">According to this letter, the one they're after is you. Are you certain that you're all right? You weren't injured at all?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Me? No, I...I'm fine, really. ............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I think you'd better take a rest, even if just for a little while.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Your clothes are all wet, too. I'll go and find you a dry towel.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Thank you. You're really too kind.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's no trouble at all. As soon as you're more comfortable, we can sit down and talk.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor... If what was written in that letter is true...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, indeed...it means this young lady is in real danger. And it also means that her pursuers might even come to this office in search of her.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'll go and lock the door.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, that sounds like a good idea. At any rate, we'll need to talk to Espella and find out what this is really all about.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">As far as I can tell, no one has followed Espella here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The weather's awful today. I hope it'll discourage her pursuers.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Let us take a breather on the couch.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You do seem really tired, Miss Espella. Let's rest here for a while.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Should I offer some tea? Oh, I need to boil some water first.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The scent of tea has a relaxing effect on people, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's really cool. I wonder if Espella would like it.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I doubt she's interested in fossils.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm...sorry to have put you both to all this trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Please, think nothing of it. Although, if it's all right with you, I'd like to hear a little more about what happened. We won't be able to protect you without a clearer understanding of the circumstances.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Protect...me?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is my belief that you are in quite considerable danger. And it is the duty of every gentleman to help a lady in trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I...I sincerely thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Now, it would certainly appear that you are being pursued... However, Carmine's letter referred to your pursuers as "they"... Could you tell me who "they" might be?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ "They"...are witches.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wi...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Did you say..."witches"?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes...witches. And they are truly terrifying. Carmine did his best to protect me from them... But in the end, he was unable to escape. They caught up with us... If they realise I'm here, then you two may also end up in danger!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Perhaps it would have been better if I hadn't come here...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You mustn't worry yourself. Everything is going to be all right.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Really?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You have my word. We'll be on our guard.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's right! Nothing to worry about. The place is tightly locked up!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ Thank you both.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Espella, I'd like to enquire a little more, if I may.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes...yes, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The town you came from is called Labyrinthia, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes...that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Espella? What's the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Um... Well, we are in Labyrinthia now, aren't we?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? No, we're in London, in England!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">"Lon-don"? "Eng-land"? I'm sorry, but...I don't understand.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What?! No way! You mean to say you've never heard of England?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Um...well, it's just that I've never come across a place by that name in Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............ Um... Espella... Are you sure you're feeling all right?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...No, Luke. I believe Espella really doesn't know. Espella, about this town of Labyrinthia... I'm afraid we've never heard of it, either. If I may ask... Where exactly is Labyrinthia?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ It's, um...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's...what?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Anything you could want to know about Labyrinthia can be found in this book!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Anything...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's an amazing design. I've never seen a book quite like it.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Espella, would you mind if we had a closer look?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh?! I must be seeing things... It was as if the words were moving on the page!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">No, Luke. It looked the same to me, too.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Look! There's a picture of the town in here. So this is Labyrinthia, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes. That's Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">How intriguing...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The buildings all look really old, don't they, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, Luke. I don't recall ever having seen this town before.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">This is my home town.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Then this must also be where the witches pursuing you are from, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Espella, what exactly is this book? It seems somewhat valuable.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ This book is the Historia Labyrinthia. As I said just a moment ago, everything about Labyrinthia is written in this book. Everything...the entire Story.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Labyrinthia's story?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If it contains absolutely everything...then it must also include something about witches.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, it does. All about the witches, the events in the town and the people living there. Everything that has happened in the town is written in this book. And not only that... but also, everything that is going to happen.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Eh?! What did you just say?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, this certainly is very strange. First that letter from Carmine, and now this book... If you ask me, Espella doesn't seem to be lying... But...witches chasing after people? It's all a little hard to believe.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's certainly hard to believe, but I do find it fascinating.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh...poor thing... Do you want to come in from the rain?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Don't open it!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, what was that?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That, Luke... was a witch.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">P-Professor! Espella's been...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, that was careless of us... But to think they might enter by such means... And after I'd promised to protect her...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Do you think that was one of those witches that Espella was talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I can't say for sure, but it certainly looked that way.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Then what we just saw... was that magic?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I don't know. But something bizarre did indeed take place before our very eyes. ...Luke. I'm going to go and search for Espella. While I'm gone, I'd like you to...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, I'm going too! Even if you disagree, I'm coming along! After all, I am your apprentice!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Okay, Luke. Then let's go.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right! I've already put the important things into the Trunk.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Thank you, Luke. We'll make sure to keep a record of all the important mysteries we encounter, as well as all the progress we make in our investigations. These will be kept in the Trunk. Open the Trunk at any time by touching Menu in the bottom left corner. To look back on the progress made so far, you may wish to have a look in Story, or alternatively, in Mysteries.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Now, I believe we're all set to go. They seemed to be headed towards the Thames. Let's follow them and rescue Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">*huff*...*puff*... We've lost them, Professor. They've got away...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... Yes, it would appear so. However, we can be quite certain that they came this way. There may be someone who saw the witch carrying Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right. Let's start asking people. Hey, look over there. Isn't that...?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">This one's really got me stumped.</line>
<line speaker="Barton">I agree, sir, a total mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Constable Barton, I don't want agreement. I want answers!</line>
<line speaker="Barton">Yes, sir. Understood, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Inspector Chelmey and Constable Barton? I wonder what they're doing here...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">They appear to be having a heated discussion about something. Perhaps it may even have something to do with the witch we're pursuing. Let's see what they have to say, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Good thinking, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What a lovely square. The police officers look out of place here, though.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This is a popular spot with an unobstructed view of the River Thames and Tower Bridge.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There's no trace of that evil thing or Miss Espella around the square.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The River Thames and Tower Bridge. Nothing seems amiss.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">In different circumstances I'd say it's a magnificent sight...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Tower Bridge was designed to match the Tower of London.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's a big passenger ship. Maybe the kidnapper took Miss Espella there?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I imagine it would be difficult for them to hide on a passenger ship.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Shame, I wanted to go for an elegant cruise down the Thames with you, Professor...</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Hey, you there! This area is off limits. Only Scotland Yard personnel allowed here. Hang on... Oh, it's you, Layton. What are you two doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's been a while, Inspector Chelmey. Has there been some kind of incident?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Hrrm, well, more of an "accident" than an "incident". Over there, a motor vehicle has been heavily damaged.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A heavily damaged vehicle, you say? That sounds rather serious... But I doubt that a Scotland Yard inspector would be involved in something as mundane as a simple traffic accident. Is there perhaps something unusual about this particular accident?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">As always, you're quick to pick up on the finer points.</line>
<line speaker="Barton">I should say there's something unusual. In fact, I've never seen nor heard of an accident as unusual as this one.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Barton! Would you leave the talking to me?!</line>
<line speaker="Barton">Yes, sir. Of course, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">An unusual accident...? Unusual in what way, precisely?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Hrrm, don't go concerning yourself with it. It's the job of the police to solve this case.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You never know, Inspector, I may just be able to help you solve it.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">What are you saying? Even I don't have all the facts yet. Clues just aren't that easy to come by, you know...</line>
<line speaker="Barton">Yes, we've got nothing so far. In fact, I'm sure we could use a helping hand...</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Oi! Barton! I thought I told you, I'll do all the talking!</line>
<line speaker="Barton">Yes, sir! Understood, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Just a moment... Hrrm... I've got it. Hey, Layton.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What is it, Inspector?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">I...uh...well, that is to say... If you're so keen on getting involved, why not go and take a look for yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That was a sudden change of heart.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It was, Luke. But a welcome one, wouldn't you say? Very well, Inspector. I will take a look. The vehicle is just up ahead there, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Yes, it is. It's in the park just over there, if you know where I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Barton">The park is fairly big, so it's quite easy to lose your way.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Hrrm, I suppose I'll have to explain. But listen up - I'm only saying this once. When you want to go somewhere else, touch the Move icon in the bottom right corner. Touch this to change from Investigation Mode to Movement Mode. The places you can move to are the places indicated by red markers. Touch Search after moving to go back into Investigation Mode. Incidentally, you're free to move to any location indicated by a red marker. This is a convenient way of moving, since you can move a great distance with only a single touch.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Look at the map and touch our desired location. That's right, isn't it, Inspector?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">That's right. So now that you know what to do, why don't you go and take a look? Oh, but don't forget, if you find anything, be sure to come and let me know!</line>
<line speaker="Barton">We'll be waiting to hear from you!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, I think the unusual accident they were talking about...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed... It could well have something to do with our own investigation... Let's go and take a look at the scene of the accident, Luke. We may find some clues.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">When I hear back from them, I may just be able to make something of this case... With the backlog of cases I've got piled up, I have to take help where I can get it.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Hey-ho, recently there seems to be no end of unusual cases...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Did something else happen recently?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">What's this, boy? Haven't you been reading the papers? There's been an incident that all of London's talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm not "boy", I'm Luke! And I'll read the newspaper later.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Hrrm. Well, it has nothing to do with this accident, I suppose. At any rate, the whole of Scotland Yard is busy with it at the moment. Normally, I wouldn't be getting involved in something like this.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It seems the inspectors are somewhat busy with other cases.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I guess we'll have to search for Espella alone.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">All these unusual bleedin' cases, one after another. It's really trying my patience.</line>
<line speaker="Barton">This is serious...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yes, it seems serious, Constable Barton. I feel sorry for the victims.</line>
<line speaker="Barton">Bits and pieces all over the place...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wh-what?!</line>
<line speaker="Barton">The hamburger I'd brought for my lunch, it's all in pieces! A complete mess... This is serious...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh, I get it! You were talking about your hamburger.</line>
<line speaker="Barton">I've been trying to draw it up in my notepad, but I can't seem to get it right. Because of this, I just can't seem to concentrate on the case.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That is serious.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Leave it to me! I'll soon have it sorted out for you!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Barton">The hamburger's back in one piece!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Now you can give your all to the investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Barton">Yes, at last I can concentrate. Not on the hamburger, but on the case. Munch, munch.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Take care not to upset the inspector!</line>
<line speaker="Barton">Munch, munch, munch, munch...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Constable Barton.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor! Look over there! There's a car up in that tree!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............! This certainly is out of the ordinary. I've never seen anything quite like it.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Like Constable Barton said, it seems extremely unusual. I mean, how on earth could something like this happen?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...we'll need to investigate this closely. Let's take a closer look at the car.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The heavy rain has made the ground very slippery.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The tyre marks end halfway towards the tree. How did the car end up on it?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Regretfully, there are no footprints or other marks that would've helped us work this out.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Onlookers have started gathering at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A car lodged in a tree is a curious sight. You cannot blame them.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yeah, that doesn't happen every day.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The more I see it, the stranger this looks. It's as if the car just flew up there. It's certainly taken some damage. You don't think... Could the witches have done this?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's certainly possible. It would appear the accident occurred only moments ago. Hmm... Wait! What's that mark on the car...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ahem, excuse me, gentlemen! Yes, you two! Would you just stop right there!</line>
<line speaker="Constable">I'm afraid I'll have to ask you to leave. This is the scene of an accident, and we haven't finished investigating it yet. As you can no doubt see, it's all rather mysterious. We don't yet know the exact cause of this here mishap. Not a safe place for spectators, I'm afraid. I'll have to ask you both to move along.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We're not spectators! We've been given permission from Inspector Chelmey!</line>
<line speaker="Constable">From the inspector, you say? So you're here officially then, are you? In what capacity, may I ask?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, not officially, as such. The name's Hershel Layton. I'm an archaeologist.</line>
<line speaker="Constable">You're pulling my leg! You mean to tell me that you're the famous Professor Layton? Now that you mention it, you certainly do resemble the good professor.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Of course he does! He IS the professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">So, Constable. If you don't mind, may we investigate a little closer?</line>
<line speaker="Constable">I've been put in charge here, so I can't afford to be wrong about this. For all I know, you might just be impersonating Professor Layton.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What? Oh, come on!</line>
<line speaker="Constable">If you're the real Professor Layton, then I'm sure you'll have no trouble solving this little puzzle that I just happen to have here.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Sounds interesting. Let me see what you have.</line>
<line speaker="Constable">All right. Take a look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">25</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Constable">That's it! You solved it! Judging by the way you solved that puzzle, there's no doubt that you must be the one and only Professor Layton! Of course, from the very start I had a fairly good idea that it was you, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">From the very start you seemed to have your doubts, Constable!</line>
<line speaker="Constable">Well, anyway, feel free to investigate as you wish. But, uh...there is one last thing.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Constable">Later, when you've got a free moment, would you mind signing my helmet?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Are you sure that's allowed?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ Come on, Luke. Let's take a look around, before the constable changes his mind. Tell me, Luke, did you notice anything strange when we looked at the car?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Anything strange? Well...to be honest, the entire accident is pretty unusual.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, yes. But if we're to suppose this accident occurred naturally, then there is one particular mark that should not be there.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A mark that shouldn't be there? Ah! Professor! The handprint! There's a handprint on the bonnet!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well spotted, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But a handprint of that size is too big to be left by any normal person!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. It would almost appear to have been left by the hand of a giant.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's a bit far-fetched...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ Luke. Let's look around a little more. Isn't there anything in this park that grabs your attention?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But Professor, from here I can't see anything strange other than that car.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">In situations like this, we need to "zoom in", Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Zoom in?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">In cases where something is too far away or is hidden behind another object, we can zoom in to see it more clearly. When you see something of interest, use the magnifying glass to look closer. When the magnifying glass turns blue, it means something important is there. By zooming in, we may just be able to uncover some new clues.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Okay, Professor! I'll zoom in right now. When the magnifying glass turns blue, just touch that area, right?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's right, Luke. Now then, let's give it a try.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Let's investigate the park a little more. Zooming in may lead to new clues. When you see something unusual, use the magnifying glass to look closer. When the magnifying glass turns blue, it means something important is there. In cases where something is too far away or is hidden behind another object, we can zoom in to see it more clearly.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">When the magnifying glass turns blue, it means something important is there, right?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's right, Luke. Now then, let's give it a try.</line>
<line speaker="Constable">Hello, Professor! Have you found any clues?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey...the statue's hand! It's about the same size as the handprint on the car. Do you think the car hit that hand when it crashed?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That is a possibility, of course. However... the handprint on the car is a right handprint, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">R-right hand? But the statue is holding a spear in its right hand. Which means, that couldn't be where the handprint came from.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Quite right, my boy... And it would certainly appear that this is more than a simple traffic accident.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I wonder what could have happened. If the handprint was made by the statue... surely the statue couldn't have...moved?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ I'm positive there's some kind of secret behind this. And whatever it may be... we can be certain it's related to the witch that took Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I think so too, Professor. How else could this kind of accident have occurred? If we investigate more closely, perhaps we'll find some clues!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">No, Luke. First, we should head back to see the inspector.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Really? But all he seems to say is how unusual it seems...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, yes. However, there is one more subject about which I'd like to ask him.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Not "what", my boy. But rather, "who". Who was in the car when it crashed?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This statue's holding a spear in its right hand.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But the handprint left on the car was made by an open right hand...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There's a handprint on the car. It's almost as if the statue somehow grabbed hold of the bonnet...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Let's go back and see the inspector. There could be other clues.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">So what do you think? It's no simple accident, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Barton">I'll bet this one's even surprised the great Professor Layton, hasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Without doubt, this is no ordinary accident. May I ask how the driver was?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Hrrm. He wasn't seriously hurt. He's a real jammy dodger, that one. In fact, we're about to take him into custody for questioning. Strictly private, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Inspector Chelmey. There's something I would like to know.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">...What's that, then?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The driver's name... Was it, by any chance, Carmine Accidenti?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">...Eh?! How the devil?! Where did you get that information?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ho ho. Well... You could just say a little bird told me. He's something of an unlucky-yet-lucky type, always getting himself into trouble only to miraculously escape unharmed.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">An acquaintance of yours, is he?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">He attended my lectures a few years back. An outstanding student.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Is that so? Well, perhaps you should have lectured him on how to stay out of trouble. We've had our eye on him for some time. He's a bit of a maverick, that detective. Always sniffing out dangerous situations and poking his nose into trouble. "Unlucky" isn't the half of it... I tell you, I wasn't surprised to find him involved in this ruckus.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor! That means... This must be the incident in which Carmine was attacked...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ Yes, it would seem so.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">What's this? Know something I don't, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">No, no... Nothing at all, Inspector.</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Hrrm, I was hoping you might just come up with something I could use... Never mind. Now I've got that detective, I may be able to wring something from him.</line>
<line speaker="Barton">I'd really like to know how such an accident occurred!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Inspector... Just one more question. Is there any evidence to suggest that Carmine was not alone in that car?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">What's that? Someone else in the car? No, there's nothing to suggest that.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Is that so? Well, was there anything else unusual about the accident that you haven't mentioned?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Anything else unusual... Hmm... No, not as far as I'm aware.</line>
<line speaker="Barton">Wait a minute! We did see those strange people in Halloween costumes...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm?!</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Oi! Barton! Like I said before, I'll do all the talking!</line>
<line speaker="Barton">Yes, Inspector. Sorry, Inspector.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">These people in Halloween costumes... can you tell me anything about them?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Hrrm, you're certainly persistent, Layton. To be honest with you, I don't think they had anything to do with it. We saw a group of them loitering around Tower Bridge. I decided to question them, but when I took my eyes off them for a second, they just disappeared. I wonder what in the blazes they were up to, wandering around dressed like that...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">When precisely was this?</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Just a moment ago. About the same time you went to the park.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Halloween costumes? Professor! Could it be...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm, I see what you mean. It seems we may have a lead.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Thank you for your help, Inspector!</line>
<line speaker="Chelmey">Now, hold on. Just what's this all about?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, we seem to have come to the right place, all right.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes... It would appear the witches attacked Espella and Carmine in the park... before coming after Espella and abducting her from my office. Following that, they must have made their way from there to Tower Bridge.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We may still catch up with them if we hurry! Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Luke, we must not dawdle here. Let's go to Tower Bridge.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Something doesn't feel quite right... What on earth could be going on?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Let's go to Tower Bridge. We may find some answers there.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Maybe we'll find Miss Espella there, too!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I am quite certain we will find some clues at Tower Bridge.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There's no one here.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This is puzzling... I'd normally expect to see more people here at this time.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It must be the bad weather. I guess no one wants to go out in this...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That could be it... Although I'm also sensing something of a peculiar presence in the air.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Eh?! Professor... Don't talk like that... ...Whoa! Th-that made me jump!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Luke! Over there!</line>
<line speaker="???">............!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yikes! What was that?! I bet it was one of them! Professor, let's follow it!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Just a moment, Luke. There's something we should review before we go running off. The method of entering a building is a little different to that of regular movement. Sometimes, when moving the magnifying glass during Investigation Mode, the cursor will change to a yellow arrow. This indicates a means of direct entry. You can also enter while in Movement Mode. Simply touch Enter to do so.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Touch the yellow arrow in Investigation Mode, or Enter in Movement Mode, right?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's it, my boy. Try not to forget. All right then, let's make haste!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Let's chase after the shadow on Tower Bridge, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Luke, we must follow the shadow that vanished further down the bridge!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We need to investigate the shadow that we saw ahead of us.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What the...? That thing just disappeared...into thin air?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... Well, I certainly don't feel that same presence I did just a moment ago.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey, Professor! What's that?! Wait, isn't that... Professor, it's Espella's cloak!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes...it certainly looks like the cloak she was wearing.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Espella... Where could she have gone?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm?! Luke, take a look at that. On the wall there, just next to the cloak...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Eh? Hey! There's some kind of mysterious pattern engraved here.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed... I believe this may demand closer investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Miss Espella's cloak. She has certainly passed this way.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, let's examine the pattern on the wall! It looks like it may hold some clues!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Nothing strikes me as suspicious at the other end of the tunnel.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That symbol's only on this side of the tunnel.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We ought to make haste. I feel a puzzle is waiting to be solved in this part of the tunnel.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There are no other clues on the road.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Maybe on the other side? Hmm... no, it must be somewhere around here.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The shadow was exactly where we are standing now when it vanished.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The ceiling is made of bricks, too. There is nothing odd about it.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The echo in here makes it seem like there's someone behind us...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The symbol on the wall looks very odd. Luke, why don't you take a closer look at it?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...What do you think this pattern is all about?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, I can't say it's a pattern I've ever seen before. I wonder what a mark like this could be doing here...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wait a sec... That figure disappeared right around here, didn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's right... Not to mention, Espella's cloak is lying right here in front of this wall. Without doubt, there must be some kind of clue here as to Espella's whereabouts.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Let's check it out! ...Wait... Can you hear something?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...........................P-Professor! The wall's moving!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">40</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Look, Professor! Th-the wall...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What's this now? Luke! Are you all right, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Uh, yes!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What is this place?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What's a place like this doing behind the wall?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It appears to have been here for some time.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I wonder who could have made this place... and why? It's so dark... I can barely see. Ah! Espella! Professor, we've got to search for Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. She could be here somewhere. Although...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So...could that witch...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Precisely. We should proceed with caution.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Okay!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ugh, it's pitch-black here. I wish we had brought a torch.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Is that an outline of a passage over there?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">How long is this tunnel...? I can't even see the end.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Something's wrapped in a piece of cloth. What can it be?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is difficult to say what it is in this darkness.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This room gives me the creeps. Even the air feels strangely colder here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A wrench, a spanner and some other tools are lying about.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It looks like a fairly comprehensive set of tools.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, why would someone leave this stuff here?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah! Professor, over there!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Quickly, let's get her on her feet!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">20</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect guess</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Espella! Are you all right?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr...Layton... It's really you... Mr Layton...you really did come and rescue me...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Of course. As I've said, it is the duty of every gentleman to save a lady in trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Thank you, Mr Layton.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's my duty too, as an apprentice gentleman! Ah! Professor! I think they're coming back!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I don't sense any immediate danger... But be sure to stay on your guard, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right! Now, let's hurry up and leave this place.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">There's no escaping them.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Carmine tried many times to lead me away from the witches... But, as you have seen, we were unable to escape them for long...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Uh-oh! What should we do, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm?!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, no!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That figure...from before.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, I can hear something! It's coming from the end of the corridor!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Just as I thought. Mr Layton! If we stay here, they'll find us!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This is bad, Professor! They're getting closer and closer!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Please! At least, save yourselves!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... Don't worry, there may be a way out of this.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I have an idea... Please, leave this to me.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...All right.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There's not much time, so listen carefully.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor! They're nearly here! And there are lots of them!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ Okay, we should be all set. Let's get going, Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Layton...</line>
<line speaker="???">...So you enjoy playing silly little tricks...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, it seems you underestimated us.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You didn't think we'd just give ourselves up, did you?!</line>
<line speaker="???">Hmph...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">So, tell me...just who are you "witches"? And why are you so determined to capture Espella?!</line>
<line speaker="???">Hmph... ...Fools...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...?!</line>
<line speaker="???">...It's yourselves... ...you should be more concerned about... ...Do you have any idea of what it means... ...to involve yourself with that girl...?! ...It would seem not...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wh-what do you mean?!</line>
<line speaker="???">...Ha ha ha ha ha ha... ...The pair of you have unknowingly... ...walked right into... ...the middle of the Story...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The middle of the story?</line>
<line speaker="???">...You'll soon see what I mean... ...with your very own eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor! She just disappeared...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I wonder what she could have meant by that...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I don't know, but I have a bad feeling about all of this... Do you think she's just trying to scare us because she lost...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... At any rate, we should try to reach Espella. I know where that ship was heading. Let's head to the port and meet Espella when she arrives.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right. And then we can give her back this book. H-huh? P-Professor! The book! It's...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Isn't this...?! Isn't this us, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Surely not...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ack! It's a little tricky.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Shall we take a break?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">All right then, Luke, why not see if you can solve this puzzle?</line>
<line speaker="Barton">Another case remains unsolved...</line>
<line speaker="Barton">Worrying about that hamburger is preventing my progress on the case.</line>
<line speaker="Constable">Hmm, just as I suspected! You're no more than an imposter pretending to be Professor Layton. Phew... And I nearly fell for it too.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Did you hear that, Professor?! Did you catch what he just said? I'm not sure I can just take that on the chin!</line>
<line speaker="Constable">I'm sure the real Professor Layton would have no problem solving this.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...there's a tough puzzle embedded here.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If we can complete this pattern correctly, perhaps it will provide some sort of clue.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What have they done?! Let's get this rope untied and free Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor! We have to rescue Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Okay, Luke. Let's give this one more try.</line>
</xml>