<xml>
<title>On Briar Road</title>
<line speaker="Roly">Sah! Constable Roly Beate, reportin' for duty! Thanks to the good offices of Lord van Zieks... ...I'm back on my beat here in the capital, doin' my best for the good citizens of London! SAH!</line>
<line speaker="Patricia">Aaah, my Roly, back on his bobby's uniform. You couldn't look any more handsome if you tried!</line>
<line speaker="Roly">Aaah...my love! You say the sweetest things!</line>
<line speaker="Roly">To us, Lord van Zieks isn't the Reaper of the Bailey at all.</line>
<line speaker="Patricia">Oh no! Of course not! He's, he's...the patron saint of bobbies!</line>
<line speaker="Roly">The patron saint? ...Oh yes, Pat. You're so right, my darlin'! Keepin' us in pocket, he is. On my first day back on the job, what did I find in the gutter? A shillin', my love! A whole shillin'!</line>
<line speaker="Patricia">Oh, Roly! I always believed in you! I always knew one day you'd find some big small change!</line>
<line speaker="Roly">With just that shillin', I could buy you a cheap bunch containing a single flower, my sugar!</line>
<line speaker="Patricia">A single flower?! Oh...how romantic!</line>
<line speaker="Roly">But...I'm so sorry, Pat... ...only moments ago that shillin'...disappeared!</line>
<line speaker="Patricia">D-Disappeared? But, but how, my love? How?</line>
<line speaker="Roly">I think maybe... No, I'm sure... ...it was this girl here, SAH! You swiped my precious shillin', didn't you, you cheeky little diver?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Blimey... ...you took yer time gettin' round to me, didn't ya? I thought that lovey-dovey stuff weren't ever gonna end. So...a shillin', ya say? Lifted from ya, were it? Dunno nuffin' about it. Where's the evidence, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Roly">Right there! The evidence is dancin' around on the back of your hand, young lady! You stole it from me! You lifted it from my pocket just now! You've got a nerve, stealin' from a bobby!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Cobblers! This coin's mine! 'Ow could ya know, anyway? 'Ow could ya know if it was taken 'just now' or not?</line>
<line speaker="Roly">Dear me, you don't get it, do you? We've hardly got a penny to our name. So that coin felt as heavy to me as a bar of gold.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Roly">I'm tellin' you, the moment it left my pocket, I knew. I felt myself get a good few pounds lighter.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Roly">Yup! That coin has got my blood, sweat and tears all over it!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Nnnnnnrrrgh... ......... Wot's the matter wiv ya, eh? Mr Narra-'Oddo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh? M-Me? Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">When a lady's in trouble, a true gent's s'posed to be there to 'elp. Straight away! Not an 'our later!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...This isn't my fault. I haven't stolen anything!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">An' wot about you, eh, Sholmes? I thought you was s'posed to be a great detective!</line>
<line speaker="???">...Dear me, Miss Lestrade...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...you took your time getting around to me, didn't you? I thought that long dispute was never going to end.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You only said, 'Give us a minute' when we spotted you over the road and said hello. And that was ten minutes ago, Ginny. We've just been standing here listening to you quarrel with this bobby.</line>
<line speaker="Roly">Do beg your pardon, madam. We shouldn't be troublin' the public with police business.</line>
<line speaker="Patricia">But that shilling belongs to us! Doesn't it, Roly?</line>
<line speaker="Roly">Of course it does, my love! It's just for you and me, my darlin'!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Grrr...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This was just supposed to be a nice stroll with Iris and Mr Sholmes before afternoon tea. Why did we have to run into another fiasco on Briar Road?</thought> I don't really see how we could be of any help, Gina. There's no way of knowing who the coin really belongs to if it was just dropped in the gutter.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I wouldn't be so sure of that, Runo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I have a feeling I might know the answer...to the question of whose coin that is!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, my bright young fellow lodger... Let us hear your deduction!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, there's actually a reason why I suggested a stroll down Briar Road.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh. What reason?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You see, I was here yesterday and, well...I dropped a little something. So I wanted to come and look for it. While enjoying an afternoon stroll.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait, you dropped something? You don't mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It was the pocket money that Hurley gave me.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What's this, Iris? You dropped that, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I'm... I'm sorry. I went to the market on Lime Street yesterday to pick up some herbs, you see. But on the way, I must have dropped it. The one shilling coin you gave me.</line>
<line speaker="Roly">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">A, a one bob bit?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes. And when I thought back over the route I took, I realised I must have dropped it here. Constable, you haven't seen it, have you? ...It's all my pocket money. And now it's gone.</line>
<line speaker="Roly">......... Well...erm... I'm, I'm, I'm afraid I don't know anythin' about that, young lady.</line>
<line speaker="Patricia">What, what rotten luck, droppin' your money like that. Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I dare say the constable and his companion could give you a run for your money with their wide eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If it's all the same to you, Mr Sholmes, I think I'd prefer not to be used as the yardstick for looking guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Well, it's tough really, innit, Iris? Ya dropped it, so it ain't yours no more. Anyway, ya know wot they say. Wot goes around comes around. So don't feel bad.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Bad luck, Iris. It doesn't look like you're going to get your coin back.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh... I can't believe I've lost it. And straight after Hurley gave it to me as well.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, regrettable indeed. I seem to recall that particular coin was rather significant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean 'significant'?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">To be specific...it was especially significant to you, Runo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Significant to me? ...Ah! You don't mean...? It was the coin...from last night's wager?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The very same, my dear fellow.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Wot's this, then? Wot wager?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It was a game of poker. A duel between Hurley and Runo.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Poker? Wot, that tricky card game, ya mean?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">'As a lawyer, I have the perfect poker face. You'll never be able to tell what I'm thinking!' said he. But depriving Mr Naruhodo of his entire fortune was even easier than finding that missing thoroughbred.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Grrr! It was so infuriating, reliving it now still makes me grit my teeth. Sorry, Iris, I had every intention of paying you back the money I owe you, but you'll have to wait, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, I know. Don't worry, next month is fine.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Let me guess, 'Oddo... Yer 'whole fortune'...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It was one whole shilling. My entire monthly stipend. And I lost all of it! As I handed it over to Mr Sholmes, I gritted my teeth so hard my gums started to bleed.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Please, Runo...don't exaggerate. That's a horrible image!</line>
<line speaker="Patricia">What about a lawyer who borrows money from a ten-year-old girl? Now that's a horrible image.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Why do I feel like my reputation with this couple has just fallen through the floor?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah ha ha ha ha hah! There are few things more invigorating than taking a man for all he's worth!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Don't be so pleased with yourself, Hurley. It's not as if Runo ever had a chance of winning.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait... What? What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, using that special ink I developed, anyone could-</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Thank you, Iris! That will do. I'm sure this conversation is proving very dull for everyone. What's done is done. The game is over now. There's no point crying over spilt milk.</line>
<line speaker="Roly">'Special ink' you say? Well, sah! That sounds like the sort of risky business that's right up my alley!</line>
<line speaker="Patricia">Oh, Roly! I love your dauntless spirit! You laugh in the face of danger!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Come on then, Iris, spill it. Wot's this 'special ink' about, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah, well! It's what's sometimes called invisible ink. All you have to do is write the suit and number on the reverse side of every card... ...and with the aid of some special glasses, the whole game is laid bare to you!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait! You were wearing glasses last night, weren't you, Mr Sholmes? You said something along the lines of 'My eyesight appears to have suddenly worsened.'</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And the moment you failed to question that as odd was the moment I knew I had won the game!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Mind games, was it? Trying to throw me off with your eccentric ways?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">So yer tellin' me Sholmes could see every card wot 'Oddo 'ad?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">WHAT?! But that's...that's not mind games! That's blatant cheating!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow! What an accusation! Would you honestly consider me a cheat? Please, I prefer 'trickster'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Whatever you call it, the game doesn't count now! Understand, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Dear me... Well, out of respect for the bad grace with which you take defeat, allow me to return your shilling.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Did you hear that, Gina? So give it here!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">...Eh? Leave me out o' this! This 'ere one bob bit was mine from the start! No question!</line>
<line speaker="Roly">No, sah! That there one bob bit was lifted from this here bobby's pocket only a few minutes ago!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">So ya keep sayin'! Come on then! Where's the evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Roly">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">The law, right, is all about evidence. I know my stuff!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You see, Mr Naruhodo? Use a trite excuse in court, and others will parrot it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Only, whenever I do say that in court, it isn't as a trite excuse, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Roly">As I said, sah...that coin has got my blood, sweat and tears all over it!</line>
<line speaker="Patricia">That's right, it has! Roly's blood, sweat and tears are the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hm, blood, you say? In that case, it's time...for this!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Do, do you think...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, if there's any trace of blood on that coin, we'll soon know about it! Alright, Ginny...hold veeery still...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Eh? Wot?! Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at that! See there on the coin? <thought>It's clearly changed colour!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In other words, there is blood on this coin.</line>
<line speaker="Roly">Once again, as I said, sah! That would be my blood, sweat and tear-</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ooh, wait. I've seen blood turn that colour before. Yes! I know whose it is! I know whose coin it is!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Wot?!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">The rightful owner of this bloodstained shilling is... ...Runo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh? Me?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And from the appearance of the blood, I would say it is quite fresh. Left within the last twenty-four hours.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Within the last... Ah! Then, in that case...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">So...this is the coin wot Sholmes 'ad off 'Oddo last night in the poker game?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, Runo! Do you mean you really did make your gums bleed?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I told you, I was so infuriated to lose, I had to grit my teeth as I handed over the money.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Blimey...yer as 'ard up as me by the sound of it. But I thought you 'ad a proper job.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Come on, Gina, just hand it over, would you? The shilling...that's rightfully mine.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">......... Argh! Fine, alright then! Just stop yer bleedin' starin'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Aaah...I finally have it back. It's like a dream come true!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Tsk. I nearly 'ad that one in the bag an' all.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's wonderful news, Runo. I'm so happy for you! Now then...as you promised... ...I'd like my money back, please. The shilling I lent you before.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You did say that you'd pay it back out of this month's pocket money, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...um...yes... Well then, I suppose...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow, do be kind to your gums.</line>
<line speaker="Roly">Looks like that shillin' was always destined to be taken from you, sah.</line>
<line speaker="Patricia">For some reason, the phrase 'serves you right' is floating around in my head...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">S...S...S..Sooo, Iris... As p-promised...here...is the shilling I owe you.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh? You're repaying me already? Well, thank you. Next month would have been fine, though.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Wot's it all about anyway? Wot are you lendin' 'Oddo money for?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah yes, well actually, it's because I went to the Lime Street market yesterday to buy herbs... ...for Runo.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">'Erbs? For 'Oddo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. The tea Miss Susato left behind is top-quality gyokuro tea, but it's just so bitter. So when Iris suggested mixing it with some herbs to make it more palatable, I asked her to buy me some.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's right. We've made a special Japanese herbal tea with the leftover gyokuro. I'm going to call it Susie's Special Blend! I do hope you'll all try it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The excruciating bitterness clings to the throat...if you can persuade the bright green gloop to leave the cup.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Why, it sounds quite delicious!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, right...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, it would appear this shilling's brief adventures are now at an end.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Adventures?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You must agree, my dear fellow, that the coin has made a considerable journey since last night.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Let's see... Originally, it was the coin I was supposed to give to Iris to pay her for the herbs. But then, in our poker duel last night, it passed to you, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Who gave it to Iris as spendin' money.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But then I dropped it here sometime yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Patricia">Then my beloved Roly found it a little while ago and picked it up...</line>
<line speaker="Roly">...Before it was lifted from my pocket by this here diver.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I then used my favourite gun to show up the blood that was on it...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">...And let slip about Sholmes's little scam in 'is card game last night.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The annulment of which resulted in the coin returning to the ownership of Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Allowing me to pay Iris the money I owed her after all... ...for the herbs she'd bought in order to make Susie's Special Blend tea.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And now, after all that, the coin is resting safely in my pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">.........</line>
<line speaker="Gina">......... Yeah, yer right, that was an adventure. But wot are we s'posed to take away from it, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That this one shilling coin belongs to Iris and Iris alone, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I cannot fault your observation, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, you know what they say... What goes around comes around!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Why do I get the feeling that Iris knew it was coming around to her from the very beginning?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah ha ha ha ha hah! Priceless, as they say! Well then, my dear fellow, how about this evening we indulge in some bitter tea and a bitter rematch? I'll even allow you to stake the coming month's spending money in advance.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I fold.</line>
</xml>