<xml>
<title>Recipe for Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Byrde">Oh... I see... I guess I should've expected this. Nobody saw the other guy, huh? But he was there when I took the coffee over, sir. Scout's honor!</line>
<line speaker="???">Maggey!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Ack! D-Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A-Are you doing alright!? How're you feeling!?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">...As if you need to ask either question, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't let 'em get you down, Maggey. And don't forget to eat well, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Roger!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You'd better square this case away, got it pal!? Maggey's innocent, you hear!? If you screw up, then I'll be doing some squaring away myself. Squaring away some paperwork for your arrest!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I-I think he's serious!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Detective! You're on our side for once, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So you'll be able to help Maggey out, right?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Really? Can you, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">O... Of course! I've got the simulation under control! I'm gonna be the first witness on the stand today. If something I say doesn't mesh with the facts, make sure you point it out, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sure.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OK. We're forming a united front today, pal. You get me!?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I can't tell you how grateful I am, sir! I've always admired you so much, Detective. I know I can count on you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Looks like it should all go pretty smoothly today, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can only wish...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Maggey Byrde.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">... Aaah, bitter!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr... Um... Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What's wrong!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Nothing. It's just whenever I addressed you in the previous trial, your response was... "Youse talkin' to me!?" It was a little, well... intimidating.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no! That wasn't me. That was the phony Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. So our trusty Phoenix Wright is back with us now, is he?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Our trusty"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, Mr. Godot. Your opening statement, please.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Mr. Trite... Whether you're a fake or the real deal... We will find out soon enough through this trial today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I can already tell you! I'm the real Phoenix Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I wasn't questioning whether you are Phoenix Wright or not. I was questioning whether you had studied law or not. That's what I intend to find out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's no denying it. Behind that mask is a man who really hates me for some reason or another!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">As everyone is aware, the court has already given its verdict on this case once. Therefore, I won't stand for irrelevant testimony during this retrial. Nor will I stand for a simple repetition of the evidence presented in the last trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not planning on repeating anything that phony me said! Trust me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then. Mr. Godot, please summon your first witness.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Let's start with the formalities, shall we? Name and occupation?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! State your name for the court!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? Oh, sorry, sir! The name's Police Department Detective. Occupation, Dick Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Other way around, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? Oh! Sorry. Anyway, I'm the officer in charge of this case since yesterday, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Since yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. The guy who was on the initial investigation's tied up with another case now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I hope Gumshoe's really got everything under control... For everyone's sake.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. So, Detective Gumshoe... Would you outline for the court the basic facts of the case?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Y-Yes, sir. The victim's name was Glen Elg. He was a professional programmer. He was on the payroll of Blue Screens Inc., a local company. This is the victim's autopsy report.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court accepts this into evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um... And here are the floor plans of the restaurant. When the incident took place, the victim was sitting right here. The poisoned coffee was brought over to him by the, um... By the waitress.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The waitress being the accused?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah... The victim died from poisoning almost immediately after he took a sip of the coffee. At the time of the incident, there were two other people in the restaurant. Mr. Jean Armstrong, the owner and chef. And a regular by the name of Mr. Victor Kudo.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It still seems to be a very straightforward case to me.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Come, Detective. Take up this hammer. And nail the defendant's coffin shut with your own two hands.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Detective Gumshoe. Let's have your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm... Yes, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">When the incident took place, the victim was alone at his table, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Using the dark, aromatic depths of coffee to conceal the poison... Classy lady!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The facts of this case seem to be ironclad. Mr. Wright. I would ask you to begin your cross-examination, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please, no intimidation tricks this time around. Is that understood?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I already told you! That wasn't me!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">When the incident took place, the victim was alone at his table, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can I stop you for just a minute?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? What is it? Did I say something that contradicts the evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He'd so desperate for that to be true, he's practically crying!</thought> Your testimony just now doesn't match the testimony given by Ms. Byrde. She claims that there was another man at the victim's table.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, that's what she said. And I--</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">What killer wouldn't say that when faced with a homicide conviction?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Sadly, her testimony isn't supported by the owner or the other customer. Isn't that right, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, it's true. Their two testimonies tie up on that. They both said there was no other guy at the table.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What should I do? Should I press on this point a little harder or not?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No, I should leave it alone. I've got a bad feeling about where this is going.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">If you got a bad feeling about this, then maybe you should leave it alone. I once had a bad feeling that I was about to have a bad feeling. It was really bad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Maybe I should move on to another part of his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, maybe the other witnesses just missed him! Perhaps their view of the victim's table was obscured in some way.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! That argument is as weak as the coffee at Trés Bien, Trite!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I have here in my possession a ticket.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A ticket? <thought>Looks more like a photo to me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Yes. A one-way ticket to guilty-ville! Population: the defendant! This is a photograph taken from near the entrance to the kitchen.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is the scene as witnessed by the chef, moments after the poisoning took place, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I think the court will agree that with such a clear view of the scene of the crime... ...how, Mr. Trite, could anyone have overlooked a second person at the table?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It certainly seems to show the victim's table extremely clearly.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We understand that the guy, Glen Elg, was listening to the radio at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He was listening to his radio, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. He had a portable radio in his chest pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maggey told us that too, didn't she? Something about how "one of them had some sort of earpiece".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What should I do? Should I press on this point a little harder or not?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No, I should leave it alone. I've got a bad feeling about where this is going.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">If you got a bad feeling about this, then maybe you should leave it alone. I once had a bad feeling that I was about to have a bad feeling. It was really bad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Maybe I should move on to another part of his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what was it that the victim was listening to on the radio, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? How should I know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Thanks a lot... We're now one step closer to the middle of nowhere.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">This isn't going very well, is it...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Detective. Could you perhaps tell us about the poison and how it was used?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Traces of poison were found in his coffee cup.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, traces of the poison were found in the coffee cup and nowhere else?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Not sure I get you, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was the poison a liquid? Or was it a powder?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If I had to put it in layman's terms, I'd say it was a powdery substance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the poison could've been in anything that was on the table. Sugar, salt, pepper...</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Do you put salt and pepper in your coffee, Trite?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The victim took his coffee black, with no sugar.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems that the poison could only have been in the coffee.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What should I do? Should I press on this point a little harder or not?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No, I should leave it alone. I've got a bad feeling about where this is going.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">If you got a bad feeling about this, then maybe you should leave it alone. I once had a bad feeling that I was about to have a bad feeling. It was really bad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Maybe I should move on to another part of his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you absolutely certain that the victim even drank any of his coffee?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh!? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to this file, "the poison was found in the victim's coffee cup." But what proof is there that the victim ever drank any of it!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, hey! You're right! That's what I was think--</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">In case you were wondering, that last objection was for the detective there.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? For me?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">"Oh, hey! You're right!"? You may be fooling the court, but I'm not falling for it. If you have the time to waste, you have the time to present that piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Th... THAT piece... sir?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Yes. THAT piece.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Um... Aheh heh heh! Wh-What piece was it again?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">This!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Should I be grateful this coffee's only hot enough to give me 1st degree burns...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh. Now I remember! Um... This is the, uh... victim's coffee cup.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Yes, the victim's cup. Take a good look at the rim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, yes. It's unmistakable. There is clearly a coffee stain on it.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Conclusive proof that the victim did drink the poisoned coffee that was in this cup. The victim gulped down the bitter death that the waitress brought to him... like this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uuuurgh!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">For the record, the only prints on the cup were the victim's and the defendant's.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Upon further investigation of this cup... we found a certain chemical substance...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And what we found was potassium cyanide. That stuff really packs a punch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Potassium cyanide? I've heard of that chemical before...</thought> Exactly how strong is this poison, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's... Well... That stuff's lethal! Eat too much, and you're history.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">How much is too much?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">A lethal does is 0.2 grams. That's about enough to finish anyone off.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">0.2 grams? How much is that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You know when you swab your ears for earwax? Yeah, about that much.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Earwax, huh? Sounds like something Gumshoe's got an abundance of...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Such a small quantity of poison could have been concealed anywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And, um... it looks like Ms. Byrde might've had, well... some kind of a motive.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Some kind of a motive"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. But if you ask me, it's been blown way out of proportion.</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">You know what my golden rule is, Detective? Chuck out a bad cup of coffee. You can always get another.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? I don't get it.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I'm saying, we can always get another witness on the stand, if we have to chuck you out.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">*gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Godot">So stick to the facts, Detective. Now then, what was Ms. Byrde's motive?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come on, Gumshoe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She was... They said she wanted to steal a lottery ticket.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I knew it... <thought>That's what we heard yesterday, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It disappeared from the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">And it wasn't just any lottery ticket. It was a winning ticket for half a million!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mr. Armstrong knew about the ticket too, didn't he? But he stole the wrong one...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Then is it possible Maggey stole the winning one? What should I do? Should I press on this point a little harder or not?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No, I should leave it alone. I've got a bad feeling about where this is going.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">If you got a bad feeling about this, then maybe you should leave it alone. I once had a bad feeling that I was about to have a bad feeling. It was really bad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Maybe I should move on to another part of his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a minute! The mere fact that the lottery ticket disappeared in no way implicates my client!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! I have here in my hand... the very ticket in question!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That's the half a million dollar lottery ticket...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">One of the female police officers found it when she was conducting a search... ...of the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WH-WHAAAAAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! She's quite a lucky bird, our little waitress.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-You will submit that ticket as evidence to the court! Immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, I'd better keep an eye on that ticket. The way the judge's voice is quivering...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The ticket was presented to the court in the previous trial, too. But it feels heavier now somehow. H-Half a million dollars, you say...?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">It's just a scrap of paper. What matters is where it was found, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I bet he wants to say it was found on Maggey's person...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You really think there are any contradictions in this testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To be honest, I don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But Gumshoe told us out in the lobby. He said we'd be forming a united front, right? How will we win the case if he doesn't throw us a line?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't have a whole lot of options right now... The best I can do is gather the facts together, I guess.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">I like an old man who knows the score.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There is also the matter of the half a million dollar lottery ticket. That alone provides a very credible motive. I mean, for that sum of money even I might be tempted to bend the rules!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I don't like an old man who is weak to the siren call of money.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Not good, Nick... The evidence against Maggey is starting to pile up fast.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, that's because the court has ruled guilty once already.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I'd say it's about time to wrap up this repeat performance... ...with one final, decisive piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's got more evidence against Maggey!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">This is the apron the delightful Ms. Byrde was wearing at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow... That's not the cleanest apron I've seen...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That stain looks like...! <thought>It can't be... blood, can it!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! It seems the star of our play was a little flustered... And somehow spilled coffee on herself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The coffee!? That's not exactly the first thing that caught my eye...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Of course. The coffee stain isn't the most interesting thing about this apron. No, there's something else that stands out even more.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Something else? I presume you mean...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Of course. I'm referring to the pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The... pocket?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">A search carried out right after the incident uncovered this... Potassium cyanide. The very poison used by the killer, was in her apron pocket!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A bottle of poison... In Maggey's pocket?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. And Maggey's prints were the only ones on it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAAAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! The court will accept these items into evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There's something still bothering me, Mr. Godot. Why have you not explained the bloodstain to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Bloodstain? What bloodstain would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Don't play games, prosecutor! The blood-colored stain that's smeared all over the apron!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">That's ridiculous! No one told me anything about a bloodstain!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You don't need to be told! Just look at it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Well, Detective!? Could this stain really be... BLOOD!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">N-No way, sir! That's... It's just ketchup. Sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ketchup!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She must've gotten some on her an apron while taking someone their breakfast that day.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... You could have spoken up a little sooner, Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Pull a stunt like that again, and I'll have you drink 17 cups of ketchup, witness!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Unnngh... I thought everyone knew what it was already.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I haven't seen anything yet to make me doubt the last verdict I ruled on this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The motive, the opportunity, and the supporting evidence... They have all been clearly established.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Well, Trite... It seems you really are a phony after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! You really know how to drive a man nuts!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, please continue with your testimony. Describe for the court the crime scene and the findings of your investigation there.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The crime was reported at 2:25 PM by a kind of scary old man, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... You identified the victim and secured your prime suspect... Very good.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Last chance to convince the court you're a real lawyer, Trite!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Don't court on any more cross-examinations after this one! So, let the fun begin!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The crime was reported at 2:25 PM by a kind of scary old man, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Scary old man", Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's an old man who's a regular at the restaurant where the incident happened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ah, we're obviously talking about the same old man...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Officers were dispatched right after the report came in, but the old guy still made a fuss. "What took you so long!?" Then he hurled abuse at them. And seeds...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Seeds...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! It was nothing! I caught each one with my teeth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess not even the mighty Godot can avoid being attacked by that guy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">The old man was only other customer in the place at the time. He took his time finding a pay phone apparently, so he was late reporting the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Poor Maggey had passed out from the shock. It must've been real tough for her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How long was the defendant unconscious for?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The officers got to the crime scene at around 2:40. Maggey was still out cold in the kitchen at that time. It took another 10 minutes or so before she came to. I woulda liked to have been on the scene myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I bet you would've liked to have carried out the search, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I woulda loved to see Maggey asleep like that, all pretty and peaceful.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You're a professional detective, Gumshoe. Not a professional bird watcher!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Save the romantics for your own time, Detective. All we need to know about is the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oops! I guess I'm pretty red right now, aren't I?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The victim didn't have any identification on him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He didn't have any? Are you saying that it was stolen, then?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No, I don't think so. The victim didn't have a driver's license or even a credit card on him, pal. All he had was 58 cents in his wallet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Fifty-eight cents...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. I can't believe I found someone with less in their wallet than me, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The victim sounds like he was a thoroughly miserable young man.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Or some kind of outlaw... Why not give him a bit of an edge?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I'm on to something here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But we figured out who he was pretty quick, and then the investigation went smoothly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a sec!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? D-Did I say something dumb again!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let me paraphrase what you just testified to this court. "The victim didn't have any form of ID on him." That's basically what you said, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, basically.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In that case, how were you able to identify the victim so quickly?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Oh... That.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's so let down, he's got the whole sagging shoulders and puppy eyes thing going...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There was a prescription bag on the victim's table along with the lottery ticket.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">It seems Mr. Glen Elg visited his doctor before he went to Trés Bien.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We got the victim's name from the medical records of the doc who prescribed the meds.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That's a reliable enough source for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What should I do? Should I leave this alone or ask to hear more?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess it doesn't really matter how they figured out who the victim was. There are more important avenues to explore.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what sort of medicine was in the bag?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well... Actually, the bag we found was empty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. Completely empty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It was completely empty...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! You're entering an empty paper bag as evidence? Desperate, are you, Trite?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Now, what happened with the investigation after that, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, the victim had no form of identification on him, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And yet, before arriving at the restaurant, he went to see a doctor. Which means... He must've had his medical insurance card with him!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! That is very true!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The fact that it hasn't been found points to only one obvious conclusion. The victim's medical card was stolen!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! True, the victim didn't have a medical insurance card. But why? Because Mr. Glen Elg didn't have medical insurance to begin with!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... As I thought, a thoroughly miserable young man.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Or some kind of outlaw... A bit of an edge never hurt anyone.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Looks like we're off course again, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness. Please continue with your testimony. Explain for the court the events following the preliminary investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">When Maggey was searched, we found the lottery ticket and the bottle of poison.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the defendant had been passed out for a while, correct? In that case... Isn't it possible someone planted the evidence in Maggey's pocket!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! Y-Yeah! You've nailed it, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It happens to me all the time! We had a department party the other day, and when I got home... ...I was wearing the boss's shoes!</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Keep up this crazy testimony, Detective, and those shoes will end up down your throat!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">So, Trite. "Someone planted the evidence in Maggey's pocket"...? That's a pretty bold statement. Care to back it up with some evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Well... <thought>I'd love to, if I had any...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It appears you have no evidence to support your theory, Mr. Wright. Continue with your testimony, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And that was it. There was nothing else missing from the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the half a million dollar lottery ticket and the bottle of poison were accounted for.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Interesting... It's true that those two items are accounted for... ..but wasn't there another lottery ticket that was stolen that day?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, yeah. The one the restaurant owner took. He won a whole dollar with it. What a lucky guy, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And they're just going to let him get away with it...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It was just one dollar, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess no one cares when it's that little... Unless it's Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If I don't find a hole in this testimony, the judge is going to hand down his verdict!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Gumshoe isn't giving us anything to work with... And we can't find any contradictions if he doesn't give us something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, that's true... But Maggey and Gumshoe are like dumb and dumber. Our only hope is that they were so dumb, they missed something obvious.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, Gumshoe! Be the dumbest you've ever been!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe. I think I should point something out to you. There is just one small contradiction in your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oho! Finally! I'm getting all anxious just waiting, so hurry up, will you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You testified that, "nothing else was missing from the crime scene." However! The prescription bag you mentioned was empty! Did the officers recover the medicine from the scene of the crime later?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, no. They didn't.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim was given a prescription right before going to Trés Bien. Where, then, did the medicine disappear to!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-You... ...are toooooo coool, pal!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-Indeed! Due consideration wasn't given to the victim's prescription in the previous trial. Witness! Why do you always overlook such vital pieces of evidence!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I, er... I guess that's the most careless thing I've done so far, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim was killed by poison! And the victim's "medicine" mysteriously disappeared! The victim's own prescription could have been the lethal poison itself!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Order! Order! Well, Mr. Godot? What do you have to say to that?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! That's all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Read for the court the name of the clinic on the prescription bag, if you will.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's the clinic's name got to do with anything...? "New Ear Otolaryngological Clinic" O-Otolaryngological?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Just what kind of illness was the victim suffering from, Mr. Godot?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Hardly an illness, Your Honor. More like a bitter war wound, you could say.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A war wound?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">The day before the incident, Mr. Elg found himself in a fight. He took a blow to the side of the head, and ruptured his eardrum.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He ruptured his eardrum!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then what on earth was the prescription he was given?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">It was a cream that was to be applied topically inside his ear canal, not to be ingested!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">It's mentioned in the autopsy report, if you read the fine print. They found traces of the medication in the victim's left ear.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes. Here it is. In very, very fine print.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">It seems Mr. Elg correctly applied some of his medication while he was at Trés Bien. Therefore, it would be absurd to believe that he would have eaten his medication.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uuurgh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems that this medication is irrelevant to the case after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! If you don't think of something quick, it'll all be over!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's right. But I can't get away with any old weak objection. What should I do...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It does seem as it the medication isn't connected to the case.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Maybe the last Mr. Trite was the real one. At least he didn't waste time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed... If you have nothing further to add to this medication issue... ...the facts of this case seem no different to those presented on the last trial. I would therefore have no choice but to hand down my verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... Umm...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Don't let him to do this! You've got to stand your ground!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, Your Honor! Actually, this prescription... is absolutely pivotal to the case!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Did you not just say the exact opposite only moments ago!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gotta lose a few battles in order to win the war, I suppose.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Only moments ago, Mr. Godot made the following statement. "It seems Mr. Elg correctly applied some of his medication while he was at Trés Bien." If that's the case, then why was the medication not found at the scene of the crime!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But the medication in question was for topical use inside the ear canal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That doesn't change the fact that it could not be found at the crime scene! However insignificant it may seem, it's a lawyer's duty to pursue the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">You know as well as I do that the medication is irrelevant. It hardly seems likely that a prescription drug would contain potassium cyanide.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It hardly seems likely that the coffee the waitress served would contain it, either! But it did! The possibility is undeniable!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Aaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough. Mr. Godot. Is the detective the only witness the prosecution wishes to call?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Godot...?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um... I, ah... I've got my own witness I'd like to call, sir. It's the old man who was there in the restaurant on the day of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Victor Kudo? The pigeon-hater?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The matter of the disappearing medication seems little more than trivial at beat. However! It wasn't explored at all in the previous trial. And that is something that bothers me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yay! Good job, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will adjourn for a 10 minute recess. After which we will hear the prosecution's next witness.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! I suppose this means I'll just have to finish you off in my last 6 cups.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is adjourned for recess!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Phew! That was close!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me about it... I nearly died in there!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">That's my line, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No! It's my line! I think I really did die a little bit.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Looks like we all nearly died in there... I can't believe Detective Gumshoe! How could he betray us like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">He said he'd help me. But he totally set me up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think he meant to do that, Maggey. He was backed into a corner. I mean, the guy's got to do his job, right?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">It's OK. I know all about lies and betrayal. I've had them my whole life. But it really hurt this time. It felt like someone punched me hard in the stomach! I hate that guy! I don't ever want to see him again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Gumshoe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So the next witness is going to be that old guy from the park, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. Mr. Kudo. Lover of waitress outfits and projectile seeds!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I bet he's gonna be really stubborn. I mean, he's pretty set in his ways, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, he's a big old grouch. Are you going to be able to handle him, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I can take whatever he throws at me. Even those never-ending bird seeds!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court will now reconvene for the trial of Maggey Byrde. Mr. Godot. Your next witness, please.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">The prosecution calls the lucky old-timer who caught the show over a cup of coffee. Will the witness please take the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Name and occupation, if you don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">The name is Victor Kudo. Born and bred in the Land of the Rising Sun! Honor and duty are what make me. Mind you, I can be quite emotional at times, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We don't need to hear about that, Mr. Kudo. Just tell the court your occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">My occupation? Kah! Listen, young'un! How much call d'you think there is for kimono embroidery here!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Kimono embroidery?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">That's what I do! Or did, back in Japan. I embroidered family crests on kimonos! My ancestors were embroidering kimonos before this country even existed!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, a real craftsman! They're a dying breed! Hey! Maybe he could embroider my costume sometime.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Anyway, like I said. There's not much demand for that kind of thing here. So I had to take a job working the cash register at a burger joint... pretending to smile!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That burger joint would've been better off putting him in the kitchen...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, witness. Were you in the restaurant at the time of the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Oh, yes! I was eating some seeds over a cup of javaccino.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Seeds?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">What do you think these are, hmm!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I see...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">So you saw everything that happened, gramps?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Did I!? Oh, yes! Oh, yes I did! I saw it all!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Then please, tell the court. We're all ears.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Sure, sure. I'll tell you. I'll tell you every last detail!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's really getting into this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">The young man was reading the sports paper.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Kudo. she is not a "serving girl". Please refer to her as a waitress.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Kah! You're as bad as the rest of them! All these newfangled words! What's wrong with old-fashioned ones, hmm!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">N-Newfangled?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">All this talk of "radios" and "glasses"! It's "wireless" and "spectacles", I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">E-Excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Listen to me, everyone! Don't forget the old values! Don't let the good old days slip away!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, um... I think it's time to begin the cross-examination, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">The young man was reading the sports paper.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you saw the victim, then? You saw Mr. Glen Elg?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">I wanted to know if Gusten Brawn retained his championship or not.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So he was looking at the sports paper the victim was reading, huh...</thought> And at the location in question... ...there are partitions between tables on the same side of the restaurant, right?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">So what if there are?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you say that you could see the victim... ...that means you were sitting at a table on the other side of the restaurant, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Kah! I go to that place to drink javaccino! I don't go to sit! I don't remember what table I was sitting at!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You mean you go there to eye the waitress!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">The serving girl brought him a javaccino... But she put something in it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Kudo. That is a very grave accusation. Are you sure about what you saw?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Victor Kudo never makes mistakes! I dot every t and cross every i!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">My eyesight's fine. The doctor said I only need spectacles for reading and driving.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I bet his eyes are only really "fine" when he's scoping out a waitress.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">And I saw what the serving girl put into the javaccino as well!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I bet I know what's coming up and something tells me I'm not going to like it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It'd be dangerous to press this too much. I'd better ignore it for now.</thought> So, what happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor. We need more clarification on what was put into the victim's coffee. I'd like to ask that the witness add what he knows about this to his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I agree. will you enlighten us, please?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Sure, sure.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">There's no question about it! She very conspicuously put some white powder in there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Did she really put that into the coffee?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">You doubt me, boy!? She too some out of a small, brown bottle and sprinkled it in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Couldn't she have been adding sugar?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Sugar!? In a small, brown bottle like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Like that"? Witness, could you please describe the bottle in more concrete terms?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! A bottle like this, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Oh, there it is! That's the one!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's the bottle of potassium cyanide, I presume?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">So what did the accused put into the coffee? I think it's clear, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">The man took one sip of it, looked like he was in terrible pain, and then collapsed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He took just one sip?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">You young'uns! You waste everything! Those javaccinos cost 8 dollars! In the good old days, we would have drank every last drop, eaten the cup, and then died!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Congratulations. You have earned the title of Battiest Man To Grace A Courtroom.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">So it was an immediate death? Well, with potassium cyanide, I suppose that is possible.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Oh, yes. He slumped over without so much as a twitch! I felt the javaccino I'd just drank turn sour in my stomach.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Oh, yes. I know that feeling.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And the waitress? I presume she is...?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">That's the serving girl, right there in the defendant's chair. I remember her well!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You said, "I remember her well" in reference to the waitress... Did she have any particular features that you can identify her by?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Particular features!? It's a disgrace, that's what it is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">You can see all the way up to her... her... You know! She's practically naked in that uniform!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the particular feature you recognize about the waitress is... her outfit!? But anyone could wear just such an [sic] uniform! Even me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Please spare the court of any further mental anguish from that image.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't get all excited, Nick! You've gotta keep yourself together!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I-I guess I got a bit carried away...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Kah! There are other things I recognize about her, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He seems pretty sure of himself. What should I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's got to be a better line of attack than this. That's what I should be looking for now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, you saw a waitress take the coffee over to the victim. But what matters is whether that waitress was Maggey Byrde or not.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Quite right. Mr. Kudo. These other "features" that you recognize about the defendant... I would ask you to add them to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Sure, sure.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"There was a ribbon in her hair, and her apron's straps were loose."</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">There was a ribbon in her hair, and her apron's straps were loose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You do seem to remember several details about her appearance. But what about the most crucial detail of all... her face?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Kah! As if I wouldn't remember that!</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">The witness noticed the straps on the accused's apron. He'd unlikely to make a mistake about her face.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">That's right! I can even tell you the color of the ribbon in her hair. It was red!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">So you see, there's nothing wrong with the witness's eyesight.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's no doubt he remembers the waitress pretty well. What should I do? I get the feeling there's something more to this somehow...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No, I must be imagining it. I need to find another angle with this guy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Kudo. You seem especially interested in straps. Why is that?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The ribbon in her hair, the straps on her apron. What's the fascination?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">F-Fascination?</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">People have all kinds of fetishes, Trite. We don't need to embarrass the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Listen, you young upstarts! I haven't got some sick strap fetish!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Is there any relevance to the witness's unusual love of straps, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was just curious as to why he was so fixated on the waitress's straps...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">I said I haven't got a strap fetish! How many times do I have to repeat myself!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Continue with your testimony, Mr. Kudo. And make it strapless.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">*grumble grumble*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The identifying "features" you described are all things you would see from the back.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">So what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is it possible that... ...you never saw the waitress from the front at all!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! He's got you there, gramps!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">People normally talk about facial features when they're asked to describe someone. But this witness's testimony is nothing but straps and ribbons!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Th-This is harassment! I tell you I'm not obsessed with straps or ribbons! I'm just telling you what I saw!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Kudo, the court requests that you add details about any identifying features... Features you observed from the front, that is, to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Sure, sure.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The old man's testimony is getting longer and longer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And if I can't find a hole in it soon, it'll get even longer, I bet.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">There wasn't anything that caught my interest about her when I saw her from the front.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You didn't find anything to be distinct, but you did clearly see the witness's face, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">No question about it! I didn't come this far to back down now! Victor Kudo never backs down!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's not the answer I was looking for, but OK...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">This has turned into a matter of pride for Old Seedy now, I guess... I wonder if he really did see Maggey's face or not...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Like I thought, we need some concrete proof of this. Proof that the old guy didn't see the waitress clearly from the front.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you think Old Seedy really saw Maggey do it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, he probably had his eye on the waitress the whole time. That's why he was there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But he was there for the cute outfits, right? Not the waitress...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I guess... <thought>Hmm, she makes a good point though...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Did I just say something clever?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder if the waitress Mr. Kudo saw really was Maggey...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's what we have to figure out, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Kudo. I would like you to please take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Kah! That filthy thing would suit filth like you just perfectly. Actually, it reminds me of what my grandson looks like, just after he's done eating.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you ever seen this before?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Of course I haven't! Do you think I'd forget something as dirty as that!? Hmm? Well? You half-witted clot!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Wh-What!? What is it!? Ever since I said, "you half-witted clot", there's been an eerie silence in here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Kudo. This apron... ...is the apron worn by the defendant on the day of the poisoning!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Uh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And as you just said yourself... ...you wouldn't forget something like this. Which means, is you had really seen this apron before...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Er...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, you know what I'm getting at! You couldn't have possibly seen the waitress from the front!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">... Oops!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! You can't just "oops" your way out of this!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Well, well... Looks like we finally have a genuine trial on our hands.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Listen, Trite. Here are the facts. On the day of the incident, there was only one waitress in the restaurant.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That being the defendant, Ms. Maggey Byrde?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Exactly. And when that one waitress put the poison into the coffee cup... ...this old guy was watching!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I hope you understand the gravity of the situation, Mr. Kudo. The fate of the defendant may rest on what you say you remember seeing.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Just tell the court exactly what you saw, gramps.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">You can rely on me, Captain! My noggin's in perfect working order. I can't remember a single occasion when I forgot what burger a customer wanted!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He can't remember? Probably more like he messes up so many times, he's blocking it out...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Let's test just how good your memory and attention to detail is, Mr. Kudo. Tell us what you remember about the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">He was another of those pesky young types, wearing a broken pair of spectacles.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The testimony we have just heard was to test how credible the witness's memory is. It seems to me that he remembers the victim in a great deal of detail.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Oh, yes! I hate those you-know-what types who are so vague about everything!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">How are we going to handle this, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We only need to do one thing. We just need to prove that the old man's memory is shot.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Just trip him up, you mean? Isn't that kind of cruel?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I suppose... But it's what I do best.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">He was another of those pesky young types, wearing a broken pair of spectacles.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Spectacles?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Dark glasses to you! One of the lenses was green, but the other was broken. Newfangled rubbish! That's why I remember him so well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He did have some kind of lens over his left eye... But I wouldn't have called it a pair of glasses.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... He seems to have been wearing some rather modern-looking shades. Perhaps I should take to wearing some, and rival Mr. Godot's sharp appearance.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! We better come up with something sharp, and quick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess I'll wait and see if I should challenge him about the "spectacles"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">He had a newspaper in his right hand, and the noisy brat kept rustling its pages!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The newspaper was a sports paper, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">That young hooligan! I nearly asked him, "Can't you even read without fidgeting, hmm!?" How was I supposed to be able to read the back page with all that rustling going on!? I needed to find out if Gusten Brawn retained his championship title!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It was his paper, not yours! If you wanted to know so bad, why didn't you buy your own!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">What are looking at me like that for, hmm!? How dare you judge me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ow! Ooow!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Gusten Brawn got beaten yesterday, by the way. Anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">The young man was listening to the wireless. I remember that well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The wireless?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">The decadent young rascal! In my day, it was one or the other! Read the paper, or listen to the wireless!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Oh boy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">And using an earpiece! It's selfish, that's what it is! I was straining my ears, but I couldn't catch any of it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Was he that desperate to listen to the radio...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">What are looking at me like that for, hmm!? How dare you feel sorry for me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ow! Oooow!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Then the serving girl in question brought over the javaccino.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean the waitress, who you only saw from behind, right?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">You're one of those, are you? You never let anything go, isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Maybe.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">What does it matter if I saw her from the front or from behind!? My eyes don't lie!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ow! Oooow! <thought>I better not push it until I've got some hard evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">The little fidget picked up the cup with his free hand and took a sip.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"His free hand"?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which hand was that?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Weren't you listening before, cloth-ears!? I said he was rustling the newspaper with his right hand, didn't I? If his free hand wasn't his right hand, then which hand was it, you moron!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ow! Oooow!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Perhaps the great Mr. Trite has three hands!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeesh! I was only asking! No need to gang up on me and treat me like a freak!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The whole point of this cross-examination is to establish just one thing... That this old guy's memory has more holes than a slice of Swiss.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess we just need to find a contradiction in his testimony somewhere, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Anything will do. Even the smallest detail. We just need one mistake, and he's ours!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Kudo. Do you remember what you were told at the start of testimony? That this was a way of testing the credibility of your memory?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">I know, I know! There's nothing wrong with my memory, I tell you! Nothing! If I got anything wrong, I'll eat these seeds and sing the pigeon song!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Care to tell us where this is going, Trite?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to Mr. Kudo, the victim was holding the paper in his right hand... ...while drinking coffee with his free hand, which would make that his left.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Kah! What is this? Kindergarten?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I would like the court to please take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's the cup victim used, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, and on the rim, you'll notice the mark left by the victim's lips.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes. There is a stain left by the coffee.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you consider where that stain is, you'll clearly see... ...that the victim was holding the cup in his right hand!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">But how...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Mr. Kudo. The court is waiting for your epic performance! You said you'd eat those seeds and sing the pigeon song!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Aaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Kudo... I'm afraid this is simply not acceptable. I think the witness had better go back to the park where he came from.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">WAAAAIT! If you think I'm going to stand here and listen to you tell me I'm mad, you're wrong! I don't care about that dirty coffee cup! I know what I saw!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-You still insist on your testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">That young brat was holding the cup in his left hand! Oh, yes. No question! I'm a good, law-abiding citizen, I am. It's that dead young hotbot and you, you spikey-haired yahoo, who are at fault!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who, me!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-Thank you, old man. We've heard quite enough from you already.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Don't call me "old man", old man! Been around for 68 years, I have. You can't ignore me! LISTEN TO WHAT I'VE GOT TO SAAAAY!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sorry, Mr. Kudo, but...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Sure, why not hear a little more?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Godot!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">But this is my 16th cup of coffee... So this is your final stand.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Thank you, Captain! You can rely on Victor!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">The boy was wearing the earpiece on the same side as the green lens of his specs.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We know that the victim was wearing an unusual monocle over his left eye.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">It wasn't a monocle, Your Honor. It was a small computer monitor often used by programmers.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A monitor? You mean, like a television screen!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">The inside of the lens is a screen that displays computer data. It's called an HMD. It's a common tool in the victim's line of work.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">HDTV, DVD, CD... All these newfangled letters drive me mad! But they don't matter. I know what I saw, and I'm telling the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's true... He doesn't seem to be lying.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">And those are the facts, in good old black and white!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">The boy was wearing the earpiece on the same side as the green lens of his specs.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the victim was wearing an HMD.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">HDTV, CD, DVD... What does it matter!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It was none of them actually, but anyway...</thought> And you're sure that he was wearing the earpiece on the same side?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">No question! I could only see that side of his head from where I was sitting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah. That's pretty obvious if you look at the floor plans. From the opposite table, he'd only have a view of the side of the victim's head.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">He kept fiddling with it all the time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seems you kept an eye on Mr. Glen Elg.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">He was getting on my nerves! Rustling that newspaper and fiddling with his earpiece all the time! And then he went and made all that fuss dying from one sip of javaccino! I wanted to say to him, "Calm down, you young brat!" Just looking at him made me suddenly speed up my seed eating! I could've chocked!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So I take it the victim was a walking ball of nervous energy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">He was fiddling with it just before he picked up the cup, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The earpiece you mentioned... Which hand did the victim touch it with?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">... You're one of those people! One of those people who uses his left hand to get things out of his right pocket. Or fastens his left cuff with his right hand? And when the tour guide says, "On your right side, you'll see the famous blah-blah"... ...you're the only one who deliberately looks left! Well? Aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No! I didn't mean...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Obviously he used the hand on the same side of his body that the earpiece was in!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ow! Oooow! Ow! <thought>So, if he had the HMD on his left side, then it was his left hand, I guess...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">And then he used the same hand to pick up the cup. His left hand!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You seem very sure of yourself, Mr. Kudo.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">That's because I know what I saw, no matter what tricks you try to play on me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looks like he really did see the guy picking the cup up with his left hand. This is a dead end!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, Nick? What do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think the guy's telling the truth. But even so... Something's not quite right.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then chuck evidence at him until he breaks!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But if he's not lying, there wouldn't be any contradictions in his testimony, right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure what the relevance of this is, but... Mr. Kudo! There is something very strange about your observations of the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You say he was wearing the earpiece on the same side as the HMD.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">No question! You can lock me up if I'm wrong! It was his left ear, without a doubt! I could only see that side of his head from where I was sitting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think so.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Wh-What did you say!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're no doubt unaware of this fact, Mr. Kudo. But the victim couldn't hear with his left ear! His eardrum was ruptured!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Traces of medication for his condition were found in his ear canal. That's right! It's impossible that the victim was wearing his earpiece in his left ear. Because he couldn't even hear in that ear!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">... Is that true, Captain?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...It is.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">...Pi... Pi-Pi-Pigeon! Hm-hm-hmm... Pretty pigeon! Hm-hm-hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This witness's testimony is completely unreliable! He only saw the witness from behind. And he claims the victim was wearing an earpiece when we know his eardrum was ruptured! Well, Mr. Godot!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Aaaargh! A single drop of milk is all it takes to destroy the pure black magic in the cup! The old man... ...is my drop of milk!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Captain! Are you calling me a drip!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is the victim's coffee cup in which the potassium cyanide was found. The mark on the rim clearly shows that the victim picked it up with his right hand!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">I'll never back down! I know I'm right! The lad drank his javaccino with his left hand!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Let me put you out of your misery... Clearly, the victim used both hands. He took a sip with the cup held in his right hand, and then switched to his left... That's what the old man saw!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Impossible! The witness has already testified on numerous occasions... ...that the victim died immediately after taking just one sip of the coffee.</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Which hand the victim used to pick up his cup is irrelevant, Your Honor. The facts still stand! With one hand or the other, Mr. Elg drank the poisoned coffee... ...Like this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sadly, Mr. Godot, that doesn't wash! The point of this testimony was to establish whether the witness's memory was credible. And the results are clear! The testimony given by this witness is useless!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Puuuurgh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe it is time to conclude today's proceedings. I am satisfied that the witness is not deceiving the court. But to be frank, his testimony is a farce!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">D-Did you have to be so frank!? Take that, you pompous old fogey!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sorry, Mr. Kudo. You can't reach me from there. I'm ordering the defense and the prosecution to investigate this case further. That is all for now. This court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">WAAAAIT! If we stop now, where does that leave me?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Leave you, Mr. Kudo?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Thanks to that blue-suited young upstart over there... ...I'm just a bumbling old man who can't even dot his t's or cross his i's now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How is your bad memory my fault!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sorry, Mr. Kudo, but there's nothing I can do.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">I've kept my mouth shut until now... ...but there's something else the court should know!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's more?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">To be perfectly honest, it might not be anything. But I want another chance! I want another crack at you, you young shark!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Me? <thought>He's looking at me like I'm some sort of evil Shogun...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Well, everyone? What do you say to one final showdown? The final chapter in this eccentric old man's scrapbook!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Sorry, gramps... I've already had my 17th cup of coffee.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">What have you got to lose, Captain? I'll give you all the coffee you want if you come to my house after the trial. I may be 68 years old, but Victor Kudo is still a man!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough, witness. I believe it will be quicker for the court to just hear your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">You bet! Much, much quicker!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can't believe this is happening...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Ha ha ha! You better get ready, youngster!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I get the picture! Just quit throwing those seeds at me, would you!? <thought>He's gotta be using some sort of infinite ammo code with that box of seeds...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">First of all, I want to stress that this might be nothing. I'm not too sure of myself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Um... Is that all?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Yes, that's all. I remember it perfectly. Eh!? You're doubting me again? You're doubting a poor, defenseless old man!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">N-No. We are not doubting you, Mr. Kudo.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't you get the feeling there's a question hanging on everyone's lips, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. "So what?" probably! That's all I can think of, and I have to cross-examine this guy!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">You're a birdbrain, that's why that's all you can think of!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well... Mr. Wright. Your final cross-examination, please.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">First of all, I want to stress that this might be nothing. I'm not too sure of myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... The court generally prefers if witnesses are sure of themselves, Mr. Kudo.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Noisy brat! I'm warning you, I'm more savage than a macho man right now! You won't beat me with this testimony! This is the final battle!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ow! Oooow! <thought>He's chucking those seeds harder than ever! I better be careful...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, Nick! Nail him!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">The young boy slumped over the table as soon as he took one sip of his javaccino...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The court has already heard that testimony, Mr. Kudo...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">I know that! I was just setting the mood. How else am I supposed to build up the suspense, hmm!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The suspense?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Isn't it enough? Should I work the audience a bit more?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, no! Please continue, Mr. Kudo. As quickly as possible!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Alright. Now where was I...? ...Ah yes. The young boy slumped over the table, and...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Well, the clumsy idiot upset the vase. He knocked it right over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A vase, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Yes. There are vases on all the tables in that place. They're accidents waiting to happen! They're practically begging to be knocked over!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, he's right about there being vases. I do remember seeing them, too... There was a vase on the table when I ate munch there.</thought> And you saw the moment when the victim actually knocked over the vase?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Well... it's hard to say... It's a bit unclear... How do you really define...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK, I get it.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">I heard it break! And the sight of it is burned into my memory as clear as day!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">It broke, and the strip of cloth covering the table got completely soaked!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Soaked in water, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Yes. It splashed me on the knee as well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You said you were sitting at a table across the room from the victim, correct? And yet, the water still managed to splash onto you?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">... It was cold! I clearly remember it splashing me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Could the water really make it all the way across to the other side of the room...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Well!? How about that? Turned things upside-down, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean, the vase on the victim's table falling upside-down and breaking?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">The vase turned upside-down, and my testimony's turning this case upside-down... It's a joke! I just wanted everyone to hear it! What do you think, Captain!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...I'm impressed. By your ability to waste time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Godot hasn't raised any objections for a while now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">So, you young show-off! With that scrap of information, I'm throwing down the gauntlet! If I lose this one, I'll take it like a man and admit defeat!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's really giving you the evil eye, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's you he's looking at, Nick, not me! It's like he's saying, "I triple dog dare you to find a contradiction, young'un!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess I'll just have to rise to the challenge then...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Kudo. This is a photograph of the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Hmph! So what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look carefully at the table. The vase is there... intact!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lost your tongue, granddad?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">... I'm no granddad of yours, hop scotch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ow! Oooow!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Enough! If you throw any more seeds in this courtroom, the cleaners will be here all night.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Aaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... What is it now?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">I just remembered something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes...? Go on...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">The broken vase... Ha ha! It was on my table!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Ah, well... You see... It startled me when that young lad collapsed. So I stood up. That must've been when it fell over. The vase on my table, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The vase on your table?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Ah ha ha! Yes, it was on my table! And that's how my groin came to be completely soaked.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*sigh* Thank you, Mr. Kudo. You've certainly earned your kudos for today.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Er, I'd like to ask a question now. Have I, er... Have I been any use at all?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps that's something you should reflect on yourself, Mr. Kudo.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Aaaargh! WAIT! WAIT A MINUTE! If that's the case, there's more! I've got more to say! Oh, yes! I remember something else...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Escort the witness out of the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">WAAAIT! LISTEN TO MEEEEEE!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well! We seem to have been considerably sidetracked. And I am still not in a position to deliver a verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defendant has not been positively identified as the waitress in question. Additionally, there are two disparities in the testimony we have heard thus far.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The mark on the coffee cup that the victim supposedly drank from with his left hand. And the earpiece which was inserted into his left ear, out of which he couldn't hear.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, Nick! You did it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I therefore require both the defense and the prosecution to further investigate the facts.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There is one more thing before I call today's session to an end.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-One more thing, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness we just heard from... He is most insistent that his testimony should be of use. So he's summarized it accordingly into this statement.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... OK...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You may each have a copy of it, if you wish.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Whatever. The prosecution doesn't need props like that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Godot's really mad, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. I would be, too.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Here you are then, Mr. Wright. There are 3 copies. My own, yours, and Mr. Godot's.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"I'm sorry"? This isn't a piece of testimony! More like a five year old's apology...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What the heck are we supposed to do with 3 copies...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is all. This court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't sound very sure, Mr. Wright. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This evidence clearly reveals the contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are the evidence and the statement just now related?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They aren't, are they...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Wright, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness's statement is clearly faulty, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry, but I can see nothing faulty. Unfortunately, I will have to penalize you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh, I must be on the wrong track...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! This court sees no reason to further prolong the trial. Nor is there any need for more time to decide the case against the defendant. This case is extremely clear. I see no room for mis-interpretation of the facts. This court finds the defendant, Maggey Byrde...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accused will surrender to the court immediately... ...to be held pending trial at a higher court within a month from today's date. That is all. This court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>