<xml>
<title>Recipe for Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! This court sees no reason to further prolong the trial. This case is extremely clear. I see no room for misinterpretation of the facts.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The evidence and testimony we have seen and heard are conclusive! The victim was alone at his table when he drank from that poisoned cup of coffee.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Well... I'd say that pretty much wraps this case up, wouldn't you... ...Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court finds the defendant...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court is adjourned.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ahh! The start of the new year always makes me feel like I can take on the whole world!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet it does, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So! I've decided that our resolution should be... Zvarri! "Take on the world!" What do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, whatever, Maya... But I think maybe you've had more than enough mistletoe cake.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Never! You've got to eat a lot of cake during New Year's! It's practically a tradition! Like watching the fireworks on TV or playing a board Game.</line>
<line speaker="???">HEY, PAL!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Happy New Year, Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Uh... likewise... NOW LISTEN UP, WRIGHT! I WANNA...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Here's to another fruitful year of lawyer-police cooperation!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um... Yeah... Me too... ALRIGHT, PAL! YOU'VE GOT SOME EXPLAINING TO...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Have you got a holiday present for me, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A what? Well... I, um... Here, have this. It-It's really nothing much, but...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yay! Thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">LOOK, PAL, WE NEED TO HAVE A TALK. TAKE A SEAT!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! What about Pearly? You haven't forgotten her present, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah... N-No... I mean, yes... I mean, no... Are you doing this on purpose?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ha ha, guess I'm busted. How did you like my first practical joke of the year?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Very funny, pal. Now let's see how funny you think it is when I show you this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it? A magazine?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, I wanna see! "Deadly Poisoning Brings Guilty Verdict. Defense Attorney Wright Trounced."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tr-Trounced!? Let me see that! "The defense attorney gave an almost childishly amateur performance yesterday..." What the heck is this!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's a report, pal. About you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Listen to this! "Mr. Wright must take full responsibility for the ruling in this case."</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">WELL!? And don't tell me you don't remember anything about it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I don't remember anything about it! When was that issue from anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm... December of last year, which I guess makes it last month.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Which makes it old news, you mean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I wasn't involved in a poisoning case in December!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm, so what do you think this is all about, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If it wasn't you, pal, then that leaves only one possibility...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No way. You don't mean...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A pho...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A phony Nick!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This must be Gumshoe's idea of a joke. Guess he's starting off the year with one, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">SO! What are you gonna do about it, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean, what am I going to do about it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, it's your fault that the judge found the defendant guilty in this case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My fault!? How do you figure that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Because THE Phoenix Wright is super famous now! Well, maybe only sort of...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. See what happens when you hotshots start getting too full of yourselves?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But I didn't do anything wrong! ...At least, not that I can remember...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You better make this right, pal. Now! And that means taking the case back to court. Got it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sounds like we've got our first case of the new year! Let's tackle it with gusto!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know... The judge already issued a guilty verdict once in this case. It's not going to be easy to get it overturned.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... I guess that New Year's resolution is going to have to wait until next year.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So you're taking the case, right!? Good! I'm gonna head over to the courthouse then. After that, I'll go back to the precinct. Drop by if you need something, OK pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess people are starting to know the name, "Phoenix Wright". If a client entrusted a case to me based on my reputation... I guess I am kind of responsible. But why would someone want to impersonate me? What sort of a guy would do that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Difficult-looking legal books stand in a formidable row. They mock me. ...Actually, I've neglected them for so long that they're covered in a layer of dust. I guess I should at least pretend to read them once in a while.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Charley. A quite decorative plant. He's sort of a keepsake... something to remember Mia by. Sure, the office is a mess, but I never forget to water this little fella.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's my desk. I don't get to use it much, so it's still super neat and tidy from when Pearls cleaned it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An old movie poster. Apparently, this was the first movie that made Mia cry when she saw it, a long time ago. Maya watched it recently, and said she cried all night, too! ...Which, I guess, is why it's back up on the wall. I have to check it out one of these days.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is a giant building just outside the window. It's the Gatewater Hotel, a high-class, luxury hotel. The chain is getting so rich that they bought a whole chunk of the next town over... ...and started building a huge theme park. It's going to be called "Gatewater Land". ...I wonder if that bellboy is going to send me a greeting card this year, too?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, what's our first move?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess we go down to the detention center and talk--</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait a sec, Nick. This person's behind bars because of you. Whoever it is isn't going to be jumping at the chance to meet you, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, hey! Let's get one thing straight. It wasn't me, it was a fake me that did this!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm, I wonder if he looks exactly like you... Your phony, Xin Eohp, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I hope not. *shudder* ...And what kind of name for an evil double is Xin Eohp anyway!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! Nick! I've got it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you're going to ask whether I've got a twin brother, the answer is no.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Spoilsport.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Did you notice Gumshoe was acting weirder than usual, or was it just me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I mean, he was really worked up. Like a guy who's just found out he's going to be a dad or something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I guess he was acting kind of strange.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe he realized he's got strong feelings for you, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Considering how we interact, I seriously doubt that, Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, if he wasn't nervous because of you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...then maybe it's because of our new guilty client?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So you've still got that badge, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!? Well, I'm a lawyer, aren't I?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, but I guess I just didn't think you'd keep on being one for this long. You have to admit, you've had some close brushes with death because of your job.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I fail to see how being a lawyer is more dangerous than channeling dead people.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can't believe you've got an impersonator.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't either. *sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww, but look on the bright side. Only famous stars have people impersonating them!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This isn't funny, Maya. It's not just an impersonation. This guy stole my identity! And someone may have been wrongly convicted as a result.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Guess you should've gone into showbiz, huh, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...*sigh* I will never understand how your mind works, Maya.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So? How's your spirit medium training going?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well... I stand under the rushing waters of the shower head every day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's called "taking a shower". What happened to the rushing waters of a waterfall?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, I'm kind of taking a break... I'm having a bit of trouble right now, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Last year's incident must still be on her mind... I haven't seen Maya train at all since that time. I think Mia said it's because Maya's at a loss these days...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia helped me out in court again last time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's so cool that you get to meet my sis like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We mediums lose consciousness when we're channeling, so I don't get to see my sis...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I never really thought about it that way. Hey! If you want to meet Mia... ...why don't we just have Pearls call her?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No... I couldn't do that. I'd be too worried about her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess Maya's got all sorts of things to think about, too. ...Despite her immaturity saying otherwise.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So you still can't remember anything about Godot, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I already told you. I have no idea who he is, let alone why he dislikes me so much.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well he sure seems to have a problem with you for some reason. You'd better watch your back, Nick. Coffee lovers can be quite bitter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're just making that up, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Digging up an old case that's already been ruled on... That's not like Gumshoe, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No. He barely manages to stay on top of the cases in front of him.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, he's always busy, and gets dirt pay. I mean, look at that dusty old coat he wears!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Did you mean he "gets paid dirt" or do you really think they pay him in gravel?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know anything about this, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Even someone as worldly-wise as me doesn't know everything about everything, Nick. So I, the great Maya, am sad to say I can't tell you much about this object.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A simple yes or no, Maya... It's not as if you had to give me a dissertation...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know anything about this person?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Even someone as worldly-wise as me doesn't know everything about everyone, Nick. So I, the great Maya, am sad to say I can't tell you much about this individual.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A simple yes or no, Maya... It's not as if you had to give me a dissertation...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's been ages since we came down to the precinct, huh, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like Gumshoe isn't around.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's got it so easy, leaving everyone else to do the work!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, he's been out there somewhere. My bet is on the courthouse. He's probably trying to arrange the retrial of this case.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Guess that means we should go to the detention center and chat with our killer, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">After being convicted without a fair trial, I'm not sure killer is the right label...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Detective">"Don't die running a red light. Die the old-fashioned way -- of old age!" We have a winner! Inject a bit of humor, that's the key.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He must be coming up with slogans for a safety campaign. ...I guess?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These are the detectives' desks. There are computers and files on each one. Funny, they're a lot tidier than I expected. I guess the detectives don't spend a lot of time at their desks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A poster of a female police officer... Wait, no. That's the latest "Babes in Uniform" calendar. My bad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be the chief of the detectives here. He's glued to his computer screen.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">WHAT! Mask☆DeMasque turned up at the bank? What's he doing!? "Hands up, you scalawags!" "You're under arrest!" Hey! That's our job!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like Ron DeLite's opted for a new career.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Detective">Quit surfing the net, Chief!</line>
<line speaker="Chief">S-Sorry... I was just, um...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Things feel pretty tense in here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, that's the police mascot, isn't it? It's so cute!</line>
<line speaker="Chief">That's the "Blue Badger". It was my idea! I made it! And now, it's the national symbol of the police force!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what's with the pink one? It's new, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She's not an "it", Nick. She's a "she", right Chief?</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Yup. Meet the "Pink Badger".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So one's called "Blue", and the other's called "Pink", but they're both called "Badger"?</line>
<line speaker="Chief">You got it! They're both married.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... Mr. &amp; Mrs. Badger seem to be cuffed together, Chief.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">You got it! That's marriage for you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoa... A mascot that's deeper than the deepest of deep oceans...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is so nerve-wracking, waiting to meet our new client. I wonder just what kind of person you tricked and got found guilty...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">K-Keep it down, Maya! That kind of talk could ruin me!</line>
<line speaker="???">Aaaaaaaah! How could you, Mr. Wright!? How could you do this to me!? They put me in solitary! I haven't been able to stop crying.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Aren't... you...</line>
<line speaker="???">Yes, I am! I am totally and utterly let down!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aah! You're... Are you...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maggey Byrde... Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maggey Byrde... She's the policewoman I defended that one time. She was accused of murdering her lover. He was a cop, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you doing in here!? Didn't I get you acquitt--</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Oh, sure! Very funny! After that fifth-rate defense job, you come in here and start making jokes!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You better hurry up and tell her what happened, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">O-Oh... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that's where we stand right now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm sorry you've been caught up in another murder...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">My whole life has been nothing but a whirlwind of bad luck and failures.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I vaguely remember her saying the exact same thing last time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">But I don't mind! What's one more disaster in my life? At least now the real Mr. Wright is here with me. I won't let the world keep me down, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Smile, you're on candid camera.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitors the visitor's room. I bet they don't get too many waitresses in here. He looks like he's getting a bit restless.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, how come you're dressed like that, Maggey? Last year you looked so sharp in that police uniform.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Hmph. I was fired after that... incident last year.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh. I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">It's OK. I don't mind one bit. I enjoyed being on the force, but I think it was time for me to move on.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, what do you do now?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">In the second act of "The Life of Maggey Byrde", I'm playing the role of a waitress.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A waitress!?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yes. In a French restaurant. It's a small place, but it's quite fashionable. My charming smile and shapely figure came through for me. And the owner, Mr. Armstrong, hired me straight away, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And then you got into this mess straight away, right?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yeah, you could put it that way...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">This whole mess started on the 3rd of last month... And it happened at Trés Bien.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Treh Bee-an"...?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yes. It's a restaurant where good service and a friendly smile are always included!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">There were two men at the table, both drinking coffee. And then... One of the men slipped some poison into the victim's cup! The victim took just one sip and was gasping for air! I was so shocked, I passed out.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, hold on there, Maggey.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">What?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You keep calling the guy, "the victim". Didn't you know the guy who was killed?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Not at all! I'd never even seen the guy before!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So she wouldn't have a motive to kill him then, I guess...</thought> And the other man, the killer. You saw him, right?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Of course! A good waitress must be attentive to the clientele.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you saw the killer, but you were found guilty of the crime anyway? How come?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">......... You tell me, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! <thought>Guess the answer to my question is "my phony"... Anyway, she saw the killer. Better see if I can get a description of the guy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, if you saw the murderer, why were you still convicted?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Because no one else saw.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Saw what?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">The other man. The one who put the poison in the victim's coffee. Everyone testified that way. Mr. Armstrong, the customer... Everyone. "The victim was sitting alone at his table the whole time."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But how's that possible?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I don't know. But nobody, not one person, would believe me, sir. Even Phoenix Wright, my one last hope for a fair trial, failed me. What a pathetic defense! My granny could've done a better job!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look! That wasn't me, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">And then! ...They found something a bit incriminating in my apron pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">A small bottle... of poison.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">WHAT!? P-Poison!? It was in your pocket!?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Well, I passed out when the victim collapsed. The killer must've slipped the poison into my pocket when I was unconscious.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And no one else saw this other guy?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">No, sir. That's what everyone said. But I don't see how they could've missed him...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I was the one who took the coffee to the two men.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh...? And what was your impression of them?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Well... When I first saw them, I kind of thought they might be in the music industry.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">In music? How come?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Well, one of them had some sort of earpiece, and an emo musician's look about him. And there was a sample CD on the table, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">An earpiece and a sample CD, huh? Did you get a look at the CD at all?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">It had a band's name written on it. I think it was "MC"-something. They must've been preparing for their debut, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So it was a band's CD. Maybe a promo disc?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe it was "MC Screwdriver"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Get serious, Maya. Would you buy the CD of a group named that?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Nngh... What was the name of that group again...? "MC Hacksaw..."? No... "MC..."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And what about the killer? What did he look like?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Well, I, um... I don't really remember. Only that he was a young man. Well-built like the victim, really.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">That badge! Is it real?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course it's real!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">That's what they all say. But I've been duped before. Give it to me for a sec!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She... She bit into it...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">And I left a few teeth marks, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can see that...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I just wish I could remember if that means it's real or a fake.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*sigh* <thought>I said it was real!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, yeah. I need to ask you about this...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Hey! This article's about my case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you tell me anything about the guy who was pretending to be me?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yes, sir! It was the morning after I'd been arrested... I met you in the visitor's room here. You were wearing one of your super-sharp suits.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yes, you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Maggey! Was my evil double Ayam here, too?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">No. I don't remember a phony you, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh... *sigh* It would've been so cool...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Then you got really worked up and passionate. "I'm gonna get you cleared of this crime!" you said.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK, I get the picture. But you've met me in person before... So how come you didn't realize that guy wasn't the real me?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">... I guess, looking back now, it was a little strange...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Only a little?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Well, OK, so you were a bit taller than normal. And you looked a bit shady. And your voice was a bit weird. Oh, and you had this funny accent. And...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the guy was nothing like me, then!?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">But he had your spiky hair and blue suit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>... Is that all it takes for someone to imitate me...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">How about everyone else in the courtroom, like the judge and the observers...? Didn't they realize he was an imposter?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Everyone had these big question marks on their faces... But it seemed that no one wanted to say anything, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This case just keeps getting weirder and weirder...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Thanks for your help last year!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aw, it was nothing. I'm glad we got you off the hook.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I hope you can help me out this year, too!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, me too. It's be sweet if we could get that verdict overturned.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Oh, Detective Gumshoe! He really looked out for me when I was on the force!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you seen him recently?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">No. He's never been to the restaurant.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Guess he's not a fan of French cuisine, huh? He's an instant noodle type of guy, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yeah, he prefers the simple things in life.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Or he's just simply too poor to afford anything else.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">No matter what happens, I never let anything get me down!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're always so positive, aren't you, Maggey?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Macho Maggey Byrde, they say! The early Byrde catches the worm! A Byrde in the hand!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! All those phrases are named after you?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">And I never turn my back on anything!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're always so strong, aren't you, Maggey?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Macho Maggey Byrde, they say! I'm a tough old Byrde!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Tough old byrde", Nick! Hee hee! Do you get it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, I get it.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I know I used to be on the police force, sir. But I'm incarcerated, now. So I can't use my connections to help you. All I can tell you about now is info about ex-cons or the clientele of Trés Bien, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww, don't let it get you down, Maggey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Probably. The court ruled in the absence of a genuine defense attorney. So we should be able to get a retrial.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Um... Mr. Wright...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Do you think we'll win next time? ...Sir?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">My life has been a full course meal of bad luck, complete with defeat for dessert. Since I was 6 months old, when I fell from the 9th floor of my apartment building... ...I've been hit by all sorts of vehicles, gotten sick from all sorts of foods... ...failed at almost every test I've taken, experienced almost every kind of disaster... I even landed a phony lawyer when I had the misfortune of being accused of murder. But! I will survive! Because Maggey Byrde always lives to fight another day! And one day, I'll find it! Just you wait and see, sir! I'll find that one, single moment of good luck!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Argh, Xin Eohp is really gonna pay for this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What are you staring at me like that for...? <thought>But Maya's right... Whoever it is that thought it was a good idea to use my name... ...and get an innocent girl convicted of murder had better watch out!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">We'll find him! Don't you worry. We'll get Xin Eohp for you!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Thank you! Oh! I'll tell you where Trés Bien is then!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trés... Ah, right. The restaurant where the murder took place.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yes, sir. When you go, please tell Mr. Armstrong I said hi!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sure! Alright, Nick! Let's go check out this restaurant and its food!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Look at this place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Look"? More like "smell"... What is with the suffocating scent of flowers in here...? Then again, girls like that sort of thing, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Actually, I'm not all that into it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... No one's coming to seat us. Maybe there's no one here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't be silly, Maya. This is a restaurant, and it's open for business. HELLO! ANYONE HERE? ... I don't believe it! There really isn't anyone here!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Perfect! Let's get intrusive! If there's no one here, we can take anything we want!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, I suppose we can...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look, it's one of those magical boxes that spits out money.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know, you're the only person who would ever describe a cash register in that way!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look at all the little trinkets tucked away in here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet Mr. Armstrong collected all of these personally. Let's see... A bouquet of flowers, some potpourri, and look! Fine bone china cups!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... I never knew you were so... cultured.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come on, Maya! This is common knowledge! Any Joe Schmoe knows this much!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the restaurant's front entrance. There's a sign hanging on the door written in French. It probably says, "Open" or "Closed". It must be one or the other, but I don't know which since I dunno Jacques about French.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's a rack full of fashion magazines. And they're all in French.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why don't you try wearing something a bit more "chic" something, huh, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. I guess I could. I'm always in my acolyte clothes, aren't I? I'd be fun to wear normal clothes every now and then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm? There's something stuffed in behind the rack.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Looks like a sports paper to me. Hey, and look at this! Someone's scribbled a little doodle on one of the pages. "MC Bomber", and one, two, three, four, five zeros... A-A hundred thousand... dollars... maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder what "MC Bomber" is supposed to be...?&#160;! <thought>This paper! It's from December 3rd...</thought> This paper's from the day of the poisoning!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">WHAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A paper from the day of the murder... This has got to be a clue! I should see if I can find out some more about this paper...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's a rack full of fashion magazines. And they're all in French.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like Mr. Armstrong doesn't get any newspapers.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, it wouldn't exactly suit the feel of the place, would it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why don't you try wearing something a bit more "chic" like in these mags, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. I'd look stunning in some of those Parisian frocks, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We found that sports paper behind this magazine rack earlier... I'd better try to find out everything I can about it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This table's set nicely. It just needs a customer.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you think this flower is, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see... Well, it doesn't look like a tulip, and it's not a sunflower, I don't think...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Duh. Even I could've told you that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, those are the only kinds of flowers I know. Dagnabit, I'm a lawyer, not a botanist!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow! It's a beautiful winter wonderland out there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really!? Cool! I love snow! Let me see! Huh? It's not white. It's not even snowing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got you! I was only kidding, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! There are lies that are OK to tell, and lies that definitely aren't.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...All I did was tell an itty-bitty white lie about nonexistent white snow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This restaurant has partitions that separate the tables. When you're seated at a table, you can only see the tables to your right or left.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be the table where the murder occurred.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess so, with all this police tape all around it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that stain must be from the poisoned coffee. Don't go licking the tablecloth, OK, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why would I lick it? I'm not a cat, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Then why can I picture you doing just that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... "MC Bomber"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And don't forget the "100,000", too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's something about that name, "MC Bomber".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, It's a pretty unusual name.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And don't forget the "100,000", too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Everyone's worried about bombs these days, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure that has any bearing on anything related to this case...)</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Anyway, we should really look into this some more!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is Maggey's second time as a murder suspect, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. The first time was a little over a year ago... She was on the police force back then.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wasn't she working under Gumshoe? That does it, Nick! We're gonna get her off the hook or I'll give up hamburgers!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Oh! A sports paper. Let's see, let's see... Did Gutsen Brawn manage to defend his heavyweight title?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, Maggey. That paper is actually a month old... It's from the day of the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And Gutsen got knocked out yesterday, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Oh, no...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I found this paper in the magazine rack at Trés Bien.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Really? That's strange... Trés Bien doesn't get newspapers. Mr. Armstrong says he's not really fond of them.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then maybe one of the customers left it behind?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anyway, what I want you to take a look at is this scribble here.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Ah-ha! That's it, sir! "MC Bomber"! That was the name that was written on the CD!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just as I thought...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess it wasn't "MC Screwdriver" after all, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">So, that $100,000 must be a down payment for a record deal, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If someone gave me $100,000, I'd sing for sure! "The Master of Kurain" or "The Spirit Song" or even "Maya's Theme"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, OK, Maya... So, if the sample CD was on the victim's table... That means this newspaper may have belonged to the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So the victim left this behind on the day of the murder, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I think we better step up the investigation, don't you Nick?</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh lá lá! Bon-JOUR! Welcome to la Trés Bien!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! Hel... lo... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What happened to Maya? She's frozen stiff...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Bienvenue! Welcome to my petite restauranté!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? "Bee Avenue"?</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, non, my petite chulip!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Me?</line>
<line speaker="???">Look at z'is face! Like la kitten rejected by its own mother. You are fatigued, non? Alors! You need z'is! An aromatic bath oil mélange of la néroli and la rose. My personal recommendation!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You think I need what...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Oui, oui! Just add a couple of drops of z'is mixture to la bath water, and voilá! It will soothe your body and your mind. It's simply fantastique!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really?</line>
<line speaker="???">And for la monsieur!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who? Me?</line>
<line speaker="???">Look at z'at face! Like la puppy rejected by life itself! You are fatigued, non? For you, monsieur, I recommend z'is! Oil of bergamot. And maybe a 'int of... Oui, Oui! I will add la peppermint and la clary sage for a fragrance exceptionnel! Such an invigorating recipe will bring out your delicious beauty, monsieur!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-My beauty!?</line>
<line speaker="???">Alors. If you will be seated, I will bring you la special menu of z'e day!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, we're not here to eat. We're lawyers.</line>
<line speaker="???">Mais bien sûr! I know z'is already, monsieur. You are la Phoenix Wright, non?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, yes... You know me?</line>
<line speaker="???">Mais, oui oui! I never forget a man who flirts wiz me! Especially in court!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess he was cross-examined by our mysterious Xin Eohp...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like everyone to do with this case knows who "I" am already.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder what sort of impression Xin Eohp's been leaving on people, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Allow me to introduce myself to you again. I am Jean Armstrong. Enchanté!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So what does "Trés Bien" mean? I know "trés". That means "three", right?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Non, non, non! "Trés Bien" is Français! In English, you would say, "Very Good".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh. Very good...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui, exactement! La atmosphere is trés bien, and la cuisine is trés bien!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If the food's good, why aren't there any customers in here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">My cuisine is not for all. Some people, z'ey do not appreciate la haute cuisine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I thought everyone liked hot cuisine...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Since I 'ave lost Maggey, I do not 'ave enough 'ands.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you're running this place on your own now?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. For la moment. No one 'as answered my advertisement. Oh, poor moi!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>... Please don't eyeball me while you say that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I am la chef. I am la manager. I am also a trained aromatherapist.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A roaming what?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">A practitioner d'aromatherapy. La art of soothing la soul wiz z'e delicate floral aromas.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Delicate? The smell coming from that bottle earlier was anything but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, could you tell me what you know about the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Bien. It makes me sad to remember it, yet I remember it so well. More z'an a month 'as passed since it 'appened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, I guess it's been about a month since Maggey's sentencing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">So. It was z'e third of last month. Just after one in z'e afternoon. A man who was in 'ere for a coffee suddenly became ill.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because of the poison in his coffee?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Z'at is la truth as I know it. It was Maggey who took 'is drink to 'im. I was in la kitchen. I 'eard z'e sound of someone collapsing. When I came out to see what it was, 'e was already slumped in 'is chair.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He was dead?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mon dieu! Oui! 'E was dead! Maggey 'ad passed out also.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And this man who died... Was he alone?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui, monsieur. All alone. I know z'at Maggey said z'ere was someone else, but...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">La police, z'ey asked me many times. "Are you sure z'ere was no one else at z'e table?" z'ey asked. But I am not z'e only one. La old man said z'e same thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Old man? What old man?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... So who is the old man that you mentioned?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">At z'e time of la murder, z'ere was another customer in 'ere.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? Someone else saw it?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mais, oui! As usual, 'e came alone z'at day. At z'e time of la murder, 'e was 'ere. 'E saw it, too. But 'e said z'e same thing, z'at z'ere was no one else at la victim's table.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But Maggey swears there were two people!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mais, mademoiselle. La lawyer, 'e could not prove z'is, non?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About the lawyer. That was me, I suppose?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mais, bien sûr!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Wow! He's the first person who's said it wasn't me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't kid yourself, Nick! Hmph. Now who's the one making stuff up!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When Maggey took the coffee over to the victim... ...did anything happen?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Ou... Oui. I-I suppose you could say so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Non. It was, er... It was nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look, Maggey says she didn't even know the guy! But she's still been indicted for murder! The prosecution must have come up with some kind of motive!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. It is true.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If there was anything at all between Maggey and the victim, it could be relevant.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So please! Tell us anything you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A Psyche-Lock!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">No way! What are we going to do, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We'll just have to remov... WHAT THE!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Magatama... It's gone!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I had it in my pocket, but... It has vanished into thin air!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">WHAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But I could see the Psyche-Lock. Maybe that means the Magatama's nearby...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maggey wouldn't just have put poison in the coffee of some guy she didn't even know. If she's really guilty, there must have been something between her and the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">N-Non. It was nothing. I am sure. Qué será, será. Perhaps Maggey 'ad another reason.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's Maggey's motive got to do with this chef? Why is he hiding things from me? And another thing... Where did I drop the Magatama? The fact that I can see the lock must mean it's nearby.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I only loaned it to you, you know. So you better find it, Nick! OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...And here I thought it was mine to keep!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Please, monsieur. Z'ere is no need to show me z'at. You are Mon. Phoenix Wright, z'e worst defense lawyer in town.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I can imagine how he formed this completely wrong impression of me...</thought> Um, the last time we met, did I show you this badge?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. You flashed it to everyone in la restaurant!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Looks like Xin Eohp is a bigger fan of flashing stuff than you are, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I am not a lawyer myself. I do not wish to speak out of turn. But your defense in court z'at day was a little, how you say, "lacking", per'aps?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Even a Frenchman who cannot speak any English could 'ave done a better job! You were very cool, though. Oh, oui, oui! So 'andsome.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, I wonder just how bad the defense could've been...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Every time you opened your mouth, z'e 'ole courthouse stirred.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, man. That is something I don't want to imagine...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We found this sports paper in the magazine rack here.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">One of my customers must 'ave left it behind.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you have any idea which customer it was?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Z'e only ideas I 'ave, mademoiselle, I save for my kitchen!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh là, là! You 'ave such a pretty smile, my petite chulip!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Who, me?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. La smile is the most important thing for us girls, n'est-ce pas?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um... Sure!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">If you want a job 'ere, it is yours, precious!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mon dieu! What beauty!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's my sister!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Ah, oui? Another delight! But you 'ave a certain je ne sais quois z'at I do not sense from your sister.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I do?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">So throw your head 'ead 'igh! Thrust out your feminine features! Do not lose 'eart, ma fille! You are a woman! A woman extraordinaire!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do I look like I need cheering up or something?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Maggey was a policewoman once, n'est-ce pas?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. But she had to quit for, um, reasons beyond her control.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui, oui. She was la suspect in la murder investigation, non?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh... You know about that?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Z'at is why I gave to 'er la perfume for la 'appiness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Happiness perfume?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. Blended from bergamot, like I 'ave given to you before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But she's been arrested again. And found guilty this time.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Z'is is true. 'Er natural aroma of un'appiness must 'ave been very strong.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just admit it! Your perfume doesn't work!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I am not surprised she was la prime suspect. After something like z'at took place before my very eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Something like what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's this guy talking about!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Does this mean... Maggey did have a motive?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We've got to ask this guy for more info, stat!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">It is 'ard to imagine, I know, but I was an apprentice for five years in la gay Paris.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! In Paris!?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">It was something la chef z'ere said to me z'at made me decide to open my own restaurant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was it?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Z'at awful man said to me, "You must train for another ten years!" Oh! It was such a shock! So unexpected! But you would 'ave to be a fool to do z'is, non?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, about this...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Félicitations! Mais... qu'est-ce que c'est?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! Um... Je... Je no comprehend...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Don't just make something up!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">... Z'at is a question you will 'ave to ask 'im yourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? "'Im"?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">La old man spends all of 'is time dans la parc.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">La p-parc? Oh, a park? What park's that?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Behind la restaurant. It is called, "Vitamin Square".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Je vous en prie, my dear!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's go check out this Vitamin Square right now, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So this is Vitamin Square.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. I see where they get the name from now. The fruits scream "VITAMINS!" at you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! That's the guy, right? Isn't that the old man Mr. Armstrong was talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That grouchy-looking grandpa?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's throwing seeds out for the pigeons.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, he's not throwing seeds for them, he's throwing seeds AT them!</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... My grumpiness-threat level has just been raised to red...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I used to love sandboxes like you wouldn't believe!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? You?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sure. Finding iron filings in the sand with a magnet was my favorite thing to do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Iron filings? Wow... That's too exciting for words.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It was my ambition to collect every single shred of iron in the sandbox. I was such a kid back then!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, did you manage to get all the iron?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No, I never did. I think I came close, though. Come to think of it, I still have all the iron filings I found way back when. You want them?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This place is so fruity!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's not a bad thing. Besides, I love apples. They're among my favorites.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then that apple slide is perfect for you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... And what is so "perfect" about it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh come on. Don't be a stick in the mud! Slide down it a few times. Go on! Woo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No way! I'd get covered in sand if I slid down that slide. Anyone can see that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, you're right. Otherwise, I'd give it a try, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, look. Pigeons!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. And heaps of them, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Did you know that pigeons are a symbol of peace?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a dove, not a pigeon.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Poor things. Just because they're gray means they can't be symbols of peace and harmony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're over-thinking this one by just a smidge, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh, there's a magazine here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a magazine full of job listings.</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">You disgusting rogue, picking up something someone else threw away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Threw away"? Did you throw this away? Are you looking for a job?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Kah! That's none of your business!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry! I guess I'll take the magazine with me then.</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">I don't want anyone else having it! Give it back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Too bad. Now that you want it so bad, I don't want to give it up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Hey! That's mine!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Looking at this orange reminds me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of what?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That you're supposed to eat a lot of them to ward off colds in the winter. You can't have fun during the holidays if you're sick in bed, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't have to tell me twice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you mind if I had a word with you?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I just want to ask you a couple of questions...</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">What's the matter with you!? Can't you see I'm busy? So you don't like my seeds, eh, pigeons!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's really chucking those seeds at them! That's got to hurt!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Go on! Eat this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, sir. Can I ask you about Maggey Byrde?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">I don't know any Maggey Byrde!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes, you do. Maggey. The waitress at Trés Bien.</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Kah! It's a disgrace, I tell you. An utter disgrace!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A disgrace?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">An innocent young girl revealing herself like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Revealing!? You mean her uniform?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">The youth of today! They don't have any shame! No shame, I tell you! Not one ounce! Whatever happened to the old bushido values of Japan, like honor and modesty?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What about me? I'm not wearing anything revealing.</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">You!? Your problem is you lack any sense of grace!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Talk about hitting a girl where it hurts...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you go to Trés Bien a lot?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Hmph! That miserable excuse for a restaurant? That garbage they serve in there's not food. Where's the sushi? The tempura? The rice!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trés Bien is a French restaurant, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Where do you think we are, boy? In Paris!? I want real food, not those snooty snacks! And what about those shameless girls!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean the waitresses?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">You can see all the way up to their... their... Yes! The waitresses! They're practically naked! It's a disgrace, isn't it? Well, isn't it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Listen, it's not my restaurant.</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Kah! It's a miserable excuse for a restaurant, that place! Miserable!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He certainly knows the place. He must be a regular! But if he hates it so much, why does he keep going?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Are you a regular at that restaurant, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's just, if you dislike it so much, why would you keep going there?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sir?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">There you are, you filthy pigeons! You want food? Ha-ha! <cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Maya">He must be hiding something, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If he is, I should be able to see a Psyche-Lock... Oh, wait... I don't exactly have the Magatama right now, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Remember, Nick. That Magatama is only on loan. You better find it or else!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If Pearls ever gets wind of this, I'm going to be in a world of pain...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, excuse me, sir. Could I just ask you about this...</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">... Hmm, ha-hmm, hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sir?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Here you go, boy! How does some pigeon feed sound to you!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This wasn't exactly what I was hoping to get out of this guy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, Maggey...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Oh, are you looking for some part-time work, Maya? Why don't you take a job at the restaurant? I bet Mr. Armstrong would hire you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? Me?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">It's pretty cool being a waitress, you know. And in the kitchen, you'll get to see all of the chef's greatest secrets!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What secrets...?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">You can't make it obvious, but just spy on him for a bit. You'll see. It's interesting.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! I can't wait to get my apron on now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, he has a pretty intense aroma, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So did Mr. Armstrong really not see the killer...?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Apparently not. Well, he's in the kitchen all the time, so I guess it's possible that he didn't.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Oh, so you met the owner, Mr. Armstrong!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's, um... Oh, how can I put this... pretty unique, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">He has a really intense aura. As a chef and as a person.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, he has a pretty intense aroma, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So did Mr. Armstrong really not see the killer...?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Apparently not. Well, he's in the kitchen all the time, so I guess it's possible that he didn't.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's really tight behind the cash register counter. Can Mr. Armstrong even get in there? And if he got in... could he get out again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a bunch of little trinkets on a shelf by the door. I bet Mr. Armstrong collected all of these personally.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a rack full of fashion magazines. And they're all in French. Ugh. All the clothes in these are absolutely atrocious! ...Some of them have been circled in red. ... I really hope Mr. Armstrong is not thinking of buying those.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Armstrong must be a pretty big neat-freak. He already has this table ready to go. Now if only the food in this place was edible...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks pretty cold out there on the streets. Peaceful, though. It's nice that people can take it easy after the holiday rush.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be the table where the poisoning occurred. The stain tells the story well. The whole area is still cordoned off with police tape. I guess it must still be under investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mademoiselle!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Are you looking for la job?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? N-No, no. I was just...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Let me see. Your style is un peu différent, but you 'ave a good face.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Different?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Félicitations! You 'ave passed! I will 'ire you! Bien! Come wiz me. I will teach you everyz'ing I know!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! HEEEEEELP!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't know whether to laugh or feel bad for Maya... Maybe I should do both...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When I think back to when I was young... ...I wonder what I found so great about playing in a sandbox. Maybe I'll come back here in the middle of the night one of these days to relive it. ... On second thought, being arrested by Gumshoe would be too embarrassing to bear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't see many parks like this anymore. What a great place for kids to play. But that old man's the only one here, chucking his seeds at the pigeons.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The pigeons are so busy pecking at the seeds, they don't notice anything else. Seeing those birds eat with such intense focus... ...reminds me of Maya when she's scarfing down a burger.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is where I found that job listings magazine before. A guy like me carrying around a magazine like that kind of gives the wrong impression. I guess I better give it back to that old man once this investigation's over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, sir. Can I ask you about Maggey Byrde?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">I don't know any Maggey Byrde!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, you do. You know, the waitress at Trés Bien.</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Hmph! If you ask me It's a disgrace! Th-That's what it is! An innocent young girl revealing herself like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you didn't like that kind of thing, then?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">... Wh-What are you trying to say about me, boy!? Explain yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, nothing! I'm not saying anything about you...</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">I know your kind! You young ones with your spiky hair and your fancy suits! That heads of yours is over-flowing with filthy ideas!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I know someone who needs to learn some stress management.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Get out of here, you young brat!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you are a regular at that restaurant, right, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're always complaining about the place, so why do you go there?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sir?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">There you are, you filthy pigeons! You want food? Ha-ha! <cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something's not right about this guy... But If he's hiding something, I should be able to see a Psyche-Lock.</thought> Oh, wait... <thought>I don't exactly have the Magatama right now, huh... I need to find it before I can get anywhere with this old man.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like they have Maggey in questioning. I guess I've asked her pretty much everything... I'll come back if there's anything else I need to ask her later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitors the visitor's room. There's nothing for him to do right now, so he's catching some vertical z's.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Poor Maya. It looks like Mr. Armstrong's really taken a shine to her. I suppose I'll just have to let her work at the restaurant for a while. I'll go pick her up from Trés Bien once things have cooled off.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, pal!? Have you found the evidence yet!? The one that's gonna find her innocent!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, no. Not yet. We've only just started our investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, whatever you need to know, I'll give you the dirt on it. I'm putting off all my other cases for now, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gumshoe's really fired up about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, yeah! One more thing! The retrial's been approved. Court's sitting at 10 AM tomorrow. And Godot's gonna be the prosecutor...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh. ... Him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Now, listen up, pal! If Maggey's found guilty again...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um... I'll... I'll make sure you get locked up good for it, got it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Detective">"Hitting the gas is like hitting the fast-forward button on your life." No. That's too obscure. You don't really get the "you'll die before your time" idea. I need something more direct. Something a bit more light-hearted. Something like, "Hitting the gas is your passport to paradise!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He must be coming up with slogans for a safety campaign. ...I guess?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No matter what, whenever I come here, that mascot's there to greet me.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">You got that right. That's the "Blue Badger". It was my idea! I made it! And now, it's the national symbol of the police force!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what's with the pink one? It's new, right?</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Yup. Meet the "Pink Badger".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So one's called "Blue", and the other's called "Pink", but they're both called "Badger"?</line>
<line speaker="Chief">You got it! They're married.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So should I expect to see Baby Badger next time I'm here...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the guilty party was Maggey Byrde, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Back when she was on the police force... ...you were her mentor when she was a rookie, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, I kept a close eye on her. I-I mean, not too close. You know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...... ......... Hey, what's with the funny looks, pal? I was with her... It wasn't anything like... Look! Sure, I was her boss when she was doing her training. But that was it. Nothing happened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gumshoe sure is sweating up a storm over nothing... ...Ah, so that's it! Our big ol' Gumshoe has a little ol' crush on Maggey!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I... I don't like her or anything! I... I was... Aaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Note to self: Gossip with Maya about this later!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Look, pal! Don't tell anyone, OK!? You've gotta keep it a secret, got it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sure... And would you mind not guessing what I'm thinking all the time?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, tell your face, pal, not me. You'd have to be blind not to see what's on your mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So I was wondering... Could you fill me in on the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Glen Elg, he was a computer programmer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see. A programmer...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He was just a regular Joe working for a small-time computer firm. Maggey never had any contact with the guy before that day. ...And all she did was take him his coffee on the day of the murder, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, Maggey also claimed to have never seen the guy before...</thought> Did the victim go to the restaurant often?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Not according to the chef. Said it was the first time he'd seen the guy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A programmer... and a first-time customer...</thought> What possible reason could Maggey have had to kill a guy like that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's what I thought. But a motive was still somehow established in her trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're kidding! What was her supposed "motive"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry, pal. I'm real busy. I haven't even got enough time to sift through these papers. Look into it yourself, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What could this motive have been...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This isn't really a proper investigation. I'm kind of working on it by myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh, that's right...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The judge already ruled on the case, and all the evidence is in already. The only problem is with Maggey's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... Doesn't sound very good for us, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Look, pal. I've got a mountain of papers on this case to look over before tomorrow. So I'm just gonna say this... Maggey Byrde's no liar. She's... She's... OK, so she's a bit out there, and a bit off base sometimes. But she was a good cop.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's not exactly complimentary, you know!</thought> So what do you think really happened? And just how contradictory is her testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The biggest problem with Maggey's testimony is the number of people at the table.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. My thoughts exactly. Maggey still insists there was another guy sitting with the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Right. But get this... Everyone else in the place says the guy was alone. Even the chef. And then there's that CD...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>CD? Oh, yeah. She did mention something about a CD...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">And there was a sample CD on the table, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But our guys turned that place upside down. There was no CD.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Not on the table. Not anywhere in the whole restaurant, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But didn't Maggey say the victim was wearing an earpiece, too?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, but that was for the portable radio in the front pocket of his hoodie.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A radio? He didn't have a CD player?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You got it. Your phony never explained that contradiction at all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come to think of it... The owner of Trés Bien didn't mention that CD either. I don't know why, but I get the feeling Mr. Armstrong's got something to hide...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what exactly is it that caught your attention about the chef at Trés Bien?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's, um... kind of hard to say... The guy's probably not even connected to the case anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, come on, Detective. Didn't you say you'd give me the dirt on anything?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, this sort of stuff is kinda... unimportant, gossipy stiff, you know pal? Look, how about this? You go to Trés Bien and investigate the place yourself. And if you find out anything suspicious about the guy... you report back to me, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Don't suppose I get a choice in this, huh? <thought>Guess I better find out more about the chef and Trés Bien; then report back to Gumshoe.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Is that thing real, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why does everybody keep asking me that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I wonder what this phony of yours is like...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He had Maggey found guilty of murder. Doesn't that tell you? <thought>I've got to track this creep down!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I wasn't at the trial myself. But I asked this one detective I know how your defense was.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what did he say?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He started off by saying, "I'm at a complete loss for words..." But he must have found some quick because he went on about how bad you were for an hour.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He said you sucked so much, it seemed like you were trying to get Maggey found guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looked like I was "trying to get Maggey found guilty"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What's that? A sports paper?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. I found it in the magazine rack at Trés Bien.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's dated the same day as the murder. You may be onto something here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And take a look at this. See this writing here?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">"MC Bomber"... Hey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I've heard that name somewhere before. Yeah, "MC Bomber"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, he actually seems to be thinking for once!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ack, it's no good. I can't remember...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...And he goes back to being the Gumshoe we all know and love.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal. I'm gonna borrow this paper for a bit, OK? I wanna get a handwriting analysis done on this scribble.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Handwriting, huh? It'd be good to know more about that, in any case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Thanks, pal! I bet this'll turn out to be interesting clue!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! So how come she's not with you today?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She's working down at the restaurant right now.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Working, huh? Yeah, it's tough being broke. I would know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Ok...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Next time I see her, I'll show her how to make the world's best instant noodles. We low earners have to stick together! It's the only way!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Um... Why is he shaking my hand with such enthusiasm...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She cross-examined me once, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? Mia did?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. That was us. The big guns locking horns. Witness versus lawyer! It was a battle of cunning tactics and tricks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But the witness isn't supposed to play any tricks...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't believe she's gone...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's the guy who's gonna be the prosecutor in Maggey's retrial tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh, really?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He was working on a bunch of more important cases at the moment... ...but he canceled them all just so he could take you on, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why's that guy so determined to see me fail?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You sure attract a lot of attention, huh? Too bad it's all the wrong kind.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm such a loser. I had high hopes for Maggey. I was gonna make her the best detective there ever was. But then all the sudden she was charged with murder and arrested. I never saw it coming. I never imagined they'd find her guilty. I hate myself for not being able to do anything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's OK, Detective Gumshoe. We still have a chance to make this right.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... You know what? You're not such a bad guy after all, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you gone to see Maggey?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course I have! But I... I wasn't much good at consoling her. I'm... I'm not very good with words.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. I guess I must've looked a bit down. Maggey was really supportive of me. It was great to have someone to talk to.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Did he go for her, or for himself...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The chef of Trés Bien, huh? You know what that chef said to me? "Oh là là! Your body is full of la toxins." And then he gave me this bottle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's in it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't know. The label says, "Juniper". I'm under orders to put a few drops of it in my bath every day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Under orders?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Yeah. You know, there's something about the lady... I mean, guy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!? You can't stop thinking about him!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Not like that, pal! Gimme a break! He's not my type. I mean, I can't stop thinking that he's involved with this case somehow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like he knows a little something about our charming chef.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you make of this...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry, pal. All I can think about is Maggey at the moment. ... ...... N-No! I didn't mean it like that! I meant...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You don't have to explain... Really...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The scent of flours sure is strong. It's almost making me dizzy... Oh, um... Hello. <thought>Who was that just now? A customer? She had sort of a dark aura about her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Ah! Welcome! Bee avenue!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow. What a cute voice.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, it's just you, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well? How do I look?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Maybe you should quit being a spirit medium...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe. But it's kind of boring being a waitress. I mean, you're my first ever customer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Then who was that woman I just saw?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, oh! Since you're here, you might as well have something to eat!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I am kind of hungry, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, how do you like your new job, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I never knew there was so much for a waitress to do! Take people's orders, bringing them their food, make coffee, work the cash register... Of course, we need a customer before I can do any of that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, it's a nice-looking restaurant. It's a shame more people don't come.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't forget about the ultra cute waitress! Check out my "gimme a tip" smile!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Why don't you order something? The chef's preparing a tasty lunch set at the moment. Or so he says.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How much is it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's the Twin-T set. So it's 20 dollars, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Twin-T set? I believe I'll be taking a pass. It's kind of expensive.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? But you can't! Come on, Nick! It's not every day I get to be a waitress! I want to try carrying plates and working the cash register!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How about cleaning the toilets? That should keep you busy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, right! Maybe later.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! A fine choice, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No. I, um...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">KITCHEN! A LUNCH SPECIAL, PLEASE! WITH ALL THE EXTRAS: DRINK, SIDE SALAD, DESSERT, AND GIFT!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't need any of that!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Just a moment, please, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya's really getting into this! So how much is this set lunch, then? 20 dollars, huh? But with the drink, side salad, and dessert, it's... 45 dollars!?</thought> Hey, wait a sec! Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sorry to keep you waiting, sir! Here you are, our deluxe Fortify lunch set!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A dish inspired by lobster and abalone fricassée with balsamic vinaigrette. Bon appétit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, thanks...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, Nick! Hurry up and try it already!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Lobster, huh? Alright... Down the hatch it goes...</thought> ... Urp!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you hungry, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm starving!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here. It's yours.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really!? ... Urp!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Remember, Maya. My wallet doesn't print money, so you'd better polish off that plate!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... I-I've just remembered! I've got to clean the toilets!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! <thought>You can't be in that much of a hurry to clean the toilets!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How does that guy manage to make good food taste so bad?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick... You want to take a peek at the kitchen?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The kitchen, huh? Not a bad idea.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, now what was it that Maggey said again? "In the kitchen, you'll get to see all of the chef's greatest secrets!"</line>
<line speaker="Maya">In the kitchen? Hmm. That sounds tasty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, wait up! Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What is it? I'm pretty busy right now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Weren't you going to show me around?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Tsk. There goes my plan to find some cool clue and show it off in your face...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better conduct the search in the kitchen myself!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About this...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sorry, Nick! I'm a waitress now. I've got a pile of work waiting for little ol' me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And here it is! The famous Trés Bien kitchen! It's my first time in here too, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... There is a weird atmosphere in here, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mr. Armstrong will be back soon, so we'd better search quickly! Chop, chop!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now THIS is one large mirror! I bet this is where he makes himself look pretty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a book on the dresser. "Claurice Armstrong's Bedtime Literature".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Not exactly Pulitzer Prize material, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like a collection of poems he's written.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Poems? Cool! Read one out! And say it in your best French accent... with intensity! OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK, um... Here's one. Ahem! It's called, "Printemps". "Zee two of zem, like actors from a film. Zee coffee still undrunk. Sweet nothings over too soon, on zat sad Sunday morning. Zee foolish cocktail so delicious. Take zee last sip of your tea and I know what I will do. I must lie to you. I must."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? That's it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup. That's a poem for you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this? It looks like a treasure chest or something.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Look at all these little bottles!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh! They're aromatherapy oils! He's got so many, they're overflowing onto the floor...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's see... 1, 2, 3... ...98, 99, 100! They're all the same, too. Hey, wait a minute...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's one bottle that's different from all the others.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well what do you know. And it doesn't have a label either.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And... *sniff* It doesn't smell.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So what's that liquid inside then, I wonder?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick, we should borrow this. I mean, look how many bottles he's got. He won't miss one, will he?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this? It looks like a treasure chest or something.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Look at all these little bottles!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh! They're aromatherapy oils! He's got so many, they're overflowing onto the floor...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's see... 1, 2, 3... ...98, 99, 100! They're all the same, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are these lace curtains for?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't know. But they give the place a real homey feel, don't they? Hmm... Lace curtains... You know, if I was a cooking pot, I'd be perfectly happy to sit on a shelf under those.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How do you respond to something like that!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now I know for sure I'm in a French restaurant. I've never heard of most of these seasonings. Hey, Nick! This container has... oyster sauce? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Isn't that used in Chinese food...?</thought> Ack! Look! Right there on the counter!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">My Magatama! What's it doing here!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What indeed...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now I know for sure I'm in a French restaurant. I've never heard of most of these seasonings. Hey, Nick! This container has... oyster sauce? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Isn't that used in Chinese food...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">And look at these knives. They look really sharp!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd like to see how one of those slices through a cheesecake.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A cheesecake? You don't exactly need a sharp knife for one of those, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mmm. That smells good. Something's bubbling away nicely in that pot. It must be the lobster and abalone fricassée with balsamic vinaigrette.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't that what I just ate for lunch?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe... What you ate is the only French dish I know the name of.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, you're just in time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The lab got back to me about that newspaper you gave me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He must mean this sports paper with the memo scribbled on it...</thought> So? What did they say? Did the analysis turn up anything?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">They said the doodle was written by the victim, Glen Elg. No doubt about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I expected as much...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The victim took the paper with him to the restaurant on the day of the murder. That's our best interpretation of the facts at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">"MC Bomber"... I get the feeling I've heard that name somewhere before... Oh, well. I guess it'll come back to me. Don't forget to report back to me with whatever you find in the restaurant, OK, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Since when did I start taking orders from Gumshoe...? Although... I get the feeling there's something I need to show him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um... I'll... I'll make sure you get locked up good for it, got it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be the chief of the detectives here. He's glued to his computer screen.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">WHAT!? Poisoned coffee waitress gets a retrial!? I knew it! I knew there was something funny about the taste of this coffee! OK! Who brought me this coffee today? Hands up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeesh! Have a little faith in your subordinates!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Detective">Quit surfing the net, Chief!</line>
<line speaker="Chief">S-Sorry... I was just, um...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Things feel pretty tense in here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what's Mr. Armstrong's secret?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You ever had lunch at Trés Bien, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So, how was it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To put it nicely... it was inedible.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, don't worry about being nice around me, pal. You and I both know the reason that place is so empty is because of the food. I mean, the place is clean, and he's got a girl like Maggey as a waitress, so...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I guess it's probably the food.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The real scoop on the guy is he's up to his ears in debt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? How much does he owe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is a copy of his loan contract. He's about half a million in the red.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Half a million? Are we talking dollars?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. Hey, if it was Sterling, he'd really be in trouble!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry. That figure just took me by surprise.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, this case is full of surprises. And I'd be willing to bet that chef's got something to do with most of them. That's my hunch.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So according to the boys down at the lab, the doodles were probably made by the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Probably?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Analyzing this kind of writing is difficult since it's done with a fiber-tipped pen. But don't worry! I'll vouch for it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why would Gumshoe have to vouch for it? Can't it stand on its own?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You got one of those aroma bottles too, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Only this one doesn't smell.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? I don't get you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This was mixed in with all the other aromatherapy bottles, but it's not the same. It doesn't even look the same, wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A cologne bottle that doesn't smell, huh? Smells like a skunk to me, pal! Mind letting me borrow that bottle for a while? I wanna send it to the lab for analysis.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The victim was poisoned, so the contents of this bottle are pretty important...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I had a lunch there was something funny about that chef.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You suspect Jean Armstrong?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I've got that guy's number. I know what his secret is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That must be the same secret Gumshoe was talking about before.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I guess I'd better fill you in on the details. About this Armstrong guy's secret, I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's for half a million dollars, pal! That's... um... half a million dollar bills!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What was the "um" in there for!?</thought> Is there really that much money tied up in this case?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't give you an answer on that, pal. Not without the case file in front of me. But I'll tell you this... That Armstrong guy would've done anything for cash. He was desperate, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I don't. But I think I sort of get the picture.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, the old guy's not here anymore. <thought>Drat. And I still have some unanswered questions for him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A scooter, huh? Who'd leave it right in the middle of the park like this? The wheel guard and the light are busted... I guess it must have been in an accident. It's totally wrecked.</line>
<line speaker="???">Gwoaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaar! Hey! Whad'youse think youse doin' wit my bike!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No! I was just...</line>
<line speaker="???">Gwoaaaaaaaaaaaar! Youse been messin' with my new ride? Is that what youse been doin'!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-New ride? Isn't that kind of an old model?</line>
<line speaker="???">Gwoar! Youse gonna pay for dis!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It-It wasn't me! I was just passing by.</line>
<line speaker="???">Ey! Den who'z de one tat covered my saddle in crap!? Huh? Gwoar! Youse gonna pay, you' catch my drift!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No! Wait a sec! I'm not a pigeon! So I couldn't have done it!</line>
<line speaker="???">A wise guy, eh? I atta beat you so hard, it'll feel like youse were smoochin' the express train!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh-oh!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Youse better watch your back! This ain't over! I'm gonna round up a group of lawyers and den youse gonna pay!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Actually... I'm a lawyer myself...</line>
<line speaker="???">Whad'youse say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm Phoenix Wright, attorney at law.</line>
<line speaker="???">Gwoaaaaaaaah ha ha ha hah! Ha ha ha ha hah! Phoenix Wright? Youse sayin' YOU' Phoenix Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, yeah... I am.</line>
<line speaker="???">So you' a wiseguy too, huh? Cause I'M Phoenix Wright. The one and only!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAT!?</line>
<line speaker="???">Outta my way! I gotta cruise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>H-He's gone...</thought> Surely that guy wasn't my phony... was he...? ... He wasn't anything like me!! <thought>Guess I better make a note of the scooter...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Kah! Pathetic!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, it's you.</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">A few threats from a little brat like that... ...and you look like a pigeon that's got seeds in its eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you been here the whole time then?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">I was in that strawberry. I had some thinking to do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>More like you had some cowering to do!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you a regular at that restaurant, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's just if you dislike it so much, why would you keep going there?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sir?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">There you are, you filthy pigeons! You want food? Ha-ha! <cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I knew it... This old guy has got something to hide. But what could it be?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why are you a regular at a restaurant that you clearly hate, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Take that, pigeons! See how you like these seeds!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's no good. I'm gonna have to break his Psyche-Lock. I just can't figure out what he would be hiding. I mean, I'm only asking him why he goes to a particular restaurant.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's time you told me the truth. Why are you a regular at a restaurant that you dislike so much?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Isn't it obvious!? People only have one reason to go to restaurants. To eat!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To eat? Is that the whole truth?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Wh-What do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think you go to that restaurant for the food at all.</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">You insolent brat! How dare you accuse me! What proof have you got!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can tell that not you nor anyone else in the world would go to that place for its food.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Take this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh!</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">You're a disgrace! An idiot! A clot! A fool! You're only worthy of this pigeon feed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ow! <thought>Looks like that evidence wasn't it!</thought> L-Listen...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The proof is in the pudding. Or in this case, the lunch menu.</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">That's the Twin-T set!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The food at Trés Bien is terrible. And expensive.</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">You're wrong. It's cheap.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">I'm rich. I inherited money when I was a boy. Yes, I'm stinking rich! I haven't done a jot of work since I was born. Other than feeding the pigeons.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What a load of crock!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Old Man">The taste's another story, but the price... It's nothing to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you're saying that you go there because you've got money to burn?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Exactly! I have so much cash, I go for a swim in my money vault every day!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Unfortunately, that's a lie.</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't have money to burn. You're flat broke!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Disrespectful youth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Take this! The finest seeds money can buy! Ha-ha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ouuuch! <thought>These seeds really hurt when they land in your eyes!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Old Man">I'm rich, I tell you! Never worked in my life! As rich as they come!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't believe you. You're lying to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is yours, right?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">My magazine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why would a rich retiree be looking for a job?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">I-I-I was... Argh! So what!?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">So I was looking for a job! I'm buying a lot at the moment. I need spending money.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">I don't go to that restaurant for food. I just go for the javaccino.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I think you mean a cappuccino. Anyway, how much does a cappuccino cost there?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Eight dollars.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Those had better be some golden beans!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Old Man">What's your problem? You think a poor man would be better off drinking dishwater, do you? Is that it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No. I wasn't thinking that. I was wondering if the coffee there is really that great... </line>
<line speaker="Old Man">No, it's not. But... But anyway! Yes! That place has free newspapers to read every day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Newspapers?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Exactly. They don't want me hanging around at home, so I go there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, sir... But there are no free papers to read at Trés Bien!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">You like seeds, do you, boy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">If you like them so much, then how about them seeds!? Now eat up, boy! You heard me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ow! Oooow! <thought>Well, oww! That was no good... Oww!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Well, boy? How do you like them seeds, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a newspaper I found behind the magazine rack at Trés Bien.</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">So? What of it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This was the only paper there. And it's dated more than one month ago!</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you see what I'm getting at here? That restaurant doesn't get newspapers. This is just one that a customer happened to leave behind!</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Ah... Aaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me, why are you so determined to hide the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">I-I'm not hiding anything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm going to have to put this guy out of his misery.</thought> Listen... The real reason why you go so much to Trés Bien is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Ah ha ha! You're wrong, you're wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh-oh. He's gone silly.</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">You're so stupid! Ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's not the food, it's not the coffee, and it's not the newspapers... What else is there?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Wh-What are you asking me about that girl for?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She was the waitress at Trés Bien.</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Therefore, the answer to the mystery... ...of why an old man would drink expensive coffee at a terrible restaurant... ...is the waitress!</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Argh! B-But I don't recognize that face!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And you are probably telling the truth here. Because you weren't looking at the girl's face... But at her outfit!</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">*gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's the truth, isn't it? You became a regular at the restaurant because of the waitress's uniform! That uniform is all you can think about, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Uh... uh... I-I can't take it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To you, that waitress was your...</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Enough! Please! No more! Stop saying that word! Stop saying, "waitress"! Stop it, stop it, stop it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Sir...</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Yes, it's true! I was there for the young girl. Fine, so I'm a dirty, wicked, sinful old devil!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no... I didn't mean it like that...</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">I even get one of those lousy cups of javaccino every time. For 8 dollars! All because of the serving girl! Punish me! Lock me up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really, that's not what I'm here for.</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">You'll be the same! Another 20 years and you'll understand what it's like! You'll know how painful it is to be an old man like me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, really. Listen, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Stop calling me that! I have a name you know, boy! So show some respect, hmm!? I'm Victor Kudo.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry... Mr. Kudo.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">You young ones think you know it all, don't you? Well, I'm not saying another word! I won't tell you anything more!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This guy was in the restaurant at the time of the incident. Which means I have to hear his testimony, one way or another!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Hmph!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't believe this... I even broke his Psyche-Lock and everything... I guess I'll have to try to get him when he's in a better mood.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Kudo! Please! This is really important.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Hmm, ha-hmm, hmm... Hmm, pi-pi-pigeon, hmm... Kah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ack. He's really giving me the cold shoulder now. But this guy's an important witness. I can't afford to lose his testimony. There must be a way to soften him up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He looks like one of those grouchy old man types.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's OK, though. I don't mind guys like that. But, if he's involved with this case somehow, that's a different story.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... sure.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Here's a tip for you, pal. If you wanna get information out of a guy like that... ...you're gonna have to find his weakness and try to get under his skin.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>His weakness? I wonder what that might be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, it's that old man... Is he still feeding the pigeons?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. He "fed" me as well. I got a bunch of those seeds in my eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh, ouch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Maya. Would you mind coming with me for a while?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Me? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's something I really want to ask that old man.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sure, OK. I'll just get changed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, hang on! Can't you... go like that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... I guess...?</line>
<line speaker="Vitamin Square, after presenting Victor Kudo profile at Trés Bien">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Hmph! You again? ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Hmm... Well, well... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh, Nick. His eyes are burning into me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's OK. I think it's going pretty well.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">... Kah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">You're still just a little child! Run along and play on the slide, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">P-Play on the slide?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! We were so close! Just a little more and he would've spilled...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Hmm, ha-hmm, hmm... Hmm, pi-pi-pigeon, hmm... Kah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How can we crack this guy?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Um, excuse me please, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Quiet! Can't you see I'm feeding... the... pige...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia!?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Well...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">If you don't mind, sir... I'd really love to talk with you.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Yes. Yes, yes. Of course. Certainly. I'm Victor. Victor Kudo.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even from beyond the grave... Wow...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">About the incident...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">You mean, the man who died after drinking the javaccino?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's like he's a different person...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">It was quite a shock! Even for me. He was a strange-looking boy. The girl took the javaccino over to him, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">And... was the customer alone?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Definitely! He was the only person at the table. Then he took one sip of his javaccino, and...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">And?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">And he said something like, "Uaaaargh!" and then collapsed. Dead.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oh, how terrifying!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">You're so good at listening, aren't you? I'll tell you anything. Whatever you want to know! Hee hee hee.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He certainly seems to be telling the truth now. But it looks like Mr. Kudo didn't see this other man, either.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Do you like the food at Trés Bien?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Well, of course! I'm really quite a sophisticated man. I was a young businessman once, you know. I set up a casino in London!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Really? How interesting!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Eating the food at that restaurant really takes me back to my days in France.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What a lovely story.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>London's in England, not France!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Oh, yes! France is wonderful. I'd love to show you around the city some time! It-It's too much! I can't take it! I want... France!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't believe Mia's laughing at the guy... *sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You visit Trés Bien a lot, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Of course! I mean, yes. I'd like to come and see you there. Heh heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Really? Oh, you're so flattering! The owner would be delighted to welcome you, I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Be careful of that chef, my dear!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The chef? You mean Mr. Armstrong?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">That's right. The man's an ex-con.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He... He's an ex-con!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Whatever did Mr. Armstrong do!?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Oh, no! Those eyes! I can't take this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mia's really got this guy eating out of her hand...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">He steals things. From his customers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">From his customers?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Gloves, handkerchiefs... Little things, mainly. He's a pilferer! So you be careful around him, my dear.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Are you sure about this?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Of course! He was arrested for it once. I was there when it happened, having my javaccino.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He really is a regular!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Let me write you a little haiku about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A haiku?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">A Japanese poem. It'll explain all you need to know about that chef.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">If he takes anything again, you let me know! If it's not too expensive, I'll buy you a replacement!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor guy. He couldn't do enough for Mia.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">OK, Phoenix. That's about as much as I can do to help.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Mia. We got some really important information thanks to you.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Honestly! I can't believe Maya called me for something like this!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You're looking upbeat, as usual.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And you're looking tired as usual, Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. That's life, huh? One guy's got it all, and one guy's got squat.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is it just me or did the room get darker all of a sudden...? You know, Detective. This is the year of the, um... gum!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-It is?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. ...I think.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Gum, huh? This is gonna be a great year for this ol' Gumshoe then, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look at that. He perked up in no time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya... Don't mess with him like that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess it's about time to wrap up today's investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Had enough of being a waitress?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. Plus, no one came to the restaurant...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh lá lá! Mademoiselle Maya! Non! 'Ow can you leave like z'is!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-I'm sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That reminds me. Mr. Armstrong had a Psyche-Lock or three, didn't he? I'm going to have to break those...</thought> Mr. Armstrong. I hope you won't mind, but I'd like to have another word with you...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Volontiers! Of course!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When Maggey took the coffee over to the victim... ...did anything happen?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">M-Monsieur... I cannot...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maggey wouldn't just have put poison in the coffee of some guy she didn't even know. If she's really guilty, there must have been something between her and the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">N-Non. It was nothing. I am sure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Somehow... I've gotta get this guy to spill the beans on everything he knows.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh lá lá! You are looking for la job also?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui, oui. Your looks are un peu, unusual, shall we say? But I love your style!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I look "unusual"?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">It will suit you perfectly, la uniform of la waitress!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I just knew it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh lá lá! So you 'ave eaten my lunch, oui? Tell me, monsieur. Did you enjoy la lunch I prepared for you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was a... unique and... wild mixture of flavors.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That was the first time I ever had lobster, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Lobster? Z'ere was no lobster in my lunch...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? But, it said, "lobster" right on the menu.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mademoiselle Maya. Please, you must read la menu more carefully. It says, "A dish inspired by lobster and abalone fricassée with a balsamic vinaigrette.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh. It's only inspired, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. Inspired by z'ese ingredients, but not per'aps made from z'em, n'est-ce pas?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, guess that's the way the cookie crumbles, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The way the lunch tasted, it's probably 99% perspiration and 1% inspiration.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Pardon, pardon. W'izout my reading glasses, I cannot see z'is. I do not read English well.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's not even looking at it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We better find a way to make him look, then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mademoiselle Maya! 'Ow are you finding my restaurant?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I think I've got the hang of it now... But I think it's time for me to...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh lá lá, non! You are quitting already? It will be a new record for z'e shortest period of employment ever!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Ah, la dead man. 'E was la first in my restaurant.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No way! You mean, the first customer you ever had!?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Non, non, non. It was z'e first time I've 'ad a dead man in my restaurant. Such a s'ame to lose a customer after only 'is first meal 'ere!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Ah, z'is old man. 'E is a regular 'ere. My specialty of cappuccino and cold water is one of 'is favorites.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was he here at the time of the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. 'E was 'ere. I am sure of it. When la incident 'appened, z'e old man was 'ere.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Wh-What is 'appening? I do not like zis 'orrible feeling.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have to know the truth. What happened that day?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">... Alors, alors! I will confess everything! Just don't 'urt me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? <thought>Well that was a new record!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">It was a lottery ticket.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A lottery ticket?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">La man who died 'ere 'ad a lottery ticket. For 'alf a million dollars!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-HALF A MILLION!?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. But after la incident, z'is ticket... It disappeared!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The ticket disappeared...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Z'is was la motive z'at la prosecution gave for Maggey. Z'ey said z'at she poisoned the man to get ze 'alf a million dollar lottery ticket.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why didn't you tell me about this sooner?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mais, alors...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've been trying to hide this information about the lottery ticket from me. And I want to know the reason why!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Non, monsieur! You doubt me? But I 'ave confessed to you everything I know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Armstrong. The half a million dollar lottery ticket... I think I know who took it. I think the winning ticket was stolen by this person.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well? How about it?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Ça va?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">It means, "'Ow are you?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh. Um... I'm fine, thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Bien. I am 'appy to 'ear it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Doesn't sound like I'm doing so fine with this Psyche-Lock though...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Poor Maggey, she was tempted by la evil, non?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No! If it was really Maggey, then you'd have no reason to hide the facts from me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Armstrong! I believe there is a very high probability that it was you.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow! That is one piercing scream, even for a man like him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mais pourquoi moi!? Why!? You 'ave no evidence! I am not Mask☆DeMasque! I'm not z'e kind of person who steals z'e property of others.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry to disappoint you, Mr. Armstrong, but I have evidence to the contrary. I present to you, proof that you have stolen from others in the past!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. Per'aps duck would be nice. A terrine, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I was just thinking about my lunch menu. Terrine de canard. What do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That sounds lovely...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Alors, Au revoir, monsieur. I must go to buy la ingredients.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess my evidence is a bit of a lame duck...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">What is z'is!? A poem? Oh, monsieur, you know me so well! I adore poems!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please, read it. And put some feeling into it.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">"Convicted before, a wicked man... or woman, repeat offender"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry to have to bring it up, Mr. Armstrong... ...but you have been arrested for stealing from your customers before, haven't you?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mon dieu! Le mensonge! You are z'e liar!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You deny it?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Do not make la false accusations, s'il vous plaît! So do you 'ave any proof? I want to see la incontestable proof that I 'ave ever stolen from one of my customers!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">♪Im~bécile, im~bécile, U ar an im~bécile...♪</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What are you singing?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Just one of my favorite chansons. It is called, "Imbécile". It is French. Come, monsieur. Sing together w'iz me. ♪Im~bécile, im~bécile, U ar an im~bécile...♪</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Armstrong's definitely stolen from his customers before... I just need to find the right evidence to prove it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seems old habits die hard, Mr. Armstrong.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Wh-What is z'at?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is my Magatama. And I found it in your kitchen.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Nooooon!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, that scream just about broke some windows...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui... oui... I-I 'ave a weakness for la little trinkets and la figurines. My 'and, it just slips out. I cannot stop it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've stolen handkerchiefs, gloves, and other things from your customers, right?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui! It is la truth! I am just a timid little girl inside, monsieur. A timid little girl! Besides, z'is time, it was not la small trinket, oui? It was 500,000 dollars! Mais, non! Why would I steal it? I 'ave no need for such money.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really now?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh, monsieur. What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't it true that you're in some pretty serious trouble? And that you are in desperate need of a large amount of cash?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Mr. Armstrong!?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mais, monsieur. It is not I who is in trouble. Is it you, non?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Une petite question...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">It means, "a little question". Together now, w'iz me! Une petite question.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oon put it keschon.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Bravo, monsieur! Oh, you are a dream! Excellent!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We're definitely not on the same page here... let alone book...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Is z'at all...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This restaurant is deep in the red, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You have a loan... to the tune of half a million dollars! That lottery ticket would have wiped out your debts.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Gnnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Mr. Armstrong!? What do you have to say for yourself now!?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Ah... Aaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Armstrong. You said that the victim had a winning lottery ticket for half a million dollars. How did you know he had something like that in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Z'e man... 'E was listening to la radio wi'z 'is earpiece.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, Maggey said something about that, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">La winning number was announced on la news, I think. All of a sudden, 'e exploded! "Yes! 'Alf a million!" 'e shouted.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the ticket?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. 'E 'ad all of 'is tickets spread out on la table. I... I was so desperately in need of money, so I...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Put the poison in his coffee?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Non, non, non, non, non! Oh, non, you naughty man! I simply 'elped myself to one of 'is tickets.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">La victim collapsed, and Maggey passed out. I thought to myself, "Pourquoi pas?" 'E 'ad so many of zem.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, but only one of them was the winning ticket, right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">How could you do that, Mr. Armstrong!? Maggey was arrested because of you!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Non! Z'is is not true!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I did not take it! La ticket for 'alf a million, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But you just told us you did! You said you took a ticket!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mais non, ma fille! It was not...</line>
<line speaker="???">That's enough.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? AAAAAAAAAH! Mr. Godot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What in the heck are you doing here!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Urgh! This is without doubt... the worst coffee I have ever tasted, Mr. Armstrong.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He came in here for coffee!? Does his craving for coffee know no bounds!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Perhaps Mr. Armstrong stole one of the victim's tickets on the day in question.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I am la air'ead, non? Just a pretty little girl who everyone is laughing at.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But, in that case, Maggey shouldn't be the only one under suspicion...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">He had the wrong ticket.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Mr. Armstrong made off with the winning ticket's pretty neighbor.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So... the ticket he took was worthless?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Not quite. He did win something. A dollar.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">You see! I am just a pretty face! W'izout my looks, I 'ave nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... What happened to the winning ticket, then? The one he meant to steal.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Indeed. What did happen to it? I don't like spoiling myself by watching trailers, so... ...we'll just wait and see how the movie turns out tomorrow, won't we?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Voilà! You two! Time to laugh at la pretty little air'ead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like I won't be needing this note anymore.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like we've got a new mystery now. Namely, where did the winning ticket go?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I've got a bad feeling about this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, anyway. We can't let Maggey suffer any longer for this. And certainly not again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think I have enough evidence yet... I should investigate and gather some more clues before I try again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nnrgh! I've made too many mistakes!</thought></line>
</xml>