<xml>
<title>Recipe for Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Byrde">Gooood morning, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Good morning, Maggey!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">So, what do you think is going to happen today, sir? Yesterday's session didn't go so well, and then ended on a giant mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's true... And we still haven't solved a single part of it yet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Are you OK, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Oh, uh... Yeah. Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I saw that! That little flash of doubt in your eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No! That wasn't doubt. That was, umm... determination!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Why don't I believe you...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's nearly time, Maggey. You'd better get going to the defendant's seat.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Roger. Don't let me down, Mr. Wright. I'm counting on you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Detective Gumshoe...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Quit stressing Maggey out! She doesn't need that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-How did you know she was stressed...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I was watching through the doorway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You look like you lost the case already. Show a bit of confidence, will you, pal!? Here, maybe this'll help.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh!? Have you taken up aromatherapy, too?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Not in a million years, pal! Don't tell me that you don't remember this thing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Come to think of it, that doesn't look like one of those aromatherapy bottles...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is the small bottle that turned up in Trés Bien's kitchen a couple of days ago.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Look at all these little bottles!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh! They're aromatherapy oils! He's got so many, they're overflowing onto the floor...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, wait a minute... There's one bottle that's different from all the others.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well what do you know. And it doesn't have a label either.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And... *sniff* It doesn't smell.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We finally got the analysis results back from the lab.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So!? What is it? Is it the poison?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm afraid not, pal. It's... medication.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Medication?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. For ears. Topical use only, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">For ears? You mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. It's the medication Glen Elg was using for his ruptured eardrum!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What was Glen Elg's ear medicine doing in the kitchen...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, what about the unidentified fingerprints? Anything on that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Someone screwed up, so they only had time to analyze the contents of the bottle. Another hour and they might have gotten something on the prints, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... That's going to weaken its impact as a piece of evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OK, pal! This is it! Make sure your defense is impregnable today, got it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Today's trial... I'm gonna expose that guy for what he's done, or my name isn't Phoenix Wright!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Maggey Byrde.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ready and waiting as always, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very good. Then we'll get underway at once. Yesterday we heard the testimony of Mr. Victor Kudo. He claims to have witnessed the defendant putting a powder into the victim's coffee. However, the witness's testimony was plagued with a number of problems.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">The mark on the rim of the cup shows that the victim drank from it with his right hand. But according to the old man's testimony, he picked it up with his left hand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, Mr. Godot. Furthermore, according to the witness's account... ...the victim was listening to the radio with an earpiece in his left ear. Yet, the victim's left eardrum was ruptured, which made him effectively deaf in that ear.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's amazing how many contradictions a single case can have, huh Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Allow me to enlighten you, Your Honor. The world, you see, keeps turning, and we must turn with it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... You've lost me already, Mr. Godot.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Don't let the mysteries of yesterday mystify you today. Only losers think like that. You've got to change with the times! That's one of my rules!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you implying that you've resolved these contradictions? You know the answers to these riddles!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">The old guy wasn't just throwing seed in here. He was throwing us off the scent. And today I'll prove it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Let the first witness take the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">And you are?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh bonjour, everyone! I am Jean Armstrong. z'e owner and 'ead chef of la Trés Bien restaurant. Enchanté!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Forgive me for asking, witness, but... are you a woman?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh lá lá! monsieur! As you can see, I am la pert and perky gentleman, non?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Er... Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">On the day of the incident, you were in Trés Bien's kitchen. Isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">W'iz you monsieur...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">...everything feels right!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, he's totally unfazed! Doesn't anything intimidate this guy...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Your testimony please, witness. Please tell the court what happened that day at Trés Bien.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui! Volontiers!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">When it all 'appened, z'ere were just two customers in my restaurant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A m...m...m... MIRROR!?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui! Un grand mirror! La most enormous mirror!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">And suddenly, the mystery disappears! Like I said, the world keeps turning, so roll with it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That would explain the coffee cup and the earpiece conundrum... The mirror would have made everything appear back to front.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What the heck!? It's way too early in the morning for this to be happening to me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Wright. You may begin your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">When it all 'appened, z'ere were just two customers in my restaurant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And who were the two customers, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mais, of course. La young man who died... ...and la other, not-so-young, man.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... You are referring to yesterday's witness, I presume?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What about the other man Maggey says she saw at the table? Something tells me Mr. Armstrong isn't planning to disclose his existence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">We need some hard evidence first before we can bring him up, don't we...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess I'll just have to try a different approach for the time being.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I remember I was experimenting w'iz some new art deco z'at day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were experimenting with art deco? How come I never heard about that before today?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">You are not familiar w'iz z'e language of interior design, monsieur?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please stay on topic! Now, why didn't you tell the court about this before!?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">But I did. Just a few moments ago!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem! Excuse me, Mr. Armstrong. This "deco" you mentioned... Are you referring to some sort of "decocture"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no! Art deco, it is a style of design! ...Your Honor. He's talking about interior design. Walls, ceilings, carpets, that kind of thing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, yes. Of course. That "deco".</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I was trying to achieve a more "la effeminate" look for my restaurant. I was planning z'e most bold remodeling of la decor.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Like 'aving a large mirror between la tables, for example.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How big of a mirror are we talking about here?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Bof! Something about 4 meters wide and, err... Oui. About 2 meters 'igh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Let's see... If 1 meter is about 1 yard... Holy glass in a frame, that's huge!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I was intending to install it on la ceiling eventually.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The ceiling!? <thought>Was there a mirror on the ceiling!? I don't remember...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mais, non. But I decided not to go through w'iz it in z'e end.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What should I do? Should I ask him more about the mirror or not?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He couldn't lie about such a huge object like that. It must've been there in the restaurant somewhere.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you really had such a large mirror in the restaurant, someone would have noticed it! But there's nothing about a mirror in Mr. Kudo or Maggey Byrde's testimonies!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">B-But...</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">You didn't ask, Trite. You have only yourself to blame for such sloppy work.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">A mirror was delivered to Trés Bien the day before the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Really?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">As Mr. Armstrong testified, he was carrying out some design changes. And as it turned out, he didn't actually use the mirror in the end.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This just doesn't add up. Even if a mirror was delivered to Trés Bien... ...it doesn't prove that it was in the restaurant on the day of the crime.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! If you want to doubt someone, Trite, look in the mirror. I'm sure the person looking back at you will be dubious enough!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So the witness yesterday had seen the victim reflected in a mirror...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui! Per'aps z'at is what la old man was looking at.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Normally, I'd expect people to know the difference between a reflection and a real object.</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">"Normally"? How does normality come into this? That's lame, Trite. Even for you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Are you trying to say that if something isn't normal, it isn't possible? Is that it? Where does that leave the porcu-headed lawyer and the topknot chick over there... and the ungodly cool guy with the mask over here? Well, Trite!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaack! Not the hair!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I do not have a topknot!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Godot is correct. A lack of normality is no basis for discounting an argument.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Bien! Logic 'as won la day!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">La cup, la earpiece, and la glasses... 'E would 'ave seen everyz'ing in reverse, non?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Everything? He would have seen everything in reverse?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick... We should take a sec and think about what Old Seedy said in his testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How did he phrase it again...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kudo">The boy was wearing the earpiece on the same side as the green lens of his specs.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">No question! You can lock me up if I'm wrong! It was his left ear, without a doubt!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">And then he used the same hand to pick up the cup. His left hand!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If he saw everything he described reflected in a mirror... ...then everything he said he saw on the "left" was actually on the "right", huh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And that clears up all the problems with his testimony, I guess... Or does it...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's kinda hard to believe everything's the fault of a mirror, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you think Old Seedy saw everything through a reflection...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If he did, it would explain all the contradictions in his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But that just makes the situation worse for Maggey! There's gotta be something in that old man's testimony! We've just gotta dig deeper!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The coffee cup, the earpiece, and the HMD... Let's think back over Mr. Kudo's testimony for a second, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">The boy was wearing the earpiece on the same side as the green lens of his specs.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">No question! You can lock me up if I'm wrong! It was his left ear, without a doubt!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, to summarize... ...we were told both the HMD and the earpiece were on the victim's left side. Now, if Mr. Kudo saw all that as a reflection in a mirror... ...it means both the HMD and the earpiece were actually on the victim's right side.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Exactement! You see, monsieur. Now z'at you think about it, it is not so 'ard, non?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Unfortunately, that's where we run into a monumental contradiction with the facts! If Mr. Kudo really did see everything in a mirror... ...why is it that the HMD is now on the wrong side of his head!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! ...Mr. Wright is correct! If the witness genuinely observed the victim reflected in a mirror... ...then we would expect the victim's eyepiece to have been over his right eye.</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">...How bitter. Trite, you should have a taste of this bitterness. It'll calm you down in no time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Are we talking about your coffee... or something completely different...?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You don't understand the way the witness thinks.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How he thinks?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You remember this, I presume?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The "I broke the vase... sorry" apology lett-- I mean Mr. Kudo's sworn testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Exactly. The old man has one very grievous habit... other than throwing seeds. The more of an impression something makes, the more muddled his mind makes it. And what's the most striking thing about Mr. Elg?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Clearly, it's the victim's eyepiece.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">And that's my point. The old man strikes again! Mr. Elg's HMD made a big impression on the old man. "I saw the earpiece and those new-fangled spectacles he was wearing! Oh, yes! They were both on his left ear! Do you hear? His left ear!" Ha...! Well, Trite?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk... <thought>That's the worst, but best impression of Kudo ever...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! I really thought he was Old Seedy for a minute there! Godot's good!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Enough! I must agree that yesterday's witness was irresponsibly rash in much of his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Bad luck, Nick. Looks like the "boil" of a contradiction you found is just a "rash".</line>
<line speaker="Godot">A mirror can't be beaten by a handful of seeds, nor can it lie. So... What exactly was the old man looking at? Fill us in, Mr. Armstrong. Go on, tell the court. We're all ears.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. I can explain. Please, if you will look at la plans of la restaurant.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Alors. Is everyone sitting comfortably?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see no problems with the explanation we have just heard. From the table next to the victim's, Mr. Kudo could have seen the victim in the mirror.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">What a naughty little coquette I am, confusing all z'e men like z'is!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Don't worry about it. We can keep up, except for the guy breaking out in a cold sweat over there again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! I hate that guy!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You said you didn't touch anything else apart from the mirror. Are you quite sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Volontiers! Of course!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Mr. Wright. Your cross-examination, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">La mirror, it was in z'e middle of la restaurant, dividing z'e two 'alves.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, run this by me again. The mirror was here, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oui? Really!? Because I know if I were you, I wouldn't have put a mirror there! It would be in the way!</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Look who's talking, Trite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You're obstructing my view, among other things.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, but, but! This is my seat in the courtroom...!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Trés Bien's "charm" is that it gives you the impression that you're the only customer. Temporarily placing a mirror in that spot would hardly be "in the way". Unlike you... Trite.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I tell you, monsieur. la mirror was z'ere, in z'e middle of la restaurant.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Z'ere is only one seat from which you could 'ave seen an image of la victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And where would that be!?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh lá lá! Look 'ow you lean towards me! I always attract z'e younger boys! Maybe I should keep you in suspense a little longer!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Armstrong! Tell the court what you know at once!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I attract z'e older ones, too, you know, 'andsome! Shall I tease you, too!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Nnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I'm already seeing a very hot someone, so I'm afraid you'll be waiting for a long time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I bet she has mocha-cream skin and cappuccino perfume.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Bien. I will tell you... Z'ere was only one seat from which you could 'ave seen...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Z'at was la seat at z'e table next to la victim's. Z'at was where la old man was sitting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So why can you only see the victim from that particular seat?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mais, monsieur. It is obvious, non? If you look at la plans you will understand. La victim would 'ave been reflected in la mirror like so. If you were sitting at la table next to 'im, you would see everything, non?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So that's the seat Old Seedy was sitting in on that day... ...when the poisoning happened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The old man was sitting at the table next to the victim? Why does that seem kinda odd...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! Mr. Kudo's words yesterday strongly contradict Mr. Armstrong's testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is... the letter of apology that was written by Mr. Kudo, is it not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I realize it looks useless, Your Honor, but this is still testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! I guess useless people are only really good at identifying useless things.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What relevance does this scrap of paper have to the trial, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Kudo's testimony is actually very relevant to the question at hand, Your Honor! Because it very clearly contradicts with this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This piece of evidence contradicts with testimony we have heard, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The crime photo...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. This photo clearly shows something that theoretically should not exist!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What on Earth do you mean by that, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">"Should not exist"? Ha... Sounds like you're describing yourself, Trite.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, if the defense would please clarify its statement. What is the something that "should not exist" in this photo?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is what should not be in the picture!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sorry? I'm afraid you've lost me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! I suppose it's up to me to clarify the defense's claim. The something that "shouldn't exist" is clearly...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait, wait, wait! I've change my mind, Your Honor! <thought>The last thing I need right now is a scalding hot coffee shower...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Gather your thoughts, Mr. Wright. In the meantime, the witness will repeat his testimony for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. I would be delighted!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... ...I'm not sure the contradiction... ...is as clear as you would have us believe, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps you should reconsider before you try again, hm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Try again...? <thought>You mean I was wrong?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Gather your thoughts, Mr. Wright. In the meantime, the witness will repeat his testimony for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. I would be delighted!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This piece of evidence contradicts with testimony we have heard, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The crime photo...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. This photo clearly shows something that theoretically should not exist!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What on Earth do you mean by that, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">"Should not exist"? Ha... Sounds like you're describing yourself, Trite.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, if the defense would please clarify its statement. What is the something that "should not exist" in this photo?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think it's pretty obvious that this is what should not be in the picture!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The vase!? What possible connection does that have with this witness's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor... I'm telling you that there should have been no vase on this table. Because it very clearly contradicts with this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... ...I'm not sure the contradiction... ...is as clear as you would have us believe, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps you should reconsider before you try again, hm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Try again...? <thought>You mean I was wrong?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Gather your thoughts, Mr. Wright. In the meantime, the witness will repeat his testimony for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. I would be delighted!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is what should not be in the picture!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sorry? I'm afraid you've lost me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! I suppose it's up to me to clarify the defense's claim. The something that "shouldn't exist" is clearly...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait, wait, wait! I've change my mind, Your Honor! <thought>The last thing I need right now is a scalding hot coffee shower...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Gather your thoughts, Mr. Wright. In the meantime, the witness will repeat his testimony for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. I would be delighted!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">After la terrible incident occurred, I move la mirror so it was not in z'e way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you move the mirror while Mr. Kudo was off calling the police?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. Exactement. I carried it out of la restaurant z'en.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You moved a huge mirror like that all by yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">What can I say? I know 'ow to pick things up, 'andsome!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">G-Godot actually laughed at something!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, given the witness's physique, I suppose it is possible. Did you move anything else from the crime scene, Mr. Armstrong?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I look like z'e obliging type, non?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">But naturally, I did not touch anything else!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I touched nothing except la mirror!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright? Is there something the witness has said that doesn't match the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, there is... I just can't put my finger on what exactly.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Suffering from a case of heartburn, Trite?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh, I 'ave just z'e thing for z'at! An oil with golden myrrh and frankenstaince...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Add a few drops to your coffee, and voila! Enjoy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Focus, Phoenix. Breathe... I need to ignore those two and just find some evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! Mr. Kudo's words yesterday strongly contradict Mr. Armstrong's testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is... the letter of apology that was written by Mr. Kudo, is it not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I realize it looks useless, Your Honor, but this is still testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! I guess useless people are only really good at identifying useless things.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What relevance does this scrap of paper have to the trial, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Kudo's testimony is actually very relevant to the question at hand, Your Honor! Because it very clearly contradicts with this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This piece of evidence contradicts with testimony we have heard, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The crime photo...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. This photo clearly shows something that theoretically should not exist!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What on Earth do you mean by that, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">"Should not exist"? Ha... Sounds like you're describing yourself, Trite.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, if the defense would please clarify its statement. What is the something that "should not exist" in this photo?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is what should not be in the picture!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sorry? I'm afraid you've lost me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! I suppose it's up to me to clarify the defense's claim. The something that "shouldn't exist" is clearly...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait, wait, wait! I've change my mind, Your Honor! <thought>The last thing I need right now is a scalding hot coffee shower...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Gather your thoughts, Mr. Wright. In the meantime, the witness will repeat his testimony for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. I would be delighted!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... ...I'm not sure the contradiction... ...is as clear as you would have us believe, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps you should reconsider before you try again, hm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Try again...? <thought>You mean I was wrong?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Gather your thoughts, Mr. Wright. In the meantime, the witness will repeat his testimony for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. I would be delighted!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This piece of evidence contradicts with testimony we have heard, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The crime photo...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. This photo clearly shows something that theoretically should not exist!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What on Earth do you mean by that, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">"Should not exist"? Ha... Sounds like you're describing yourself, Trite.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, if the defense would please clarify its statement. What is the something that "should not exist" in this photo?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think it's pretty obvious that this is what should not be in the picture!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The vase!? What possible connection does that have with this witness's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor... I'm telling you that there should have been no vase on this table. Because it very clearly contradicts with this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... ...I'm not sure the contradiction... ...is as clear as you would have us believe, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps you should reconsider before you try again, hm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Try again...? <thought>You mean I was wrong?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Gather your thoughts, Mr. Wright. In the meantime, the witness will repeat his testimony for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. I would be delighted!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is what should not be in the picture!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sorry? I'm afraid you've lost me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! I suppose it's up to me to clarify the defense's claim. The something that "shouldn't exist" is clearly...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait, wait, wait! I've change my mind, Your Honor! <thought>The last thing I need right now is a scalding hot coffee shower...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Gather your thoughts, Mr. Wright. In the meantime, the witness will repeat his testimony for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. I would be delighted!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It is pretty strange, though, isn't it? I mean, nobody mentioned anything about a really large mirror. You'd think someone would've, but Maggey didn't, and neither did Old Seedy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then the only logical explanation is... ...that there was no mirror inside Trés Bien that day. <thought>Now I've just got to prove it... Somehow...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is one thing that was clearly demonstrated by yesterday's testimony. Mr. Kudo broke the vase that was on the table where he was sitting. And yet! As the court can see, there is an unbroken vase on the table next to the victim! Why? Because Mr. Kudo was not, in fact, sitting at the table next to the victim at all!</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Don't be an idiot, Trite! That's impossible! That seat's the only one he could've seen the victim's reflection from!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is only one conclusion we can draw from this contradiction. There was no mirror in Trés Bien that day! Your testimony, Mr. Armstrong, is an elaborate lie!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mon dieeeeeeeu!</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Don't try to confuse the court, Trite! Obviously, the witness cleaned up the vase... ...while the police were taking their time getting to the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Unfortunately, Mr. Godot, that doesn't quite work for me. Mr. Armstrong already testified to the contrary. In his own words... "I did not touch anything else" except the mirror!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ur... urgh! ... Gaaaaaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, witness? What do you have to say for yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">*sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I was right! There was no mirror in the restaurant that day!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">In light of this revelation, we return back to the original problem. Why did the victim have an earpiece in an ear in which he couldn't hear?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! You only get one shot in life. There's no turning back. If you want to claim that the mirror wasn't there, Trite... ...then this problem is all yours. How do you explain what the old man saw?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I can answer this, then I'll be that much closer to the truth! I can feel it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Are you going to be OK? Can you really solve this contradiction, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's more than just this one contradiction, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Remember what Maggey told us? "There was another man at the victim's table." And, "there was a sample CD on the victim's table." It all flies in the face of Mr. Kudo's testimony. <thought>And I think I know the reason why nothing in this case is adding up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright? Let's hear your answer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. The reason behind all the contradictions in Mr. Kudo's testimony is simple.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Clearly, Mr. Kudo made a mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Mr. Trite... You're the one who brought up all these contradictions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And...?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">If you're trying to tell us the old man just made a mistake... ...we can wrap up this case right now with a guilty verdict!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How about it, Mr. Wright? Should I just declare your client guilty?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is that the best you can come up with, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm sorry, Your Honor. I was the one who made a mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'll give you one more chance, Mr. Wright. Think carefully before you answer this time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe we're looking at this the wrong way. It was actually the doctor's mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. The doctor got the wrong ear!</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Well, I believe we saw an autopsy report yesterday. One that stated the victim's left eardrum was ruptured, and had medicine in it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm beginning to wonder if it's not your eardrum that's ruptured, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is no time to be playing with people's perceptions, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm sorry, Your Honor. I was the one who made a mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'll give you one more chance, Mr. Wright. Think carefully before you answer this time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This case is riddled with contradictions. Yet, there is one very simple answer that clears them all up.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-And what is that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The incident Mr. Kudo witnessed, and the incident the victim experienced... ...were two completely different events!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes! The "victim" that Mr. Kudo saw wasn't Mr. Glen Elg at all! It was an imposter; a phony pretending to be Mr. Elg! Obviously, unlike the victim, there was nothing wrong with the imposter's left eardrum. That's how he ended up wearing the earpiece in his left ear by mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Phwoooooooh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court! Settle down, or I'll clear the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Quiet, gramps! Why don't you clear out of here, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAT DID YOU SAY!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Trite... Are you saying what Mr. Kudo saw was a set-up?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. Someone pretended to be Glen Elg and acted out the whole coffee poisoning. All for the express purpose of creating a "witness" out of one Mr. Victor Kudo!</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Get real, Trite! Why would anyone want to do that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't it obvious? The thing Mr. Kudo was most insistent about in his testimony was...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">The serving girl brought him a javaccino... But she put something in it! That's the serving girl, right there in the defendant's chair. I remember her well!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-It's so hard to believe, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was one, and only one reason to show Mr. Kudo this fake poisoning! To show Maggey Byrde in the act of poisoning the coffee!</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Are you insinuating that the waitress in the old man's story was a fake as well? It's true that there were no customers in the restaurant at the time, but... ...it's also true that the chef was there! He would have noticed what was happening.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That's right! Well, witness? If your restaurant really was the scene of such theatrics... ...you would have known about it, correct!?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh lá lá... Z'is is most difficult for me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, it's quite simple. All you have to do is testify. You are under oath, after all. Was there, in fact, a phony at Trés Bien that day!? The defense demands that Mr. Armstrong tell the whole truth about what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense's request for additional testimony is accepted. You will accurately explain, in detail, the events in the restaurant that day!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Ou... Oui.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">La victim, Monsieur Elg, 'e came to my restaurant alone.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Just so we're clear, there was no mirror in the restaurant, after all?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Je vous demande pardon! Forgive me, Your Honor! I lied because I wanted z'is mess to be cleared up quickly.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What you have just done is commit perjury, Mr. Armstrong! I will decide how to punish you later.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">O-Oui...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">For now, we will hear your cross-examination, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm.. He took that perjury charge a bit too well. But I'm guessing he'll be more serious trouble after this cross-examination!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">La victim, Monsieur Elg, 'e came to my restaurant alone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was he alone at his table as well?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mais, oui. I saw 'im from la kitchen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yet the defendant, Ms. Byrde, remembers it differently. She swears there was another man at the victim's table.</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Unfortunately for you, Trite... ...yesterday's witness also testified that the victim was alone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You know, seeing you squirm like that reminds me... ...of a certain coffee's bitter-sweet bite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What kind of coffee has he been drinking!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's not coffee, it's love! It's love that's bitter-sweet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hearing Maya say that makes her seem wise all of a sudden...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I remember la old man arrived not long after 'im.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By old man, you mean Victor Kudo, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. 'E comes often for my special coffee.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I drank your coffee once, Mr. Armstrong. It's special, I'll give you that. It's worth a sip just for the experience.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh, you make me so 'appy, monsieur! You are most welcome any time!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I said it was worth one sip, and nothing more.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So old Mr. Kudo arrived at the restaurant around the same time as the victim. Maybe I should ask about his arrival in more detail.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All I need to do is establish that this phony victim really existed. Asking more about the old man is only going to cloud the issue.</thought> I think that's enough about coffee. Please continue with your testimony, Mr. Armstrong.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">You are welcome any time too, Monsieur Wright. I'll brew something special for you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you're saying that not much time elapsed between when the victim and Mr. Kudo arrived?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. Z'at is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But that still leaves the possibility that something happened in that gap of time.</thought> And by your recollection, how much time would you say elapsed?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Let me see... Approximately 2 minutes, I would say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">T-Two minutes!? That's all?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It seems unlikely that anything untoward could have happened in such a short time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Rats! I knew I shouldn't have pursued this line of questioning...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Out of curiosity, about what time was it when Mr. Kudo arrived?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh, no... I cannot remember, monsieur.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I believe we were told by a witness yesterday...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The crime was reported at 2:25 PM by a kind of scary old man, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Does that perhaps jog your memory, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">La incident 'appened about 20 minutes after 'e arrived. So the victim must 'ave arrived between 2:00 PM and 2:10 PM, non?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Just after 2, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Thank you for your 'elp, in jogging my memory, monsieur. You are wonderful!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hah hah hah! I can't sit here all the time and do nothing now, can I!? The time of day will be added to the witness's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui, Monsieur Judge. Everything I do, I do it for you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Merci bien. That's French, isn't it? Hah hah hah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm glad at least one person is in a good mood...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-He's even humming a song to himself...!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I remember la old man arrived not long after 'im, just after 2 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you absolutely sure about the time?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">When I think really 'ard, 1 am sure it was just after 2. Oui. It is la time I stop serving la lunch menu.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Quite right. I always break for lunch when the restaurants are serving their specials. I've been known to wind up a case early just to make it on time! Hah hah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess you should never get between a hungry judge and his lunch...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, would you look at that! It's almost lunchtime already.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Witness! Get on with your testimony, please!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Z'ere were no other customers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So your only customers were Mr. Kudo and the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">How many times do you need to ask the same thing, Trite? You'd never catch me drinking the same blend twice!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You're trying to establish the presence of a "phony victim" in the restaurant. But you're wasting your time. You can't grind bird seed to make coffee, if you catch my drift...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But there's a hole in this testimony somewhere! I'm sure of it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">When 'e got word 'e won la lottery, Mon. Elg became very excited.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you see him?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Non, I was in ze kitchen. But I 'eard 'im. I remember 'im shouting, "Yes! 'Alf a million bucks!"</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Presumably the defendant heard that too, then, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Maggey...? She looked like a poor little frightened dove!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what about Mr. Kudo?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">La old man chocked on some bird seed z'at got stuck in 'is throat.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It seems we now have yet another incident on our hands.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">It was approximately 5 minutes later z'at la poisoning incident occurred.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what were you doing at that point? Without any customers, you must have had time to kill.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I am multi-talented woman, monsieur!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Z'ere is la renowned chef, Jean Armstrong, and la tragic poet, Claurice Armstrong.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">C-C-Claurice...?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. I was writing a poem. An angry tale of a chef in 'alf a million dollars of debt... ...cooking for a man who won 'alf a million dollars on la lottery! It is called, "Pourquoi". It means, "Why". Per'aps I could recite it for la court?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please don't...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Non, z'ere was no time for a phony to do la acting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean you contacted the police as soon as the incident occurred?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I asked la old man to call from la pay phone.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">By your own argument, Trite... ...the purpose of this "phony victim's" performance was so the old man would see it. In other words... ...once the incident occurred, this opportunity would completely disappear.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Bien. It seems la shadow of doubt 'as been lifted, n'est-ce pas?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess Mr. Armstrong is connected to this case, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Absolutely. Someone was impersonating Mr. Elg, and I refuse to believe he was oblivious. He was there the whole time, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But if you're right, wouldn't Maggey have noticed, too?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She fell unconscious when the incident occurred, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! You mean that's when the phony staged his act?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We'll know for sure once I find a hole in this testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm afraid I've finally got you, Mr. Armstrong.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Q-Quoi? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At the time in question, the victim was listening to the radio with his earpiece. The show he was listening to was "Millionaire Radio". Each week, they announce the winning number of a half million dollar lottery ticket.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. Z'at must be la show Mon. Elg was listening to.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can't see any problem with this testimony, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You say the victim arrived at your restaurant after 2 PM, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui, oui. I am sure of it. I remember it perfectly now! I know it was z'at time, because I 'ad just finished serving la lunch menu.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Get to the point, Trite. If you have one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That show is broadcast live at 1:30 PM. And it claims to be "the most thrilling 10 minutes of your life"...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-It's on the air at 1:30!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, supposedly, the victim made some noise when it was announced that he had won. And yet... I don't believe his cry of joy could have occurred after 2 PM! Because the show had already finished more than 30 minutes earlier by that point in time!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Nooooooooon!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This "victim" we've been told about has done nothing but the impossible! Listening to the radio with a ruptured eardrum, catching a show that was already over... There is only one conclusion you can draw from these facts! This "victim" was an imposter, acting out the poisoning 30 minutes after the real murder! Yes, there were two Glen Elgs in Trés Bien that day. The real Glen Elg, now dead, having been poisoned by the real killer... ...and the phony Glen Elg, acting out the events for Mr. Kudo's witness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-It certainly seems that way... I mean, if that wasn't the case, how could you explain the time discrepancy?</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Quite a performance, Trite. You were almost on a roll.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">But sadly, you lack the rock hard foundation of rhythm to build your song!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...What is this? Music Theory 101?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Let's recap. According to your "imaginative" theory, it's now just after 2 PM... The phony Elg is performing a play for the benefit of Mr. Kudo. How do you explain then, where the real Glen Elg is!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't believe I have to spell this out for court! However! At that time, the real Glen Elg was already dead!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's certainly the obvious conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Thank you, Trite. That's exactly what I was hoping you would say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Now, I presume you can prove this theory of yours...? Can you explain where the missing corpse went to!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-The missing corpse...?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">According to the old man's testimony, there was only one other customer there. If that "customer" was the phony Glen Elg... ...then where did the killer hide the body of the real victim!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Naaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The prosecution has a valid point, Mr. Wright. If your theory is to stand up to examination by the court... ...you must provide us with proof by answering the prosecution's question. Where did the killer hide the body?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">No conjecture, Trite. Let's hear some facts for once. Show the court a piece of evidence that proves where the body was hidden!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Evidence!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-What's with the intense pressure in here all of a sudden!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I thought I had him with that contradiction. But he's turned it all around and backed me into a corner instead!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright? The court will now hear the defense's theory and evidence. First, where was the body of the real Mr. Elg concealed?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Clearly, there's no place to hide a body inside Trés Bien. Therefore, the killer must have hauled the body outside!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Nice supposition. But the real question is, "Can you back it up?" Where's the evidence that proves the body was hidden in that location!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Too bad... I don't think you'll ever grasp the real heart of Rock'n'Roll.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He means that your evidence is irrelevant, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, Nick! You've got to think it through! Feel the beat! And then hit him with some heavy metal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>OK, I need to calm down and get my facts straight. What should I do now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I think I need to clear my head...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! I'd say it's already empty, Trite!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm inclined to agree.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Yo también.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's with the Spanish all of a sudden!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's nothing wrong with my logic so far, I'm sure of it! I'll hit them with another piece of evidence and see if that helps...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It'd would [sic] have been too dangerous to take the body outside. Obviously, the body must have been hidden somewhere inside Trés Bien.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Interesting... But where could a body have been hidden inside a restaurant? Perhaps you would care to show the court on these plans, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. The exact location where the body was concealed inside Trés Bien is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The body was hidden here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Nice supposition. But the real question is, "Can you back it up?" Where's the evidence that proves the body was hidden in that location!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Too bad... I don't think you'll ever grasp the real heart of Rock'n'Roll.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He means that your evidence is irrelevant, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, Nick! You've got to think it through! Feel the beat! And then hit him with some heavy metal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>OK, I need to calm down and get my facts straight. What should I do now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I think I need to clear my head...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! I'd say it's already empty, Trite!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm inclined to agree.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Yo también.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's with the Spanish all of a sudden!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's nothing wrong with my logic so far, I'm sure of it! I'll have another go at proving where the body was hidden.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Armstrong! Do you recognize this bottle?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Non! Non, non, non! I 'ave never seen z'at ugly bottle before in my life! I only use la very best bottles, monsieur! Z'e 'ighest quality only for me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Where was that bottle found, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Interestingly enough, Your Honor. it was found in the kitchen of Trés Bien.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Eh? Quoi!? But I only ever use z'ese bottles for my aromatherapy oils.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But this bottle doesn't contain aromatherapy oil, Mr. Armstrong. No, it contains a medication.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What kind of medication?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure everyone remembers, don't they? That Mr. Elg visited an otolaryngological clinic, and was given medication that day!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Y-You can't be serious...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense had the contents of the bottle analyzed, and I have the lab results here! The contents of the bottle match the prescription that was given to Mr. Elg!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Bwooooar!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Glen Elg's murderer hid the body in the restaurant kitchen. At which time, this bottle fell out of the victim's pocket. Mr. Armstrong! When the incident occurred, didn't you say you were in the kitchen?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">M-M-Mon dieu!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, you know about what I'm about to say, It was YOU who hid the victim's body! You did a fine job pretending to defend my client, Maggey Byrde. However! You were setting her up to take the fall behind the poor girl's back!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Nooooooooon!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Order! Order! This is an extraordinary development. Witness! Did you... Did you murder Mr. Glen Elg?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Never! I could not do such an 'orrible thing!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Noooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Godot!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...The bitterness... Every time I get lied to, I always down a mug of coffee. ...That's one of my rules.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Do you have the slightest idea how many cups you've had by now...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Then I like to do the same to the person who lied to me. I like to take them down with my empty cup! Listen up, chef! How about a brand new flavor in your ear, my "h" deficient friend?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Je vous demande pardon! Please, you must 'ear me out! It is a trap! Listen to me! Por favor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yo hablo Español, Mr. Armstrong, and "Por favor" is Spanish.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I'm only going to ask you once. Did you do it?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Non! Non, non! Absolutely non! I simply... I...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Let's hear it. You've got one shot. Right, gramps?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! The court will permit you the chance to make one final statement. If you lie under oath again, Mr. Godot's coffee mug awaits you... As does my gavel!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">O-Oui... It is clear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What do they always say in the movies... "I've got a bad feeling about this..."</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well! Begin your final testimony, Mr. Armstrong!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">It is true, I 'id la body in la kitchen.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You were "forced"? By who!?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I-I cannot say! Or I will be... erased!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's try a different question then. When Mr. Elg died, was he really the only person at his table?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">... Z'ere was... Z'ere was another man.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I knew it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maggey was telling the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You may cross-examine the witness now, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's just one more thing I need to do. I gotta break this guy, and get him to tell us the name of the real killer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">It is true, I 'id la body in la kitchen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you carry the body by yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. I carried 'im. And I carried Maggey, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maggey, too!?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">When she saw la victim collapse, she fainted. I could not leave 'er z'ere.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But why did you hide the bodies?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">A man forced me to do it. I 'ad no choice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What man? Who was he?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Non! Non, I cannot say! I fear for my life!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's really scared...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You'll just have to put the words in his mouth, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, you're right. If he won't tell me, I'll tell him.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But why would you go along with this man?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You have a half a million dollar debt, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">H-Half a million dollars!? Is this true, Mr. Armstrong?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui! Je suis désolé! I was weak, and I borrowed la money!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is Mr. Armstrong's Achilles heel. And that's why you couldn't refuse anything asked of you by this man!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can tell today has worn you out. You have my permission to go home, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. You are tired. Z'is oil is a mild blend of myrtle and lavender...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Don't worry, Trite. We've got this covered.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Covered!? Like I'm going to leave it to you to finish!</thought> Anyway, the point I am trying to make is that Mr. Armstrong has this one, fatal weakness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's end this dance of Ring Around the Rosie, Mr. Armstrong. This is the man that you've been referring to!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Aaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who is that!? I feel like I've seen him somewhere before...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, I don't know... Maybe a month ago in this very courtroom?</thought> This man is Furio Tigre. He's the manager of a loan office called "Tender Lender".</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no point trying to hide the truth anymore, Mr. Armstrong. I know you couldn't go against Mr. Tigre. At least, not while he had this on you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can tell today has worn you out. You have my permission to go home, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. You are tired. Z'is oil is a mild blend of myrtle and lavender...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Don't worry, Trite. We've got this covered.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Covered!? Like I'm going to leave it to you to finish!</thought> Mr. Armstrong! No more games!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I 'ad to go along w'iz 'im because... Z'ere was a reason why I could not refuse.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what reason would that be, Mr. Armstrong?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">You know, monsieur...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Surely you cannot expect a young maiden to talk about such an embarrassment?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A "maiden"!? You're a bit old to get away with that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">And a bit too male!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't finish the cross-examination without establishing his reason. So I'll just have to prove it... with evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You have a half a million dollar debt, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">H-Half a million dollars!? Is this true, Mr. Armstrong?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui! Je suis désolé! I was weak, and I borrowed la money!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is Mr. Armstrong's Achilles heel. And that's why you couldn't refuse anything asked of you by this man!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can tell today has worn you out. You have my permission to go home, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. You are tired. Z'is oil is a mild blend of myrtle and lavender...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Don't worry, Trite. We've got this covered.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Covered!? Like I'm going to leave it to you to finish!</thought> Anyway, the point I am trying to make is that Mr. Armstrong has this one, fatal weakness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's end this dance of Ring Around the Rosie, Mr. Armstrong. This is the man that you've been referring to!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Aaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who is that!? I feel like I've seen him somewhere before...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, I don't know... Maybe a month ago in this very courtroom?</thought> This man is Furio Tigre. He's the manager of a loan office called "Tender Lender".</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no point trying to hide the truth anymore, Mr. Armstrong. I know you couldn't go against Mr. Tigre. At least, not while he had this on you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can tell today has worn you out. You have my permission to go home, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. You are tired. Z'is oil is a mild blend of myrtle and lavender...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Don't worry, Trite. We've got this covered.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Covered!? Like I'm going to leave it to you to finish!</thought> Mr. Armstrong! No more games!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">But I did not kill 'im! I swear it! You must believe me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you are claiming that all you did was hide the bodies? Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui! Z'at's right!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If we are to believe you, Mr. Armstrong, you must tell the court everything! You must make clear the identity of the man who ordered you to do this.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's already confessed this much! He might as well stop dancing around the real issue!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. But he really doesn't want to tell us who the killer is.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then sock it to him, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, that's not a bad idea!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A half million dollar loan from a black-market loan shark. And you had no way of paying it back, did you? That's why you were forced to do anything this man told you.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">... Oui, it is as you say.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mr. Armstrong...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">La Tiger... 'E told me 'e was going to use my restaurant for a business rendez-vous. On la day in question, 'e was meeting la victim to demand z'at 'e repay 'is loan. I don't know why it 'appened like zat! I just did what 'e told me to do. I 'ad no choice! I carried la body and la inconscient Maggey out of la dining area... ...and into z'e kitchen. After z'at, I just tried to forget what I 'ad seen!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think we can now safely say that the man who forced your hand was Mr. Furio Tigre.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I do have one further question for you, Mr. Armstrong. The poison and the lottery ticket were recovered from the defendant's apron pocket. Was that your doing as well?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Non! I knew nothing about z'at! Making it look like it was Maggey who 'ad done it... I was... I was not... It is déspicable!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Godot!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You will summon this Furio Tigre as a witness! I doubt that can be arranged today, so we will adjourn for now. Proceedings will continue tomorrow...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...Thirty minutes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">The trial will go on. I'll see to it myself. I need half an hour to get that guy on the stand. Not a minute more.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-How the...?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Don't sit back and relax yet, Trite! No one knows if that chef is really telling the truth or not. This trial could still go either way.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Your request is granted, Mr. Godot. We will resume once Mr. Tigre is ready to take the stand. Until then... Court is adjourned for a 30 minute recess!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So we're finally going to see The Tiger on the stand! We've almost got this case won now, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wish I could agree.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When I cross-examined Mr. Armstrong just now... ...he said he was just doing what The Tiger told him to do. But Godot picked up on it, remember? He pointed out that without proof, we don't know if what he testified is the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You mean, you think Mr. Armstrong was lying?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know. But if that's the line the prosecution takes, we could be in trouble. <thought>I get the feeling that we don't have the case-making evidence we're going to need.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you so jumpy about, Detective!? Your hair's standing on end!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, that's the pot calling the kettle black, little Ms. Topknot!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's not a topknot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Never mind about the hair! Just calm down, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-I can't stand still when I don't have a job to do! I-I-I kinda get wound up. Aaaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No kidding!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You gotta have something you need me to do, pal! Anything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, um...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, I'm gonna take a jog back down to the precinct. I could get some prints analyzed for you if you've got an hour!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An hour!? The trial will have reconvened by then!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But, Nick! We still don't have a really decisive piece of evidence, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>True. Without some kind of trump card to pull out of the bag, we're really stuck...</thought> You said you could get some fingerprint analysis done in an hour?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You bet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In that case, would you mind checking the prints on this for me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you're going back to the station anyway, could you find out whose prints are on this?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, hey. That's that small bottle I gave back to you this morning, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. I think it's time we solved the last mystery of who the prints on it belongs to.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure thing, pal! Actually, that's been gnawing at me, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you doing, Nick!? If Detective Gumshoe's going to check some prints for us, shouldn't he be checking this?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's that small bottle I gave back to you this morning, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim's ear medication that we found in the kitchen?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look, it even says, "covered in unidentified fingerprints" right in the Court Record!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You're right! Actually, that's been gnawing at me, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So you'll look into it for us? Awesome!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, what about the thing I asked you to run a check on?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, that. Sure, I'll see what I can do if I've got any spare time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Spare time...? I feel so unimportant right now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OK, I'll get this off to the lab right away. Just make sure you don't lose the case before I get back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is pretty much the final showdown, I guess...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's time to separate the phonies from the real guys!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court will now reconvene. Mr. Godot. Did you find this Furio Tigre...?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I even tamed him for you. It was a 3 cup job. No problem.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>T-Tamed him...? The guy's name may be Furio Tigre, but come on...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">He's pretty lively. Be careful... He still bites.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Please show Mr. Tigre to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Um... Witness. Please state your name and occupation for th--</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Grrraaaaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Don't hide under the table Maya! ...Unless there is room for me down there too!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I, uh... Um... W-W-W-Would you mind...</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">What'youse say to me!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">N-N-N-Nothing! I didn't say nuddin'! Honest!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who could've guessed that fear would induce a bad Brooklyn accent in the judge?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I got business to take care of, ya hear me? So who the hell called me into dis hole? Was it you', spikey!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack, no. Of course not... It was... the judge... ... Your Honor!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, dear! I, um... I seem to have dropped my pen. Where on earth is it...? Don't mind me! Just carry on with the proceedings as normal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's it. We're doomed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Maybe youse didn't hear me! I said, who the hell was it dat called me in here!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">There's no need to shout. We can all hear you.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Whad'youse say?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">There's no point struggling. You're caught in a snare. The relentless snare of the law! And I'm the one that hauled you in!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Grrr...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>T... Too cool...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't let him get the better of you, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Let's start with the basics. You know about the incident in question, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Incident!? I don't know nuthin' about no stinkin' incident, mask boy!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You mean you didn't attend the previous trial of Maggey Byrde?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Maggey who!? I've got more important things to do dan watch courtroom dramas!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Of course. Well, perhaps you could give us your testimony, then? Please tell us about what you did on the day of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">...Hmph. Phoenix Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Youse de one who set dis up, didn't you'? Youse gonna regret the day you ruffled The Tiger's fur. You' hear what I'm sayin'?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*gulp* <thought>Maybe I should've brought a diaper with me today...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Get a grip, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I don't know nothin' about no murder.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, at last I found my pen. Very well then, Mr. Wright. Your cross-examination, plea--</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Aaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What is it!? Please, witness, if you could refrain from shouting out like that.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I know de kinda games dat guy in the blue plays! That lowlife ain't no lawyer! He just punches away at stupid details 'til he wins.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">L-Lowlife...? Me?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Listen up, smarty! Every time you' ask me some'ding dat doesn't relate to dis case... ...I'm gonna bill you 50,000 dollars! And youse gonna borrow the cash from me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... <thought>That's one loan contract I refuse to sign!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">And don't think it ain't gonna hurt when you' get tangled with The Tiger!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! I love a good spectator sport.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">J-J-Just a minute! That's really not...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">This witness is... How can I put it? A hungry tiger roaming the urban jungle! Get on his bad side, and he'll bite everyone's heads off. Yours, too!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. I have no choice but to impose a penalty system here.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Youse better be listening. I said I got business to take care of. Big business! If I don't split now, I ain't gonna catch my bus...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will impose a penalty for any irrelevant pressing of witness testimony. Keep that in mind as you begin your cross-examination, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You can do it, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come out from under there already, would you, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I don't know nothin' about no murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't buy that you haven't even heard of the incident that occurred at Trés Bien!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Heh heh. Youse got a big mouth, Wright! Youse tryin' to say I was on some mob hit? Is dat what you' tryin' to say? Where's your proof, then!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... E-Evidence, yes... Well...</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">"For an attorney to make an accusation in court, he must have evidence." That's from "Loan Shark to Lawyer: A Beginner's Guide", yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah! I see you're studious type, Mr. Tigre. Very good.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Why don't you ask him to represent you sometime, Trite?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grrr... What should I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Tigre!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Whad'youse want!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Err... If you wouldn't mind going into a bit more detail...</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">This is a dead end, Trite, and you know it. Remember the rules!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Pressing the witness without evidence to back up your attack is prohibited. As I said earlier, the court will impose a penalty for such behavior!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ouch. The pain...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's too dangerous to press things without knowing where they might end up. I'd better just focus on gathering information at the moment...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Tigre... Would you mind repeating your testimony from the beginning, please?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">My time ain't free, you' hear? Youse betta remember dat! If I miss that bus, someone's gonna pay!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I was tied up with business in December last year. Spent all'a my time in my office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure about that? We're talking about one month ago, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">You' see these teeth!? That's how sharp my secretary is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sharp...? <thought>Is he talking about Viola Cadaverini?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">She writes everything in my scheduler. "December: Mainly in the office." That's what it says, so that's where I was!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That seems like a rather, err... sketchy schedule...</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Gwwrrr...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There he goes again! Hmm... What The Tiger did all December isn't the issue... What's important is what he was doing on the day of the murder... So, now what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Tigre!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Whad'youse want!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Err... If you wouldn't mind going into a bit more detail...</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">This is a dead end, Trite, and you know it. Remember the rules!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No! It's essential that we establish the witness's alibi accurately.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I agree.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim was killed on December 3rd. Were you in the office that day, too?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Maybe youse ain't listening. Of course I was! I never set foot outside. I had meetin's all day with a bunch of cats wantin' to do business wid me. I ain't never seen that young kid before!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I do believe the witness's last statement was important. Um... Mr. Godot, if you could please...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Mr. Tigre. The court asks you to add that last statement to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">...Hmph!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Don't let an animal beat you! Be a man, Your Honor, and ask him yourself!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's too dangerous to press things without knowing where they might end up. I'd better just focus on gathering information at the moment...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Tigre... Would you mind repeating your testimony from the beginning, please?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">My time ain't free, you' hear? Youse betta remember dat! If I miss that bus, someone's gonna pay!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">The day youse talkin' about, I was in de office, too. I never saw that kid before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You didn't know Mr. Glen Elg? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I don't mess with the guppies when there are bigger fish to fry. Whaddya say, boss!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm? Who? Me!?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Howse about I hit you with a fat 200,000 dollars?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, I was thinking about purchasing a nice car from Europe...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's seriously considering this!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, The Tiger's a really good salesman, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. And if I want to sell this case, I need to copy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">How about you hit him with a fat piece of evidence, boss?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wish it was that easy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I got whales lined up to borrow cash from Tender Lender every single day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So I take it you get a lot of customers at your black market loan office?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">It's tough for de little guys these days. Small businesses are feelin' the pinch. Bosses of companies like that wanna get in good with me. I'm deir best friend.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. That's very admirable of you, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Yeah, well. Tender Lender's motto is "Win Through Compromise" ya know.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Win Through Compromise"? What is that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">"Compromise the customer to win." That's what it means. Youse got it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...With "best friends" like you, who needs enemies!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Here, let me spell it out for youse all! You don't pay me back within 3 days, Spikey, I take what's due, and you' stupid hair! Youse follow what I'm saying!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... But I'm not one of your customers... <thought>Should I ask more about Tender Lender or not?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Tigre!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Whad'youse want!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Err... If you wouldn't mind going into a bit more detail...</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">This is a dead end, Trite, and you know it. Remember the rules!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Pressing the witness without evidence to back up your attack is prohibited. As I said earlier, the court will impose a penalty for such behavior!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ouch. The pain...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's too dangerous to press things without knowing where they might end up. I'd better just focus on gathering information at the moment...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Tigre... Would you mind repeating your testimony from the beginning, please?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">My time ain't free, you' hear? Youse betta remember dat! If I miss that bus, someone's gonna pay!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Youse wanna check my alibi, just ask Violetta.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By "Violetta", you're talking about the Cadaverini family's...?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Yeah. You' don't wanna cross them, or youse gonna wind up sleepin' with de fishes. Once the Godfather finds out youse been draggin' Violetta through the mud... ...he'll... do you... in...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Sorry, I... I couldn't quite put it all together towards the end there...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He said that just like Viola, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I get the feeling this might not be the right time to probe him about her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Tigre!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Whad'youse want!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Err... If you wouldn't mind going into a bit more detail...</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">This is a dead end, Trite, and you know it. Remember the rules!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Pressing the witness without evidence to back up your attack is prohibited. As I said earlier, the court will impose a penalty for such behavior!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ouch. The pain...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's too dangerous to press things without knowing where they might end up. I'd better just focus on gathering information at the moment...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Tigre... Would you mind repeating your testimony from the beginning, please?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">My time ain't free, you' hear? Youse betta remember dat! If I miss that bus, someone's gonna pay!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Just think! All you have to do is press him on something irrelevant, and bam! $50,000!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Get real, Maya! How about you pay back the money then. Your allowance should cover it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! I'm no idiot, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I'M certainly not the one who thought the $50,000 was free money!</thought> Anyway, I need to work this guy without pressing his testimony too hard.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But his testimony is pretty solid as it is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I admit nothing jumps out at me as a contradiction. But I've got to find an opening somewhere... Or I need to make one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Tigre... You claim you didn't know Mr. Glen Elg. But it appears that Mr. Elg knew you.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Elg left this little note on his calendar. "Meet with The Tiger"... Dated, December 3rd.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">D-December 3rd!? That's... the day of the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, Mr. Tigre, I submit that you did indeed know one Mr. Glen Elg! Because on the very day of the incident, you met with him!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">... Grrrah ha ha ha hah! Not bad! Youse actually not bad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I was just messin' with youse to see how good you' were.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Did you hear that, Nick? He said you're not bad!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's one compliment I can do without! Plus, he's lying through his teeth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Um, witness. Please remember that you're under oath. Lies will not be tolerated.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Youse callin' me a liar!? Is that what you' doin'!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ruh-roh!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">So you're saying that your claim to have "never seen that kid before" is the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I said I'm dead serious! Youse betta believe that's truth!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Then I'd say that gives me time... to enjoy another cup of pure black magic! That is, while you testify for the court again, Mr. Tigre.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, yes! Um, would you mind indulging the court, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He never actually met the victim!? That's got to be a lie right there! It's time I nailed this guy!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I ain't no liar. I never met Glen Elg.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... That all seems perfectly logical. You had arranged to meet with the victim, but he didn't show up.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I've heard it's pretty hard to keep appointments when you're dead.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. You may begin your cross-examination, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Didn't I tell you I got a big deal goin' down today? I ain't gonna make my bus now. I'm gonna have to take the express train. That bill's goin' straight to you... Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Grr...</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I ain't no liar. I never met Glen Elg.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And yet, your name was written on the victim's calendar!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Get that horse calendar outta my face! I'm The Tiger, not a lame horse, you' porcupine! Tigers like me eat horses like that for breakfast!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, no, no! Witnesses aren't permitted to eat evidence. Not that they ever would! ... Well, there's was [sic] a case once, where a young lad ate--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Anyway! If you had never met the victim before, how do explain this note he left?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">There was some lame guy with that name, though. Wanted to borrow cash from me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's very strange. According to the manager of the firm where the victim worked... ...December 3rd was the date he had to repay his loan. He wasn't due to discuss borrowing money, but repaying what he owed...</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Oh. Yeah. Maybe youse right. Whatever it was, it was goin' down at the beginnin' of December.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you did meet Mr. Elg, then!?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Hey, Wright. Youse might wanna cool your jets a sec.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I set up a meetin' with the guy... at my office, Tender Lender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So your meeting wasn't supposed to be at Trés Bien, then?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Why would I wanna go to a dump like dat? If I wanna talk with my clients, I got an office decked out for the job. I got the best punching bag youse ever saw in there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not exactly a professional office you've got there, you know...</thought> So you were in your office on the day in question?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I waited around for him, but he ain't ever showed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He didn't show up?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! What do you think, Trite? Let's see. How does a dead man get from a French restaurant to a loan shark's office?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And you yourself didn't go to Trés Bien?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">What are you' tryin' to pin on me here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Why don't youse come down to my office? We can chat about this thing my way, yeah? I got the best punching bag youse ever saw in there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no! No need! I'm good, thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Listen up! I ain't got nothin' more to say, except this.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I ain't never been to that Trés Bien joint, youse hear?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Never? Not even once?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Not even once. I was in my office the day that went down. I didn't put poison in no kid's coffee. Capice?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you think he really didn't meet Glen Elg?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not likely. Because I'm convinced this guy's behind the whole thing.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So you mean... that whole testimony he just gave was a lie?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course. So we can't afford to give him time to think of ways to plug the leaks in it. I've got to nail him while I still can!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Tigre. Is there something you'd like to tell the court about these matches?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Matches? What youse talkin' about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We found them in your office at Tender Lender. They're from "that" restaurant.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Wh...!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you've really never been to Trés Bien before... ...what was a book of the restaurant's matches doing on your desk!?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Youse been snoopin' around in my stuff now too, wiseguy!? What are you', my ball and chain!? Ain't no broad controlling me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Well, witness? I think it's time you started telling us the truth, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Grrraaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-Sorry! I'm terribly sorry! Forgive me!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I ain't no pussy-cat! I don't go back on what I said! But, OK... I was at the joint that day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">But listen good, alright? I might've been there, but I still never met that kid.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Well, well... Looks like an order just came in for another testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm this close to proving it was him! He did meet Glen Elg that day. And he did put poison in his coffee! He must have!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I was supposed to meet wid the kid at the restaurant that afternoon.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... You didn't actually meet with him in the end, then. Well, Mr. Wright. Your cross-examination, please.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> If I wait around here any longer, I ain't even gonna make the normal express. No more stupid questions.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! No problem. Any time Trite presses you on something irrelevant, I'll see he pays a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Godot! That's my job!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Your job is to slam that little hammer of yours and call a guilty verdict. So do it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">The special express ain't cheap, Wright! Just so youse know since youse payin'!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, man. Doesn't the rule of law mean anything around here!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I was supposed to meet wid the kid at the restaurant that afternoon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the meeting wasn't due to take place at Tender Lender at all then?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">The kid was makin' a fuss about comin' into de office. It's always that way when I wanna talk about repayments. Even though I got the best punching bag you' ever seen if there are any "issues".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe it's because of the punching bag that people are scared to come?</thought> So that's why you decided to meet at Trés Bien?</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! You're going over old ground again, Trite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You just earned yourself a penalty. Now suck it down!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You will suck down the penalty, Mr. Wright. And you will like it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Thank you, sir, may I have another!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">When I opened the door to the joint, I saw one ugly scene.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An "ugly scene"? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">The witness has already told us, Trite. Which makes that question... irrelevant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But...!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I limit myself to 17 cups of coffee during a trial. That's the rule. You better limit the number of times you take a penalty, Trite. Or your guts will look like the inside of a chimney! Ashen!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Don't make me burn you again, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I shouldn't have pressed him on that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Guess I'm gonna make that special express after all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, to recap... This "ugly scene" you saw was...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">The guy was laid out over the table, stiff as concrete.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean you saw Glen Elg's dead body?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I guess I did. But I only saw him from behind. He was wearin' some raggy bit of cloth he called a hat.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what time was this?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I dunno.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">You' know what winds me up more than anythin' else in the world? Watches! Round watches! I ain't gonna pollute my paws wid some tickin' henpecker!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Out of interest, Mr. Tigre, what winds you up the second most?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Huh? Whad'youse think!? Square watches!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is this guy for real!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Look, all I need to know was that somethin' bad was goin' down in that place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I figured if the place wasn't hot already, it was gonna be, so I split.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you didn't actually set foot inside the restaurant, then?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">The Tiger is a busy cat. I don't hang around for no one. I ain't got time to be caught up in no murder investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, when exactly did you pick up the matches?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">There are matches just inside the front door. Our detective friend wound up in trouble with the chef after taking 5 books home.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Gumshoe... It's almost enough to make a man cry...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I heard the cop's sirens on my way out, and I went straight back to my office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You went straight back? Did a bout of guilt suddenly hit you for what you did?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">What're youse trying to say!? You' tryin' to tell me youse ain't never been guilty of nothin'?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">We all have our crosses to bear. We all have to swallow the dark secrets we hide... ...Like this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The courtroom's not exactly the place to talk about dark secrets, is it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems you've done it again, Mr. Wright. Another irrelevant line of questioning. I must impose a penalty accordingly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How about a penalty for those two jokers and the garbage they keep coming up with!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, Nick? What do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's running out of ways to avoid the truth. I need to press him fast before he has time to think things through. I've got to come right back at him with a contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Be careful what you press him on, though, or you'll get penalized, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're something of a loan collecting pro, aren't you, Mr. Tigre?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">No one escapes The Tiger's clutches!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well I'm something of a lie detecting pro.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And no one escapes The Phoenix's clutches! I think it's time we got something straight.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">What's this, Trite? A new line of irrelevant questioning?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These are the floor plans of the crime scene. You say you were standing at the entrance, Mr. Tigre? From there, your field of vision would have covered an area something like... this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. The witness would have had a clear view of the victim's seat.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Isn't that what I just said? I saw the back of the kid's head.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Unfortunately for you, that is not possible. If the court would think back, you'll remember that between each of the tables... ...is a tall partition!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why...! That's true!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now look at the plans again! The truth is painfully obvious! From the entrance, the field of vision of any customer walking in... ...ends here!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, from the entrance of Trés Bien, you couldn't have seen the victim's seat. But you did see the victim that day... because you met with him!</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Wrong! Have you forgotten the old man's testimony yesterday? The victim was alone at his table.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the defense just proved that point to be moot! The "victim" witnessed by Mr. Kudo was not Glen Elg, but a fake!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In order to have Mr. Kudo falsely testify... ...the real killer posed as the victim he had just killed and acted out a charade!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That will do! This trial has gone on long enough without the obvious question being answered. Who exactly was this "real killer" who impersonated the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You say the killer murdered Glen Elg... ...and then impersonated his victim in a performance for Victor Kudo? In that case, Mr. Wright, reveal the identity of this "criminal" to the court!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Obviously, it's the person you least expect! Um... What's the matter, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, nothing! I just dropped my pen again. Don't mind me. Carry on with the proceedings as normal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Better think again while he's down there, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I should've picked the obvious choice...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very good. I've found my pen now. So, allow me to pose the question again, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Obviously... ...the killer is Furio Tigre! No one else could have done it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What!? Well, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">... Grrrah ha hah! Now that's cute! Youse think you can pin this on The Tiger!? Maybe youse don't understand. The Tiger is king of the jungle! So I dares you' to say it again! Come on! You' got the guts!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Y-You can't threaten m-me, Mr. Tigre! I-It's the defense! Go ahead and tell the witness, Mr. Wright! Mr. Wriiight!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Sounds to me like it must be you', old man. Youse got guts, I'll give you that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-M-Mr. Wright! Do not leave me to handle this alone!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...Ha...! Perhaps I can end this embarrassment.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Godot!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Let's just go back over Mr. Kudo's testimony one more time. The old man didn't see just the victim! Oh, no, no, no.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">The serving girl brought him a javaccino... But she put something in it! There's no question about it! She very conspicuously put some white powder in there!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Was the victim he saw the real victim or not? That doesn't matter. The fact remains, he saw the accused put the poison into the coffee!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...! Yes, it was the waitress who poisoned the coffee--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">V-Very impressive, Mr. Godot. ...Waiting for my absence to launch your attack!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Found your pen at last, Trite?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was in my pocket. *ahem* But anyway... Mr. Kudo witnessed two people that day. He saw the victim, the "supposed" Mr. Glen Elg, and the "waitress"... from behind.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes... Your point, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think the conclusion is obvious. If this "Glen Elg" was really the killer in disguise... ...then surely it's possible the "waitress" was also part of the show.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What!? You mean, the waitress was an imposter as well!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defendant, Ms. Byrde, fell unconscious immediately after the incident. And someone used her fainting to hatch an elaborate plan to pin the murder on her!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who on earth was it!? Who was this "waitress" that Mr. Kudo witnessed?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Obviously, it's the person you least expect! Um... What's the matter, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, nothing! I just dropped my pen again. Don't mind me. Carry on with the proceedings as normal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Better think again while he's down there, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I should've picked the obvious choice...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very good. I've found my pen now. So, allow me to pose the question again, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Who is this woman?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Her name is Viola Cadaverini. She's an employee of Tender Lender.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Youse makin' a big mistake... D'you know who Violetta's grandfather is? You' betta be goin' home in an armored truck tonight, if you' know what I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Stop shaking, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-Where was I? Yes, the defendant, Ms. Byrde, has stated the following...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Well, when I took the coffee over to the victim's table... ...it's true there was another customer in the restaurant.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Umm... She was sort of creepy... And she had a kind of cackling laugh.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are just too many contradictions in this case. The "second man" at the victim's table who nobody but Ms. Byrde seems to have seen. The earpiece worn by the victim in his left ear when that eardrum was ruptured! And the radio show he was supposedly listening to half an hour after it was over. There is only one logical explanation that clears up all of these contradictions! The whole incident took place twice! Once for real, and once for show! And, Mr. Furio Tigre, the only person who could have committed the crime... ...was you!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">... ......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Witness? What have you got to say?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">... That's cute!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Youse alright. I could do with a guy like you' around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">OK, I'm in on this game! I'm gonna have to charter a jet to get me to my meetin' now, but... ...I'm gonna give youse one more thing to think about before I go.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something to think about?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Youse got it all wrapped up nice, huh, Wright? But youse missed out one real important thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that can't be!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I was in the joint that day. And I met that kid, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">But I couldn't have poisoned him, youse hear?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What!? Do you really expect us to believe you now, Mr. Tigre?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! What a troublemaker.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">T-Troublemaker...?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Looks like we're going to need another one for the road. One more steaming cup of hot testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. Witness, you will explain yourself to the court. I will give you one more chance to testify. What happened that day at Trés Bien between yourself and the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Yeah, I loaned Elg cash. About 100,000 dollars.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, I see that the principal amount you loaned to Mr. Elg was 50,000 dollars...</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Yeah, well. Youse got the vig to take into account. Interest builds up fast, you' know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's faster than fast! 100,000 dollars is twice his principal!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">And the repayment deadline was December 3rd, the day of the incident in question.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Yeah. He was one lucky kid! He got that half a million just in time. So I ain't have no reason to kill the kid. And if I ain't got no motive, you ain't got no case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>His motive? Hmm... He has to have one, but what is it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Yeah, I loaned Elg cash. About 100,000 dollars.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did he have any way of paying the loan back?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">The fool was a gambler. He said he couldn't give it up 'til he landed a big win. So I agreed to help him.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Help him? You?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I kept hittin' him with ideas for ways he could getta big win. But the guy kept losin'.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you were helping him for his sake? Or yours?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">"Win Through Compromise"! Youse help me, I help youse! What's the difference, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I don't believe this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, would anyone really ever loan money to someone they thought was unreliable? Like, for example, if it were you, I'd only loan you five bucks, max.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Thanks a lot, Maya.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">That day, we was due to have a little chat. The kid had hit his payback date, see?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So how much were you expecting him to pay you back on that day?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">What d'youse think!? The whole package! $100,000, including interest.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's a real heavyweight punch!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Once a client misses a repayment, you' call the whole loan in. You' wanna make it in my world, that's all youse gotta know.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And how many times had Mr. Elg been late with his repayments?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Once.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And how much was he supposed to pay back every month?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">50 bucks.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sounds like Mr. Elg was in a real sticky spot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, at 50 dollars a month, he'd never pay that huge loan off!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">So anyway, he tells me he's got no way to pay up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How much did he have left on his debt?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">You want it in round figures? About 100,000 bucks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's the whole amount!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">We're talking about a guy who had 58 cents in his wallet.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">What!? Youse tellin' me he wasn't even gonna pay for the coffee!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He certainly seems to have been a brave man, this Mr. Elg.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">That guy was smooth, I tell youse. Real smooth! "You'll have your money in less than 5 minutes!" That's what he says to me. The guy then calls me the "Tender Tiger". He was skatin' on thin ice with me!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I'm about to flatten the guy, when he starts screamin'.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was that because he...?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">The guy won the lottery. Was his last chance at a big win.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And you confirm that this is the ticket in question?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">...That's it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The "Millionaire Radio" show starts at 1:30 PM and runs for 10 minutes... That fixes the time you two met with some accuracy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And the whole scene was acted out again 30 minutes later. All so that Mr. Kudo would see it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I can still see the kid's face now. I ain't never gonna forget it.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">"Yesss! I won! Half a million bucks!" He got lucky, you' know. Real lucky.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was there anyone else in the restaurant at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I don't remember.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If there was no one there, I'll wear that ridiculous tiger shirt for a month! Mr. Armstrong, Maggey and if I'm right, Viola Cadaverini, were all there at that time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, the victim had intended to repay you from his lottery winnings from the beginning?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Seems dat way to me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But you wouldn't normally expect to win the lottery, would you!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! The undying belief that your next roll will end the worst losing streak you ever had... That's what defines a true gambler.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He makes it sound so cool...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't be tempted, Nick! You haven't got the will-power for it!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">All I know is, the kid took a shot and he got lucky in the end.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">If that waitress hadn't done what she done, everythin' woulda been over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The waitress. You mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">The girl with the glasses in the defendant's chair! Who else could I mean!? If she hadn't got in the way, things woulda been, bada-bing, bada-boom, over and done with!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe I should push a little on this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What exactly are you implying the defendant did?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">How about you go ask four-eyes about that half a million dollar ticket! She wanted it so bad... ...she poisoned Elg's coffee.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A likely theory! Your word hasn't held water lately, Mr. Tigre.</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Let's not forget this witness was actually at the scene, Trite.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">The law don't exactly agree with some of the deals I send down. I couldn't be there when de cops showed up, so I split.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I see...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Your Honor! The witness's last few statements are worth a good two cups of coffee.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I concur, Mr. Godot! You will amend your testimony accordingly, witness!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Ha ha ha! So that's what youse after, Phoenix Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean things would have been over and done with?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Are youse all there or what!? I'm talkin' about the cash! I was there to get my 100,000 bucks back. That's all. I'm a business man. It was all comin' together before that waitress got in the way.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... As far as I can tell from the witness's testimony... ...other than recouping his loan, Mr. Tigre had no motive for killing the victim. Witness! You will amend your testimony to reflect what you just said.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The Tiger's motive, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Thanks to what she did, my business with that kid was over!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The Tiger's trying to pin the crime on Maggey. If I ask him about what he saw, it's only going to damage our case.</thought> What do you mean things would have been over and done with?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Are youse all there or what!? I'm talkin' about the cash! I was there to get my 100,000 bucks back. That's all. I'm a business man. It was all comin' together before that waitress got in the way.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... As far as I can tell from the witness's testimony... ...other than recouping his loan, Mr. Tigre had no motive for killing the victim. Well, Mr. Wright? Are you happy with the testimony, or would you like it amended?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I better leave it at that and try to figure something out...</thought> Thank you, Your Honor, but there is no need to amend the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Continue with your cross-examination, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not going to get anywhere with the testimony as it stands...</thought> Your Honor, the defense would like the testimony amended.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Witness! You will amend your testimony to reflect your recent statements, please.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I was after the $100,000. I didn't have no other reason to kill the guy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you saying you had no other motives that day?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Yeah, so what?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Then why didn't you take the lottery ticket when you left?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Why d'youse think!? Because of four-eyes over there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Because of Maggey!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">How about you go ask four-eyes about that half a million dollar ticket! She wanted it so bad... ...she poisoned Elg's coffee.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A likely theory! Your word hasn't held water lately, Mr. Tigre.</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Let's not forget this witness was actually at the scene, Trite.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">The law don't exactly agree with some of the deals I send down. I couldn't be there when de cops showed up, so I split.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I see...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Your Honor! The witness's last few statements are worth a good two cups of coffee.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright? Are you happy with the testimony, or would you like it amended?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I better leave it at that and try to figure something out...</thought> Thank you, Your Honor, but there is no need to amend the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Continue with your cross-examination, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not going to get anywhere with the testimony as it stands...</thought> Your Honor, the defense would like the testimony amended.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Witness! You will amend your testimony to reflect your recent statements, please.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you just intended to get back the 100,000 dollars Mr. Elg owed you, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I loaned the guy the cash, so that's my right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Unfortunately for Mr. Elg... I don't believe the 100,000 dollars is what you were after.</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">What are you getting at, Trite? What else would a moneylender be after other than money!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, the moneylender was after money. But money in a totally different league. The kind of money that a single disc like this would fetch!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A computer virus, Your Honor. A virus called "MC Bomber"!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A "computer virus"? What does one of those do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A computer virus is a program that wreaks havoc on the insides of a computer.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A "computer"? What does one of those do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess the beard isn't the only part of His Honor that is from the stone age!</thought> I'll explain it to you later, Your Honor. Right now, this is the important point... A virus like "MC Bomber" would be worth several million dollars on the black market.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-Several million dollars!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lending money with no hope of ever seeing repayment would normally be bad for business. But in this case, the very fact that Glen Elg had no way to repay the money is crucial.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Glen Elg was a programmer. A highly skilled programmer. That skill was the collateral Mr. Elg put up in order to borrow the money.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">...</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">You're trying to suggest the witness's motive was to get hold of that program?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">The witness may be poor fashion sense, but he is by no means an idiot, Trite. A man like him could get his hands on one million dollars without resorting to murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course he could... Provided that he had time. But what if he had needed the money right then? When the pressure's on, the luxury of choice tends to disappear.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems you have a logical conclusion for this theory, Mr. Wright. Would you care to share it with us? Why did Mr. Tigre need money to the tune of one million dollars?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is the meaning of this, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">It's evidence... that Trite has no idea what he's doing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You're way off track, Trite. That evidence is irrelevant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Since when did he have the right to dish out penalties?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">A-Are you alright, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">100,000 dollars wasn't enough for Mr. Tigre. He needed much more money than that. And in a hurry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In December of last year, you found yourself in need of a huge amount of money.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About 6 months ago, you were involved in a traffic accident, weren't you? An accident involving a car and a scooter, in which a young woman was injured. She was taken to the hospital, where she underwent surgery.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Wh-Where did youse get all this info...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These medical papers document the treatment of the young woman in question. According to these, her operation cost... one million dollars! Payment for these expenses was due in December of last year, and was paid in full!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-One million dollars!? A preposterous sum! Someone should sue these HMOs!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! No one would pay a bill like that. If the medical association got wind of it, the hospital would end up as dead as a morgue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But Mr. Tigre had no choice but to pay! Because his very life depended on it!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Grrraaaaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Order! Order! Order! You say his very life depended on it, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Indeed it did. Simply because the injured woman was none other than Viola Cadaverini.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...! Did you say, "Cadaverini"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Bruto Cadaverini, Mob boss in charge of all underworld activities in the city, and... ...doting grandfather to his precious "Violetta", also known as Viola Cadaverini.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Bwooooar!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your life was in danger unless you paid "compensation" to the boss, correct? It makes sense! You were desperate to acquire the one million dollars Cadaverini demanded of you! So desperate, in fact, that you decided to sacrifice Glen Elg's life to pay your debt!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you just intended to get back the 100,000 dollars Mr. Elg owed you, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I loaned the guy the cash, so that's my right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Unfortunately for Mr. Elg... ...100,000 dollars wasn't enough to cover it, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About 6 months ago, you were involved in a traffic accident, weren't you? An accident involving a car and a scooter, in which a young woman was injured. She was taken to the hospital, where she underwent surgery.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Wh-Where did youse get all this info...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These medical papers document the treatment of the young woman in question. According to these, her operation cost... one million dollars! Payment for these expenses was due in December of last year, and was paid in full!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-One million dollars!? A preposterous sum! Someone should sue these HMOs!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! No one would pay a bill like that. If the medical association got wind of it, the hospital would end up as dead as a morgue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But Mr. Tigre had no choice but to pay! Because his very life depended on it!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Grrraaaaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Order! Order! Order! You say his very life depended on it, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Indeed it did. Simply because the injured woman was none other than Viola Cadaverini.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...! Did you say, "Cadaverini"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Bruto Cadaverini, Mob boss in charge of all underworld activities in the city, and... ...doting grandfather to his precious "Violetta", also known as Viola Cadaverini.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Bwooooar!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your life was in danger unless you paid "compensation" to the boss, correct? It makes sense! You were desperate to acquire the one million dollars Cadaverini demanded of you! So desperate, in fact, that you decided to sacrifice Glen Elg's life to pay your debt!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! What do you say to that, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">...Grrr... urgh...</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">It's a nice little fairy tale, Trite. But even if the witness did need a million dollars... ...that doesn't tie him to Mr. Elg's murder. Mr. Elg only owed him 100,000 dollars, and had no hope of repaying it anyway!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Yeah. That guy wasn't worth my spit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think so. In fact, the opposite is true.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">The opposite?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lending money with no hope of ever seeing repayment would normally be bad for business. But in this case, the very fact that Glen Elg had no way to repay the money is crucial.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you know where you're going with this, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've got to think outside the box, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Outside the box?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's very straightforward. Mr. Tigre wasn't after the 100,000 dollars at all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems you have a logical conclusion for this theory, Mr. Wright. Would you care to share it with us? What exactly was Mr. Tigre "after"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is the meaning of this, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">It's evidence... that Trite has no idea what he's doing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You're way off track, Trite. That evidence is irrelevant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Since when did he have the right to dish out penalties?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">A-Are you alright, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Tigre needed one million dollars. Recovering a loan 100,000 dollars wasn't enough. <thought>Besides, Elg had the means to make that kind of money if he wanted to.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Glen was a programmer. A highly skilled programmer. That skill was the collateral Mr. Elg put up in order to borrow the money.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Care to explain how skill can be used as collateral to secure a loan, Trite?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He had the skill to create a computer virus, and so he did. A virus known as "MC Bomber"!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A "computer virus"? What does one of those do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A computer virus is a program that wreaks havoc on the insides of a computer.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A "computer"? What does one of those do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess the beard isn't the only part of His Honor that is from the stone age!</thought> I'll explain it to you later, Your Honor. Right now, this is the important point... A virus like "MC Bomber" would be worth several million dollars on the black market. Mr. Tigre! You couldn't have cared less about the 100,000 dollars! Isn't that right? All you cared about was one thing! The virus!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Grrr... Grrraaaaaaaaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So The Tiger was meeting Glen Elg to get his money back. If Mr. Elg had just given him the lottery ticket, that would have been the end of it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, so what's The Tiger's motive? <thought>This is the big one. If I don't manage to undermine this testimony, it's all over for us.</thought> Why would he have to poison Mr. Elg? And why did he loan him the money in the first place, when he knew he couldn't repay him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the day of the murder, Mr. Tigre's sole intention was to get his hands on this CD! Glen Elg had no way of paying back the 100,000 dollars, and Mr. Tigre knew it. But then a miracle happened. The kind that Mr. Tigre would prefer to say never happened. But he can't. Neither can I.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">The lottery win?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly! At the eleventh hour, Mr. Elg won half a million dollars on the lottery! Which left Mr. Tigre with no way of getting his hands on the all-important CD. At least, no legitimate way. So he resorted to illegitimate means.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">That's crazy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He murdered Glen Elg, and then made his next move... To frame Maggey Byrde for the crime! Mr. Tigre posed as Glen Elg... ...while Viola Cadaverini played the role of Ms. Byrde. And then they re-enacted the whole thing, in order to establish a witness. The witness being the one we all heard testify yesterday, Mr. Victor Kudo.</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Like I said, Trite, that's crazy. No one could pull off a stunt like that. For starters, there's no way the chef could've been kept out of it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But Mr. Armstrong knew all about it. Have you forgotten already, Mr. Godot? Mr. Armstrong owed the witness money, too. Half a million dollars, in fact. He had no choice but to go along with Mr. Tigre's plan!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Silence, or I will clear the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Grrraah ha ha ha ha hah! Youse put on a good show, Spikey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">If youse wanna stay alive in the loan shark business, you' gotta be careful. Youse sayin' I dressed up like that kid, created a witness, and framed someone? If I did something crazy like that, I'd leave a trail as bright as my shirt! I ain't dumb enough to do something sloppy like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I agree.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Whaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Despite your appearance, you are very careful. That's why you took one more precaution. One more trick to make sure Ms. Byrde had no way out!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What!? Another one, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Interesting. Why don't you fill us all in, Trite? What was this trick you say Mr. Tigre performed to frame the accused?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Godot">And? What's the relevance of that, Trite?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... It's, uh... just a little intro...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">An intro into what?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems all this has been an elaborate trick on the part of the defense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No! Wait! Mr. Tigre did play a trick! A huge trick!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What on earth is that? What an insult to think anyone could be fooled by such a childish imitation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Consider yourself insulted, Your Honor!</thought> Mr. Tigre. You didn't just pose as the victim on the day in question. A month ago, in this very court, you posed as me!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whaaat!? That's... That's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...The truth.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But! The witness looks nothing like you, Mr. Wright! ... ...... ... Although... Now that I think about it, it was you, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No doubt it was you... Standing in here, this very court, a mere month ago. The Phoenix Wright who put up the most disreputable, shabby defense I had ever seen!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Grrr... Grrraaaaaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Can you prove that, gramps? Prove the "attorney" who represented the accused here a month ago was this man. Are you prepared to take the stand and testify that it was him!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...*gulp* H-Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">H-Hey... F-Forget about it, yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I wouldn't do somethin' like that. Not me. You... You made a mistake, right? It was someone else, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you no pride, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">This isn't a matter of pride. In case you didn't know, Trite, here in court, we deal with people's lives!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nrrrgh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Mr. Godot is right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Speaking for myself, I am absolutely convinced. The attorney in question was the witness standing before me now! However... I preside over this court as the judge! With the vested power to hand down a verdict. Someone in my position cannot be swayed by a memory without evidence to support it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If the defense has no further evidence, the court will now excuse the witness. The circumstances surrounding Mr. Tigre are dubious for sure, but not conclusive!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But we've come so far!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You say he impersonated Glen Elg. You say he impersonated you. But none of that adds up to a murder charge. You don't have a shred of evidence that the witness poisoned the victim's coffee!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nnaaaaaaaaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">... Ha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Sucks to be you, Wright. Don't mess with The Tiger, or you're gonna get mauled, youse got that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All we managed to do here was chase him around a bit. But I was so close to getting him to admit his own guilt!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Looks like I won't be needing a refill.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I just had one more piece of evidence... One more piece of evidence and maybe I could get Maggey off the hook!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This witness's cross-examination is over. You are free to go, Mr. Tigre!</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Waaaaaaaait!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">D-Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry I took so long, pal! I... I... I staked everything on this. My badge... The works! So here it is! My heart's counting on this, too!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What is it, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Isn't it obvious, pal? It's the final, decisive piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh... Whaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry it took so long, pal. But I finally got the results from the lab.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The results?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">About the prints, pal! From this medicine bottle!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! So? Do you know who the prints belong to now?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Do you think I'm some kind of hack detective? Of course I know!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So? Tell us! They're The Tiger's right? I knew it!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Heh heh heh! You bet! Clear as crystal, all over the bottle! They're Furio Tigre's paw prints alright!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's great! We've got him now, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's wrong with you!? You've hardly said a word since Detective Gumshoe got here. He's laid everything on the line for this, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know. Look, I'm sorry. This is kind of hard to say, but... It really doesn't make any difference whose prints are on that bottle now.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh!? What!? Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What we need to produce at this stage in the trial... ...is irrefutable evidence that The Tiger put poison in Glen Elg's coffee. He's already admitted that he met the victim. The fact that his prints are on this bottle... That's really doesn't make any difference now.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...! ... I knew it. Great... No matter how hard I try... I'm never of any use.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, don't be so hard on yourself...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This was our last chance to help Maggey. And I've been working on some useless piece of evidence the whole time! It's alright. I'm a real loser. It's not breaking news to me, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Um... Detective... Gumshoe...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">M-Maggey!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">You've been working on something... for me?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Sorry I let you down, Maggey. I know you didn't do it. And I'm a detective! We're supposed to be able to prove stuff like that! I'm really sorry! I'll get out of your hair now.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Detective Gumshoe! Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's gone...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Isn't there anything we can do now, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wish there was! Gumshoe worked so hard to get that evidence. If only there was some way I could use it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I granted you a recess so you could prepare this "decisive evidence" you've discovered.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Don't keep us all in suspense, Trite! Show us. Naturally... ...we can assume it's evidence that will actually stand up in court... can't we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Think, Phoenix! Don't let Gumshoe's hard work go to waste!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">How much more of my time are youse gonna waste!? I ain't been to no court before... ...but youse lawyers sure know how to blow things outta proportion!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No doubt, given the nature of the evidence, it will speak for itself. Nevertheless, you will talk us through it, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well I know I can't prove anything new with this evidence. I'm really backed into a corner here. But maybe if he thinks he's got me beat... ...he'll let his guard down a bit!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Don't keep us waiting any longer, Mr. Wright. Present this final, decisive piece of evidence to the court!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Quite frankly, Mr. Wright, I'm disappointed. I was wondering what evidence you could possibly produce that would sway me...</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I see the idiot's point. That's decisive! Real decisive! It's decisive in sayin' that I ain't guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, Nick! Don't let Gumshoe down!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the defense's final piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Isn't that the victim's...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor. Naturally, the court is already aware of the contents of this bottle. However, interesting new information has come to light. We have clearly identified some fingerprints on it. Fingerprints belonging to you, Mr. Tigre!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But, Mr. Wright... What conclusion are you hoping to draw from this new information?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Everyone in here knows what this bottle contains. Except one man. One person in this courtroom should theoretically be in the dark.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">My prints are on that pansy-lookin' bottle? Is dat what youse sayin'? Well, what the hell's in it anyway!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A phony trial, a phony lawyer, and phony clues. Everything about this case has been phony. Seems like the perfect excuse for some phony evidence!</thought> Mr. Tigre! This is the decisive piece of evidence that will prove your guilt! Why? Because it contains...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The evidence on its own isn't worth anything. I guess I'll just have to take the plunge and...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-Wait a minute, Nick! Aromatherapy oil's not going to help anyone now, is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! If you think I'll allow you to indulge in speculation at this stage, you're wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oops. Looks like I better reconsider. I've got to take advantage of the fact that The Tiger thinks he's won... ...and lead him into a trap! And a phony piece of evidence is the way to do it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As we all know, this bottle contains Glen Elg's medic--</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you doing, Nick!? What did you just tell Gumshoe and I outside in the lobby a few minutes ago? You said, "The fact that his prints are on this bottle makes no difference now!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! If you think I'll allow you to indulge in speculation at this stage, you're wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oops. Looks like I better reconsider. I've got to take advantage of the fact that The Tiger thinks he's won... ...and lead him into a trap! And a phony piece of evidence is the way to do it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the bottle containing the potassium cyanide.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">P-Potassium cyanide...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The poison used to murder Mr. Elg, Your Honor. The victim's killer used this very bottle!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">... ......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And on this bottle, Mr. Tigre, we found your fingerprints. Well!? How do you explain that!?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">... Ha ha ha ha ha! You'd make a good clown, you' know that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Youse ain't never gonna get this to stick. Youse just makin' me laugh now. You' think a cheap bluff like that's gonna fool The Tiger?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A bluff?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">I can see straight through you, Phoenix Wright! That ain't the bottle with the cyanide in it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no. This is the bottle we found traces of the poison in.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Don't mess with The Tiger or you're gonna get ripped to shreds! The cyanide bottle was brown. And it was made of glass. That cheap piece of trash don't look nothin' like it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Got him! At last...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Wh-What? Why's everyone gone quiet? I said that bottle...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is this the bottle you're referring to?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Yeah! That's it! That's the bottle the cyanide was in. But youse ain't gonna find my prints on that bottle! Don't let that cozy-lookin' suit fool you people! That lawyer's just playin' games! Tell him, Godot! Tell that guy where to go!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You still haven't figured it out...? Don't you realize what you just said?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">What I said? What did I just say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were summoned to this court for the first time earlier today. If you really had nothing to do with the murder... ...you shouldn't have known all the little details. For instance, you shouldn't have known what kind of bottle the potassium cyanide was in.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Err... grrr...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But just now, you slipped up in front of every single person in this courtroom. You described the exact bottle used by the killer to hold the poison!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Err... ummm... Youse don't know who youse messin' with! I'm The Tiger! I control millions of dollars on the black market! Youse think I'm gonna let some jumped-up suit get the better of me!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, the last piece of evidence was phony. But that's just what you deserve! The phony trial with a phony lawyer... It was all played out by you, the biggest phony of all!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Grrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr... ... Gwoaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's going on!?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">It looks like a blackout.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Well done... Trite. I saved my 17th cup of coffee just for you. Savor it... While you watch your caged prey.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wright, you caught a tiger by his toe, but if this one hollers, he won't be let go. The prosecution will be sure to take care of Mr. Tigre, won't you, Mr. Godot?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">He is being arrested on suspicion of the murder of Glen Elg, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Fortunately for us... ...we managed to rectify a very grave error. Ms. Byrde was found guilty in the absence of a genuine defense attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, she was.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">And in the absence of genuine evidence. But The Tiger made one mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. He very nearly got away with everything if it wasn't for that one slip of tongue. Furio Tigre is a truly frightening criminal.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! The truly frightening one... ...is that defense attorney over there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Godot...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well. I am now in a position to deliver my verdict. This court finds the defendant, Maggey Byrde...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is all. This court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Mr. Wright! I-I-I... I'm at a loss for words! Thank you, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Congratulations, Maggey!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I was so mad when Mr. Wright landed me in all that trouble a month ago. But now I feel like I can forgive him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! That wasn't me, Maggey! That was The Tiger.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look, Nick! In the doorway!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Detective Gumshoe!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh. Guess I'll be heading off then. See you 'round, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... ...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Detective Gumshoe...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, oh yeah. Congratulations, Maggey!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Thanks...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-I knew you were innocent all along.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">... Why didn't you say that in your testimony then?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? Oh... Well... I was... ... Well, guess I'll be heading off then. See you 'round.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait up, Detective! <thought>He just ran off!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maggey! Why are you being so hard on him? He busted his butt for you! It's thanks to him that we got the medication bottle...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">That wasn't even any use!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">It's only because Mr. Wright used it so cleverly. Detective Gumshoe was just running around in circles.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor guy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Looks like she still isn't ready to forgive him. Can't you put in a good word for him, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, Maya is right. I should help Gumshoe out. It's clear he needs it.</thought> Uh, Maggey... You know, Detective Gumshoe's been really worried about you through all of this.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I wanted to believe that, sir. But on that first day of the trial... ...he practically gave the judge a free pass to lock me up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He didn't have any choice, Maggey. He's a detective. He has to report the facts.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">He doubted me, that's why! He thought I might have done it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've got to prove her that Gumshoe really cares about her. I know. I'll give her a little present to celebrate her freedom...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here you are. A present to celebrate your freedom!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Th-That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A present from Detective Gumshoe, made with a ton of love.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He said you lost weight and he was worried about you.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">D-Detective Gumshoe... ...... ... I... I actually really like weenies, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Did you guys hear that!? I'm pretty hungry myself, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, the trial dragged on a bit today, didn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Um, is it OK if I eat this now?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So? How is it, Maggey?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">It's... It's really good!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">...? Um... What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!? Uh, I thought it'd be a good present. You know, to celebrate your freedom.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">... Oh. Well, I don't really get it, but... Thanks! I'll treasure it always!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That didn't seem to do the trick...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Well, I guess I'll be going now, then.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Good things are going to happen to you from now on, Maggey. I'm sure of it.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Of course! No one can be that unlucky forever! I'll do my best to have some good news to report to you next time we meet, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good. We'll look forward to it.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Goodbye. I won't forget how you helped me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't sound very sure, Mr. Wright. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This evidence clearly reveals the contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are the evidence and the statement just now related?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They aren't, are they...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Wright, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness's statement is clearly faulty, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry, but I can see nothing faulty. Unfortunately, I will have to penalize you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh, I must be on the wrong track...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! This court sees no reason to further prolong the trial. Nor is there any need for more time to decide the case against the defendant. This case is extremely clear. I see no room for mis-interpretation of the facts. This court finds the defendant, Maggey Byrde...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accused will surrender to the court immediately... ...to be held pending trial at a higher court within a month from today's date. That is all. This court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>