<xml>
<title>Recipe for Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Maya">So how do you think the trial went this morning?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How do you think it went!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It got a bit crazy in there. I just wonder if that killed our chances.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I guess it did get out of hand. Mr. Kudo's testimony did nothing to help us. Plus, now we don't even know the identity of the waitress who laced the coffee.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All we know is what old Mr. Kudo saw... The apron straps, and the ribbon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that the victim was wearing an earpiece when his eardrum was ruptured.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Talk about a terrifying case of contradictionitus.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Time to play doctor and find ourselves a cure then, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, we've gotta find one for Maggey, or she's going to have a terminal case of guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well? I'm officially at a loss as to where to start.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, me too. Let's try some brainstorming. You go first.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess we should try to put Mr. Kudo's testimony to some sort of use.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And we need to figure out the identity of the waitress and who the victim really was... Somehow, I think the key to this case has got to be at Trés Bien.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well then, let's go back there and check it out again. Oh! And we should drop in on Maggey and see how she's doing, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... Anything on your mind?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Actually, there is something...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I was wondering about Xin Eohp... You know, like what he's like and stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, yeah. I almost forgot about that guy.</line>
<line speaker="???">I atta beat you so hard, it'll feel like youse were smoochin' the express train!</line>
<line speaker="???">Phoenix Wright? Youse sayin' YOU' Phoenix Wright?</line>
<line speaker="???">Cause I'M Phoenix Wright. The one and only!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually... I've learned a little something about my doppelganger.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? You did? What did you find out?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, yeah, Maya was working at the restaurant when I ran into Don Foneeonay...</thought> Let's just say he was such a terrible version of me that I wanted to sue for defamation! <thought>What's that guy's story, anyway? What does he have to gain by impersonating me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">That badge is totally useless, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I mean, no one suspected that Xin Eohp wasn't a real lawyer. I bet he didn't have an attorney's badge!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I guess you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Or maybe he did have one! And maybe he switched your real one for a "fugazzi"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My badge? A fake!? ... Ha ha ha... That's a good one, Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why the nervous laughter? ...Aha! I knew it! Your badge really IS fake, isn't it Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This doodle here... It was drawn by the victim, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is a newspaper from the day of the incident, so, yeah, we've got to assume so. There must be a clue in there somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess we should show it around and see if anyone can tell us more about it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can't believe there's a fake Nick running around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I know. What's the deal with that? Why's he impersonating me?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe he's got something against you. People do tend to have a distinct distaste for you, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>True enough... The only thing prosecutors seem to like about me is pushing me around...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Or... maybe he's got something against Maggey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So he pretended to be me to get Maggey convicted?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">That thing must've been in an accident. It's a total wreck!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what the guy I met at the park was riding. And I'm betting he's the fake me.</line>
<line speaker="???">Gwoaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaar! Cause I'M Phoenix Wright. The one and only!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His voice is still ringing in my ears.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Introduce me next time, Nick! I want to meet Xin Eohp, too!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A loan of half a million dollars! I wonder what Mr. Armstrong did to get into that much debt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm going to guess he spent money needlessly. You'd better watch your spending, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, I've got a great idea! What if Mr. Armstrong charged $20,000 for the Twin-T set?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you hit people with that kind of bill, Maya, they will hit you back!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A letter of apology from the old man? Aww, how sweet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, it's his "testimony"... If you can call it that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So? What's it say? ..."I broke the vase at my seat. I'm sorry."? Heh heh! I used to break things all the time when I was little, you know. And I used to have to write apologies all the time, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, Pearls and Adrian seem to have picked up where you left off...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's the cup the poison was in, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, and the stain on the rim shows that the victim used his right hand to pick it up.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But the old man swore he saw the victim pick it up with his left hand...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If Mr. Kudo wasn't mistaken, then what could account for this contradiction...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe I should try the lottery sometime, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, why not? If you hit the jackpot, you could win half a million bucks.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, what are you waiting for, Nick? Buy one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No way! Don't you know the lottery is a tax on people who are bad at math!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Blah. Fine then. At least I can add it to the newly renamed "Paths to Wealth"! I'll have to call Pearly later and have her add, "Buy lottery tickets whenever possible."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's almost surreal that this artsy apron is what got us this far.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, as art goes, this piece definitely leaves an impression.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess that means the old guy never saw the front of it, huh? Which means he didn't see the waitress's face, either...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can't believe they found this in Maggey's pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, but she was passed out, right? So the killer could've easily planted it on her.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Where do you even get a hold of something like this? It's not like you can go down to your local CostMo' and buy it in bulk for $5 a pound!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She has got a point... How the killer got a hold of this poison is pretty important.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">"New Ear Otolaryngological Clinic". Hmm... I guess if your eardrum was ruptured, you couldn't listen to the radio, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. It'd be pretty pointless to wear an earpiece of any kind.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The medication in the bag is missing too, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The mysterious vanishing medication... Much like our mysterious "other person"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So? How's your spirit medium training going?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, I'm kind of taking a break... I'm having a bit of trouble right now, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Last year's incident must still be on her mind... I haven't seen Maya train at all since then. I think Mia said it's because Maya's "at a loss these days"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia really bailed me out again yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Argh! That seedy old man was so rude to me! He didn't realize just how awesome I am. If he had, I bet he would've treated me better.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Since when did you become so awesome?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Godot got it good today, huh? He was even smoking at me end there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He'll have a new witness ready for tomorrow, though. You can count on it. <thought>We need to figure out the facts before then, or we're doomed!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">A lot of strange conflicting things kept popping up today in the trial, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, and they seemed to come out of nowhere.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's why we've gotta go talk with Maggey and get out this whole thing straightened out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maggey said that when she brought the victim his coffee... ...there was one more people sitting at the table. This single contradiction is probably the most important one we have to resolve...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Have you noticed the victims in our cases tend to be people we know nothing about, Nick? Take Glen Elg, for example.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now that you mention it...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We don't know what kind of guy he was, or why he was killed. I say it's time to get out there and find some answers!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I really felt sorry for Gumshoe today. He really wanted to help Maggey out, but he kept getting backed into a corner.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maggey took it pretty bad, didn't she? Do you think she feels betrayed?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe. We've got to cheer her up somehow. She's a friend, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A friend? Hmm... Never really thought of it that way, but I guess she is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's the seedy old man! What's his name again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Vermin Kudo, is it? I can't remember, either. I've never seen a witness mess up so badly in court before.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Better stay away from him a while, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah. It might be more than seed that he chucks at me next time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">The chef's a witness too, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I suppose so. He was in the kitchen at the time of the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, since Old Man Seeds's testimony is pretty much useless to us... ...I guess we should speak to Mr. Armstrong again, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Looks like Gumshoe's not here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Never mind that. What's going on? It feels different in here somehow...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. Everyone seems to be on edge.</line>
<line speaker="Detective">What are you doing!? Call in the officers for the briefing, quick! Can't you shut down the station's server? Chief! Quit playing on the Internet!</line>
<line speaker="Chief">But my e-mail pen pal, 1337aZnPrInceSz!</line>
<line speaker="Detective">Save it for later! I'm turning it off NOW!</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Noooo! 1337aZnPrInceeeeeSz!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Everyone's keeping busy in here, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Keeping busy? More like panicking, if you ask me. <thought>Something's going on. Something big...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Detective">"Even pickpockets can have their pockets picked." That's a keeper! Better to go with something that doesn't sound too much like a slogan.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He must be coming up with slogans for a crime prevention campaign... ...But I'm not sure even he knows what kind of crime he's trying to prevent.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be the chief of the detectives here. He looks lost, now that the power to his computer has been cut.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Oh, well. I guess I'll just have to write her a real letter instead of an email.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Alternately, you could write up some reports... Just a suggestion.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Chief">"Dear 1337aZnPrInceSz, How are you? I'm OK! How was the show last night...?"</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, what an awesome job! Maybe I should send in my resume and become chief!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, that's the police mascot, isn't it? It's so cute!</line>
<line speaker="Chief">That's the "Blue Badger". It was my idea! I made it! And now, it's the national symbol of the police!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what's with the pink one? It's new, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She's not an "it", Nick. She's a "she"! Right, Chief?</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Yup. Meet the "Pink Badger".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So one's called "Blue", and the other's called "Pink", but they're both called "Badger"?</line>
<line speaker="Chief">You got it! They're both married.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um... Mr. &amp; Mrs. Badger seem to be cuffed together, Chief.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">You got it! That's marriage for you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoa... A mascot that's deeper than the deepest of deep oceans...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess Maggey's still in questioning.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But! But we've got questions to ask her, too! Magg-ey! Magg-ey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Keep it down, Maya! This isn't a playground, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Empty, as usual.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, and it's lunchtime, too.</line>
<line speaker="???">That's it! Come on, come on, come on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, that sounds like...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Now just call an "8", pal! Come on! I know you can!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's getting really worked up about something.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Noooooo! That's the wrong number! Argh! Look like an "8" would have only netted me five bucks anyway! What a rip off!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's the problem, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh!? Oh, it's you... I, uh... I was uh... Hah hah! I was just... Hah hah hah! I was just listening to the radio, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To the radio?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Detective Gumshoe's having lunch here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He is! And he's having the Twin-T set...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aha ha ha... What can I say...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the restaurant's front entrance. There's a sign hanging on the door written in French. It probably says, "Open" or "Closed". It must be one or the other, but I don't know which since I dunno Jacques about French.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It could say "Entrance" or "Exit", too. Did you think of that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's a rack full of fashion magazines. And they're all in French.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why don't you try wearing something a bit more "chic" something, huh, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. I'd look stunning in some of those Parisian frocks, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This table's set nicely. It just needs a customer.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick. Do you think Old Seedy was talking about a vase like this today in court?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It does look like it's ready to fall over any second. Looks kind of fragile, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I bet if Mr. Armstrong charged 10,000 dollars for every vase a customer broke... ...he'd be able to pay off his loan really quickly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you hit people with that kind of bill, Maya, they will hit you back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow! It's a beautiful winter wonderland out there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really!? Cool! I love snow! Let me see! Huh? It's not white. It's not even snowing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got ya! I was just kidding, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! There are lies that are OK to tell, and lies that definitely aren't.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...All I did was tell an itty-bitty white lie about nonexistent white snow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This restaurant has partitions that separate the tables. When you're seated at a table, you can only see the tables to your right or left.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, you really can't see the table in front or behind you at all! It's the perfect setup for slipping poison into your enemy's coffee.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is a nightmare! How am I supposed to look Maggey in the eye now, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You really drove her into a corner, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You always blow apart my testimony! Why, of all days, didn't you do it today!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry... There just weren't any holes in it... for once!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, what happened? Usually, your testimonies are like Swiss cheese!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">S-Swiss cheese...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Would he have preferred, "crumbly like aged parmesan"? Anyway, this case has already been ruled on. There shouldn't be any holes left to find.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So... Did Maggey say anything to you? About me, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, um... How did she put it again...?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I can't believe Detective Gumshoe! I hate him, sir! I mean it! I don't ever want to see him again!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wah... Waaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">P-Please! Detective Gumshoe! I didn't mean...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Why!? Why is this happening!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's banging his head against the wall, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, man... Poor Gumshoe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, did you like the Twin-T set?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I've never paid that much money for lunch before. I was so nervous, my hands were shaking.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So? How did it taste!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well... For 20 bucks, I guess... I dunno how to describe it, really. It was... delicate.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Delicate?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean you liked it!? It didn't taste bad to you?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's the matter with him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like he's thinking...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... That's it! I've been trying to think of the right word to describe the taste. I just got it right now... "Bad"! That's it. It tasted bad!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's kinda hard to admit it to yourself when you pay 20 bucks though, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe he should've found out about the price AFTER he had finished eating...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe that's why Glen Elg came here. Maybe he heard about the famous Twin-T set!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Glen Elg, the victim, huh... Which reminds me. We still hardly know anything about the guy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why don't we ask Gumshoe what he knows, seeing as he's here?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So what were you all excited about earlier?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right! You said you were listening to the radio or something.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, that? That was nothing! I-I wasn't excited!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, Detective Gumshoe! You can tell little ol' me! What were you listening to?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">N-Nothing, really. It was just the, um... "Daily Exercise Show"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What the...!? A Psyche-Lock?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hah hah hah! Mmm... This lunch special's lobster is great!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then why are there tears in your eyes...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, Detective Gumshoe. You can tell us what you were listening to on the radio.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But I already told you. It was the, um... the... weather forecast, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Didn't you say it was an exercise program earlier!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It was nothing, really. Hah hah hah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even if it's nothing, the fact that he's hiding it makes me really curious!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Is that thing real, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why does everybody keep asking me that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I wonder what this phony of yours is like...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He had Maggey found guilty of murder. Doesn't that tell you?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It tells me the guy is cruising for a bruising!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're really caring, aren't you, Detective Gumshoe? About Maggey, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's the sports paper the victim wrote something in, right? ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I know I've heard that name somewhere before... "MC Bomber"... Yeah... I heard it real recently, too...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, he actually seems to be thinking for once!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ack, it's no good. I can't remember...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...And he goes back to being the Gumshoe we all know and love.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I haven't got anything to say about that, pal. ... Just take it away already, please?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Spending 20 dollars on this has got to be killing him inside...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! Are you putting this up for sale, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No! Why, would you want a busted up scooter like this anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. Plus, the seat's all covered in pigeon poop!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Who cares? If it runs, that's all that matters to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>My phony was riding this bike... Maybe if I head back to the park. it'll be there again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A one-way ticket to happiness, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Glen Elg died because of this ticket.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, but it's still a one-way ticket to happiness, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And Maggey was found guilty of murder because of it, too.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Looks like anything about Maggey is an instant conversation stopper.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. He's got a real soft spot for her, and it obviously hurts when you hit it!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's the apron Maggey was wearing. Yeah, it still smells like her, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Does this mean Maggey smells like ketchup?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We never did find the contents of that bag.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It was medicine for Mr. Elg's ruptured eardrum, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. We found traces of it in his left ear canal. He must've used it while he was at Trés Bien. We're sure of that much.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Godot agreed to take this case just so he could face you, pal. He was working on a bunch of more important cases, but he cancelled them all...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? But then... ...why didn't Mr. Godot take this case... ...when Maggey's first trial came up?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. that is kinda odd. I mean, everyone thought the defense was "Phoenix Wright". So why didn't he try to fight "me" then?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, according to Mr. Godot... ...he knew the guy was a phony right away, so he didn't want to bother with the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He couldn't be bothered to tell the judge!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Maggey's probably crying all alone right now, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, thanks to you.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aaaaaaargh! I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya! Don't torch poor Gumshoe feelings like they're are some sort of cheap crème brûlée!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're really crazy about Maggey, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No! No, no! I'm just... I'm not... It's not that I...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You don't have to hide it, Gumshoe! It's pretty obvious.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, you're way too plain-looking for Maggey. Right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'd arrest you right now if you weren't so right...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This guy was a real programming genius. They called him "the walking computer" at the place where he worked.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What happens when he crashes though!? Does he just stop moving all of a sudden!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*groan* He wasn't a computer, Maya!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Anyway, there's nothing between Maggey and the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. That's what we found out yesterday, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Detective Gumshoe. Don't you have any information that's a bit more fun?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">F-Fun? I, uh... Oh! I know! So, have you paid a visit to where Elg worked yet? You might as well.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">His workplace? Where's that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A computer firm called "Blue Screens, Inc." or something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sounds like a real stable company. This could be fun, Nick. Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Computers aren't really my thing, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We'll be fine! I know all about that hi-tech stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder about that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's just around the corner from this joint. You should take a look.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A computer firm called "Blue Screens, Inc." huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I know I look a little rough around the edges. But the truth is, I'm a lot more "detective-like" than I used to be.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? Like what part?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Like the color of my coat.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, but what about what's inside the coat...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You know, in all my years, I've never seen a witness who was that confused before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, you looked pretty confused by his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nothing against old guys, I like them and all... But... He sounded like he was pretty sure about what he saw.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, that's the impression I got, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Me, three... But then, why doesn't even a single part of his testimony corroborate any of the facts?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You know what that chef said to me? "Oh lá lá! Your body is full of la toxins." And then he gave me this bottle.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's in it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't know. The label says, "Juniper". But I'll tell you want. This stuff works like a charm. I slept like a rock last night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh, really... That's nice...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That lady is the boss of Blue Screens, Inc., pal. Yeah... I figure she's clean. She got nothing to hide. She seemed kinda like a doll to me. In a good way and a bad way. ... Kinda makes you think she might be hiding something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think about this, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry, pal... I can't discuss anything connected to the case.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! I thought you said you were going to help us out!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't help you out if I don't have any info!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I suppose the retrial has only just begun...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright, Detective Gumshoe, tell me the truth. What were you listening to?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No way, pal. Now that you've made a big thing out of it, I'm not gonna tell you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We'll see about that, pal. Considering all the noise you were making while you were listening... ...it's pretty clear what kind of radio program it was. I'd say it was related to...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Detective Gumshoe!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah! That's it, pal! You got me. You sure are something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Then how come I'm still seeing the lock? Guess I was wrong... Now, what was it he shouting when he was listening to the radio...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's it! Come on, come on, come on!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Now just call an "8", pal! Come on! I know you can!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Noooooo! That's the wrong number!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It seems so obvious... I'd better ask him again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">D-Don't tell me you're not through yet...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm right, aren't I? You were listening to the lottery results, weren't you? You thought you'd try to win big, just like Glen Elg did!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-It's... It's like you can see right through me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? I've cracked him already...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's why I said it was nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm usually pretty lucky so I figured I'd give it a try.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's with everyone and the lottery...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So? How did it go?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I won 50 cents! It'd be better to win nothing at all than half a lousy buck! I was so mad!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, I know the feeling.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I bought the same kind of ticket as Mr. Elg. When they read those results out on the radio, it really gets your heart pumping! You know they broadcast it live when they're picking the numbers? It's intense, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I bet that's what Glen was listening to on the day he was killed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. What time is it now?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Uh, it's... It's just after 1:30.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And are the lottery results always broadcast at the same time?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. Look, I got this flyer when I bought the ticket.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Millionaire Radio"? That sounds cool! I want to try it, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then buy a ticket, Maya. With your own money!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Apparently everyone's listening to this show now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's because everyone wants money.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">They say that the victim, Glen Elg, was really into gambling.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yep. You can't beat gambling! I love it, too! I won 500 dollars last night playing cards with Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? We were playing for money!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Of course! So you'd better pay up!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You're a smart one! ...Waiting for a cop to be present before asking for the cash!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... I don't see any sign of Mr. Kudo. Do you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe he went to buy another ton of bird seeds. I was kind of hoping he wouldn't be here, anyway. At least, not for now. <thought>Besides, any more seeds today and I'm liable to turn into a real phoenix!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, check this out...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wouldn't get too close to that if I were you. Otherwise you might be in for a shock. My phony must be lurking someplace nearby... Just imagine! A Tiger, loose in the city!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Meanwhile the real Phoenix is like an abandoned chick, lost in a vast urban jungle!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't worry. Someday, you'll grow up and become a ferocious tiger, too! Don't lose hope!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why is she trying to pep-talk me into becoming my phony...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Looking at this orange reminds me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of what?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That you're supposed to eat a lot of them to ward off colds in the winter. You can't have fun during the holidays if you're sick in bed, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Speaking of fun, if we get Maggey acquitted, may be can all get together sometime.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">OK! ...But what do we play with someone who's never even won a game of Tic-Tac-Toe?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How about we change the rules a bit, then? We could play Old Maid, and... um... We could say the person who's left with the old maid at the end is the winner. How's that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Not bad... Not bad at all! We could even rename the game to "Fair Maiden"!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Mr. Armstrong's talking to someone.</line>
<line speaker="???">I'll be back next month.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui! Naturellement! I will be waiting for you!</line>
<line speaker="???">If you haven't got it by then, I'm afraid it might get a little... hot... around here.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Non! I will 'ave everything ready, I promise!</line>
<line speaker="???">I love fire, you know... I love the way it crackles... Hee... Hee... Hee...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Non, non, non! Stop it! I beg you!</line>
<line speaker="???">Then don't let me down... I'll be watching you...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mais, non! Z'is is not necessary! You can trust me, mademoiselle!</line>
<line speaker="???">Talk to anyone... and I'll drive a knife... right through your heart.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh, non! You do not 'ave to worry. You know, you worry far too much. Maybe z'is will 'elp you relax. It is la oil of sandalwood.</line>
<line speaker="???">I do love... raw meat... from time to time... Hee... Hee... Hee...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Aaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="???">I'll be taking my leave... Goodbye... for now!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Urgh! I 'ave la shivers! I must rub some of my oil all over my body before I become z'e nervous wreck! Z'ere. Oh, oui, oui! Z'at feels good!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urgh!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh lá lá! Excusez-moi, monsieur!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-My eyes! My EYES!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Your eyes? If you 'ave trouble wi'z your eyes, you need z'is. La oil of sandalwood!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't this just the leftovers of what you were just using!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mmm. That smells good. Something's bubbling away nicely in that pot. It must be the lobster and abalone fricassée with balsamic vinaigrette.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't that what I ate yesterday for lunch?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, I think it's been permanently burned into my brain now... ...as an example of what truly awful food tastes like.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I bet it'd taste really good if it was prepared well. ...Balsamy even!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't exactly have many customers, do you, Mr. Armstrong?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Non, you are right, monsieur. But per'aps z'at is la perfect time for you to visit me, non? Now I can give you my undivided attention, and cook for you la dish suprême!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Putting on a brave face, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's what girls do, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">But you are right. Business is very difficult z'ese days. Per'aps ze name is la problem. People do not understand it. Z'ey think it is "tray". I just wanted people to think z'at my restaurant was exclusive.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But they think you just serve fast food on cheap, plastic trays?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! That's the kind of thing that can make a girl cry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you forgotten that Mr. Armstrong is a man, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">But z'is restaurant is my life! It is everything to me! I will defend it to la finale! No one will take it from me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So who was that woman you were just talking to?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh lá lá! You saw z'at?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, well... Yes. Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So? Who was she!? She looked so polite and graceful.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">P-Polite!? G-Graceful!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And she likes raw meat and fires, right?</line>
<line speaker="???">I'll be back next month.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui! Naturellement! I will be waiting for you!</line>
<line speaker="???">If you haven't got it by then, I'm afraid it might get a little... hot... around here.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Non! I will 'ave everything ready, I promise!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that I think about it...</thought> Hey, Maya... I think it's pretty clear what kind of conversation they were having.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You think so? Well, then let's show him that piece of evidence and see what happens!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The woman who was here earlier... I take it that she's... um...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Why 'as it come to z'is...? What a tragedy! Suddenly I find myself so deep in la debt. It is a sign of la bad, bad world we live in, uh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No. I'd say it's more of a sign of la bad, bad culinary skills...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Z'e woman who was 'ere... Z'e scary woman... She is from la loan office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Loan office? Is that where you borrowed half a million dollars from?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. Tender Lender, it is called.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Catchy name. Just hearing it makes me wanna borrow some money.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Please! You must not borrow from z'em. If you must, no more z'an ten dollars!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ten dollars? Sounds like your whole monthly stipend, Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! I get a bit more than that, thank you very much!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So Tender Lender is the loan office you borrowed half a million from, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder if they've got anything to do with this case...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I am weak woman. When I am upset, I 'ave to buy something nice to cheer me up. Thanks to 'im loaning me la money, I 'ave to pay back 'alf a million dollars now! I am like 'is slave. I 'ave to do everything z'at 'e tells me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um... Who's this he?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">La Tiger...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The Tiger?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. 'E is la manager of z'e Tender Lender. A terrifying man! La big city mobster! When 'e shouts at me, my knees are trembling and 'is voice is ringing in my ears for 3 days! As soon as I 'ear la noise of z'at battered old scooter 'e rides, I start to cry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A big city mobster who rides a battered old scooter...?</thought> Um, does this guy resemble me by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh, non, non, non! Z'is man 'as a presence! A most formidable personality! Although... Oui, 'e does 'ave la spikey 'air just like you. Oui, z'ere is a resemblance z'ere, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Sounds like this loan office is worth checking out after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">If you want to visit z'e Tender Lender, it is just beyond Vitamin Square.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick... If you need money, I can loan you some... As long as it's less than 3 dollars...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Thanks for the offer... <thought>...Just beyond Vitamin Square, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh, what a beautiful pendant! It would look stunning on me w'iz la earrings!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Please don't steal it again, OK? It's one of a kind!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I could just 'ave a sliver of it, non?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-It's not a block of cheese, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the paper the victim brought with him.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">"MC Bomber"...? Oui...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Does that mean something to you?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Non, I only speak French, mademoiselle.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But we found it behind your magazine rack...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh, 'ow naughty I am! I 'aven't cleaned for such a long time!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh lá lá! So you 'ave eaten my lunch, oui? Tell me, monsieur. Did you enjoy la lunch I prepared for you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was a... unique and... wild mixture of flavors.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That was the first time I ever had lobster, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Lobster? Z'ere was no lobster in my lunch...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? But, it said, "lobster" right on the menu.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mademoiselle Maya. Please, you must read la menu more carefully. It says, "A dish inspired by lobster and abalone fricassée with a balsamic vinaigrette.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh. It's "inspired", is it?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. "Inspired" by z'ese ingredients, but not per'aps made from z'em, n'est-ce pas?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, guess that's the way the cookie crumbles, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The way the lunch tasted, it's probably 99% perspiration and 1% inspiration.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Is z'is your scooter?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no! I saw it before in Vitamin Square, you see...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mon dieu! Non, non, non! Take it away! Do not show z'at to me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Talk about an allergic reaction...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">So long as z'at paper exists, I am but a delightful angel w'iz la broken wings!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">An angel, huh...? Doesn't bode well, when you think about it...</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui! Z'ey kept 'arassing me month after month. In z'e end, I 'ad to give in. I agreed to 'elp z'em.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Help them? With what?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Mais bien sûr, if I did not owe z'em la money, I would 'ave refused. But my 'ands were tied!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please! What did you agree to help them with?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Non. I-I cannot say! If I tell you, z'at woman, she will slice me up... ...and eat me w'iz la salad garnish!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Eww! I hope he doesn't mean that he'll literally be sliced up and served with garnish...</thought> I'm going to guess that woman has something to do with your loan contract. Am I right?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Please, Mr. Armstrong, tell us about that woman!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Ah, it is true. My vases are broken all z'e time. I bought a new one z'e next day after la incident. But z'ey wouldn't let me put it on la table because of la investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">If only I 'ad taken z'e right lottery ticket... I would not 'ave any debts right now. I would be free!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look on the right side, Mr. Armstrong. You won a dollar, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A lack of remorse for having stolen something: Priceless.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh là, là! You 'ave such a pretty smile, my petite chulip!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Who, me?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oui. La smile is the most important thing for us girls, n'est-ce pas?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um... Sure!</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">You 'ave la perfect face for a waitress, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, thanks. I guess if things don't work out someday, then maybe I'll be back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What things? Is she talking about her being a spirit medium...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Oh, 'ow it 'urts me to see z'at poor girl's face!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maggey's?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">I 'eard she was super'umanly un'appy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Superhumanly...?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">And if she 'adn't come to work for me, she wouldn't 'ave got into z'is mess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? I'm missing something here, aren't I?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Je suis désolé, Maggey! Forgive me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! This place is so hi-tech! You can almost smell the electricity in the air!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It is a computer firm, Maya. They can't work without electricity, you know.</line>
<line speaker="???">Who are you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, umm... Hello...</line>
<line speaker="???">I'm sorry. Access is restricted to authorized personnel only. This is a computer programming laboratory. There are far too many trade secrets that could be leaked.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! What secrets!?</line>
<line speaker="???">Everything you see here is classified. No information can leave this building.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Understood!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who is this woman? She's like a robot from some kind of whacked edumacational show...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Basil">My name is Lisa Basil. I'm the company director.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Director!? <thought>Sh-She's human!? She seems more like a ghost in a shell. And that thing over her eye... Isn't that the same device as Glen Elg's?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's an [sic] DMH, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nice try, but it's the other way around, Maya. It's an HMD.</line>
<line speaker="Basil">All of my programmers here at Blue Screens, Inc. are supplied with HMDs.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then do you write programs, too?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">No. I just enjoy wearing this.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They ARE pretty cool! I wouldn't mind one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Those pillars almost look like they're moving. It's kind of unsettling.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nah, they just look a bit twisted or warped or whatever word I'm looking for...</line>
<line speaker="Basil">This office was designed with a futuristic feel in mind.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Futuristic?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">Yes. We tried to imagine what things might look like in the future when we designed it. It helps to soothe and calm the soul.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... On second thought, I agree with you, Nick. This place is really unsettling.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, look Nick! It's a super-computer! It looks like it's really smart and wise, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Computers are only as smart as the humans who use them, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That explains why we don't use the computer in our office!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You work there too, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, but at least I'm...</line>
<line speaker="Basil">Please. Don't argue about something that's so trivial. Otherwise the computer will laugh at you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She said she'd laugh at us, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's a human, Maya, not a computer!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's really pounding that keyboard, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! I bet that's where the "pro" in "programmer" comes from, huh? I guess I shouldn't be resting on my laurels. Gotta expand my skill set and all that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, that's a good idea.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe I could become Old Seedy's apprentice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Um... And what about your spirit medium training?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Look at this mess!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like they're all betting tickets.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What kind of betting tickets?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">For betting on which horse will win a given race. They're horse racing tickets.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, wow... His drawers are stuffed full of these...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like they're all losing tickets, though.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">This many tickets would get you... what? A buck down at the recycling center? You're hopeless, Nick. You know what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm just taking them as evidence, Maya!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Look at this mess!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like they're all betting tickets.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What kind of betting tickets?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">For betting on which horse will win a given race. They're horse racing tickets.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, wow... His drawers are stuffed full of these...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like they're all losing tickets, though.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa! Look at this desk, Nick! What a mess!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks pretty average to me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But you can't get any work done with everything all over the place like this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You think? Real whiz-kids can work under any condition, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's trying to hint that I should tidy my desk more. I'll clean up my desk when Maya stops asking silly questions... No hurry then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! This calendar...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about it...? If this is another hint about tidying, you can forget it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Someone's marked December 3rd in red pen!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">December 3rd? That's the day Mr. Elg was murdered! Is there anything else?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. Umm... It says, "Meet with The Tiger."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The T-Tiger?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa! Look at this desk, Nick! What a mess!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks pretty average to me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But you can't get any work done with everything all over the place like this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You think? Real whiz-kids can work under any condition, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's trying to hint that I should tidy my desk more. I'll clean up my desk when Maya stops asking silly questions... No hurry then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... What exactly is this firm's business?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">I will try to simplify it so that you can understand... We analyze the data management systems required by certain branches of industry... ...and deliver optimum operating system and source-level components.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? You lost me on the corner of Analyze and Management.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It doesn't matter. They analyze stuff. You got that much, right?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">The software we produce is distributed on CDs.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">CDs...?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">Yes. Compact disc. Digital optical storage media.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Of course, CDs are used for software as well as music...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Basil">It is a small firm, but all of my employees are first-class programmers. Let's ask one of them what they are doing. Excuse me. What are you working on right now?</line>
<line speaker="Programmer">I'm researching the impact of time-slicing common areas in multi-threaded code on logical access to shared global variables. Obviously, program structure heavily influences response time and performance, so the co-independence of global variables and memory overheads is vitally important to the success of the execution.</line>
<line speaker="Basil">Well, you get the idea. This is the sort of thing we are involved in. Did you good people follow all of that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-Y-Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Your blank smile just said otherwise, Maya.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know about what happened, right, Ms. Basil?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">You mean about Glen being poisoned? Yes, I know. It's terrible.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Can you tell us anything that might be helpful?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">I don't think so. A police officer was here earlier, too. But I couldn't tell him anything either, because... ...the waitress who committed the crime has nothing to do with Blue Screens, Inc.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How about Mr. Elg's desk? Have you cleared it out already?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">No, not yet. It's the one, right in front of you. If there's anything that might be useful to you, you are welcome to take it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess there might be a clue here somewhere...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, about Mr. Elg... Was he in some kind of trouble?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">I'm sorry? Why would you think that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I thought you said something about it just now? You said he got himself into trouble because he was a bit of a "loser".</line>
<line speaker="Basil">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A Psyche-Lock?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess Mr. Elg is like every other man with his pile of secrets.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please tell us more about the trouble that Mr. Elg was in.</line>
<line speaker="Basil">I'm sorry. I don't know anything about that.</line>
<line speaker="Basil">I do not pry into other people's affairs.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She just gave us the dreaded "professional, business-like cold-shoulder", huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I need to find out exactly what the victim was involved in. Looks like I've got to break her in a "professional, business-like" manner!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, about Mr. Elg...</line>
<line speaker="Basil">He was a top programmer. I would even say he was a genius. But he did suffer from one or two bugs in his personality.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh? Like what?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">He was a bit of a "loser"... Perhaps that would be the best way to describe it. That's what got him into trouble... ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">He was a top programmer. I would even say he was a genius. So he was really no trouble at all. A model employee.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, wait a minute! Just now you said something about him being in trouble! <thought>We've got to find out what this trouble was exactly.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm, would you mind taking a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">I'm sorry. That data is SuPer-Admin Restricted Desktop Access password-protected.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">SuPer Admin Restricted Desktop Access password-protected!? What!? This is madness!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Maya. That is SPARDA. She won't tell us unless we say the right code word.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A code word? Hmm... ... Sesame!</line>
<line speaker="Basil">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If it's not "sesame", then it must be her mother's maiden name. That's how it always is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no point in having a password if it's always the same thing, Maya. <thought>I guess she just doesn't want to talk about this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe we should focus on asking about Glen Elg. What do you say?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I'm gonna head back to the precinct now. We've got a big meeting starting in a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">About Maggey's case, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No, that's pretty much wrapped up now... There's another big case going down at the moment, so she's been pushed aside...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">OK. Well, see you later then.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Bye!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......... Y-You better get going, Detective, or you'll be late.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Actually, I, um... I've kinda got a favor to ask. It's a big one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A favor?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah... It's for, um... Maggey, actually. I was kinda hoping... you'd give this to her for me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's a lunchbox. I got up early so I could make it. I've been real worried about her. She looked like she'd lost a lot of weight.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Detective Gumshoe... ... How many weenies are in here!? There's not a person on earth who could down this much meat.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You think? I love weenies. I can't get enough of their tender juiciness. So will you give to her? It took me ages to make, so please say you will, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't exactly say no, can I?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe I'll eat it myself if I get hungry!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't forget, OK? I'm counting on you to give that to Maggey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's finally gone...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...This place gives off a really strange vibe, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like "The Tiger" isn't in his lair. <thought>And that is, as they say, a very good thing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...Welcome...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*gulp* <thought>Talk about a creepy voice! It makes your soul want to shrivel up and die!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">You're here... to discuss a loan...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, no. Not exactly...</line>
<line speaker="???">The manager is away at the moment... Wait quietly... please...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She's gone! Just like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess we'll just have to come back another time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But this is the perfect opportunity, Nick! This place reeks of suspicion! Come on, Nick! Let's take a look around, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you think it'd be OK...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Of course! No one will ever know...</line>
<line speaker="???">...Coffee...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="???">I'll leave it here for you to enjoy... Quietly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes! Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="???">Do not touch the desk... Please...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-N-Nick! Let's g-get out of here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>NOW She wants to get out of here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's one impressive desk on one impressive rug!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's solid gold, Nick! Gold! Just look at that shine! Only real gold shines like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you really want such a shiny desk, though?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't know, but let's see what it's like to sit at a solid gold desk... Wow! I'm completely dazzled!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's because it's completely dazzling!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can see up my nose in the reflection! That's gotta be really distracting!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So the desk isn't practical. No surprise there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a punching bag.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? No way. You wouldn't catch me walking around with a bag like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean, "walking around"?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The design's gross to start with, and it's way too heavy to be practical. And why's it called a "punching"-bag? Don't people know messenger bags are in! I knew it. I was right before, back at Trés Bien. Paris fashion is more my thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I really, really hope she's pulling my chain on this one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a CD player on the desk. But the desk is so loud, it's a wonder you can hear it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The lid's open. I wonder what kind of music The Tiger's into.</line>
<line speaker="???">Have you finished... ...the coffee?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, thanks. It was... lovely.</line>
<line speaker="???">... So... You drank it... all? Hee... Hee... Hee...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="???">...If you touch anything else that doesn't belong to you... There's always another cup...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Th-That coffee! I-It was laced with something! I'm almost sure of it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! My stomach... It's killing me! ... Oh, wait. Maybe it was just the burger I ate for breakfast...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I sure hope so... <thought>We better take a look at that CD while we're still alive and have the chance...</thought> What the...!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? It's not the Rocko soundtrack, is it? Claw of the Tiger?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's... It's a demo CD... The artist's name has been hand-written on the disc in pen. "MC Bomber"...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">WHAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This must be the CD Maggey told us about!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's listen to it! I bet it's heavy metal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No way! That woman'll make us drink more coffee if we do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a CD player on the desk. But the desk is so loud, it's a wonder you can hear it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The lid's open. I wonder what kind of music The Tiger's into.</line>
<line speaker="???">Have you finished... ...the coffee?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, thanks. It was... lovely.</line>
<line speaker="???">... So... You drank it... all? Hee... Hee... Hee...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="???">...If you touch anything else that doesn't belong to you... There's always another cup...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Th-That coffee! I-It was laced with something! I'm almost sure of it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! My stomach... It's killing me! ... Oh, wait. Maybe it was just the burger I ate for breakfast...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I sure hope so...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's see... This round doll thing is called a "daruma"... I think. I figured I'd read a book or two and be more cultured, in case you're wondering.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean you aren't making stuff up for a change?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Heh. I bet you also didn't know that no matter what, he'll always right himself. Go on, Nick! Give him a good shove!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Only if I feel like dying!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now, this yellow thing... This is a Japanese chess piece. I think it's a "king"? Not that I'm an expert or anything... I'm more of a Reversi person, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Assuming she knows what she's talking about, these aren't exactly your typical... ..."mobster wannabe" items. They're not... "trophies", are they...? *gulp*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey... There's a piece of paper sticking out from under here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it? ...A repair bill? <thought>Looks like he did some repair work on his car... Does he even have one...?</thought> $15,000 to replace a bumper and a light!? That's insane!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The car's registered to... the "Cadaverinis"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? So it's not even The Tiger's car? <thought>Why would someone else's repair bill be in The Tiger's office...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Win Through Compromise"...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder what that's supposed to mean...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It must mean something if they took the trouble to frame it like that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah well, it still doesn't make any sense to me...</line>
<line speaker="???">...That...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="???">That's Tender Lender's guiding principle.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="???">"Compromise the customer to win."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">O-Oh, I see... How about you, Nick...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, umm... Well, as long as we don't have to compromise my hair, I'd say we're OK... <thought>That's one slogan no business owner should ever explain to their customers... *shudder*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, no. Someone's dropped the ashtray on the floor. That's going to be a nightmare to clean up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. It's all over the rig and everything.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I accidentally knocked over a really big space heater once. Cleaning up was such a pain. It was one of those super antiques where you have to burn a ton of charcoal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How did she manage to knock one of those over? Aren't they supposed to be super heavy?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, hey! There's a book of matches here, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Matches, huh? Places don't give those out much nowadays. ...Hey, wait a second!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look what's printed on the back! It says, "Trés Bien"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>These matches could come in handy. We might be able to use them...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. The pilot light for the office boiler keeps going out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Swing and a miss, Maya. Swing and a miss.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, no. Someone's dropped the ashtray on the floor. That's going to be a nightmare to clean up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. It's all over the rig and everything.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I accidentally knocked over a really big space heater once. Cleaning up was such a pain. It was one of those super antiques where you have to burn a ton of charcoal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How did she manage to knock one of those over? Aren't they supposed to be super heavy?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, look at this Parisian-style coat! It's so chic!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks more like a pimp coat to me... Guess I haven't got an eye for fashion.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, look at this... This suit is the same color as the one you wear, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... The same color as my suit...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Keep your voice down, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! You've got to take a look at this!</line>
<line speaker="???">Some cake...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="???">I'll just leave it here for you...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh... yeah... sure... I, umm... Thanks...</line>
<line speaker="???">Just wait here quietly... Otherwise...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">S-S-Sure! Did you hear that, Nick? Wait quietly, she said!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah! Sure!</line>
<line speaker="???">I have my eye on you... Only so I can "take care of you".... Understand...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aah! I'm scared, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...So? What were you getting so excited about before?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look, on the lapel of this suit...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's...! That's an attorney's badge!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is The Tiger a lawyer!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No way! Look at this badge! It's made of paper!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">For some reason, your badge suddenly looks really cheap to me, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why doesn't anyone recognize an obviously fake badge when they see one...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, look at this Parisian-style coat! It's so chic!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks more like a pimp coat to me... Guess I haven't got an eye for fashion.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, look at this... This suit is the same color as the one you wear, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... The same color as my suit...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Keep your voice down, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! You've got to take a look at this!</line>
<line speaker="???">Some cake...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="???">I'll just leave it here for you...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh... yeah... sure... I, umm... Thanks...</line>
<line speaker="???">Just wait here quietly... Otherwise...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">S-S-Sure! Did you hear that, Nick? Wait quietly, she said!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah! Sure!</line>
<line speaker="???">I have my eye on you... Only so I can "take care of you".... Understand...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aah! I'm scared, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come out from under the desk, Maya!</thought></line>
<line speaker="The Tiger">Whad are youse two snoopin' around in my office for!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-Nothing. W-We were just...</line>
<line speaker="The Tiger">Gwoaaaaaaaaaaaaaar! My precious carpet! Youse got ash on my rug! You' gonna wish your ugly feet never came through my door!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-It wasn't us! It was already like th--</line>
<line speaker="The Tiger">Youse wanna argue with me!? Is that what you' doin'? You dink youse can take me on!? I'm gonna flatten youse two into pancakes and turn youse into my new rugs!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="???">...Oh... Don Tigre... You're back...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ack... That voice... It's like evil seeping into your head through your ears...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...I'm sorry... Don Tigre... I knocked over that ashtray before... and...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Eek! Has she got a death wish or what!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="The Tiger">... Oh, right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="The Tiger">F-Forget about it, Violetta. I-It's noddin'...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What, what, what!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="The Tiger">I ain't gonna get mad at you. You' too cute, you hear!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's so unfair!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Here... Have some cookies... I just baked them... And you'll need some strong espresso... while you're discussing your loan...</line>
<line speaker="The Tiger">Gwoaaaaaaaaaaaaaar! Phoenix Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes!?</line>
<line speaker="The Tiger">Youse either crazy or just plain stupid to chase after me! I worked so hard, but now youse gotta come and mess up my plan...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So it was him... He's my phony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="The Tiger">Heh, but I don't care. No one gets in my way!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What? I mean, e-excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="The Tiger">Heh heh heh! Youse shoulda left de little girl at home, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... I have a few things I want to ask</line>
<line speaker="The Tiger">Gwoaaaaaaaaaaaaaar!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="The Tiger">No questions! Dis is de last time we meet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! Wait! P-Please!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...That was pretty weak, Nick. You waited until he was out of earshot before you shouted after him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Like you're one to talk! I didn't hear you scream, "<cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn>" either!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...The espresso...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="???">...And cookies...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This woman is definitely not good for my heart. Now, what was it The Tiger called her...? "Violetta"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... I'm kind of curious about your company, Tender Lender...</line>
<line speaker="Violetta">...With the warm and friendly atmosphere you'd expect from a family-sized business... ...a conscientious rate of interest... and an attractive repayment policy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I get the feeling this sentence is not going to end well...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Violetta">...we will tenderly lend you that little bit extra, here at Tender Lender.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick. Things are a bit tight for Wright and Co. at the moment, aren't they? I mean there's that 500 dollars you owe me from our card game for starters. Why don't you take out a loan?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Would I like to take out a loan from a place like this? Not so much...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Violetta">Tender Lender is... on your side... Hee... Hee... Hee...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, um, let's say I'm late with my repayment... What happens then?</line>
<line speaker="Violetta">...We'd give you more coffee... ...Strong coffee...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, right... I think I'd rather skip down!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Just remember I can make strong coffee too, Nick! Strong tea, as well!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, um, do you know about the incident we're investigating?</line>
<line speaker="Violetta">What incident...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, a man was poisoned in a restaurant just near here. That incident.</line>
<line speaker="Violetta">Let me see... I was here that day, with the manager...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The manager being The Tiger...?</line>
<line speaker="Violetta">...Furio Tigre...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">F-Furio...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...T-Tigre? <thought>So that's where the "Tiger" thing comes from...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Xin Eohp's got a real name! Nick! Hurry up and find out more about him!</line>
<line speaker="Violetta">I'm very... frail, you see... Just recently, I... died... Once... Hee... Hee...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You d-died!?</line>
<line speaker="Violetta">About 4 months ago... The doctors said to... abandon all hope...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess they were expecting her to take a boat ride across the River Styx.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Violetta">But Don Tigre... He saved me. He gave up everything...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Everything!?</line>
<line speaker="Violetta">When I found out what he had done for me, I... was happy...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No offense, but I'm finding that a little hard to believe.</line>
<line speaker="Violetta">I decided I'd pay back... with my life... by serving him coffee... and espresso...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I still wonder about what's in her coffee...</thought> So... is that why you've got that bandage around your head?</line>
<line speaker="Violetta">Hee... Hee... Hee... This?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, so what's the story with the bandage?</line>
<line speaker="Violetta">... They put it on after the operation...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Operation?</line>
<line speaker="Violetta">It's just a little injury... A little, fatal, injury... Hee... Hee... Hee...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A f-f-fatal injury!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya just suffered one herself, by the sound of it...</thought> So, that's the injury you were talking about before when you said you had died once?</line>
<line speaker="Violetta">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Urgh! She really creeps me out, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Same here. But we've got to find out the truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Violetta">It was very complicated... The operation... They opened up my head... And performed surgery on my frontal lobe...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Urgh! Just thinking about it sends shivers down my spine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So how did you get this "fatal injury" that left you needing an operation?</line>
<line speaker="Violetta">I made a promise to Don Tigre... I said I would never tell... Cross my heart and hope to drink 100 cups of espresso...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh. <thought>That much caffeine would raise anyone from the dead!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Violetta">Besides... It's a very precious memory to me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A... A precious memory...? <thought>I'll never find out what she means if I can't break her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can I ask you about The Tiger, I mean, Mr. Tigre?</line>
<line speaker="Violetta">...Cookie...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">S-Sure...?</line>
<line speaker="Violetta">How do you like my cookies? I baked them myself... Hee... Hee... Hee...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Go ahead, Nick! The honor is all yours!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no! Ladies first, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Violetta">Hee... Hee... Hee...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No matter how I look at this, I just don't get it... What are The Tiger and this scary girl doing working together?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Violetta">We... are lovers...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's exactly coming across in your tone of voice...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Violetta">And I owe Don Tigre my life... He's the one who saved me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Tiger... saved you...!?</line>
<line speaker="Violetta">Please, address him properly as "Don Tigre". Otherwise, I'll have to...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK, OK! Don Tigre! Of course! I'm sorry. <thought>He saved her life? I'd sure like to how that happened.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, about this...</line>
<line speaker="Violetta">More coffee...? You must have more...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No! Um, thanks! I've had enough. Really! <thought>I'm so thirsty!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Violetta">I don't leave the office... I can't tell you about anything... except Don Tigre.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There he is! Old Seedy's back feeding the pigeons again!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">There! Take this! And this! And get out of my park!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Like I thought, he's really mad... Come on, Maya. Just keep your head down and let's sneak away while we still can...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What? Why? Hellooo, old man!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you doing, Maya!?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Huh!? ...Kah!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, he just turned his back on us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not surprised. I bet I really hurt his pride in court this morning.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Mr. Kudo!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Hmm, ha-hmm, hmm... Hmm, pi-pi-pigeon, hmm... Kah!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look, we really need to talk to you, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Out with the demons! In with good fortune!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ow! Ow! Ow! Seeds... Shell splinters... Painful...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I always knew you were a demon, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... I'm sorry about what happened in court earlier today.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Kah! Everyone'll be talking about me behind my back now! A dirty old man who was so busy looking at the serving girl's backside... ...that he can't remember her face! A filthy, depraved animal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-Not at all!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Are you listening to me, boy!? I don't care what you say, I saw that waitress put it in! She put some white powder into the young lad's javaccino!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We hear you...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">And another thing! The young layabout was wearing an earpiece! On the same side as the lens of his broken spectacles!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-We're really sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">So I made a little mistake about the vase. So what!? I know what I saw! I tell you, I tell you, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK, OK! Take it easy, please, Mr. Kudo.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Don't tell me to take it easy, you spikey-haired brat! Take this!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um... You said you were a craftsman, right?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Kah! The modern world casts honest craftsmen like me aside in droves!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">S-Surely it's not that...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">I come from a long line of craftsmen. Right back to the time of the shoguns! Do you hear me!? I didn't become an embroiderer, I was BORN one!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Actually... I'm kind of in the same situation myself.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">I... I... I wanted to stick my fingers up that dribbling old judge's nose... ...and scream right down his earhole... "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>"</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh... So, did you want to become a lawyer when you were young...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think that's quite it, Maya. I think he's just in a bad mood, that's all...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">I've got a tsunami of frustration inside and it's ready to burst out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If we let him start rambling now, we might never shut him up! What should I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, actually, we've got places to go, things to check and stuff... Maybe another time?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Fine! Whatever! Just don't forget! I've got a tsunami's worth of grumbling to do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, yes. This girl right here is really looking forward to hearing it all. Honest!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? I never said that!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Come to the place where I work, then. Here. Bring this along with you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is this? It's covered in seeds... A discount coupon for a burger!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">He really wants someone to grumble at, huh? ...Although, it IS a burger joint...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess I better let him talk...</thought> So, there's not much call for craftsmen these days, then?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Of course not, you idiot! All I'm good for nowadays is running errands!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Errands?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Everyone takes advantage of the elderly! "Buy some bread, gramps!" "Take the dog for a walk, granddad!" "Feed the pigeons, old man!" What am I? Some sort of two-bit community handyman!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, well...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">"Buy some bread", now that I can understand. But what's the point of feeding some seedy pigeons!? Why don't people say what they mean!? "Get lost!" That's what they're trying to say! Oh, yes! I'm just an inconvenience, you see! At home... At that restaurant... I just get in the way, don't I!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm sure you don't. <thought>Wait a minute! What did he just say? At home and... at that restaurant?</thought> Hold up... By "restaurant", are you talking about Trés Bien? Did you get asked to run an errand there, too?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Yes, I did! The very day that young brat was poisoned.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WH-WHAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So on the day of the incident, what were you asked to do?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Glad you asked, boy! Because I'll tell you what I was asked to do! All of a sudden that young lad slumped over the table... The serving girl collapsed... And I broke that vase. It all happened so fast, I was in a bit of a daze, you see. Then the owner shouted over to me.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">"Excusez-moi! You! Call la police!"</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">"Call them yourself!" I should have said back. But I didn't think of it at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, did you end up calling the police?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Like I said, I was in a bit of a daze.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you call them on your cell phone?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Kah! Do I look like I'd have one of those new-fangled thingamajigs? I went out looking for a pay phone, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You went looking for one...?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">I couldn't find one right away, you know. Wandered around for 5 minutes or so.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">F-Five minutes...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So for five minutes after the incident happened...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Yessiree, the owner was at Trés Bien on his own.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why didn't you mention this in court this morning?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Well, I would have if you'd given me the chance! But you all bullied me out of the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*sigh* Thank you, Mr. Kudo. You've certainly earned your kudos for today.</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">WAIT! WAIT A MINUTE! If that's the case, there's more! I've got more to say! Oh, yes! I remember something else...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Escort the witness out of the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">It's not my fault! You're the ones to blame!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You could have at least told us before we got to court.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is it really that important that Mr. Kudo was the one who called the police...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's important is the unaccounted time before the police arrived. The victim was dead, and Maggey was unconscious. Which leaves that woman... I mean, that man, alone in the restaurant!</thought> Mr. Kudo might have been chased out of the place on purpose.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe a certain someone didn't want him in the restaurant.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Oh, sure! You go ahead and say I was in the way as usual! I suppose I should've been getting myself covered in pigeon poop instead, hmm? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We need to get more details about what exactly happened... ...from Maggey... and from Mr. Armstrong!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So on the day of the incident, what were you asked to do?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Glad you asked, boy! Because I'll tell you what I was asked to do! All of a sudden that young lad slumped over the table... The serving girl collapsed... And I broke that vase. It all happened so fast, I was in a bit of a daze, you see. Then the owner shouted over to me.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">"Excusez-moi! You! Call la police!"</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">"Call them yourself!" I should have said back. But I didn't think of it at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, did you end up calling the police?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Like I said, I was in a bit of a daze.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you call them on your cell phone?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Kah! Do I look like I'd have one of those new-fangled thingamajigs? I went out looking for a pay phone, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You went looking for one...?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">I couldn't find one right away, you know. Wandered around for 5 minutes or so.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">F-Five minutes...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So for five minutes after the incident happened...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">Yessiree, the owner was at Trés Bien on his own.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, would you mind taking a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">... Kah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Kudo">You let me get a million of my grumbles off my chest, and I'll take one quick look. I've got an earthquake of frustration inside and it's ready to rumble!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...On second thought, forget it. A million grumbles for one quick look doesn't sound like a good deal... for me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Looks like Mr. Armstrong's out again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the place is open for business... You can't have an open restaurant without a chef!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! It's not my fault, Nick! Don't take it out on me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Only a couple of minutes after the incident happened... Mr. Kudo left the scene, leaving Mr. Armstrong here alone.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Argh... Missing when we need to talk to him the most.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe he's trying to avoid us on purpose?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Oh, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hello, Maggey. So they finished questioning you?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Wasn't it just unbelievable in court today, sir!? I'm going to stay up all night and blog about everything that happened!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Weren't you scared? It was pretty touch and go in there.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yeah, but you totally nailed that old man!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, he was all over the place with his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">He's not the only one!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Everyone else's testimonies don't match up either. Not with what I remember of the incident, anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is it possible she is the one misremembering things...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maggey... You know how you said that everyone else... ...provided testimony that didn't match up with what you remembered?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yup. There are just so many things that don't seem to add up. The biggest contradiction is the other guy I saw at the victim's table. HE was the one who slipped something into the victim's coffee. I'm sure it was him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But didn't Mr. Kudo testify earlier today... ...that it was the waitress who put some white powder into the coffee cup...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So you really think it was this "disappearing man" that did it...?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Well, he's not the only thing that disappeared. The CD vanished as well. You know, the CD with the writing on it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, yeah. The "MC Screwdriver" album, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was "MC Bomber", Maya. That name was scrawled on the sports paper as well.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">They never did find that CD at the crime scene, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Or the victim's medication. That's gone missing, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ouch, my head... This is getting way too complicated for me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You said that you passed out when the victim, Glen Elg, collapsed, right?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yes. It's so embarrassing. I mean, I used to be a cop! When I came to, the restaurant was buzzing with police. And before I knew what was going on, they arrested me, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So between the time the victim collapsed and the time the police arrived on the scene... ...you have no idea what went on at Trés Bien.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">No. No idea at all. Why? Is it important, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The other witness, the old man from the park, was pretty much chased out of the picture.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">"Chased out of the picture"? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Old Seedy wasn't inside the restaurant because he was told to go call the police.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. And you, Maggey, were unconscious. That means Mr. Armstrong was alone in the restaurant for a brief period of time.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">No... Y-You don't think Mr. Armstrong... set me up... do you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When you consider the facts... ...it's hard to imagine that Mr. Armstrong isn't involved in this at all.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Grr! It's like the master biting the paw of the dog that it feeds! Are you sure about this, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, the old man said as much when we spoke with him earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I don't know. The things that man says don't add up for some reason, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maggey looks like she's trying to figure something out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">We'd better find outexactly what happened to the old man on that day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is there anything about Mr. Kudo's testimony that stood out as odd to you?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Actually... Yes. The fact that he was even testifying to begin with doesn't quite...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...? "Doesn't quite" what?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Well, when I took the coffee over to the victim's table... ...it's true there was another customer in the restaurant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, we know that already. It was Victor Kudo.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">But I can't really say it was an old man.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">OK, then how about calling him a really old middle-aged man!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">No, age isn't the issue. The other customer was a woman.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A woman!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Are you sure, Maggey!?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Well, I'm not a hundred percent sure, but I think so.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So? What did this woman look like?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Umm... She was sort of creepy... And she had a kind of cackling laugh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Creepy"?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Cackling"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I get the feeling I've come across a woman like that recently?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">That's the paper the victim had with him, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's what we think, madam.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I kind of remember him having a paper, actually. And I remember something about this "MC Bomber", too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It was written on the CD that disappeared as well, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I don't suppose it makes any difference if there was one CD or two, right?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Just thinking about the trial that day gives me the creeps.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Was it that bad?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Don't forget that was my phony, not me!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">He was supposed to say, "Surely the defendant isn't the real criminal!" But instead he shouted out, "Surely the defendant is the real criminal!" ...By mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, ouch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">L-Like I said, that was my phony, not me!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I...! I don't want to think about it anymore...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Trust me, neither do I...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Ah, I feel much better after the trial this morning. I've been a bit of a courtroom proceedings addict for years now. It feels like forever since I was a witness as slippery as that old man!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's not really that bad of an old man though.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Still, I feel a bit uneasy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? I thought you just said you felt much better...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maggey. If there's something on your mind, you've got to tell us. Especially if it has anything to do with Mr. Kudo or his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Roger! I'll spill it all and see what you make of it!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">That's the cup I took over to the table, sir. But! I didn't put anything in it... I just... I could never do something like that!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's right! You could never do anything like that!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I'm not good at carrying those large trays, you know. Trying to balance a tray with one hand to put something in the coffee with the other... That'd just be asking for trouble. I'd drop something, for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Th-That's right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I-Is she expecting me to claim that she's too clumsy to have committed the crime...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Oh, yeah. That's from when I was carrying a customer's breakfast over to them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The ketchup splotch, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">My whole face was fire-engine red, thanks to that stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But you spilled the ketchup in your apron, didn't you? I don't see how...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">The ketchup-covered omelet went flying and hit the customer in the face.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, talk about a tomato-red face! Makes me wish I could've seen it myself.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yeah, I guess... It was kind of a sight to behold.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Potassium cyanide? I've never heard of that poison before in my life, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">OK, maybe I have. But I've never seen it before. That's the truth. I wouldn't even know where the nearest potassium cyanide dealer is in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Potassium cyanide dealers? Sounds like another group of drug pushers to avoid...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In any case, this definitely isn't something you can pick up just anywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Ooh!! Curse my rotten luck! The criminal must've stuck the bottle in my apron while I was unconscious!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, yeah! I've got something you're going to love!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Really? What is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A lunchbox, just for you. Here!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Wow! A lunchbox! Weenies, too! I can't believe it! Thank you, sir! Did you make this just for me, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nah, it was Detective Gumshoe! Who else would make such a nice lunchbox for you?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's really worried about you. Looks like he put a lot of effort into making this, too!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">... I can't accept it. Detention Center rules. No gifts allowed, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, come on, Maggey. Don't be like that.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">The rules are the rules! They'll lock you up if you break them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Somehow, when an ex-cop turned waitress says that, it seems a whole lot scarier.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">And anyway... I hate weenies!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">O-Oh... really?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">It's all yours, Maya! You can enjoy it with Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... She's right... It's better than letting it go to waste.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But! ...I guess so.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">... Well? How was it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That hit the spot! I love weenies.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Oh, good! I'm glad I gave it to you, then, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Ah! Is that... your attorney's badge?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, it's a fake.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Hoooly smokes! That's it!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">That's the badge your phony had, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You got duped by this...!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But it's a completely different color!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what about the fact that it's made of paper!?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">He said the badge got a tan as well, while he was in Hawaii on business.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm beginning to see how my phony was able to gain her trust...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Ah! That's the victim, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That day was the first time you'd ever seen this man, right?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yes. I'd never met or seen him before then. I just happened to be the waitress who served him his coffee, sir. That's all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seems he was a computer programmer.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Really? I'm useless with computers. Completely hopeless. I don't know any computer programs.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Did she mean "programmers"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Back when I was an officer, Detective Gumshoe always looked out for me. But today! Today was the one who had to look out for him; trying to incriminate me the whole crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've got to remember, Maggey. Gumshoe's a detective. He's got a job to do.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">My old boss... I thought at least he'd be on my side.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He is on your side! He'd do anything to help y--</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">You can't fool me! I saw him in court today! I felt like a poor little baby woodpecker being pecked on the head by its own mother!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gumshoe's testimony was pretty solid... No wonder it hurt her so much.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I hate him, sir! I mean it! I don't ever want to see him again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ouch. I think I just saw Gumshoe's chances go down in flames like the Hinderburg...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't think it's getting through to her that he really was trying to help...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Mr. Armstrong was very good to me after I was fired from the force. I can't believe someone as nice as him could have anything to do with this...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, in the time between the victim being poisoned and the police being called... ...the only person who was on the scene and had a chance to do anything... ...was Mr. Armstrong. There was no one else there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">M-Mr. Armstrong wouldn't... He wouldn't set me up... would he!?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Hoooly smokes! That's him!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">That's your phony, Mr. Wright! Just look at that ridiculous suntan!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... For the record, I'm not sunburned like an over-dried tomato so I don't know...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">He told me he'd been on a business trip to Hawaii and that's where he got the tan.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not hearing this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I know I used to be in the police force. But I'm incarcerated, now. I don't pick up much information in here. All I can help you out with now is the menu at Trés Bien.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, come on, Maggey. Don't let your spirits fall!</line>
<line speaker="Detective">The main server just went up in smoke! Why the heck isn't the press conference set up yet!? The Superintendent's here already!</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Yeah. And there's a problem with the Internet, too.</line>
<line speaker="Detective">I already told you to stop using your computer, Chief!</line>
<line speaker="Chief">But I'm watching videos online! I'm catching up on my Asian soap operas!</line>
<line speaker="Detective">It's gonna have to wait, Chief. I'm throwing the switch!</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Nooo! Just when Sum Yung-Gai was about to confess to his son's hot-to-trot girlfriend!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! This place is really buzzing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something must be going down. Something really big.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh!? What are you doing here, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You can't be here right now. You'll be roped into the briefing if you stay.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We've got big problems here today.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why? What's going on?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's a virus! A virus!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A virus?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's a virus ripping through the precinct's computer system.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But I really need to ask you some questions...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Detective">"Your batteries won't last forever. Remember that when you're having fun... in bed." We have a winner! A little joke to make people think about their smoke alarms. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He must be coming up with slogans for a fire safety campaign... ...I guess? ...Does he even know what he's trying to get across anymore?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be the chief of the detectives here. He looks lost, now that the power to his computer has been cut.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Oh, well. I guess I'll just have to read the paper now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Alternately, you could read some reports... Just a suggestion.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Chief">What the heck is this!? This paper's more than a month old! And someone's written all over it! Who's the clown that put this on my desk? Well? Speak up!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He just wadded it up and chucked it in the trash!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that's an important piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OK, I'm only gonna say this once, so listen up!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No matter how poor you get, never borrow money from a place like this, you hear?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um... OK...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If you got money trouble, just go on a diet of instant noodles and hang in there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, we're not thinking about borrowing money, Detective! We want information.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh... Is that all? Well, let's see... Tender Lender is considered to be even fishier than the average illegal loan shark. And it seems it ran into trouble just recently. Those guys have been pretty heavy-handed, calling in all their debts.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't go poking your nose around in their business, pal. You'll really regret it if you upset that lady.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright, I get the picture. <thought>Hey, wait a minute! What did he just say!? "That lady"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Who's this lady he's talking about, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We better find out what the story is with this "lady"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So what exactly is a computer virus, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I dunno.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Look, I just go with the flow, alright, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And here I thought detectives were supposed to be somewhat knowledgeable...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What's with that face, pal? You think you know what a virus is?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, Nick? Do you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A computer virus? Sure. I mean, only in simple terms, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? Wow, you know everything. Professor Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. I'm gonna call you Dr. Wright from now on!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, that sounds pretty cool! Don't you agree, Dr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I get the feeling they're making fun of me?</thought> OK, fine. I'm no expert, but I can at least explain the basics to the two of you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A virus is a program that gets inside a computer and causes damage.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Damage? You mean it makes the machine go "boom" and explode?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No. The damage is, um... Well, it's all internal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So the inside goes "boom", right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Imagine all the case data you've got stored on your PCs here in the station... A virus could wipe out all that. That's the kind of damage I'm talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa! That's scary.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. And what's even more scary is that viruses are infectious.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Infectious?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Most computers are connected together on a network, right? A virus can move on machine to another over the network. So the virus just keeps spreading faster and faster.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmph. Just like a real virus, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But, Nick! Why would anyone want to make a program like that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. It takes ages to type in all that data. Why would you wanna destroy it, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No. People don't infect their own machines. They send the virus to someone else's.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? That's horrible!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, I get it... It's like you sneezing on Godot so he catches a cold.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right! Then he wouldn't be able to turn up in court because he'd be too sick. You really shouldn't do stuff like that, Nick. It's wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who? What? Where? When and why did the conversation jump to talking about me!? Anyway, that's what a computer virus is. A bad program that causes damage.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And all the different viruses have names, right? I kinda feel like I've heard the name of the virus we caught somewhere before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The name of the virus, huh? I feel like I've heard of it before, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We already knew about the MC Bomber virus from a while back. A group of criminals issued a series of demands to the head honchos of law enforcement. They threatened to release the virus if their demands weren't met.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Who are they?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I dunno. Some hotshots from the criminal underworld would be my guess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And now the virus has been released, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. It's in every computer in every public office in the city. Everyone's going nuts! They're hopping around like they're dancing at a carnival!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All this stuff with criminals and viruses... It almost feels like we're in a sci-fi movie!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Apparently the programmer who made the virus was a real genius or something. The focus right now is on tracing the route of this virus on the black market.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean someone put this virus up for sale?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. And because this one's so powerful... ...they're estimating its price tag was in the millions of dollars, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>In the millions!? A virus can be worth that much!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure if I really want to get involved in this, but who are the Cadaverinis?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Who are they? A scary bunch of people, that's who!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You're a cop, and you're scared? What's that about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Trust me, it doesn't matter if you're kid or a cop, these guys are scary. They've got some serious clout in the criminal underworld. We can't touch them. They've got too much moola.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Moola...? As in?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">They pretty much control all the cash on the city's black market.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The black market, huh? And that includes Tender Lender, I take it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure. No one stands up to Bruto Cadaverini. And I mean, no one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Interesting...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So Viola's the granddaughter of some mafia boss then?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. And everyone know how much Bruto loves his little girl. She means everything to him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... How did she end up at Tender Lender?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I dunno, pal. But I heard she and the boss of the Tender Lender are pretty tight.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Tight?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's what it said in a file I read related to Maggey's case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like a pretty important clue.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe, umm... about this...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What!? I'm trying to concentrate on Maggey and this virus right now, so I... Aaaaaaaaaaah!! This is it! This stupid name! I remember now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I thought so. Here it comes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't just nod to yourself and keep me in the dark, Nick! What's going on!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's OK, Maya! You don't have to cry about it!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The name scribbled on that sports paper and written on that CD... That's the name of the virus! "MC Bomber"!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">WHAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah! The virus that's just infected every computer in the station, pal. It's MC Bomber!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you give us any more details? Please?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This guy was a real programming genius. They called him "the walking computer" at the place where he worked.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What happens when he crashes though!? Does he just stop moving all of a sudden!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*groan* He wasn't a computer, Maya!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Anyway, there's nothing between Maggey and the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's the girl who works over at Tender Lender. You wanna stay away from her, OK? I mean it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She does look kind of unforgiving, doesn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That should be the least of your worries, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's that supposed to mean? What could be worse...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Her name's Viola Cadaverini. She's the only granddaughter of Bruto Cadaverini.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Bruto Cadaverini? Do you know who that is, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Never heard of him.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Bruto Cadaverini's the boss of the Cadaverini family.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Cadaverinis? <thought>That's one scary-sounding name!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We can't touch them. They're way too powerful for the police. But you're thinking of taking them on, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No! I don't remember ever saying I was going to! <thought>I better get some more info out of Gumshoe about this "family"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, this guy... The Tiger...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is he famous?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. This guy's not a loan shark, you know. Nope. He's a big loan cat!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hence the name?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't pay him back, and you'd better say your prayers, because he'll eat you alive.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're shaking, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Like a leaf...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm just... you know... kinda on edge at the moment... If you know what I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I wouldn't go flashing that photo around if I were you, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That guy rules the criminal underworld. You could get yourselves in serious trouble. I'm talking say-your-prayers trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're shaking, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Like a leaf...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm just... you know... kinda on edge at the moment... If you know what I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-And that is...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You know, the lunchbox! How did everything go!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">L-Lunchbox?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You remember. The weenies...?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I hate weenies!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, yeah... Those weenies.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So? How did my weenies taste when they went down the hatch?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Um... Well... It was... delicious!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah? That's what she said? Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... Well... Not exactly...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't worry about it, pal. I figured something would happen, so I came prepared.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Prepared? What do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I made a jumbo lunchbox!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Do me a favor again, huh, pal, and deliver this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This sure is a heavy burden... In more ways than one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can just imagine Maggey's little eyes sparkling with joy when you bring her that!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Weenies, again, Nick? Tell me we don't have to eat all these too...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I really can't eat any more...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't forget to give that to Maggey, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But they don't allow presents for the prisoners in the detention centre, right...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, you're right... ... Well it doesn't matter. I'm counting on you to get it to her somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm a lawyer, not a delivery boy, Gumshoe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, how about you tell me what kind of trouble Mr. Elg was in?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">I'm sorry, sir, but we don't deal with trouble-shooting here. Perhaps you'd like to speak to someone in customer service?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's she talking about!? I guess I'd better just take a shot and see where it gets me...</thought> Ms. Basil. Let me ask you something. Did Mr. Elg's troubles have something to do with this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Basil">What is that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A lottery ticket. There were hundreds of these on the victim's table at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Basil">And what is the relevance of that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim, Mr. Glen Elg... ...had a gambling habit, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">I don't think that's a logical conclusion based on the facts. Everyone dreams of being rich. Even I listen to Millionaire Radio.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's right. That is a bit weak on its own.</thought> But Mr. Elg's gambling wasn't restricted to the lottery, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Basil">Everyone likes to gamble from time to time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">But be careful! If you're careless, you could lose everything -- your money, people's trust, etc.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like I got that one wrong.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Basil">What is that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A bunch of horse racing tickets. All losing ones.</line>
<line speaker="Basil">With that many tickets, you could get 1 dollar at the recycling center. You good people are very, very bad. Cashing in on others' misfortunes is immoral.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Why did I get a whiff of hypocrisy just now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Basil">But what is the relevance of these tickets?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim, Mr. Glen Elg... He had a gambling habit, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">I don't think that's a logical conclusion based on the facts. Everyone likes to go to the races from time to time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, but not everyone buys this many tickets!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Basil">Anyway, I don't believe that proves anything on its own.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're right. But I'm not through yet. Mr. Elg's gambling wasn't restricted to horse races, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Basil">Everyone likes to gamble from time to time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">But be careful! If you're careless, you could lose everything -- your money, people's trust, etc.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like I got that one wrong.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well? What do you think!?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">I'm not sure. Let's ask one of the programmers... Excuse me. Can you answer this man's query, please?</line>
<line speaker="Programmer">The data queue that manages system tasks for trouble-shooting requires that the multi-tasking simulation for local variables be put into sleep mode so that data transmission on active nodes can be bundled correctly according to the source code. ...Obviously.</line>
<line speaker="Basil">So I'm afraid that is the situation, you see. Did you good people follow all that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not even slightly! What was all that mumbo-jumbo?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">It is exactly as my programmer explained.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm guessing I picked the wrong piece of evidence there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Basil">Would you like to input another question?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The lottery, horse racing... He bought a lot of tickets, and lost a lot of times. That's got to have hurt his wallet pretty bad, don't you think? Maybe bad enough to be the cause of some pretty serious trouble perhaps!?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">Noooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Basil">You are right. Glen did have a gambling habit. You good people must not follow his example, do you understand?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trust me. Even if I wanted to, I don't exactly have the money to buy any.</line>
<line speaker="Basil">But... if you win, there's no problem, is there? And Glen had a winning ticket, didn't he? For half a million dollars?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, but...</line>
<line speaker="Basil">It's hard to imagine how he could have been in trouble then, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's true that Mr. Elg won half a million dollars... in the end. But that was his first stroke of good luck. He was in deep trouble before that.</line>
<line speaker="Basil">Deep trouble? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Elg's real problem was with someone or something more terrifying and ferocious!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Basil">All good people get into trouble sometimes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">Let's ask one of my programmers what they think... Excuse me? What do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Programmer">I'm taking a break.</line>
<line speaker="Basil">Yes. Perhaps I should take a break, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wish I could take a break from my troubles, but the rest stop was about a mile back.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Elg met with someone on the day he was killed. He even made a note on this calendar about the meeting: "Meet with The Tiger."</line>
<line speaker="Basil">What is the relevance of that? Are you trying to suggest Glen was meeting him to discuss his debt?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah. That's what I was thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Basil">But I have never heard anything about this "Tiger" before. Maybe he's not even human. Maybe he really is a tiger!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm no programmer, but does she really expect me to buy such messed up logic?</thought> In that case, I think it's time to introduce you to The Tiger.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well? What do you think!?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">I'm not sure. Let's ask one of the programmers... Excuse me. Can you answer this man's query, please?</line>
<line speaker="Programmer">The data queue that manages system tasks for trouble-shooting requires that the multi-tasking simulation for local variables be put into sleep mode so that data transmission on active nodes can be bundled correctly according to the source code. ...Obviously.</line>
<line speaker="Basil">So I'm afraid that is the situation, you see. Did you good people follow all that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not even slightly! What was all that mumbo-jumbo?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">It is exactly as my programmer explained.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm guessing I picked the wrong piece of evidence there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Basil">Glen had a lot of friends, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Furio Tigre, aka "The Tiger", is the boss of a loan office called "Tender Lender". This is who Mr. Elg met with on the day of his murder. And the only thing a loan shark would talk with him about would be his debt!</line>
<line speaker="Basil">Noooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Basil">It's true that Glen had racked up quite a bit of debt from his gambling habit. About 100,000 dollars, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>100,000 dollars? Ouch!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Basil">But I heard he won the lottery, so he should have been in the clear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Shame Maggey couldn't get a bit of that good luck.</thought> OK... ...So the guy got lucky and won the lottery. But what if he hadn't won? What was his plan then?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">Well... This isn't easy to say, but... He said he would use his talents to repay the money.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His "talents"?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">I suspect he was talking about programming.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What computer program is worth 100,000 dollars!?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">... Perhaps you good people should leave so I can get back to my work.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm so close to cracking her!</thought> The program in question... Was it by any chance... this!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Basil">This is a very delicate matter. Without the necessary data, there's really no way I can access the information.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I know Mr. Elg created some sort of program! She can't deny it if I show her the program itself as evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well? This is it, isn't it? This is the virus that's infecting computers world-wide as we speak... "MC Bomber"!</line>
<line speaker="Basil">Noooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Basil">Glen's head had more processing power than any computer. But it had been infected with a "gambling" virus. Glen was... in too deep.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean he was in debt?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">Yes. 100,000 dollars in debt. Not an easy amount to repay. So... He said he was taking on some extra work. Something a bit risky.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Risky"? How?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe he was going to become a waitress at Trés Bien!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Where do you come up with these ideas!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So it's safe to say Mr. Elg was the creator of this virus, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Basil">The "MC Bomber" virus? Yes. It was a work of genius. In a bad sort of way, of course. But still genius. Something like that would probably fetch several million dollars on the black market.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Inconceivable! Gumshoe was right for a change!</thought> This date, December 3rd, that is marked on his calendar... That was his deadline for repaying his debts.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess we won't be needing these horse racing tickets any more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Use the trash can, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This man is your grandfather, right?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">Carrying a picture like that around with you... You should watch your back...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-Thanks for the advice...</line>
<line speaker="Viola">The family is always watching me... from the shadows...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The "family"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I thought I saw something suspicious under the corner of that rug!</line>
<line speaker="Viola">One wrong move and... you might disappear forever... Hee... Hee... Hee...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This feels like Halloween... Only a whole lot more real... And a whole lot scarier, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You said that bandage around your head was from an operation?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You also said you suffered a "fatal injury" to the head, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">Yes... The operation was very... difficult, apparently...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, by "fatal injury", you mean you were hurt very badly somehow, right?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">... Hee... Hee...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did the injury in question have something to do with this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well!?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">Donuts...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">I baked them myself... Home-made donuts... Have one...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm, what's inside?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">Jam, and... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, but I didn't quite catch that...</line>
<line speaker="Viola">Hee... Hee...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Thanks, but no thanks... I think I'll pass. <thought>I guess that was a flop. What happened to this woman for her to have such a huge bandage around her head? There must be some piece of evidence that'll prompt her to tell me what happened...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have here a car repair bill. From this, it seems pretty obvious that this car was involved in an accident.</line>
<line speaker="Viola">Let me see that... ... This bill is made out to the "Cadaverinis"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, it is.</line>
<line speaker="Viola">I don't think... I ever introduced myself... Tell me... what do the "Cadaverinis"... have to do with me...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something tells me she's not about to say hi and introduce herself... Alright, then...</thought> Your relationship with the Cadaverinis is very strong... And this is why.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So!? What do have to say for herself now!?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">Pretzels... For you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">Don't worry about the little white specks on the surface... I just sprinkled a small quantity of... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...N-No thanks! <thought>My evidence must still be half-baked...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Viola">I really don't know... the "Cadaverinis"... Further...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know exactly who you are, Viola Cadaverini! You sustained that injury in a traffic accident, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">...</line>
<line speaker="Viola">It happened about 4 months ago... I was driving in one of our family's cars... when someone pulled out in front of me... It was a motorbike... or something like that... I don't remember it much... Anyway, I swerved to try to avoid it, but... ...I took a blow... to the head... A bad one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, I can imagine...</thought> So what happened to the person on the bike? I'm guessing they didn't get away with injuring THE Viola Cadaverini, right?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">I... don't know... what happened to them... They ran away... Or so I heard...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ran away?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">If they'd stayed, I'd have... Hee... Hee... Hee...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, is it possible...? Could the person who committed the hit and run have been...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The person who caused the accident that gave you that injury was--</line>
<line speaker="Viola">No more.. I don't want to... think about it anymore... Here... try one of these tomatoes... We all picked them together... as a family... And I added my own, special, flavoring...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No thanks! <thought>The person who caused the accident was riding a motorbike... Who could it be?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was this man, wasn't it? He was the cause of your accident.</line>
<line speaker="Viola">... It wasn't Don Tigre! I refuse to believe it!</line>
<line speaker="Viola">We collided... The motorbike, and my car... But Don Tigre isn't injured at all... is he?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It was The Tiger who caused Viola to crash. I can feel it! Plus, one of her locks just broke, so she must suspect it was him, too...</thought> I'm sorry, Ms. Cadaverini... But I have proof that The Tiger was involved in a traffic accident on his bike!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And this is my proof!</line>
<line speaker="Viola">Hard-boiled eggs...? Please, try one...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Eggs?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">I raised the chickens these eggs came from myself... I invented a special diet... so their chicks would be blue...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not exactly a motorbike, but... ...Mr. Tigre rides around in a scooter, doesn't he? And you'll notice that the front wheel guard is badly damaged.</line>
<line speaker="Viola">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Cadaverini... You know the truth, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">... Hee... Hee... Hee...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This repair bill was paid by Furio Tigre. The Cadaverinis have known for ages who caused the accident, haven't they?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">... It's possible... Perhaps...Somewhere inside me... I know that may be true...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I knew it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Viola">But... Don Tigre still saved my life...The operation was very complicated... It was very, very expensive...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How much are we talking...</line>
<line speaker="Viola">... Very, very, very expensive...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She seems kind of hesitant about giving me an actual figure. I should back off...</thought> Well, anyway, it was The Tiger who paid for it, right?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">After I recovered... Don Tigre told me... He said he paid for the operation because... he cared about me... I... believe him...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? But do you honestly believe that to be true?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you want to know what I think...? I think the reason he paid the operation wasn't because of you, but someone else... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know this must be quite a shock for you, but...</line>
<line speaker="Viola">Overcoat...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">I made it myself... It's been so... cold lately...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, just hearing your voice sends shivers down my spine!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Viola">Please, try it on... ... ...Oops!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... What was the "oops" for?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">I'm missing a few pins... I must have left them in the coat...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-On second thought, I'm fine, thanks! Roasty-toasty, that's me!</line>
<line speaker="Viola">Don Tigre told me, you see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Perhaps I shouldn't be saying this, but... ...your grandfather, Bruto Cadaverini, controls a lot of "dubious" cash, right? And you are his beloved pride and joy.</line>
<line speaker="Viola">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, I don't know exactly how much the operation cost, but... ...if you weren't granddaughter of Mr. Cadaverini... ...do you think Mr. Tigre would have paid the money?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">... One million dollars...</line>
<line speaker="Viola">Four months ago... I was in a traffic accident... That's why I needed the operation... When I woke up... they told me it was nothing serious... A simple procedure...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! Really?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I guess if she recovered in 4 months, it couldn't have been too big...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Viola">They said the operation... cost one million dollars...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A... A... A million bucks!?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">My grandfather ordered Don Tigre to pay... One million dollars... In "compensation"...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Compensation", huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's underworld lingo for paying money to settle a score. Basically, pay or get into some serious trouble! <thought>But a million bucks!? This has to be related to our poisoning case somehow...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Viola">I wanted to believe him... I wanted to trust what Don Tigre said... He said it had nothing to do with my grandfather being Bruto Cadaverini... I wanted to believe he helped me because he cared about me. Not about my grandfather... But I knew... That wasn't really true...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow. I'm so sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Viola">What he did to get the money was... It was... evil!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Viola">He said it was all for me... So I... I helped him...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You helped him? In what way?</line>
<line speaker="Viola">Here... Take these...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What are these? Medical papers?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Viola">I'm Bruto Cadaverini's granddaughter... He had to pay compensation... He was made an offer... He simply... couldn't... refuse.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, I feel so bad for Viola.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's inexcusable!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There are two things that I consider inexcusable. Poisoning, and betrayal! Only a coward would hurt people using either of these tactics.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is everything alright, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We should get going. Right after we finish our espresso.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wouldn't need to convince Viola of anything else, so I guess I can get rid of this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Eh, bonjour! I 'ave been waiting for you to return.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mr. Armstrong...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, good timing. I was hoping to find you here. We'd like to ask you a few questions...</line>
<line speaker="???">Well, he hasn't got anythin' to say to youse fellas!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! It's Xin Eohp...</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Who you callin' "Zinnee Ooooope"!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come out from under the table already, Maya!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">OK. Hand it over!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Youse wanna play games wid me? I don't recommend dat! The medical papers! Now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh, oh... I think he wants Viola Cadaverini's papers back...</thought> Y-You mean... this? The million dollar medical papers?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Cadaverini trusted you. That's why she said that she helped you.</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Forget about it! That girl's dumber dan an eggplant. Youse wanna know what's sad? I'll tell youse what's sad. And it ain't only her face. She thinks she's got power cuz she's Bruto's little girl... Now THAT's sad...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't let you have these papers. Tomorrow in court... ...I'm going to expose what you did to get the one million you used to pay this off!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">... Are you crazy or somethin'!? I don't care if you wanna give it to me or not! There's two of us here. You got dat? Two.</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Err... oui! Oui, oui!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Armstrong!?</line>
<line speaker="Armstrong">Forgive me! Désolé! I cannot argue wiz 'im!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">U-Urgh! <thought>...That... really hurt!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Is dat all youse got? I'll be takin' dose papers now. Armstrong! Get that lighter!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait...!</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">Don't take it too hard... ...Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That was so stupid... I shouldn't... have let my guard down. Those medical papers were... vital... evi...dence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Detective Gumshoe!?</line>
<line speaker="Tigre">D-Detective!? Youse think you gonna stop me, copper!? Beat it! Gwaaaaaaaaaaar!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whoa! C-Come on, Gumshoe! Keep it together! You guys! Get outta here! Leave this guy to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Go, pal! And take this! If you get hurt, who'd look after Maggey, huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! A-Alright! Thanks, Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait, Nick! Don't leave me behind!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll get even with that guy tomorrow... in court! Tender Lender is going down!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think I have enough evidence yet... I should investigate and gather some more clues before I try again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nnrgh! I've made too many mistakes!</thought></line>
</xml>