<xml>
<title>Reunion, and Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaaaaaaat!? Prosecutor von Karma!? You mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I heard it's his successor this time...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Successor...? ... Manfred von Karma. He was a really sinister man. He pulled all sorts of nasty tricks; all so he could win.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He was a man obsessed with the word "perfection"... He had a perfect record... for forty long years. Who knows what sorts of dirty tricks he used to get each of those guilty verdicts? And now, his successor... I wonder what kind of person they will turn out to be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's no good...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pearly! You showed up! Thanks for coming all this way!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I was really worried about you...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, where's your mother? Didn't you two come together?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mother is watching over the trainees. She said they have training for two days straight with no breaks.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh!? Then... Then... You came all by yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yup! I snuck out of the manor and followed a map.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't tell me you walked all the way here...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Of course not! ...I ran!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's... I can't... Oh my... <thought>If it takes two hours by train... Oh man...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pearly... What about the train?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Huh? What's a... "tray-in"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I give up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...It's time, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um... I'm really scared... What if Von Karma tries to do something to me? At least I know Mr. Edgeworth would be nicer to me than Von Karma!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Eh-ji-werth? Who is that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, he's Nick's rival... Well, he's also a friend.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I still remember him as if I had just seen him only yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Every trial was a scorching fierce battle until the very end.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It was always back and forth with them. But when you're rivals for life...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya! Please don't mention that name ever again...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh...? But why, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm... I'm sorry, Maya. I forgot you don't know... He... He's... He's gone... And he's not coming back...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaaat!? W-W-Wait... Wait a second!! What's that supposed to mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Court will commence shortly. Please proceed into the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Let's go. Now's not the time to talk about that anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N...Nick...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Maya Fey. Are the prosecution and the defense prepared?</line>
<line speaker="???">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>What is with this girl...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">... *Ahem!* Mr. Wright!! Are you finally prepared!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? A-Ah, yes, Your Honor. <thought>Why does he always seem mad at me!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Mr. Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="???">You must be a little shocked because I am a woman, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Hold on. So this kid is the "famed" Prosecutor von Karma...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Revenge...? <thought>Is this about her father, Manfred von Karma...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Um... If it's something of a personal nature, I'm sure you can... Oww!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Please speak with your mouth like a normal person... I beg of you...</thought> Yeow!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor von Karma, your opening statement, please...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">V-Very well... What is the defense's position?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Does the defense wish to enter a plea of "not guilty"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Justified self-defense"... A plea usually reserved for when a person unintentionally kills in defense of himself. We could very easily make a solid case that it was self-defense, but...</thought> The defense stands by the plea of "not guilty", Your Honor! <thought>Because to plead "justified self-defense" is to say you did kill someone.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's just as scary as her father. Like father, like daughter I suppose.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir! My name is Dick Gumshoe. I'm a detective at the local precinct. Aah!!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yes, sir! Um, if everyone would please look at this map. The Channeling Chamber has no windows and the door was locked shut. At the time of the murder, only the victim and the defendant were in the room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What were they doing in there?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um... They... Well, they were channeling... a spirit... Sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ch-Channeling a spirit??</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The look of disbelief on the judge's face is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">*ahem* Anyway, a few minutes after the channeling started, gunshots were heard coming from inside the room, sir. A few of the witnesses broke the door down, and rushed into the room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, and that's when they found that the victim was already dead, correct? Hmm, I believe this is one of the most open and shut cases I have ever presided over.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, how was the victim killed?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I was about to get to that...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The direct cause of death was a pistol shot to the forehead, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So the victim was stabbed before being shot...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is the victim's autopsy report, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court accepts it into evidence. Mr. Wright, you may question the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The direct cause of death was a pistol shot to the forehead, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The murder weapon, Detective Gumshoe. Whose pistol was  it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It was the victim's.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim?  Now, why would he have...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Fingerprints? There were fingerprints?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Along with the victim's, the defendant, Maya Fey's were also on the grip, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. So the defendant's fingerprints were left on the murder weapon...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I walked right into her hands there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The shot was fired from point-blank range.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Point blank, huh? So about how far away was it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It was anywhere between 12 to 20 inches away.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And how do you know he was shot at point blank?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Excuse me!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Gunpowder burn?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Gunpowder exploding is what makes a bullet fire, and that gets real hot, pal. And there were definitely some gunpowder burns left on the victim's forehead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow... Never knew that... Live and learn, I guess...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But before the victim was shot, sir, he was stabbed in the chest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Stabbed... And what was he stabbed with?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A fruit knife.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. And whose knife was it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It looks like it belongs to the Feys, sir. And of course, Maya Fey's fingerprints are all over it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... All over it, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Urk. This does not look good...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The wound was very severe, but not enough to cause instantaneous death.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How severe was the wound?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If it had been half an inch more to the right, it would've hit the victim's heart. After a stab like that, it's impossible to fight back, let alone stand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This testimony makes Maya look like she had stabbed him with the intent to kill...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The murderer used the pistol to finish the victim off after the stabbing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure he was stabbed first, then shot?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup. Sure as sure can be. One look at the wounds and you'd come to the same conclusion too, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grr... What a pain...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nothing sounds out of place so far... I should try to learn more about the murder weapons, for now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! We have clearly established how the victim was murdered.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I brought the two murder weapons with me today.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court accepts them into evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And the two murder weapons, both with the defendant's fingerprints on them...? Hmm... This does seem like an open and shut case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is going from bad to worse... As if the summary just now wasn't oversimplifying things to the extreme...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is quite true... Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Even in the face of all this, do you still wish to plead "not guilty"? It's the opinion of this court that if you do not adjust your plea, you stand to lose.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What will you do, Mr. Wright? Will you change to "justified self-defense"? Because now would be the time to do so. This is your final chance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is a huge decision! I'd better think this through all the way!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If Maya is convicted, then it's all over. I really should play it safe, and try to soften the blow...</thought> Your Honor. The defense would like to change its plea to "justified self-defense"...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Understood. Let the record show that the defense has entered a new plea.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...There's nothing else I could do... Mia...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">...You already hold the key... ...If you don't believe, you cannot win...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...! If we plead "justified self-defense", we would basically be confessing to murder! After the trial, Maya's life would be destroyed, and she'll be labeled a murderer... Can I really... Can I really let that happen!?</thought> Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense... The defense retracts its previous statement. And instead, will prove beyond the shadow of a doubt that the defendant is not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If we plead "justified self-defense"... we would basically be confessing to a murder! After the trial, Maya's life would be destroyed, and she'd be labeled a murderer... I can't let that happen!</thought> Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Have you reached a conclusion, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense will not change its plea. We will accept nothing short of complete acquittal!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um... Y-Yes... sir...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">N-Now, see here! Proceedings are run by... Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, yes, of course. Go ahead Detective and give your testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry, pal but there's an even more incriminating piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So this is the costume... There certainly is evidence of a back spray of blood on this.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This piece directly links Maya Fey to the crime, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... The court accepts this into evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Alright, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya's fingerprints on both murder weapons and blood splatters on her clothes... Could this situation get any worse??</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Please stop calling me by my full name. It's disturbing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry, pal but there's an even more incriminating piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why didn't you say so in your testimony earlier!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Uh... You're kinda scary today, you know, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Come now, Mr. Wright... There is no need for that kind of attitude in my court...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-Alright. Just, please stop glaring at me like that...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is the costume the defendant was wearing at the time of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya's... costume?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. She was wearing this when we arrested her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya... She's wearing her channeling costume today too... Is she not allowed to wear anything else...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">As you can see, it's covered in blood.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This blood on the costume...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Lab results show that it is the victim's blood.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So there is blood from the victim on the defendant's clothes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Definitely not good... Urk.</thought> Hmm, where there any other clues you could gleam from this piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, well...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, yes, Ms. von Karma is perfectly correct...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grr... Now even the Judge is on her side! But if I bite off more than I can chew here... What should I do!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why is Ms. von Karma suddenly putting up resistance? There must be a reason as to why she suddenly threw out an objection like that... There must be a clue somewhere on this costume! I just have to look harder!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Ms. von Karma's logic is perfect. There is no way for you to poke a hole in it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! Looks like my time is up. So, about the costume...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I pursue this and I turn up nothing, it could be disastrous...</thought> You're right, Your Honor. There is absolutely nothing more to this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good. Well, Detective, please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor. Actually, there is something very wrong with this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What are you talking about, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Where is this problem you are talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've come this far... There's no turning back now!</thought> The problem I have with this piece of evidence is here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I ask the court to please take a look at the sleeve of this costume.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The sleeve? ...! There is a tiny hole here...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">..A... A hole...? But that wasn't in the report.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hold on! What's this around the hole? I-It smells faintly of gunpowder!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">G-Gunpowder!? No one ever told me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A hole that smells of gunpowder...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looks like I've found the "hole" I was looking for!</thought> Your Honor, the only logical conclusion you can make is that it must be a bullet hole!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!! This is a very grave matter. It's best we correct the Court Record first before anything else.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry about that. I guess we messed up, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>I-Is she actually... smiling!? What else is she hiding!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-How can you say something like that!? This is a huge oversight!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">While I agree it is a mistake on the part of the police, what Prosecutor von Karma has said is true. The evidence still stands. If you do not find a more definitive problem with the evidence, then...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No way!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Detective Gumshoe, please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yes, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The problem is obviously the blood splatter here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But... We've determined that the blood splatter is from the victim. Where is the problem in that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, where, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I wonder about that too...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That last antic of yours just pushed me over the top, Mr. Wright. I am declaring that this cross-examination period is over...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Please wait, Your Honor! <thought>Ack! I'd better not mess up again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is a problem... somewhere around... here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What does he mean, Ms. von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well said. You certainly do take after your father!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've just been made to look like a fool again... Alright... Focus, Phoenix!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I pursue this and I turn up nothing, it could be disastrous...</thought> You're right, Your Honor. There is absolutely nothing more to this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good. Well, Detective, please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright. I'll give you that the blood spatter is from the victim, but... what is this hole in the sleeve?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um... Sorry, pal. We must've thought it was just a tear in the seam...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Missing the hole is not what I'm asking you about. I'm talking about the hole itself! The smell of gunpowder  clearly gives away that... it is a bullet hole!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But they do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Grr... I know there's something more to that costume.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Yes, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The defendant attacked and killed a person who, without a doubt, was not fighting back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He wasn't "fighting back"? How do you know if he was or wasn't!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We could find no evidence that the victim put up any sort of struggle, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So did the murderer have a fight with the victim, or not? Depending on this, the circumstances around this murder change drastically.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... We're in real trouble now... If only I had something to prove that the victim did fight back...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That Von Karma! She thinks she can decide the verdict with this testimony alone! I have to somehow find a critical contradiction and then I'll have her!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Dick Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yes? Heh, having you call me by my full name is kind of a weird feeling...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You said that my client killed "a person who, without a doubt, was not fighting back."</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, I did.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then what, may I ask, is the bullet hole you police overlooked supposed to mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Eh, um... What does it mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll tell you what it means. It means that the victim had fired off a shot. Is this what it means to "not fight back"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A-Ah! You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would seem that way! If the victim tried to shoot the defendant, then... It would change everything...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Alright! The wind seems to be shifting...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is with that "are you finished yet" laugh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Now that you...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, that's right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nooooo!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Well... Yes, that's true...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Huh? How so?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aaah!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? You mean... By myself...? You want me to put together the scenario all by myself? Aah!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yes, sir! Right away, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">During the channeling, the defendant saw her chance to stab the victim in the chest.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... This scenario you have put together does make sense...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just by listening, it does make sense... However, I won't give up that easily!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">P-Please refrain from glaring at me like that... Now then, your cross-examination, please.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">During the channeling, the defendant saw her chance to stab the victim in the chest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is quite a difference in height between Dr. Grey and the defendant. Add in body strength, and it seems unlikely the defendant could have stabbed the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Now that you mention it... Yeah, I guess...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't believe it... She even studied up on the Kurain Channeling Technique!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Um... Uh... About what you were talking about... I didn't quite get it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Um, n-never mind. Let's continue with the testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course, the victim used the last of his strength to fight back, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So he was stabbed, but the stab wound didn't kill him.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But if you think about the blood loss, it was pretty bad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How bad would you say it was?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Actually, I went to give blood the other day. And afterward, I felt a little lightheaded and dizzy. ...I guess the damage was maybe... about 10 times the dizziness...? Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">S-Sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">While the two were fighting, the victim took out his gun.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Where in the world did that pistol come from?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It looks like the victim, Dr. Grey had specifically bought it for that day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But a handgun...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He got it off the black market about 2 days before the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why did Dr. Grey bring a gun...? Was he taking precautions against something...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The victim took a shot, but because they were too close, he missed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you're saying that the bullet hole in this costume was made then?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry, pal, but that's what I'd think. The two of them were already fighting when a shot was fired.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya... I'm really glad you weren't hurt...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The defendant then picked up on the opening and took the victim's gun and ended it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya has never fired a gun before in her life!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The victim had already taken off the safety. With the safety off, even an amateur like you can fire it by pulling the trigger.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even me...? I wonder...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>His testimony certainly makes us look very bad, but there's gotta be a contradiction in there somewhere... And uncovering it is going to uncover the truth! I can feel it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Missing the tiny hole on this costume... will be the prosecution's undoing.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Eh? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This little hole has actually created a huge hole in your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">E-Explain yourself, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You said the two of them were fighting when the victim fired his gun at point blank. If that were true, then where is the gunpowder burn on this costume!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">G-Gunpowder... burn?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is what you testified earlier: "When something is shot from point blank, a burn area is left around the bullet hole."</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But there is not a single trace of gunpowder burn on this costume!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is a very good point. And... what exactly does this mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It means that when the shot was fired, they were standing apart from each other.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then I implore you to disprove my line of thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As if that was even possible. According to testimony, the wound from the stabbing was very severe. The victim would not have had the strength to push the defendant very far after that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That does make an awful lot of sense. What do you think, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I must be careful. I can't afford to make a mistake here! Concentrate and think!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ack, it's no good. I can't find a "hole" in her logic at all this time...</thought> I admit it. Somehow, your reasoning makes logical sense.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It does look that way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Oh boy... If I don't do something soon, it'll be curtains for Maya...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, I think we can...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! Please... Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who was that? Mr. Wright? Please refrain from making unnecessary outbursts!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't care how, but I must find something to go on in Von Karma's explanation!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is a fatal flaw in her argument, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Fatal...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Flaw...!? Yeow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There has to be a snag in her explanation somewhere! "She put some distance between them before rushing to make the final blow. And when she was about to strike, the doctor took his shot." There must be a piece of evidence that contradicts this line of thinking!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Why are you showing this to me, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Prosecutor von Karma's explanation and this piece of evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Do not contradict!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Haha, looks like you need to use your brain a little more, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... Being lectured by Gumshoe, of all people, is so embarrassing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Come on! Hurry up and get that thinking cap on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the piece of evidence that destroys your logic.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is that? A folding screen?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I would like to point the court's attention to the "hole" in this folding screen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like you already know what I'm talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Who? Where? What?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Your explanation, please!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Are these two really that clueless...?</thought> The bullet went through the defendant's sleeve first, then the folding screen. It passed through at a height of approximately 8 inches off the ground... Which means! When the shot was fired, Maya... I mean, the defendant, was not getting ready to strike, but was actually squatting low to the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Th-This changes everything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please look at this diagram of the crime scene. The victim, Dr. Grey was here when he fired the shot. And the bullet hit this folding screen. It hit at this location, about 8 inches off the ground. At this time, the defendant was in this area.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Behind the folding screen...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Yeah, I guess so...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Boy, did I just screw up royally... What's done is done. For now, I should focus on where Maya was at the time of the crime.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Somewhere around here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh. The judge's face is scrunched like he just smelled some serious bad breath...</thought> Uhh... Um... That is, I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wait! I just realized I forgot to brush this morning... Excuse me while I freshen up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, sure...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In the meantime, I want you to think things through again, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ah, of course... Whoops... What's done is done. For now, I should focus on where Maya was at the time of the crime.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She was standing here, near the folding screen!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You, of all people, should know the answer to that question, Ms. von Karma. If she were shot from somewhere closer, there would be gunpowder burns present. However! There is nothing of the sort around the bullet hole of this costume!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I believe it has now been proven that the defendant was standing a ways from the victim when she was shot at. But do you think this has changed the defendant's situation...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, even with that explanation, it feels like nothing has changed... But I can't give up just yet!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Honestly, Your Honor! This changes everything! The prosecution has claimed that the defendant was aiming to kill by stabbing. If that were true, delivering the final strike with the knife would be ideal. However! Where and what was the defendant doing at the time...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Squatting all the way by the folding screen...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. If Maya Fey was the real murderer, why would she be by the folding screen instead of preparing to strike?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Upon further consideration, it does make very little sense.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, I figured there had to be a reason.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Figuring things out and proving the logic behind everything is YOUR job!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oof...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Alright! With this, the rest of the trial should be in the b--</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...blast radius of disaster.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uuugh. Of all the things to inherit, why did it have to be that smarmy smile!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-Huh!?... How is it all my fault??</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...P-Punishment...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Next witness...? That's gotta be Lotta!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court will take a 5 minute recess. After we reconvene, we will hear from the next witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phew, that was a close one.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I know you were giving it your all to defend me. But I could feel the death penalty hanging in the air...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I felt like I was pretty close to dying myself...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But you were wonderful out there. You listened carefully, made theories, and tricked everyone into believing you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-Thanks. Wait... Tricked??</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That must be the "lawyer's" secret technique, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">By the way... Is the next witness who I think it is...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I'm pretty sure it's Lotta Hart.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh... Another jam, like always... Remember, Nick! You promised you'd save me! If you lose, my ghost will come after you with my sis', and we'll haunt you!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Your sister...? Um, are you talking about Mystic Mia?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. Do you remember her, Pearly? My sister was a super good lawyer! She was also Nick's teacher.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Oh, I didn't know that...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court will now reconvene. Now, the first order of... Oww!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey, Phoenix! How ya doin'?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just fine...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Sorry 'bout this. Didn't exactly have a choice, ya know...? Yeowza!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I-I declare! What in tarnation!? Hey, Judge! This here is violence against my fair self!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's fine.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">"That's fine!?" That ain't fine!! That's a whip! Eaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I haven't even gotten to say my name and job yet...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">The name's Lotta Hart, paranormal photographer, and I'm here to testify!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, now, let's all be one big happy family... OK...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Only the Doc and the defendant went into the Channelin' Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And did you take a picture of the scene right after the murder took place?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Reckon course!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eh? ...Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Reckon course! It's short for "Ya reckon!? Of course I did!" Aah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The moment of truth. What will be in that picture?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Umm, let's see here... This here's the picture!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It would certainly seem that only the defendant and the victim were in that room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I will clear all doubt about Maya through this cross-examination... Just watch me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Only the Doc and the defendant went into the Channelin' Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was it really only those two that went in!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes. Dr. Grey and Maya were the only two who went into the room...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">H-Hold on! We can't have the defense testifying against its own client!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Anyway, folks, only the two of 'em went into the Channeling Chamber, ya hear?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">We were waitin' outside the door and then, "bang!" we hear this gunshot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was it really a gunshot!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes. I think it was something that sounded like a gunshot...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And why are we here listening to the defense testify!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...And the world becomes just a little crueler...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I heard a gunshot a long time ago, so I know. And I tell ya that was a gunshot I heard. Now, this -- this is where the story heats up!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Mr. Lawyer there broke the door down, and we rushed into the room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, let me get this straight! This "Mr. Lawyer there" broke the door down!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Yes, Ms. von Karma... I broke the door down. Sorry. <thought>Why does this feel like an inquisition?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">No need for apologizin'! That was great! You're a real man!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, really? That's something I would've liked to see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The judge is smiling rather openly. I'll take that as a  good sign...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Inside was the dead victim, and the defendant, wavin' a pistol around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure it was the defendant, Maya Fey!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Sure, I'm sure!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Lotta seems awful confident in her testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lotta! Please, think back to that day one more time.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Wh-Whatcha getting' at?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Remember what you said when we broke into the room...?</line>
<line speaker="???">...I was... murdered...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lotta! At a time like this!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Times like this are perfect for snapping up shots! But anyway... what's going on here!? This gal... Is she... ...Maya!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When you saw the murderer at that time, you couldn't even tell if it was Maya Fey or not! Am I correct!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ah, um, well, ya see...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Ms. Hart! You are here to present accurate testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yeah, ah, s-sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Good. This shifts things back to my side...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">When they entered...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yeah, that's right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah... It was Maya that went in.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It looks like we've come to a collective conclusion. The person in this picture is most certainly Maya Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Rats! And I'm trapped like one... Again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even I can see that any normal person would know who that was. It's no good. I shouldn't push my luck on this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I swear, other than those two, there was no one else in the room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you absolutely certain of that!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Sure am! But that old witch chased us out of the room, so...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Old witch"? Does she mean Morgan Fey?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">But there was no one else in there, and you know it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The Channeling Chamber was very dark, almost pitch black... Was there really no one else in there? What about...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about... behind the folding screen? Did you check back there?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Reckgiven!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What in the...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Reckgiven! Ya know! "Ya reckon!? That's a given!" I took me a good look around the room once! There ain't no way anyone was hangin' out behind that foldin' screen!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... If I may have a word with you, Ms. Hart...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Wh-What? Ya got a problem!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Reckgiven!... I mean, I am having a little difficulty in understanding you. If you would stop saying such things as "Reckongiven" and so forth... Aah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about... behind the door? Did you check there?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">What do I look like to you? I wasn't born yesterday, ya know! First off, the one that bust that door open was you! With the way ya slammed that door, anyone standin' behind it woulda had more face and less nose, free of charge!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She actually had the police investigate that too!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about... under the flooring? Did you check there?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I ain't no ignoramus to make it out here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?... Wh-What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Don't "what are ya talkin' about" me! Under the floorin'? C'mon!, even a bug wouldn't crawl under that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh... Yeah, that was a bit far-fetched, huh...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! Her story adds up... What's worse is that I was there at the scene of the crime at that time too, and her story is exactly how I would have told it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! Just as I thought, there is nothing wrong with her testimony! I was with her, so I know she's telling the truth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Enough. It seems that there are no issues with Ms. Hart's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... The face of the defendant can not be verified in this picture. However, if we think about the circumstances, it would have to be the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What am I going to do!? If I just let this go...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, Mr. Wright? You look as if you have something to say...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I make one wrong move, I'm going to have the judge against me... Is there anything I can present that would prove it's not Maya in that photo?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It is possible that the person in this photo is not the defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Wh-What!? Do you know what you are proposing!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Y-Y-Yeah! That's just plain fool's talk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Thanks guys. Your show of support was just great...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Now, then, Mr. Wright. Please show the court some proof. Prove to this court that the person in this photo is not Maya Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here is your proof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is there a problem?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. I'm sorry, but I don't follow your logic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Shoot. I guess I wasn't showing enough confidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nothing, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I didn't say anything about giving up! I just don't have the right piece of evidence to prove my argument...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I-Is this it...? Is this all I could do...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think it is quite obvious to this court that a verdict of not guilty is not possible.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. von Karma, do you have any further questions for this witness?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What about the defense? No further questions, I presume?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I... I couldn't protect Maya...</thought> The defense... The defense...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mia!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I guess I made it just in time, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You... But... P-Pearls!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Her clothes ARE a bit small... Anyway, what are you waiting for, Phoenix!? Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But how!? She's already taken away every advantage!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The advantage is still in your hand! Think carefully, one more time, about what you saw in the Channeling Chamber. Do you remember what you told me yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Dr. Grey!!</line>
<line speaker="???">...I was... murdered...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lotta! At a time like this!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Times like this are perfect for snapping up shots!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You see... There is one final piece of the puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Question Lotta one more time, Phoenix. I don't know if she's doing it subconsciously or on purpose, but... she's not testifying truthfully.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, this court would like to end the cross-examination period.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please wait, Your Honor! The defense would like to request that the witness testify one more time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Overruled. I'm afraid you're too late, Mr. Wright. The cross-examination has already ended. Furthermore, any unrelated ques-</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But... I mean... I have some place I must go after this... Mmph! A-Al-Alright! I'll allow it! Ms. Hart! Hurry and give us another testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well... heck... What am I supposed to talk about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please tell us once more what happened when you burst into the Channeling Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">OK! You got it!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">See, you got through to the judge somehow, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, actually it was Von Karma's whip that got through to him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">When we broke into that room, all I could focus on was Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Nothing sounds different from before...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Some parts of her testimony were very vague. I should press her on those sections!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">When we broke into that room, all I could focus on was Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what did she look like?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ya know, she looked almost like a different person.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A... A different person?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, that is true... Well, then, Ms. Hart. Did you happen to see anything else?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I was... uh, kinda scared of the dead body, so I didn't take a good look at it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then perhaps that body was not Dr. Grey's at all!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Eh!? W-Well... I reckon that's possible...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, what if it was that of Maya Fey after the channeling? Or maybe -- Oww!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Urk... Sorry, Maya...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Are y'all done here? Can I continue?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I'm really bad when it comes to blood and ghosts and stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And even knowing that, you still persist in being a paranormal photographer?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">That's why I'm getting out of this here business. This gal's gonna get the dirt on the stars and be a tabloid photographer from now on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She goes through jobs faster than a baby through diapers.</thought> Wah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well? Would it, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nice, tag-teamed in stereo. Guess I should be grateful it's not in 5.1...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">But I still managed to point my camera at Maya and take a shot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">There must be something we can use in her testimony just now. We must find it! At all costs...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Two, right?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">T-Two what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Two shots. You took two shots.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... Only one has been submitted as evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Hart! Where is the other picture you have been withholding!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">No, no, no! You've got it all wrong! It's not me! I-I didn't mean anything bad! I know I can be a little mean, but I ain't evil!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, at least she knows herself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then why have you not shown this "other picture" to this court yet?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well, ain't it obvious!? That prosecutor woman told me to shut my trap about it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-What!? V... Von Karma!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-M-Ms. von Karma! Y-Y-You... You're hiding critical evidence...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Unforgivable, von Karma. Suppressing evidence like this... You're as bad as your father!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! The defense asks that Prosecutor von Karma be held in contempt of court!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... But you hid evidence from the court... On purpose! That's... That's... That's not fair!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">P-Phoenix!! Are you a lawyer or a school child?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ack! I was so angry I lost my composure...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Argh! I'm so mad that even my throat's clenching up! I'd better let the Judge handle this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. von Karma. Would you care to explain yourself to this court?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-How could you think...!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"M-More trouble that [sic] it's worth!?" How... How can you say that!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Wh-What is...? What is this picture!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I think the important point here is the person in this picture! This is most definitely NOT Maya Fey! What is the meaning of this!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This might be the break I was looking for... Now, should I or should I not insist that the person in this picture is not Maya?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>It's no good. We've been through this so many times...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is not like you, Mr. Wright! Why are you not objecting!? The person in this photo is clearly not the defendant and yet...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Explain yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! As you can plainly see, the person in the picture is not Maya Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes, I see that... It's not just her face! Her whole body has taken on a different appearance!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is only one conclusion that can be drawn, then. That somehow, this other person snuck in and traded places with the defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!! Well, yes, I believe you are correct, Mr. Wright! The person who was inside the Channeling Chamber was not Maya Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia! We did it!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...You're too soft.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You're softer than Aunt Morgan's strawberry desserts, Phoenix. Take a look at Prosecutor von Karma's face.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>S-She's... smiling...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Ms. von Karma! What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Maya Fey? But... Isn't this a totally different person!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's unbelievable... That she can...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I wonder if she knows what she's doing...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>M-Mia!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Taking pictures of someone during a private visit is illegal. That picture can't be submitted as evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-What is she...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I... I don't have even a single witty line...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">It looks like we've been had.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't claim to understand this, and I still cannot believe it... Are you saying that this person... this person is the defendant, Maya Fey!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I give up here, the trial will end! But... If I slip up and say something wrong, it will cost me... Is there any way I can prove that the person in this picture is not Maya!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's no good! My argument doesn't hold any water!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see the defense is staying silent on this one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes... Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes... Well, then. I believe we have reached a conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You can't give up! Please, for me? Take a look at the Court Record again and try to find some way out of this jam!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... Some way...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The judge is about to close the trial. You can't let that happen!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh... It's come down to this!</thought> Your Honor! Within this picture lies a critical contradiction to all the testimony up until now.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, now, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please! Please let me explain!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! The fire has returned to your eyes, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This picture... Within this picture lies a critical contradiction to all the testimony up until now.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A contradiction!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please direct your attention here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...T-To her... face?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">With your own two eyes, you can clearly see that this face does not belong to Maya Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AAAH! THAT HURT!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I know you ain't no dummy, so don't think yer foolin' no one here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There is a limit to everything, Mr. Wright. And that includes patience!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix! You have to think before you speak! You can't just blurt out any old thing.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Nick! You're supposed to be helping me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*cringe* Even Maya's mad at me now... I have to focus!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The contradiction lies... Here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...You don't sound very sure of yourself, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, but can you really tell me how much confidence I have in this!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AAAH! THAT HURT!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I know you ain't no dummy, so don't think yer foolin' no one here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There is a limit to everything, Mr. Wright. And that includes patience!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix! You have to think before you speak! You can't just blurt out any old thing.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Nick! You're supposed to be helping me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*cringe* Even Maya's mad at me now... I have to focus!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please direct your attention here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...T-To the sleeve? But... But there isn't anything odd about it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that is exactly what is so odd. Something that should be there is suddenly missing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was a bullet hole in the sleeve of the defendant's costume! If that's the case, then it should be in this picture as well!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. von Karma!! Y-You... You intended to hide this valuable piece of evidence!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You will most certainly be assigned a penalty for this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Alright. This should do some major damage to her argument...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Don't celebrate yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You like to bring down the mood, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Take a look at Ms. von Karma's face.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! She's got that condescending grin plastered all over her face again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What do you mean? And what "incompetent fools"...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's lying through her teeth! I know it! That woman knew about everything! The bullet hole, the picture -- everything!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">But you can't prove that. Franziska von Karma's idea of a "perfect case" is quite fascinating, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Gumshoe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">In any case, this is a very big problem! When the defendant was taken into custody, her costume had a bullet hole in its sleeve. However, from this photo, it would appear that right after the shooting, there was none!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The judge is confused by this strange twist of events. This is your chance, Phoenix! Load all you've got into this one shot, alright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it! <thought>Watch this, Maya!</thought> Your Honor! There is only one logical explanation for the contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The fact that the defendant's costume has a bullet hole in its sleeve is a fact! Which can only mean one thing. That this picture is a fake!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey! You callin' me a forger now!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, no, not you exactly... Well, not per se...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Oh no ya don't! Don't you be scratchin' yer head with that goofy smile like some monkey! Now, why do ya think I'd do somethin' that nasty!? C'mon now!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix! Use your brain for a change!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry, Chief...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is only one explanation for why there is no hole in the sleeve in the picture! The hole was created much later, after the murder took place!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-After the murder!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey! Those two gunshots we heard were before we broke in, or did ya forget!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... I-Is that how it went?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You do know how to count, right?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix! What are you doing!? Try it one more time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Chief...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defendant's sleeve had a bullet hole in it. However, this person clearly does not. There can be only one explanation. The person who shot Dr. Grey was not the defendant, but a different person altogether!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! If order is not restored, I will suspend this trial! Oww!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aah!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Why me!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A complete mess? I fail to see how! Please, enlighten us.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Aah! What the heck!? Is that any way to ask a gal a favor!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well, ya know...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">L-Look, sis... You're lookin' mighty scary so why don't we say you... Waah! I-I swear! I wasn't lyin' or nothin'! There wasn't anyone else in there! Honest!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... <thought>Why is it lately, all I want to do is cry...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, if the person in this picture is not the defendant, then this poses 2 very big questions. First, where did the defendant vanish to, and second, where did this person come from?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Come on! You can't fall apart here, Phoenix Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't believe that even Mia's calling me by my full name... But... I mean... How am I supposed to prove something like this!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>To "turn things around"... That's right. Mia would always turn things around and change her perspective!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So, where did this intruder appear from, and where did Maya disappear to? I need to look at this situation from a different angle! Let's see... What if before we broke in, the third person was already in the room... And what if Maya had left that room somehow... If I could prove that either one of those conditions were true...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Let's hear what you've come up with.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think what happened before we forced our way into the Channeling Chamber is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! I would like to present some evidence! I have proof that there was someone else in the room before the murder took place!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please take a good look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Okay...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And? What is the purpose of this item?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't you see, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... *sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think it is the court that should be sighing at you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ouch, that stung...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think the way I'm going about this is all wrong... I have to start over and try to think about things in a different manner...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya had left the Channeling Chamber at some point! And the defense can prove this!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Anyway, let's see some evidence. Prove that from the murder until the time of arrest, the defendant had left the room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The evidence you're looking for is... this?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Why the heck is there a "?" at the end there for!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, actually, I'm not really sure about this evidence, you know...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Next time, only present evidence you actually do have faith in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oww... That burned...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think the way I'm going about this is all wrong... I have to start over and try to think about things in a different manner...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, but I simply can't.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... As I thought. Another big waste of this court's time.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix! You can't just give up like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But Mia!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Rethink things one more time! There has to be an explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grr... Alright, Wright. Calm down and let's try this one more time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Hart. Do you remember this key?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Um... Well, I've seen it... Hey! That's the Channeling Chamber key, right? Before the channeling started, Maya locked the door from the inside with that...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yeah! That's why we all couldn't get the door open. That key's the only one of its kind, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh... One of a kind, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes? <thought>It looks like she's catching on...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Huh? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If Maya Fey locked herself in, then the key should have been with her.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, agreed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However, she did not have the key at the time of her arrest!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Aah! Well, ain't that a kick! So how come you're holdin' it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I got this as a present from a certain little girl. And that little girl was nowhere near the crime scene at the time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This means that Maya Fey must have left the room! If she had not, then I would not be holding this key you see before you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems we have come to an impasse. This picture has clearly captured the face of the murderer. However, is this person the defendant or not? The defense is arguing that this person is not the defendant. Furthermore, as proof, this key has been submitted as evidence. Ms. von Karma.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">At this point in time, a verdict on the defendant is not possible.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! If you would like to continue, do so in the lobby. Court will reconvene tomorrow at 10 AM. That is all. Court is adjourned.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Woooow! That was you Pearly!? You summoned my sis!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes. I felt I had no choice...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Great going, Pearly! I knew you were special! Hey, Nick, did you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Umm, yeah. It's not like anyone else in there could have done that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm, Nick... I know you're trying really hard and all, but... I really don't remember ever leaving that room.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">And I don't think that a third person... could have gone into that room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah... Well, at least we have until tomorrow to figure things out. Like, what happened in that room, for instance.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. I'm counting on you!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah... I envy the two of you...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, by the way, Nick. Do you think you could take Pearly back home for me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure. Alright, Pearls. You ready to go buy some tickets?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Huh? A tik-ket?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor thing... So sheltered.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't sound very sure, Mr. Wright. Objection denied.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection denied. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This evidence clearly reveals the contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are the evidence and the statement just now related?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They aren't, are they...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Wright, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness's statement is clearly faulty, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry, but I can see nothing faulty. Unfortunately, I will have to penalize you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh, I must be on the wrong track...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! This court sees no reason to further prolong the trial. Nor is there any need for more time to decide the case against the defendant. This case is extremely clear. I see no room for misinterpretation of the facts. This court finds the defendant, Maya Fey...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accused will surrender to the court immediately, to be held pending trial at a higher court within a month from today's date. That is all. This court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>