<xml>
<title>Reunion, and Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Maya">Um... Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Did you know that Von Karma's daughter is only 18... Just like me...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, yeah. ...Why?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I was just thinking about how strong she is... I mean, she's been in Germany all this time all by herself, and she's so grown up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, and I'm sure she felt a lot of pressure from her father's reputation.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...And then you look at me, and, well... I'm the daughter of the Master, but I'm still just a little girl. And on top of that, I'm the suspect in a murder trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Um... But I think you're really strong too, Maya, for all you've gone through...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Good morning! The two of you look like you're doing well today. I'm happy for you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Morning, Pearly!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You'll be safe today, Mystic Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">My mother is coming today to show her support!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-Yeah... Yeah! That's right, Pearly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Pearls...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...? Yes, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, do you think you could do me a big favor? Could you channel Mia today too?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Huh? ...I was sort of hoping to sit in the audience today and watch...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Please. It's very important to me. I don't feel confident enough without her help...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! That's enough! You can't show weakness in front of the person you love!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">P-Pearly! N-Not this again...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please, can you do this for us, Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... Alright. I'll do it. I'll do it for Mystic Maya's sake. See you later, then! I'll leave you two to your alone time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Phew, thank goodness.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This way, Pearls won't be able to see today's trial...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Wh-What do you mean...? What's going on...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Maya Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">All over the world, huh? Sounds like you've made quite a name for yourself, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Uh, huh... That's nice, Ms. von Karma.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uhh... It's true what they say... Women really are scary when they fight... *gulp*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then. A very interesting theory was presented during yesterday's session.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes. And this key is proof of that. This key, the only key to the Channeling Chamber, was not where it should have been.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-Alright... Let's hear it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... Ms. von Karma! Then... How do you explain this picture? Are you saying then, that the person in this picture is not the defendant...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-Then what is the meaning of this...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Can you substantiate your claim?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...Just as I suspected. Aunt Morgan...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Mia... She seems really torn by this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">My name is Morgan Fey, and I am a spirit medium, in a manner of speaking...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sorry, but what do you mean, "in a manner of speaking"...? Aaah!</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Yes, that is correct. I performed the Spirit Severing Technique on Mystic Maya then.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-Spirit Severing Technique?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">A technique to remove a spirit from a body and send it back to the other world. That is...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes...? That is...? Mmfph!</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">...Yes, that is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What in the world could've...!?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Mystic Maya... She escaped from the room...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! Ms. Fey! Please testify to this court what happened during that time!</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Your Honor, I will try my best...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I think someone just upped the ante on this trial...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">After we heard the gunshots, those two broke the door open and entered the Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why have you hidden this until now!?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">I... I did not wish to cause more trouble for Mystic Maya. However... I must correct falsities when they arise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why is she making it a point to take a stab at me... Never mind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, your cross-examination, please.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">My aunt is a very smart and sly person. It's going to be hard for us to find a crack in her testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">After we heard the gunshots, those two broke the door open and entered the Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just now, you said, "those two." Who were the two people you were referring to?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">I was referring to that foreign lady and yourself, good sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Lotta's not a foreigner... despite how she talks...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Oh, is that so? I'm sorry... I simply could not understand her atrocious English, not to mention she looked awful!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can already see people in the heartland gearing up for a riot...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">In any case, I have already sent the repair bill to your office, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, uh, thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... What did you do after that, Ms. Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">I requested that Mr. Wright and the other lady please contact the police.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was it really necessary to have two people do something so simple as call the police? If there was a possibility of escape, then one of us should have stayed behind!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, yes. That is a very good point.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">At that time, I, myself, was a little confused. On top of which, there was another...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Another what, madam?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Oh, it's nothing. No need to concern yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I want to hear the end of that sentence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was another reason you wanted both of us out of that room, wasn't there!?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You must testify! Why did you chase us out of the room!?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">...I simply did not wish for there to be more victims.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">"The lives of both the good sir and that camera woman may be in danger..." is what I thought to myself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, that was very noble of you, Ms. Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is bad... Now people have a good impression of her and a bad one of us...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Looks like she caught us napping. That's my aunt for you...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you satisfied now, Mr. Wright? Ms. Fey, please continue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The last bit of her sentence sounds like a red herring... If that's the case, I'm not going to fall into her trap today.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">If the defense has no further questions, let us press on.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">A pistol was hanging from Mystic Maya's hand and she was in a daze...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">During our investigation, you stated that you struck the defendant on the head, and this strike caused Maya to lose conciousness. Do you stand by this statement?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">I'm afraid I don't. The statement I gave you was a lie...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! B-But why would you lie about something like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">It is very painful for me to say this, however...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She was... covering for Maya...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you were "covering for the defendant"!?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Well, yes... It was only later that I was informed of what had occurred. That the renegade Mystic Maya had done something very unexpected...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-Something unexpected!? What, pray tell, did sh-- Oogh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes, very well...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... Why does it suddenly feel like there's a rock in the pit of my stomach...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm sure Von Karma's allowing this testimony because it's advantageous to her... ...Which means I shouldn't press Morgan any further...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Then, quite suddenly, she thrusted me away from herself and escaped from the room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was it really that easy for her to escape from you?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">I'm ashamed to admit to such a thing, however, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you are physically larger and stronger than the defendant. There is no way she could have escaped from you so easily...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Growing old is such a mysterious thing. Trust me, I know first-hand.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Basically, Mystic Maya's body was still that of the nurse she had called.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But if she had run away, wouldn't you have given chase right away!?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Well, yes, I would have... however...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">With great strength, she hit the base of my neck and I fainted for a short while...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You fainted...?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">I became dizzy, and then collapsed onto the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How long were you unconscious?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">I... I'm not sure. About ten minutes, perhaps.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... And the defendant almost certainly went somewhere in that time...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">I'm afraid I have no knowledge of where she went after that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that because you were unconscious?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Why, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great, well, now what...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So while you were unconscious, you have absolutely no idea where the defendant went?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">I would think that's obvious, good sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If that's true... then how can you know for sure that the defendant left the Channeling Chamber at all!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now that you mention it... I have to wonder myself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean by that!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It means she has another witness up her sleeve. That's what. It looks like Ms. von Karma is ready to move on to her next witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If she fainted, then there's no way she can testify any more than she has... If I press her, I'm not going to get anything useful anyway...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, then... Let's continue on with the testimony, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I can't see a crack in her testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What should we do...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">For now, we should try and get more information out of her. After we get more information from her we may be able to use it later to our advantage.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! From what I can tell, there is nothing wrong with this witness' testimony. And from what she has said, we can establish that Maya Fey did leave the Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I hope this isn't going to come back and bite us in the butt...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, yes... That is exactly what we should b-- Eeek!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She... She went to speak with someone!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Who was it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-Ini Miney...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I think you can see where this is headed...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Um... OK, so my name is, like, Ini Miney. I'm, like, researching, like, parapsychology stuff at the, um, university.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is this "parapsychology"?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Um... Let's see... It's, like, I guess, most people call it "occult stuff".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Even if that's what most people call it, I can't say I understand what that means...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Um... Well... Hmm... Like, I guess...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>For the love of all things good, Your Honor, have some spine... For my sake...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, when the channeling started, I was, like, sleeping in the Side Room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now hold your horses, young lady! You're saying the person that entered was your sister!? Don't you mean the defendant, Maya Fey...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-Are you saying that the spirit was the spirit of this witness' sister!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh... W-Well... This is...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...Um, like... Do I totally, like, really have to?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Miney... please.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">... My sister... Like, this is what she said to me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">She "took her revenge?" Are you sure that's what she said?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Y-Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I still can't believe it. I can't believe that a spirit would go so far as to use a medium to get revenge...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...What do you think, Mr. Wright? It certainly seems like all the loose ends are accounted for...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This... This testimony just now... Was it all made up? Was it just one huge lie...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Of course it was, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Mia! What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's well constructed... but that's all it is. But even the most well-spun lies can be undone. We can do it, Phoenix. Let's find that one loose thread and unwind this tapestry of lies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! There is room for doubt, so the defense will cross-examine this witness. We believe that our cross-examination will reveal the real truth behind this murder!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, when the channeling started, I was, like, sleeping in the Side Room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was that because of your, um... sesame allergy, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, that's right. I, like, think there were sesame seeds, like, in the lunch they served that day. I had this, like, premonition that it was going to totally be a "seedy" day.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Am I the only one who missed the boat here...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Anyway, so you were taking a nap. Did something happen while you were sleeping?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, a little later, someone came into the room, like, really suddenly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know the time?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Um, uh... Like, maybe a little before 11 AM? Something like that, I think...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Eleven AM...?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Yeah. Like, my stomach is totally ready for, like, food.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Ah, no... I think you misunderstood me... I'm not asking what time it is now... I meant what time was it when the "someone" came into your room!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Oh! So, like, that's what you meant! Like, you shoulda been more, like, clear about it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry. My bad.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">No, it's OK. Like, it's really...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's it? Why'd you stop mid-sentence!?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Did I? ...So, like... what was I talking about again...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... N-Never mind...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">It was, like, oh my gawd, totally my sister!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you absolutely sure?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...I guess?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You "guess"...? Was it or was it not your sister who entered?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, I don't know. I mean, like, I totally don't know "your sister" at all, Mr. Smith.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>First off, my name is not Mr. Smith. Second, I'm an only child. ...Hmm, but more than that, she's managed to mess up the question with her answer...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-The defense rests...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I, like, hadn't seen her in, like, so long... I was so happy in, like, a sad way...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were... happy in a sad way...?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Yeah, like, I mean, it was my sister!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But wouldn't most people react here with surprise at seeing a dead loved one alive again?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Um, but, like, maybe if I was, like, someone who didn't know about, like, the occult. But I, like, know all about the Kurain Channeling Technique.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Yeah, like, what she said.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Should I drop this  line of questioning...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you really didn't think anything "strange" of the whole encounter?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">No. Like, there wasn't any reason for me to, like, think anything was "strange".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... OWW!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You know the phrase, "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>"? Could you try using that once in a while...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Mr. Wright. This question of what the witness felt when she saw her sister... is it really that important?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Is it really that important?" Let me ask you: Is it really that important for you to ask?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Of course it's very important.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I don't think it's that important at all! Yeow!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, OK.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It is very important! <thought>Although I haven't quite figured out what "it" is yet. But I've got to bluff for now and make it seem like I know what I'm talking about...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Alright, Mr. Wright. Ms. Miney, please amend your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, OK. I'm, like, totally cool with that.</line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"I, like, hadn't seen her in, like, so long... I was so happy in, like, a sad way..." to "I wasn't, like, scared at all. And, like, her costume looked totally, like, normal."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's no need to press her over something this minor... I should be trying to find a more decisive problem with her testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">So, like, is it OK? I'm going to, like, finish my story, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I wasn't, like, scared at all. And, like, her costume looked totally, like, normal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, there was nothing odd at all about your sister's appearance?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, yeah. Nothing was, like, weird.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Hmm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hm? ...Mia's talking to herself like she's found something wrong...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">...That's impossible...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, is everything OK? Can I, like, go on...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ini">My sister... She, like, told me something, like, totally terrible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something "terrible"? What was this thing she told you?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Huh? Like, didn't I just, like, tell you about it? Did you, like, forget already?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, excuuuse me, Princess. ...Anyway, should I ask to hear the story again...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I did just hear this story. It's not like my memory is that bad...</thought> Actually, the defense is fine and does not need to hear the story again.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. You may continue your testimony, Ms. Miney.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, but could I hear the story one more time?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, sure, no problem. I'll even, like, tell it all spooky-like for you.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...Like, how was that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It was a little scary...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, I'm sorry. Maybe I, like, put too much spookiness into it...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I know there has to be something here I can use... But where!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">She really put a lot of thought into this lie, didn't she? We can't rush this. Let's take it slowly, one step at a time. She's bound to slip up somewhere. Don't give up. But don't get careless, OK? Remember, calm and collected.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was a very well-spun lie, Ms. Ini.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's well constructed... but that's all it is.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Stealing MY lines now, are we, Phoenix?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Miney, may I remind you of what you said? You said that there was nothing strange about your sister's appearance.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">L-Like, yeah... And...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I don't really think you thought that at all. Take a look at this picture. This is a picture of the "sister" you met. I would think that even you would be surprised if someone like this appeared before you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Miney! Why did you not include the blood you saw in your testimony!? If you were really testifying, and not lying, you would have noted it right off the bat!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Ummm...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Ms. Miney! What is the meaning of this!?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Ms. Miney?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I'm thinking! Don't interrupt me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Um, that... Eep!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Um, uh... Well... I... I uhh...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That witness... Her personality did a complete 180 there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lots of people do that when they get on the stand, though.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">... Like, I'm sorry. I, like, didn't mean to snap...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-If you please...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... The judge still looks a little shaken up... A lot of help he's going to be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, the Side Room was, like, kinda dark, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes, now I see. And you have given us a clear reason for why you didn't notice the blood.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">You think? Like, thanks, gramps!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you satisfied, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Alright, I guess not... Very well. You may question the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, the Side Room was, like, kinda dark, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? Because I thought it was pretty bright inside that room.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, that's right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, excuse me, but how is my statement any more subjective than Ms. Miney's?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, OK.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uuugh... Can't breathe... Let me outta here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">So like, the costume is, like, purple, right? The blood totally blended right in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You... didn't see the blood...?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But she must have had the gun with her at that time as well.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...! That's um...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you going to tell me next that you didn't notice the gun either!?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I, like, totally didn't. All I was looking at was, like, her face...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">And I, like, persuaded my sister it wasn't, like, right to do something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what was your sister, Ms. Mimi Miney, like at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Well, she was, like, totally flipped out 'cause she just shot Dr. Grey... But, I think, like, she knew. She, like, said she did something really bad. And, like, she said she wanted to go with me to, like, apologize to Ms. Morgan.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did Mimi's spirit really say all that to you...?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">May I ask you one more thing, Ms. Miney?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, sure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was there anything you found strange, unusual, or just out of place?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Something out of place? Huh? Like, when do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, when...? Um... When you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm talking about when you were in the Side Room, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Um... Like, no, nothing strange.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... What should I do...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Think harder! I know you can remember something!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I, like, totally can't!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if I put too much faith in Ini's ability to do anything with that brain...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even if I push her, this is probably a dead end... I should search for something stronger to hook her with.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Hmm... Well, if the defense is finished, please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, OK.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm talking about when you were going to the Channeling Chamber, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Um... Like, no, nothing strange.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She answered rather quickly... Now what...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Think harder! I know you can remember something!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I, like, totally can't!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's not good enough! You have to explain yourself clearly to this court!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Do you think, Mr. Wright, that whether or not there was something odd on the way to the Channeling Chamber is all that important?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I ask because it is VERY important! <thought>...Not that I know where I'm going with this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Ms. Miney, if you will, please include a statement about this in your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, I don't get why, but, OK.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"I, like, didn't see anyone on the way to, like, the Channeling Chamber."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Actually, I really have no idea!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then don't say it like you know what you're talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's continue on with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even if I push her, this is probably a dead end... I should search for something stronger to hook her with.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Hmm... Well, if the defense is finished, please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, OK.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm talking about when you arrived at the Channeling Chamber, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Um... Like, no, nothing strange.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... What should I do...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Think harder! I know you can remember something!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I, like, totally can't!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if I put too much faith in Ini's ability to do anything with that brain...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even if I push her, this is probably a dead end... I should search for something stronger to hook her with.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Hmm... Well, if the defense is finished, please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, OK.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">And then... like, I took my sister to the Channeling Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was your sister calm by that time?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, I guess so... I guess maybe, like, taking her revenge on Dr. Grey, like, made her feel a lot better...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She says with her whip at the ready...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">And, like, Ms. Morgan was the only one in the Channeling Chamber, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">May I ask you one more thing, Ms. Miney?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, sure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was there anything you found strange, unusual, or just out of place?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Something out of place? Huh? Like, when do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, when...? Um... When you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm talking about when you were in the Side Room, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Um... Like, no, nothing strange.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... What should I do...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Think harder! I know you can remember something!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I, like, totally can't!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if I put too much faith in Ini's ability to do anything with that brain...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even if I push her, this is probably a dead end... I should search for something stronger to hook her with.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Hmm... Well, if the defense is finished, please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, OK.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm talking about when you were going to the Channeling Chamber, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Um... Like, no, nothing strange.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She answered rather quickly... Now what...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Think harder! I know you can remember something!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I, like, totally can't!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's not good enough! You have to explain yourself clearly to this court!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Do you think, Mr. Wright, that whether or not there was something odd on the way to the Channeling Chamber is all that important?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I ask because it is VERY important! <thought>...Not that I know where I'm going with this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Ms. Miney, if you will, please include a statement about this in your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, I don't get why, but, OK.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"I, like, didn't see anyone on the way to, like, the Channeling Chamber."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Actually, I really have no idea!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then don't say it like you know what you're talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's continue on with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even if I push her, this is probably a dead end... I should search for something stronger to hook her with.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Hmm... Well, if the defense is finished, please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, OK.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm talking about when you arrived at the Channeling Chamber, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Um... Like, no, nothing strange.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... What should I do...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Think harder! I know you can remember something!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I, like, totally can't!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if I put too much faith in Ini's ability to do anything with that brain...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even if I push her, this is probably a dead end... I should search for something stronger to hook her with.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Hmm... Well, if the defense is finished, please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, OK.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I, like, didn't see anyone on the way to, like, the Channeling Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Try to remember that time!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">... Oh! Like, I remember! I remember, like, I totally didn't see anyone on the way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I guess this really is a dead end...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Something you finally pull out of a witness is never a dead end, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've finally found the fault, or I guess in your case, the "crack" in your perfect lie.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a look at this urn.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, urn...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are cracks. Do you see them?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">S-So? Like, what does that prove?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, yeah. I already, like, said I didn't see, like, anyone on the way to the Channeling Chamber. I didn't, like, totally say anything about, like, an urn, did I?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like you still don't understand. I propose that if you had really been walking along the Winding Way at that time, there was no way you could not have seen this person!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oops, silly me. Slip of the finger.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Wright. You need to keep control of that finger of yours'.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...As I thought, this is the wrong piece of evidence. Oww!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oww... So it's come down to a blunt "go home"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Don't over-think this. All you need to do is remember what happened yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd like to introduce someone to you. This is Ms. Morgan Fey's daughter, Pearl Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes...? And how is this child relevant...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It just so happens that at the time of the murder, Pearl was playing in the center garden.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And she just happened to break this urn.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh... OHHH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup. She accidentally knocked it over with her ball!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Nnaaawrr!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You say that you didn't see anyone on the way to the Channeling Chamber... However, that is impossible! I'd like to introduce someone to you. This is Ms. Morgan Fey's daughter, Pearl Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It just so happens that at the time of the murder, Pearl was playing in the center garden.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup! Which means anyone walking through the area would have to have seen her! So, Ms. Miney, what do you have to say to that!?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Nnaaawrr!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not preposterous, and I can prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is no way someone walking along the Winding Way could not have noticed Pearl!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oops, silly me. Slip of the finger.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Wright. You need to keep control of that finger of yours'.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...As I thought, this is the wrong piece of evidence. Oww!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oww... So it's come down to a blunt "go home"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Don't over-think this. All you need to do is remember what happened yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This urn is my proof.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know why it's cracked? It's because Pearl broke it! That's why!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">She broke the urn...? Yeow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This urn was broken around the time the channeling started!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No good. I can't find anything wrong...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix, the Judge believes this testimony. If you don't find some sort of hitch in her statement...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He'll end the trial... I know...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">We have to give it another shot! It doesn't matter how many times we listen. We can't give up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And Pearl was the one who put it back together... ...while sitting right in the middle of the Winding Way!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">WH-WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Miney.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearl was there, in the Winding Way at that time. She was hard at work, putting the pieces of the urn back together, you see. If you couldn't see that while you were walking, I'd have to declare you legally blind!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">G...Grrrrr...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think I have sufficiently proven one thing, Ms. Miney. You are a masterful liar!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Arghnnn!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! You need to watch what you say!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The one who needs to watch what she's saying is the witness! So, Ms. Miney! Tell us the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">A-About what!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About what!? About where you really were at the time of the murder, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Th-That's right! I was, like, sleeping in the Side Room...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Can I really believe her? Was she really sleeping in the Side Room...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I guess so. Sorry, my mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Now, then, let's proceed.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wait! Phoenix!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What? Did I miss something again?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You shouldn't let up on this line of questioning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Who is the only person you didn't see with your own eyes at the time of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was Ini Miney, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Which means, you can safely assume... She is the real murderer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a pretty daring assumption...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">But it's the most obvious, isn't it? I mean, is there anyone else?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, no, I guess not.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's worth a shot, even if it's in the dark. So, let's try to prove that Ms. Miney was not in the Side Room at the time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Umm, this is bluff number...? We've done this so many times in this case I've lost count.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your lies end here!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Wh-What do you!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness says that during the actual murder, she was asleep in the Side Room. And I say that's not possible, because there is clearly a contradiction here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A contradiction...!? Where is this contradiction!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The answer is in the Court Record!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court will see this evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mia!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I don't know what you plan on showing to the court, but I can guarantee you the answer is not there. Just this once, I'll lend you a hand. Now, rethink your answer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Alright...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. What is your answer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! OK, time to add another bluff to the pile...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, I may have overreached on this one... Is there really a contradiction somewhere...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Don't worry, you're on the right path, Phoenix. It might be a little hard for you to see the contradiction, but it's there. So, just this once, do you want me to help you out?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please, I need your help right now!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">H-Hold on... First, calm down, Phoenix. ...Good. ...That girl... She slipped up with her words.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Her words?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">If she really was in the Side Room the entire time, then she just testified about something she shouldn't have any knowledge of.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-And what is that!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The rest is for you to figure out on your own.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. What is your answer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! OK, time to add another bluff to the pile...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, it's "hard for me to see"...? I can't just accept her help without thinking it through myself!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ha ha, that's the spirit. Give it another try.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. What is your answer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! OK, time to add another bluff to the pile...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Earlier in your testimony, Ms. Miney, you made the following statement.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">And, like, Ms. Morgan was the only one in the Channeling Chamber, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's true that at the time, both myself and Ms. Hart were not there. We had gone to call the police.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...S-So? Like, what does that, like, have to do with anything!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's very simple. Ms. Miney, how did you know that fact?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...H-How...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I concede that Ms. Fey was the only person in the Channeling Chamber. However, someone who was "asleep" in the Side Room could not have known that!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which means, Ms. Miney! You did, in fact, go to the Channeling Chamber. However, you didn't go there by way of the Winding Way!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Gwaaaaaaaaaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But! Look at the manor guidemap! If one were to go between the Side Room and the Channeling Chamber, one would have to use the Winding Way!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, that's right, Your Honor. Which is why... Which is why I ask this very important question! Where was the witness at the time of the murder!?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...Umm... Urrrr...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Miney! Please answer the question!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Now's your chance, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The only person who could have killed Dr. Grey was Ini Miney! So now is the time to prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then, Mr. Wright. Let's hear your answer. Where was the witness when the murder took place...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She was here...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix! Did you turn the map upside down!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Oww... Sh-She slapped me on the wrist...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">There is no way she could've committed the crime from there!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*ahem* You two! Keep disrupting this court, and this trial is over. Is that clear!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor... Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Miney was here, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wha... But... But that's... the Channeling Chamber...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right! Ms. Miney was at the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! ...That's... Why, that is...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uwaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes! Yes, that is correct! Please, explain yourself, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Simple. Ms. Ini Miney was hiding at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I... I was hiding!? Where!? Like, where was I hiding!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Miney was hiding here! Owww!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Hah! Go home, boy, and look up what "hiding" means!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh... Looks like I'm going to have to one up her!</thought> Yeah, count on it!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix, you can't lose your cool like this! ...And, grow up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eh?... Oh, um, sorry, Chief...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-Behind the folding screen? Aah!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">There ain't no way anyone was hangin' out behind that foldin' screen!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">See! You stupid jerk! Quit being so quick to pin it on me, slimeball!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...N-Now, now... Ms. Miney... One so young as you shouldn't be saying...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Shut it, gramps. As if you know exactly how old I am!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I'm sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like the pipe's about to burst... Guess I should help it along...</thought> The witness was hiding behind the folding screen... With the help of this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Yeah, you go ahead and use that to hide!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's with these two...? It's like they did a mind meld all of a sudden...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Don't let them affect you! Just think about the correct answer.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">What's wrong, boy!? Come on, say something, you loser!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Miney! How you were able to hide at the scene of the crime is very simple! You were hiding inside this box!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Aaah! Th-Th-That tiny little box!? No person could fit in that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but your theory has already been disproved. <thought>Lotta disproved you when she was hiding from me in it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Umm...!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Th-That's right! I was sleeping there, so I should know! That clothing box was there in the Side Room, the whole time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Mr. Wright. Do you think you can prove where the clothing box was at the time of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... It's kind of hard to prove...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... I guess by that look, there is a way to prove it?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">If you look in the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess I should take a look at the Court Record...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, then. If there are...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Please wait... I said it was hard, but I didn't say it was impossible to prove!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then stop puffing up your feathers and hurry up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And now, I present the piece of evidence that will prove this clothing box was at the scene of the crime when the murder took place!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">..............................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Um... Your Honor...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I... um, fell asleep...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You got lucky, Phoenix! Now give it another shot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Alright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a look at this clothing box.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">You're soooo stupid. As if there's any sort of evidence in that old thing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...! Th-This... What on earth...!? Mfph!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-There's a hole! About 8 inches off the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, a hole about 8 inches off the ground. Where have we heard that before...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right! I hope this has opened your eyes to what happened! At the time of the shooting, the clothing box was sitting behind the folding screen. Which is why the bullet from the pistol hit both the box and the folding screen! It went through the screen, and then into the box.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...Nnngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Miney! You were hiding behind the folding screen, waiting for your chance! Yes, for your chance to kill Dr. Grey!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Aaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! ...So what you are saying--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That is exactly what I am saying! Ms. Ini Miney! You were hiding inside this clothing box all along! And you wore a medium's costume to masquerade as Maya Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">T-To masquerade as Maya Fey!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She had it planned from the very beginning! She would kill Dr. Grey, and pin the blame on my client!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...N...No... S-Stop...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure it's possible if you were to try! Ow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, I wasn't talking about that exact point... I meant, people, humans. If we want to do something bad enough, then...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! Beyond simply proposing that it is possible for one person to commit this crime, it is the duty of a lawyer to back up his or her claims.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Yeah, it's your duty!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you can't do that, then your proposal falls flat.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Yeah, it totally falls flat!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Why... Why do you have to hurt me so...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's alright, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It isn't possible for one person to commit this crime, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>... Ack! That's... That's right!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It really is impossible. For one person to do all the preparations, that is. Owww!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait! Ms. von Karma... You said it was not possible for "one person", correct?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...*huff*...*huff*...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Miney! You had an accomplice!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accomplice was...?? Any thoughts, Ms. von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Really, Phoenix! You even got Ms. von Karma to give up on you too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">..."Too"?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">As in, "me too".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh... Okay, I'll think more carefully this time...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...Grr... This person...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If it wasn't someone from Kurain Village, you couldn't have gotten the costume. And if it wasn't someone from the Fey household, you wouldn't have that box to use.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Isn't that the wonderful lady witness we had earlier!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you have to say to this, Ms. Miney!?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...Grrr... Grrrrrrrrrrr...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You shot Dr. Grey with your own two hands! Do you deny it!?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think this is what really happened. The murderer had planted herself at the scene of the crime long beforehand. Dressed in a medium's costume and wearing a wig, she pretended to be the defendant. And then, the channeling started. The murderer crept silently towards the other two, both of whom had their eyes closed. ...First, she drugged Maya Fey with a strong sleeping agent. Then, she stabbed Dr. Grey with the knife! Next, she hid my client inside the clothing box... She did that so she could take Maya's place and frame her for the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...But that's when something unexpected happened.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Unexpected...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Dr. Grey was actually not yet dead! With the last of his strength, he fired a shot at his attacker! And that is why the hole in the folding screen was so low to the ground! The murderer then took the gun from Dr. Grey, and...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">After that, you and the other lady thought to break into the room...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, a gunshot is certainly something you wouldn't expect to hear. Which is why, upon hearing the shots, we forced our way into the Channeling Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Miney... She immediately covered her own costume with blood...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And pretended to be Maya Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which is precisely why Ms. Morgan Fey chased us out.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Please leave this area to me. Go quickly and inform the police! Hurry! Before there are more victims here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What is one supposed to say...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the real truth behind this murder.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Who is that!? Laughing at a time like this...!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What is it this time...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Ms. von Karma... Surely...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAT IN THE WORLD!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that is...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eh? Well, that's... Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Yeah, that's right! That's exactly what I was gonna say!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Yeah! That's exactly what I wanted to say too! Yeah! Motive! I don't have a motive!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A... motive... That's... <thought>I can't say she has no motive here! I have to think of a motive now! What is her reason for wanting Dr. Grey dead...?</thought> The reason you wanted Dr. Grey dead is this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Ho-hum, ho-hum... Is this a word search? I'm having a tough time finding the word "motive!"</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uuugh... My breathing is becoming labored...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">My eyesight is failing me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Ack! I've got to take my time and think carefully about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix, think back! What kind of ax would Ini have to grind with Dr. Grey? ... There is only one reason, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Only one...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">...Hah! Just as I thought. You bore me with your silly answers, Phoenix Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just great. Now even SHE is calling me by my full name...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">You think I did this to get revenge for my sister's death?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes! Because through that accident, you suffered a lot of hurt and pain yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Don't be stupid! No one has proof that Dr. Grey drugged my sister, right? And you want to say I wanted to take revenge based on nothing?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What do you mean by that...?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Senile, stupid gramps. ... I'm, like, going to explain, so, like, please listen, OK? It's been over half a year since I was discharged from the hospital. If I, like, wanted revenge, then, like, I wouldn't have waited this long. Um, and 'sides, like, the guy that thought of the spirit thing, was, like, Dr. Grey. It was, like, a total coincidence he asked me about it, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She... She's back to her airhead self...!</thought> H-However, you see-- Eeeowch!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think we have our answer, Mr. Phoenix Wright. What Ms. Miney has stated is very true. The revenge plan is overly complicated, and she has no motive in the first place. Furthermore, there is no reason for Ms. Morgan Fey to cooperate with this plan. You don't even have any truly decisive pieces of evidence to demonstrate your point.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nnghuuurk! <thought>Wh-What happened!? I thought I had her for sure!...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Hee hee... See, like, that's what I, like, told you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I'm going to serve you a slice of humble pie!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, I now conclude the cross-examination of Ms. Ini Miney!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your Honor. Please, allow the defense one more minute.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Alright.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You can't lose here. Have faith in yourself, Phoenix!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes, it does sound like a ridiculously messed up plan for a murder, but you know, regardless, that girl trained for this crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...R-Really?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... Listen, Phoenix. Everything happens for a reason. There is a reason for why she had to kill Dr. Grey. And it is also the reason she had no choice but to kill him in this fashion.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Time is up, Mr. Wright. Your final answer, please. If you want to say that you can prove Ms. Miney had a motive, then... why did she kill the victim in this way? Can you provide the reason?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Can I... Can I really do this...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I am not totally confident here, but I know that I must press on no matter what...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's right, Phoenix! Only you can do this now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I will show and substantiate the fact that Ms. Miney had a motive!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Ha ha ha. Too bad. You're too late! My cross-examination has already ended, after all. Eeek!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Wh-What!? Y-You're supposed to be on my side! Aiiiii!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">N-No way...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court will take a 5 minute recess. We will continue the cross-examination after we reconvene.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">H-Hey! W-Wait a sec, here!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Is it really true... about my aunt...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm afraid so, Maya. There is no way Ini could've killed Dr. Grey by herself. And under the circumstances, there's no one else other than your aunt, Morgan.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That... That's terrible... Why? Why would my aunt...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! Ms. von Karma!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why are you doing this!? Why are you trying to take revenge on Nick!? Nick had nothing to do with what happened to your dad.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ugnn... ...Looking down on me, even though we're the same age...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you done yet? You've caused me enough pain and suffering.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...But even if you do that, it won't bring your father back...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court will now reconvene. Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Can you prove Ms. Ini Miney had a motive?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, I believe I can. <thought>Ini Miney and Dr. Grey have only one point of connection. And that is the car accident one year ago. The motive I'm looking for must be there...</thought> Ms. Miney. Please testify to this court about your car accident last year.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Huh? I thought, like, you wanted to, like, ask about my, like, motive. I, like, don't see the point in, like, bringing up the past.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Miney, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...OK, OK. Like, I totally don't think it'll do any good, but...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">That was... like, last year, in May.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I think I've heard of this incident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was all the talk on the tabloid shows, day after day, last year.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, and there was talk about Dr. Grey... drugging your sister...? Gwuugh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, yes... Mr. Wright, you may question the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Right now, it's impossible to prove that Dr. Grey did in fact drug Ms. Miney's sister.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... Which means I'll have to work this from another angle.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">That was... like, last year, in May.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Didn't some sort of medical malpractice happen at your sister's hospital then...?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Yeah, like, that was in May too. Like, the thing with all the patients dying was, like, May 2nd, and like, our accident was, like, on the 24th.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Two accidents back to back... Do you assume it's just a coincidence?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">My sis was, like, totally tired, so that's why, duh.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, something really bad had happened at, like, my sister's clinic around then...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was the malpractice incident where 14 patients died, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was the cause of the mistake?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, I heard it was 'cause the medicines, like, got mixed up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was that the fault of your sister, Mimi Miney?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, no way. Dr. Grey, like, wanted to blame it on my sis...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Which means as far as the "real" facts are concerned... Mimi Miney is the one who made the mistake...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">But, like, it really wasn't my sis...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">And like, the night of the accident, my sis was totally tired while she was driving.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She was "totally tired"? You mean, exhausted?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, she had to talk to the police, and, like, was being investigated, like, every day. It was, like, a totally terrible situation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's no wonder, then, that the car accident happened, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So then, why didn't you ask to switch places?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Huh? Like, what are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I meant switch drivers. If your sister was so tired, then you should have switched with her.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">True, true.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Ah, but like... I don't, like, have a driver's license...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Ms. Miney, please amend your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, OK. Anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"I, like, didn't have my license, so, like, I couldn't take over driving for her."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's no point in asking her about her sister. I should be trying to find out more information about Ini!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">So, like, can I go on?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your sister... Mimi Miney, was she that exhausted?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, she had to talk to the police, and, like, was being investigated, like, every day. It was, like, a totally terrible situation.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, if only you had your license and were able to drive for your sister.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Y-Yeah... That was, like, too bad...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I was, like, totally pooped too, so I, like, fell asleep in the passenger's seat...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The accident happened at night, correct...?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Yeah, like, it was at, like, 1 AM or so, I think. I had, like, a paper due, like, really soon... so, like, I hadn't slept and was working, like, real hard.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I, like, woke up 'cause of a jolt, and, like, it was a sea of flames around me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And your sister? What happened to her?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I... I didn't see her... The car was, like, totally black, and there was, like, a ton of smoke... I, like, totally had, like, no clue what was going on.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I, like, opened the door and, like, got away.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please tell us about your escape in more detail.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I... I, like, kept wanting to forget that time, so, like, I don't remember things about the accident in, like, details anymore...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, well, it's alright. No need to push yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I think I, like, gave an interview after the accident. Like, that would probably be the most accurate, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, if it's that article, then I've already got it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">I, like, didn't have my license, so, like, I couldn't take over driving for her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's why you were in the passenger's seat?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, yeah. I was, like, at my college's research lab 'till, like, really late... So my sis was, like, giving me a ride home.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You can't do this. You're being too easy on her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's got to be some sort of secret sleeping in this testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes, so let's find that one crushing contradiction and end this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Miney. That was a lame lie just now.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know you had a license back then! This is a photo you took for the express purpose of getting a driver's license!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is the meaning of this, Ms. Miney!?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Ah, um... Uh... That's... That's right! Y-Yeah, I had, like, a license... But... ... But I didn't get it until after the accident!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, you had it. You had it at the time of the accident! Director Hotti... or the guy pretending to be him anyway, said so!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">What, are you talking about that perverted fake clinic director?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, that perverted fake clinic director. And how did you know he was perverted. Eowch!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, last November.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? N-N-November...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What in the!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-Th-Th-Th-That's what happened, Mr. Wright! At the time of the accident, Ms. Miney did not have a driver's license.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uuuuurk... OW!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Anyway, without a license, the witness and her sister could not have switched drivers.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I'm, like, glad you get it, but... like, even if I had my license, I, like, don't think my sis woulda, like, let me drive.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Hmm...</thought> Yeow!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Don't just stand there "hmm"-ing to yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not you too, Mia! With the whip... And the pain... And the oww...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ms. Miney! Why do you think you would not have been allowed to drive anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Eh? Um... That's because...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think this situation calls for a more detailed testimony. Ms. Miney, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Eh? Like, how annoying. Oops, like, sorry. Didn't mean to be mean...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, around that time, I was, like, really close to getting my license.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see... A bright red car for sports... Now then, the defense may question the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I'm not terribly knowledgeable about cars, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, around that time, I was, like, really close to getting my license.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what do you mean by, "really close"?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, I had one of those "permit" things. I think that's what they're called.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, "permit"?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Wow, the big name lawyer boy doesn't even know what a driver's permit is!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, this lawyer never had a permit. Wah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is with her...? All she's said in the last few minutes is utter nonsense...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">So, like, may I continue?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">My sis was, like, this totally big fan of cars and, like, really valued them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She "valued" cars? How much would you say she valued her car?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Well, like, she'd flip out at, like, a drop of rain... and, like, she would notice if someone, like, touched the car door with dirty hands.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>In that case, why bother taking the car out of the garage, ever!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did she take such special care of the car?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">How can you say that!? It was a brand-spanking new car!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...New car?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, you wouldn't want to, like, get it dirty, would you, Mr. Lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I would think that cars getting dirty is just another fact of life, but... I guess people who really love cars think otherwise...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix, try asking something of more significance, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Ms. Miney? What kind of car was it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I just don't get what's so special about cars...</thought> Alright, then, please testify about your sister's car.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">She, like, had just gotten this really shiny, bright red sports car.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was a new car...?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Yeah. She had, like, just gotten it. It was, like, from the U.K.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm? The "U.K."? Was that her boyfriend's initials?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">And it was a really special model. She had waited for a whole year for it to arrive.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess her love of cars would be the obvious next topic...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But I really don't know anything about cars... But I had a feeling this was bound to come up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... Please continue...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Hold on! Phoenix! You can't just ignore this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia... I had no idea you liked cars so much too...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's not my point!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh, yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please append what the witness has just said to her testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You mean the part about it being a special car from overseas?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*sigh* Well, if you like cars that much, then...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's not my point! <thought>Though to be honest, I don't know what the point is either...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Miney, would you please fix your testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Sure, whatever.</line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"She, like, had just gotten this really shiny, bright red sports car." to "My sis' new car was, like, a totally special model from England."</line>
<line speaker="Ini">My sis' new car was, like, a totally special model from England.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>I yelled, "Hold it" pretty forcefully, but... I don't actually know what to ask about cars...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... So, yes... <thought>What am I supposed to pick for a topic...?</thought> Let's start with this. Why are British cars good?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They're expensive, and their driver's seat is opposite to our cars here in the States. It would seem there is no benefit to owning one.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like... Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This whole steering wheel on the right side thing; it's kind of goofy, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Y-You! What do you know!? That sleek shape! The purr of the engine! The wild way it starts! And its smooth handling! The raw feeling of manual transmission! The cool breeze of the AC!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uuugh... Forgive me... <thought>Her personality really changes at the drop of a hat...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's interesting, isn't it, Phoenix? Bit by bit, we're beginning to see the real "contradiction" behind this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I really stink at talking about cars... If I ask the wrong question, I might make someone mad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Miney, I believe you may continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ini">She, like, would say things like, "No way am I letting a newb drive my car!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was your sister good at driving?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">She was, like, totally awesome! She, like, said she was going to be the, like, "Racing Queen of the Nursing World".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Somehow, I think she bumped my question off-track again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">So, like, that's why I ended up in the passenger's seat that night too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that was when the accident occurred, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, yeah... I, like, immediately reached for the passenger side door, and fled, like, in a daze...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Sounds like you had a terrifying time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">There is something very big here. It's going to be hard to break apart such a natural-sounding testimony. But we have to attack it. And by doing so, a flaw will show itself. It has to.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Do you really think so?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Believe. There is a path, I know it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Mia almost sounded like a prophet for a second there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Miney. Do you remember this article?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's an article about the accident. You had said this in it: "But I opened the right door, and, like, got out"... That's correct, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, why are you suddenly asking me about that...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor. Which side is the passenger's seat: the left or the right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, it's on the right side, of course, because the driver's on the left side.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That would be if it were an American car. But it would be the opposite in a British car.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Opposite...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The two of them were riding in a British car! In that case, the passenger side would be the left side!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What do you mean by this!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Miney! You said that you had escaped using the right side door of the car! But if you were sitting there, then that means you were in the driver's seat!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Aaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Order! Order in the court! Order! Ooooooooorder!! Order... Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That is what Ini said, yes But that is where her story falls apart. Somewhere, all of us made a big error in our assumptions! </line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix. It looks like you've finally found the real root of this murder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If we connect all the dots, there can only be one answer! I'd like to ask the court a question. Ini or Mimi -- who was really driving that night?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the answer is Ini Miney, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Why would you say that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Ini Miney just said so herself in her testimony! She said that she escaped the car from the right side door! Which would have been where the driver's seat was! Owwwww!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that is why the accident happened!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Hold it, Phoenix! It looks like you still don't see the real truth behind the accident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-The "real truth"...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Think outside the box! Isn't that what we always say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A-Alright, one more time...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The answer is the one person who had her driver's license, Mimi Miney. After all, that makes her the only person who could legally drive!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But, you just said... The witness, Ms. Ini Miney, was the one in the driver's seat!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which leads us to the next question...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Th-The</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-The next question!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who is the person standing on the witness stand right now?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">... Uuughn!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll tell you what her name really is. This witness' real name is...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Would the defense please inform the court of its birth name?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Phoenix Wright... Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, what a relief. I thought you'd forgotten your own name... Again.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I was beginning to think he forgot too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a second... I screwed up didn't I?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Big time. Listen. This is the grand finale. Don't hold back! Let it all out on this one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Alright, I'll give it another shot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mimi Miney. That is your real name.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When she was admitted into the hospital, this witness was suffering severe facial burns. So for the purpose of facial reconstruction, they used a picture.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the picture she gave to her doctors at the time. That's right! It's a picture of her younger sister!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Nooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But... Mimi Miney... She died... In the car accident!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what everyone thought. However, that was not the case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was the body of the real Ini Miney. Isn't that right... Ms. Mimi Miney!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That car accident one year ago... The one who died that night was Ini Miney. Her sister, Mimi, then stole her face... And was reborn as Ini. With this, she effectively erased "Mimi Miney" from existence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your Honor. I'm sure you can now see why Mimi had to kill Dr. Grey.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What do you mean? Aaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Dr. Grey wanted to call back the spirit of a dead person. Specifically, the spirit of his nurse that died in the crash, Mimi Miney. However, that would not have been possible! Because "Mimi Miney" was still, in fact, alive! And that fact would have been discovered had the channeling been conducted. So this witness had to stop that from happening... ...at all costs!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. Before the channeling, Dr. Grey had the misfortune of consulting this witness about communicating with the dead. And in that moment, his fate was sealed!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-W... Well, Ms. Ini...? I mean, Ms. von Karma... Eek!</line>
<line speaker="???">... Looks like I've been unmasked.</line>
<line speaker="Mimi">That's right, I admit it. My real name is Mimi Miney.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mimi">That quack doctor... He got what he deserved in the end. And I was so close to finally ditching "Mimi" too. So close...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... But why!? Why would you go so far to throw away your self...? To become your own sister!?</line>
<line speaker="Mimi">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I understand why... Mimi Miney wanted her self to disappear because of this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Dr. Grey was right. The mistake was caused by the nurse. A nurse by the name of Mimi Miney. That's right, the person standing before us today. And a few weeks after this mishap, Mimi Miney had a car accident, in which she lost her younger sister.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Fourteen patients dying in that incident, and her own sister's life, extinguished. It was all too much to bear.</line>
<line speaker="Mimi">...I found a way for myself to escape it all... The only way...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She lost everything in the flames of that accident, her sister... ...and even her own face. This was her last chance... Her chance to throw away her past and start a new life as her "sister"...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Unbelievable... A plan beyond my wildest imagination...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Just stop.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I feel embarrassed for you for even thinking of showing that piece of evidence. That woman... She had lost everything. So this was the only way to make things right, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like this wasn't the right piece of evidence after all... I guess I don't fully understand this case yet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mimi">That jerk... If only he hadn't thought of that channeling mumbo-jumbo...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Mumbo-jumbo?</line>
<line speaker="Mimi">Becoming Ini has been the most horrible experience in the world. Spirit channeling, the occult... I hate it! I hate it all!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I believe there are still a few unsolved riddles here... Why did you set a murderous revenge plot into motion? And why did Ms. Morgan Fey agree to help you with the plan...? Regardless, I believe one thing has been made crystal clear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The innocence of the defendant, Maya Fey...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm going to enjoy the news tonight, Ms. von Karma. How about you? It's going to be broadcast all over the world, right? Your defeat, that is... Yeow!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ohhh!</line>
<line speaker="Mimi">Aah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Owowowowwwowoowowowowwowwwowwowwwooowowwooowowowoowooowowowoowooww</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ph-Phoenix! Hang in there, Phoenix!! PHOENIX!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Now then, it looks like it will be some time before Mr. Wright regains consciousness... so I will go ahead and pronounce the verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is all. This court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Congratulations, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">S-Sis!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's good to see you, Maya... How are you doing?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sis! Sis... I-I didn't kill anyone, did I?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">No, you didn't. It was all just a dream... A really bad dream.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, sis... In my dream, I smelled a really familiar scent.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">A familiar scent...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I was inside that clothing box, right? That box... That was the box you used to store your clothes in a long time ago...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... There is still one thing I don't quite get.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What would've happened if Mimi hadn't shot Dr. Grey...? I mean, we broke in because we heard a gunshot.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I think Mimi Miney had planned to open the door to the Chamber herself. And then, you and Lotta would have witnessed quite a scene; a "possessed" Maya Fey, who had just committed a murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She had it planned down to the smallest detail, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Congrats, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Thanks! Looks like you bailed me out of another jam.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... you know...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But... I really don't want something like this to happen ever again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm fine because I have you to help me out, Nick... But every time something happens, I lose someone special to me. First my sister... And now my aunt...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick... Tell me... Tell me why my aunt went and did something so horrible? Why would she help Ms. Mimi with a plan like that...!? I just... I just don't understand it, Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, it's over. Why don't we just let it be.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, please, I need an answer...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The reason Morgan helped Mimi with her plan was...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Pearly?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Four years from now, a new Master will be "born" into Kurain Village. And that person will be you, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A-And...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, if you weren't there... then the main family's blood-line would disappear... And what would happen then...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... ...The branch family... My aunt...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...No, Morgan's spiritual power is too weak. The next person would be... Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Aaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Everything was done for her sake. It was all so that Pearls would become the next Master.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-Yeah... I can see that... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...? Did Maya say something just now...? I think that she was saying... "I thought so"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...? I don't get it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, me neither. Even I don't really know why Morgan cooperated with Mimi Miney...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, this whole thing is over now, so let's not dwell on the past, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah... Thanks, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I just don't know the answer to this one... I'm just as confused about the situation as she is... So why the "thanks"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't sound very sure, Mr. Wright. Objection denied.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection denied. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This evidence clearly reveals the contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are the evidence and the statement just now related?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They aren't, are they...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Wright, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness's statement is clearly faulty, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry, but I can see nothing faulty. Unfortunately, I will have to penalize you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh, I must be on the wrong track...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! This court sees no reason to further prolong the trial. Nor is there any need for more time to decide the case against the defendant. This case is extremely clear. I see no room for misinterpretation of the facts. This court finds the defendant, Maya Fey...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accused will surrender to the court immediately, to be held pending trial at a higher court within a month from today's date. That is all. This court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>