<xml>
<title>Reunion, and Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Pearl">Thank you very much for bringing me home, Mr. Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're welcome. I had to come and look into a few things here today anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... I thought about this a little.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">If Mystic Maya didn't kill that nice man...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She definitely didn't!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes, of course. But if she didn't... Then someone else did, right? Um, that "murderer" person!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder what's wrong... She seems sad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's an old-style phone booth. I can't say it fits in with this area too well. I called the police from this phone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what did you think of seeing your first trial?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I was really surprised! I had never seen so many people before!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">And Mystic Maya looked so small... and helpless.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, Maya's already naturally short, so...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">And then, that snobby woman with the ruffly clothes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ruffly... Oh, she means Franziska...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">She had such a bad attitude! She acted like she had already decided that Mystic Maya did it... I am going to tell her what I think of her tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wouldn't miss tomorrow's trial for the world...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Why was that woman bullying Mystic Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, she's the opposite of a lawyer -- a prosecutor, so her job is to prove people guilty. They don't care if someone's innocent. All they care about is if they win.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Th-That's terrible! B-But... She's really a good prosecutor with a heart on the inside, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... There's no one like that. All prosecutors are the same. ... Well, "he" might have become a good guy... Eventually...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">"He"? Who are you talking about, Mr. Nick? Is it that person Mystic Maya was talking about? Mr. Eh-ji-werth...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That was a long time ago. He's not around anymore...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He clutched onto his foolish pride too fiercely... and died for it.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">O-Oh... That's too bad...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By the way...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, you wouldn't happen to know anything about who the murderer is... would you?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wh-Why are you asking me!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I was just thinking earlier...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I didn't see anything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She "didn't see anything", huh...? Speaking of that... During the murder... where was Pearls, and what was she doing...? And on top of that... This key... Just when did she pick this up...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I just realized that I never asked you what you were doing at the time of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls, where were you and what were you doing when the murder happened?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wh-What I-I w-was doing? Ah, I-I w-wasn't d-doing a-anything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's really bad at lying...</thought> You can whisper it to me. I won't tell anyone else. I promise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aah!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... Um... I guess you can see through my lie, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... Clearly.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I can't lie to you, can I, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You really won't tell me what you were doing at the time of the murder...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But with the Magatama, I can unlock your Psyche-Locks, right?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes... Ah, what should I do...? Should I tell you what my secret is...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If you would just tell me, it would be easier for the both of us...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm so nervous...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Pearls is holding the key to this whole case! I can feel it! ...Speaking of keys, this one turned out to be quite important too... I didn't think it would literally be the "key" to today's trial.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So... that's a lawyer's Sacred Treasure?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I feel like it has a mysterious power, just like my Magatama...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, well, I guess I can let her think what she wants on this one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So you like things about spirit channeling too? The Kurain Sacred Writings are on this folding screen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? Is that what's written on it?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">There are six lines to the Sacred Writings. Cleanse thy soul... Open the door to the spiritual realm beyond... Converse with the departed... ... Cast on thyself Protection... Maintain the spell... Release the spell...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So basically, this has nothing to do with the murder... Well, that's super.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About this key, Pearls... You found it on the day of the murder, right?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, where you found this key is very important. So, please tell me, Pearl. Where did you find this?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... I found it in the incinerator...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The incinerator? <thought>Hmm, is she talking about the one in the garden?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">The door on it was a little open, so I took a peek...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When was that?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It was after the channeling, when everyone was in a panic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...? Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Are you going to tell my mother?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? You mean, tell Morgan what you did?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes. If she finds out that I was playing in the left-over trash, I'll get a spanking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ah, gotcha. Well, let's keep it a secret from her then, alright? <thought>Hmm, the incinerator, huh? Sounds like a good place to search next...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I've seen this knife before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really!? Where!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-My kitchen...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh... That's right... This knife belongs to the Feys...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'll skin and cut up some apples for you later, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-OK... Thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Th-That's Mystic Maya's!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ack!! I shouldn't have shown her something this violent...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I-I-Is that... Blood!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... It's nothing. Really. Just forget your ever saw this, okay? <thought>What was I thinking? I can't show stuff like this to a child.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>On second thought, showing her this picture might cause severe trauma...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I knew her for a little while. Mystic Mia was your teacher, right? I'm sure she was a great Master of Lawyers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Master of Lawyers"... I guess...? I mean, it's not exactly a martial art...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You should keep training, Mr. Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, you're probably right.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">To tell you the truth, I really want to grow my hair out, just like Mystic Maya. But my mother wouldn't let me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think your hair now suits you perfectly.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">R-Really? Th-Thank you! *fidget, fidget*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*fidget, fidget*</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah! This person! I can't let her get away with bullying Mystic Maya like that! I'm going to cast a curse on her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">C-Can spirit mediums really do that...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... Actually, no, I guess not... Grr... I have to find something I can do, then!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>When they're mad, the women of the Fey family could give Medusa a run for her money...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This case has had me out of the office most of the time... I can come back tomorrow. Helping Maya should be my top priority now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Charley.  A quite decroative plant. He's a handfull but i've grown quite attatched to the little fella. He also helps me to remember all the good times with Mia.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya must still be in questioning... She'll probably be done in a little bit, so I'll come back later...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's really empty... There's supposed to be training held today, but I guess it's already over...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A door that leads to the Channeling Chamber, the place where spirits and people meet. The iron in this door was tempered, making it very solid. But I guess it wasn't strong enough to withstand The Phoenix!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Hmm, looks like Morgan's here too, but she hasn't noticed me yet... What is she doing...? She looks like she's talking to a picture...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">...Don't you see? Take a look around... Finally, my chance has come... I've waited for this day for so long! That's right... Prepare yourself, dear Misty...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What in the...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Who's there!? ...Oh, if it isn't Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Just curious, but that picture you were just looking at...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Oh, today was that event, was it not, good sir? I heard you did well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh, oh, yes... Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">I am terribly sorry I could not attend the trial today. Please accept my apology. I had a previous engagement, as I had to watch over the trainees' training today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I get the sense she really doesn't want to talk about the picture...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">All because the Master can't be here with us, you understand. And that is why a lowly branch family member such as myself must do this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is some empty space behind the folding screen. The light of the candles can't reach back there, so it's completely dark. There wasn't anyone back here at the time of the murder... Or that's what Lotta testified in court... <thought>I knew I should've taken a look... I can always count on Lotta to make things hard...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you remembered something about the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">No, I told you everything I know already.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Where[sic] you in this room the whole time when Lotta and I went to call the police?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Yes, of course. I was by Mystic Maya's side the entire time. I performed the Spirit Severing Technique and held her in my arms afterward.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, you said that yesterday as well. Did anything else happen?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">I would like to say more did, however that is all that occurred.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ah, I was really hoping for some new info...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">I suppose nothing happened in the end, good sir. Sorry to have played on your hopes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I feel like I was just made fun of in the worse way possible...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So do the students train every day?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Yes, absolutely. They were given a day off the day after the murder, of course, however...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And I assume both Maya and Pearls went through this training...?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! Yes, yes! <thought>Wow, she got real scary, real fast...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">How many times must I tell you before you understand, good sir? They are to be addressed as Mystic Maya and Mystic Pearl.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry... I meant Mystic Maya and Mystic Pearl... Wait... I'm sorry, but "Mystic" Pearl? Isn't that going a bit too far...?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Next question, please.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh man... She's really being a pain in the butt about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Please remember to watch not only what you say, but how you say it, good sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the Master is... um, Maya's mother, right?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">...Mystic Misty... She is a brilliant medium.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And where is she now...?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">We are not sure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not sure?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">About 16 or 17 years ago, Mystic Misty failed at channeling a certain spirit. And after that... she simply disappeared.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">I don't believe she will return to this village, in any case. And in four years' time, her name will be forever erased from this village.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Erased?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">A person who has been away from the village for over 20 years is considered dead...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">And that is four years from now for her. When that happens, a new Master will be appointed to Kurain Village.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And...?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Mystic Maya was supposed to become the next Master... However with this... murder, I'm afraid...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I must be imagining things... I thought she was laughing to herself for a second there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">There are six parts to the Kurain Sacred Writings. To think that this valued treasure of our village... and Mystic Maya were both shot by a gun...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, that's...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Even if it was something that occured during a channeling, it is an unforgivable act.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">This... This is the key to this room!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">B-But why do you have it, good sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That, I'm not telling.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">R-Return it at once!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I can't. It's evidence, after all. <thought>I think she knows exactly how important this key is to this murder... But what is this feeling I'm getting from her? It feels... Hmm... I can't describe it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">That is Mystic Maya's costume, isn't it...? It's a shame. I never thought anything like that would happen to her...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But we don't know that it was Maya that did it...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Oh, poor Mystic Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Do you ever listen to anyone other than yourself?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">That is Mystic Maya before I applied the Spirit Severing Technique... This picture... It was taken without my express permission. I knew allowing a person like her from the "Heartland" into our country was a bad idea.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You do realize that the "Heartland" is a part of this country, right...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About this person...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Oh! It is that man, is it not? A man who wishes to borrow a departed spirit's power to hide the lack of his own. What an insignificant man. And see how pitifully he died.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Insignificant...?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">That would mean you are that man's insignificant little friend, dear sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Then I guess that makes Maya my insignificant little assistant, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">...Oh, my... I think I may know of this person from somewhere...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's Mia. You know, Maya's older sister?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">...! Aah! Yes, that is who she is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...How could you forget a daughter of the Master...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">If memory serves, she became a lawyer. Oh, how splendid for her, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That soft, kind smile... It's the kind that tells you a pair of devil horns are not too far away...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Come to think of it, I don't believe I have seen my child today. Would you happen to know where she is, good sir?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, I wouldn't.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Honestly! Take one day off from training, and it is neigh impossible to make it up. Good sir! I pray you are not teaching her strange, fiendish things in her time off!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh boy. Here comes her anger. ...And we were having such a civil conversation too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Being born as one of the Fey family, but of weak spiritual power... It makes the people of this village look down upon you, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I didn't know that...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">But I will be alright. ...As long as I have Pearl. I am satisfied because I have my Pearl.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think about this?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">I am terribly sorry, but I am afraid my spiritual powers are not as strong as you might think... I really am terribly sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Um, but this has nothing to do with your spiritual power...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like there's no one here... And even though the weather is gorgeous today, it's raining inside my heart...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's the "Side Room". Looks like guests can use it as a place to take a break when they feel tired.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a really old urn. There are the ashes of a person long dead inside. It looks like something with a long history... Other than that, it's not very interesting, so time to move on.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The bedding is all laid out today too. Guess I'll leave them alone for now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's still charming to see a real sliding door like this in person. From here, I can see the Winding Way and the little garden in the courtyard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Excuse me... ... <thought>Who am I talking to? There's no one here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, I keep wondering about this box. I'm sure this wasn't here before the murder took place. It looks like a box for storing clothes... But it's pretty big for just clothes... It's mostly empty, but a few folded pieces of channeling costumes sit at the bottom.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey, there's someone by the incinerator... Ooh, looks like they've noticed me. And are now running at top speed towards me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Oh, hey! *huff, huff* Like, *huff, huff* You're that dentist guy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, it's Phoenix Wright, attorney at law. Nice to see you again.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Ooh, like, real suave. So, it's, like, my turn. It's nice to see you, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what's up? You're all out of breath...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">L-Like, huh? Oh! Like you mean... Like, I'm just totally happy and like, totally excited to be here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excited?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, I mean, there are so many things to, like, see! It's, like, the real deal here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, really? For example...?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">For example... Like, that urn over there. Do you, like, know about it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All I see is an old, cracked piece of pottery...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right... Pearls said she found this key inside the incinerator. I guess I should take a look inside for myself... ... Th-This... This is from Maya's costume...! There's blood on it... A tiny bit, but still...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, this piece of cloth was burned in this incinerator. And this key was also found in there. Hmm, I get the feeling this incinerator plays a crucial part in this murder...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So there's a spirit in this urn, huh? Hmm, all I see are a bunch of cracks. But I guess maybe the spirit could live in the space between the cracks... Hmm, looks like something's written on it... "I AM"? Huh? Weird...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is there some sort of legend connected with that urn?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, yeah! It's, like, this village's treasure!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh. Didn't know that.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">And, like, it's sealed inside that urn.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Um... "It's"...? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, you know! Ami Fey's spirit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ami... Fey...? Who's that?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, jeez, Mr. Smith. Get with the program! Everyone knows the lady that founded the Kurain Channeling Technique was Mystic Ami.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, you don't have to get upset with me...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">So, like, as long as her spirit, like, lives in that urn, the spiritual power of the Fey family'll stick around. Like, isn't that totally romantic?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Romantic, huh...? <thought>If that urn is really as important as she says, it could be a vital clue...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ini, I want to ask you about the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Murder...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Dr. Grey's... Remember...? <thought>As if there's another one?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Oh, that one! Like, you shoulda said so in the first place! So, like, I totally don't know anything 'cause I was, like, sleeping in the Side Room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, that's not much help... Did you notice anything at all?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, come on. What a total bore. I, like, totally have nothing to do with this, like, murder thing...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, yeah. You only introduced Dr. Grey to Kurain Village. No relation, sure. Even if you were only "acquaintances", that still means you knew him. Furthermore, your sister, who died in that accident, was a nurse at his clinic...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright then. Why don't you tell me about your sister's fatal accident.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">... Like, why? You think, like, it's got something to, like, do with the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know yet, but I'm trying to chase down every lead I have...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...A... A Psyche-Lock!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like I'm going to need something to pry her mouth open on this one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, about the accident, Ini...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, you're totally not gonna give up, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I'm not.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I totally want to forget about my sister, you know? Time to move on and all that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess I have no choice but to remove those locks...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Wow, so, like, the Kurain technique is the real deal. I'm gonna, like, have to write about it in, like, my report for school. Hey, so, like, you'll give me this picture for, like, the report, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No way!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">She's, like, in a lot of trouble, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's stealing quick glances at the picture while smiling like a cheshire cat...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">But, like, this will totally prove the power of channeling.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>..."This"? What "this" is she talking about...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, that's totally Mystic Maya's cousin, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. Her name is Pearl.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Hmm? So, like, this little kid is, like, the next Master...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, no, no, no. Maya is the next in line to be Master.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Ah, oh yeah. Like, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick... I've been waiting...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...She looks so helpless...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So? So? How was it!? What did you find out!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Well... I found a few things...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">My eyes are tearing up, Nick. Don't make me cry...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I just need a little more time. It'll all come together by tomorrow, I promise.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm sorry, Nick. Every time I see you, all I do is cause trouble...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So how was it? Today's trial, I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You were fantastic, Nick! Every time I thought our goose was cooked, you managed to turn it all around. I bet it would make a great Hollywood movie!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't be silly. We have to concentrate on the trial. We're going to win this, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Thanks a lot. Really. Hey, Nick? The person who shot Dr. Grey wasn't me, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course not. You're completely innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If that were true, then I'd be really happy, but... there wasn't anyone else in that room with the two of us, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, did you check behind the folding screen?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um... I took a quick glance, but there wasn't anyone there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... <thought>That's exactly what Lotta said too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why do you believe in me? Why do you think I didn't kill Dr. Grey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Because of something Mia told me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">My sis? What did she tell you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She said that spirit mediums can't have dreams. When you're channeling, it's impossible for you to dream because your soul leaves you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now that you mention it... Wait, then... then... I really am...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You are not the real murderer. I think that... maybe before you even called the spirit, you were drugged.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Drugged...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think this was planned from the very beginning. And you were set up to take the blame for killing Dr. Grey.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's... That's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I want to ask you something about Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pearly? What about her?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No matter what I try, she won't answer me. I want to know what she was doing at the time of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... W-Wait! Nick! Y-You don't think she did it, do you!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, nothing like that...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She'd never do anything like that! You hear me!? Never! She's a great kid, and really cute... And really great... And cute.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I didn't really think she was the murderer. But... she's definitely hiding something.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were with her on that day, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. The two of us. We were playing with her ball.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A ball, huh? <thought>Sounds like a dead-end to me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, about this ball...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's nothing really special... Just a plain old ball. I think she was still playing with it when I started the channeling job that day. Pearly really loves to play with that ball.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She "loves to play with that ball", huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">When she wants to get it, she always climbs right into the clothing box.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The clothing box?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. Pearly's always hiding in there. You know the Side Room? There's a clothing box in there. It's really big, so once you see it, I'm sure you'll know what I'm talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The clothing box in the Side Room, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's the same as the last time I saw it. You just like to show it off, don't you, Nick? Are you that thrilled to be a lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That's not what I meant by it, but... I mean, I don't really think about it. I just sort of shove it in people's faces... Force of habit, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That hole... It looks an awful lot like a bullet hole...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's probably what it is.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's TERRIBLE! How could this happen to such an important screen!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Um, instead of dwelling on the hole, let's focus on the fact that you weren't shot...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Hey, you're right! So I was the one who was about to get shot, huh? Th-That's TERRIBLE! Who'd want to shoot little ol' me!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess she didn't realize she was the one being shot at until now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! That's... The Channeling Chamber's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the only one in the world, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. During the trial, I was kinda wondering why you had it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I got it from Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's weird... I swear I locked the door... and then put the key into one of my pouchy sleeves...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your sleeve? But how and when would your sleeve leave the room? It didn't grow a pair of legs...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder where Pearly found that key...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's a knife from my family's kitchen. I'll never be able to use it again...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's alright. I'll buy you a new one, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Argh! That's not the point! ...I don't ever want to see another knife... ever again...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That... That's... That's mine, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Dammit! I upset her again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It really was me, wasn't it? Wasn't it, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This... This is me, right? I guess I really did shoot Dr. Grey...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that's not you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is not!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is too, is too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should've kept this picture to myself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's Kurain's Sacred Urn. Mystic Ami's soul is sealed inside of it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I know all about it. About how she's the founder of the Kurain Technique.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh, look at Mr. Smarty here! Thinks he knows all! You sound like an occult fanatic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Trust me, this isn't going on my resume any time soon...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, I haven't looked at this in a long time. I wonder when it became so cracked?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not too sure myself, but I found it just now inside the furnace.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Is it trash burning day already?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's not something I would know about... <thought>I guess she didn't notice the bloodstain. Probably better that way...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What am I supposed to do, sis!? ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pearly... She definitely has more than me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Who I think the next Master should be... I mean, she's got more spiritual power than me, and she really works hard at her training...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Way to go Phoenix... Way to bring the mood down even further... *sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So she's Prosecutor von Karma's daughter, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, then... she'd know about that person, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"That person"...? Is she talking about "him"?</thought> It's alright. We don't need to talk about that right now...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Mystic Ami. She's a Legendary Spirit Medium. I like the way that word sounds... "Legendary"... Ever since I was young, I've dreamed of being a "Legend".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, this murder will make you into a "legend", alright... Hmm... I probably shouldn't say that last thought out loud...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, I can't think of anything special about it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">AAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Hey! Wait! Please! Lotta! ... <thought>She ran off into the manor...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lotta...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Aaack!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Hey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...*sigh*...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! Morgan!</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Yes, what is it? ...And must you be so noisy!? We have a rule here: "The hallway is not for running" Now then, in a calm manner ask your question.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay... Anyway, did you see Lotta come by here?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Ah, that girl from the "Heartland"... I'm sorry, but she did not pass by here at any time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grr... Lotta! You sure know how to waste a man's time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm pretty sure I saw Lotta run in this direction... but it doesn't look like she's here...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's Pearl's ball. Maya said that it's always kept in the clothing box... So then, what is it doing on the floor...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the clothing box where Pearl's ball is usually kept. I wonder what's inside...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaa!? Wh-Wh-What were you doing in there!? What were you thinking!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I'm a bad person! Just another piece of human trash. I needed a hole to crawl into...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>So you crawled into this clothing box because there wasn't a hole to crawl into? Oh man... ...Huh?</thought> There's a small hole in this clothing box... And it's about... 8 inches off the ground! That's the same height as the hole in the folding screen! Then, could this...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the clothing box where Pearls keeps her ball. I thought I felt my soul shake when Lotta jumped out at me. So it's big enough to fit a grown adult... Well, if she can be called an adult...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, Mr. Nick! That person ran by here just now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What person?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, you know... The person with the fluffy cotton candy hair...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ah, she means Lotta.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">She said, "Don't look at me with 'em eyes!" but... I'm not that scary, am I...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I don't think that's quite what she meant.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, that's right. She also wanted me to tell you, "Goin' on a trip to find myself, so don't ya bother findin' me!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh... Well, thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You're welcome.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearl. You have to tell me what you were doing when the murder happened, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... But what if I can't just tell you what happened...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then I'll guess what happened. How does that sound?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Eh!? Y-You can do that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You'll tell me if I guess something right, won't you?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Y-Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, when the murder was taking place, you were here, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm pretty smart, Pearls. I know you were right here.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">No, I wasn't...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? I'm wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ooh, I feel a little better.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ooh, I feel a little warmer... from embarrassment. ...I'd better try again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were here, weren't you Pearls -- in the Winding Way?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">W-Wow! ...Y-You got it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So? Do you think you can tell me now?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...I'm sorry... Not yet...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Man, oh man... Alright, what next...? OK, I think I know what you were doing there.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">D-Do you really know that much?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I am a lawyer, you know. Now, what was it Pearls was doing in the Winding Way?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I feel just a little better.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You are a lawyer, but you're also still a person, after all...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, I'll get it right this time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were... playing with this ball, right?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah! That's right! How... How did you know...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya told me that you love to play with your ball.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... Yeah. I was playing with my ball.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Un, huh. And then?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something happened, huh? ...Something really bad...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">*gulp!* Wh-What do you mean, "something"!? N-N-Nothing happened...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is it. While you were playing with your ball, this happened!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Were you so surprised that you were shocked into silence?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Yes, at how wrong you are, even though you were so sure of yourself...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh? <thought>Way to embarrass yourself in front of an 8 year old, Wright...</thought> Ah, sorry, sorry. Just see if you were paying attention... Ah heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It's okay Mr. Nick. You can always try again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This urn... It's a village treasure, right?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah... Um...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the spirit of the founder of the Kurain technique is sealed in here, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Y-Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this? It's cracked all over, isn't it? There's even a few gaps here and there...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... Please don't tease me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearl, you broke the Sacred Urn, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The ball smacked into it and knocked it over, right? And if Morgan found out, she'd get really mad, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She doesn't seem to be fighting back... I think I hit the bull's-eye this time. But it's strange that the lock hasn't broken yet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I-It's... It's a really old urn, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I-I-It's so old... So it's not that weird... to have a few cracks...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Her voice is shaking...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">H-How can you tell that urn has been broken!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...I'm sorry. I don't want to be mean, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sigh* I figured...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, do you want to try again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. <thought>I'm sure I can get it if I think about it some more! The thing I'm missing... must have something to do with what's written on the urn...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who started the Kurain Channeling Technique?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Eh? Um, it was Mystic Ami...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. And how do you spell her name? Do you know?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">How do I spell her name? Um... I don't know...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's spelled "A-M-I".</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">*gasp!*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I thought it was a little odd when I saw "I AM" written on this urn.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's how I knew that someone must have broken this urn. And made a mistake in spelling when they put it back together again...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Around when Mystic Maya started the channeling on that day, I was playing in the Winding Way... with my ball.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's when you... broke the urn?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Y-Yes... I broke it... I... I accidentally let Mystic Ami's spirit fly away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry. Morgan will never know, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm a bad child... Breaking a village treasure is unforgivable. I thought... that maybe they would make me leave the village. But the broken pieces were pretty big, so...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You thought you could put them back together, and no one would notice?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I found some glue and brought it to the hallway... and fixed the urn there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The hallway? You mean "Winding Way"?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes. The channeling had already started, so I didn't think anyone would walk by.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, I see... So, about how long did it take you? It must have been a nasty repair job.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes. I might be strong at spiritual things, but when it comes to arts and crafts, I am not nearly as skilled. When I had finished fixing the urn and looked up, I saw you coming into the manor...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's around when Lotta and I were coming back inside after reporting the murder.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">When I saw that, I packed everything up in a hurry. Um... Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it, Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm... I'm going to get banished, aren't I?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I really don't think that's going to happen. I mean, I bet Mystic Ami's happy to be free from that cramped urn.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Y-Yeah, I hope so...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No harm done, and a happy resolution... Phew!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mia!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix, it's good to see you. I was really worried so I thought I'd see how you were doing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You might get caught on film again...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">There are certain risks you have to take in life, or in my case, death. Anyway, how are you doing? Have you found anything useful?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, only a little. I think I'm slowly beginning to understand everything, piece by piece.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Everything will resolve itself by tomorrow, somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">There's still a whole slew of questions for you to answer before the trial tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean like how did the real murderer get into the room and kill Dr. Grey...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes. Also, when did the murderer enter the Channeling Chamber...? You guys were all standing around in front of the room after the channeling started.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which means that the murderer must have gone into that room before the channeling...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's what I think, in any case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But Maya's already said there wasn't anyone else in there.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...That's true... But if we can't figure out the murderer's movements, we're stuck like a beached whale.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">I thought I'd never see this day. Are you actually asking me about spirit channeling?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This case is all about spirit channeling. And I feel like I don't understand a thing about it...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, that's only natural... After all, spirit channeling isn't exactly an everyday thing, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I guess you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The power to change your physical appearance into the person you're calling was something our ancestor, Mystic Ami Fey acquired.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've heard that name before...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The Fey family was originally a family known for its service to the gods. When Mystic Ami was born, she was given a certain fate through her name. Because, you see, she was named after one of the Buddhas of Buddhism, "Amitábha". To this day, her soul is still sealed in the Kurain Sacred Urn. It usually sits in the Winding Way, and has her name written on it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Aww, come on, Phoenix. It's just a fairy-tale.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Are you saying that me being able to see you is just a fairy-tale too...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Come on, Phoenix. We don't have time to be looking at things like this. We need to find out everything we can for the trial tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, it's about time I left.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mia!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">We'll be in big trouble if the guard sees me here... Phoenix...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Chief!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">There is still a lot of dirt left in this case. Once you think you've gathered all the evidence, then come back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes, Chief.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Phew. I think I've found everything I can. But I can't see how they all add up... Hmm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And is Ini Miney being here just a coincidence...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How is it that the spirit Dr. Grey wanted to call just happened to be that nurse, and that nurse turns out to be Ini's sister... It's too... convenient...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wish I knew a little more about Ini, but where am I going to find info like that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aah! L-Lotta!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Oh, so ya finally noticed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I thought I heard a mosquito buzzing in my ear, although I couldn't understand a word...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well, I gotta hand it to ya. Ya sure know how to chase down garbage! I mean, I'm grateful to ya for chasin' this large lump of one around like this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Thanks...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">But ya know, you're just wastin' yer time. I'll be fine on my own.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What are you going on about? And as for "following" or "chasing" or whatever it is, isn't that what YOU'RE doing!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Um, well, ya see... Well, yer not exactly a real gentleman with a lady's heart, are ya?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You're not exactly the world's number one charmer either, sister.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Look, I'm really dang sorry about today! When I get all fired up about somethin', it's impossible to stop me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You hurt Maya really badly, Lotta.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Um... I don't suppose you could forgive a gal like me...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I guess. You did help Maya out too, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">For real?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, for real.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ah, thank goodness... I'm still...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"I'm still..." what...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">N-No, no, nothing, nothing at all. Just talkin' to myself, ya know, gibberish... ...Now then! Lotta Hart, at your service!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I'll share with ya all the dirt I've dug up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-Thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey, don't be all surprised! Tell ya what, I'll even give ya all this info for free!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Lotta not taking money? Now I KNOW this one's an alien clone...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not done...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And to think we trusted you, Lotta, and what do you do!? You stab us in the back! You stressed us all out and even gave Maya a few strands of white hair!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Urngh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now I'm going to have to pray she makes it, or she may come back as a ghost...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ack! That's enough! Ya can stop right there! Look, I'll tell ya everything I know! Everything! I'll spill it all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Everything?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yeah, ya got it! Everything! But... Well, actually... Tell ya what, I'll even do it for free!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You were expecting me to pay you after what you did to us!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If Maya is not the real murderer, then... who do you think is, Lotta?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well heck, ain't it obvious? It's that occult freak!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean Ini Miney?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well, there ain't anyone else it could be, right? That granny, you and me, we were all together that whole time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So, Lotta suspects Ini... Which means she might have already found some info about our mysterious Ini...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Speaking of Ini, do you have any other information about her?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Sure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, what is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ha ha ha... It'll cost ya... And it'll cost a lot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, silly me. Here I thought "free" meant "no money necessary".</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">That girl was hospitalized about half a year ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hospitalized...? But why?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well, heck, you can go find out on yer own.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Here, I'll give ya the clinic's address. Maybe ya can find out something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Maybe"...? What's that supposed to mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well... See, actually, it was gonna be annoying, I reckoned, so I didn't actually go there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aargh...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well, that's the way the gumbo spoils, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Spoiled gumbo sounds... Eww... I mean, look, don't blame this on... Oh nevermind! <thought>Looks like I don't have much of a choice. Better go check out this "Hotti Clinic"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About this clipping...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Now, you listen here, boy, and listen good. You can't go lookin' at such an old piece of paper, ya hear!? People's got eyes on the front side. You know why? So they can see in front of themselves! Not behind! So how about it? You feelin' my energy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nope, not an electron.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ya think I could have the guts to carry one of these around? A celebrity photographer with a gun? Ya think it'd work? "Bang, bang!!" ...Nah... Thanks, but nah. I can't see myself like that.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Aaaaah! Th-There's... There's blood on it!! Get that away from me! Where do you get off showin' somethin' like this to me!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oops, guess that was the wrong thing to show her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I'm a real natural, aren't I? I caught the murder just right, and even managed to make it mysterious.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mysterious!? All you managed to do was forget to focus your lens!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Shaddup! That's my technique! My technique, now, ya hear!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey, it's that Dr. Grey guy. It's a pity what happened to him. Pretty scary what ghouls and ghosts can do to a man, huh? Gawd rest his poor soul.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Since when was Lotta so religious...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Now, this kid -- I think she needs to be taught some manners. This here's her second time in the stew, right? My Pa woulda slapped me straight!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ya know what they say, if there's a second time, there's bound to be a third, and a fo- OW! Nngh... Ya didn't have to slap me. I get it, I get it. Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hmm... I overlooked this little kid.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I mean, I didn't think it, but ya know how it's always 'em silent types?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Huh!? Wait, wait, wait...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">The little tyke's nothin' but a ball of happy goodness, right? So I reckon, she's the type to have done it! Well, now, that's just how the world turns.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think this has anything to do with how the world turns...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">That old lady sure can be forceful. She scared me that day. ...Well, only a little, now, ya hear?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Heh, that's Ini Miney, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. I was wondering if you know anything about this girl...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ya know! Actually, I did a little checkin' up on her the other day. Her sister, she's the one that Dr. Grey wanted to call back from the spirit world.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I had heard as much... I had also heard that Ini was the one to introduce Dr. Grey to Kurain Village.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ya don't say? That's one sneaky gal, if you ask me... Hey, ya want me to tell ya more about her?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ya know, I'm beginnin' to get sick of this hairstyle. Next time I go to the salon, I'm gonna get my hair straightened, I reckon. What do ya think, Phoenix?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think if you got rid of your afro, I wouldn't recognize who you were.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yeah, that's kinda the problem, ain't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Please, can we get on with the important stuff...? Say, like the murderer...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey, this is that prosecutor gal. The one that likes breakin' all the rules. Switches are for horses and lights, not people! How's that? I made a pretty clever pun, didn't I?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Sorry, didn't hear you.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ah, well, I'll forgive the wax in yer ears this once and tell it to ya one more time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...So, this is where Ini was hospitalized...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Hmm, yes... Are you here to visit a patient? Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, yes... Are you a doctor here...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Hmm, yes... I'm Director Hotti... Hoh, hoh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ack! I didn't think I'd be speaking with the Director himself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes...? So what can I help you with? Uh, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd like to ask you a few questions about Ms. Ini Miney.</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm? Ms. Miney? Ms. Ini Miney? ...Hmm... Yes... Hmm... OH! Her! Ah, it's too bad. I'll tell you something. That girl left here a long time ago.</line>
<line speaker="Nurse">Here you are! Sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">?</line>
<line speaker="Nurse">You know you shouldn't be up and about! Come on, it's back to your room with you!</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Ah, Sweet'ums! Calm down, calm down. Don't be so harsh to an old man like me.</line>
<line speaker="Nurse">Don't you dare start that "Sweet'ums" thing with me! If you don't behave, you'll get yourself tossed out of this hospital!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow. I didn't think nurses could be this direct or forceful towards their boss.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nurse">Come now. Be a good boy and give me the Director's white lab coat!</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">OK, OK. I got it. I. Got. It. Hmm, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes? Uh, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't "Hmm, yes" me. Who in the world are you?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">I'm Director Hotti. Hoh, hoh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The nurse went off some-where... Oh the inhumanity. Only person I can talk to... ...is this guy... ...Uuuugh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be the waiting area. It's got the feeling of one and there are sofas lined up... but I don't see all that many patients.</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes... Well, it's the quality, not quantity that counts. Uh huh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What in the world did that have to do with anything...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder where that door way down there leads to...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Oh, that's the X-ray room. Hmm, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-H-How did you know what I was thinking!?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes... Well, it's... Because that's the X-ray room... Uh huh, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There is something very peculiar about this guy... Because I know it's not me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This patient is undergoing rehabilitation.</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">And look at that strained face twisting in all those ways... and that oily sweat... hmm... His whole body is swaying back and forth, wobble-wobble, like he's about to fall. Hmm, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! Don't just cut into my monologue like that! I'm explaining things here!</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Ah, sorry. Hmm, yes... Most sorry... Yes... Uh, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the clinic's reception desk, but it doesn't look like there's anyone at the counter. On the wall is this month's "Word to the Wise: Do something in vain, and your only reward is tiredness." Hmm, not exactly the best thing to be telling your patients, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what exactly do you treat at this clinic...?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes... We treat all sorts of... doctory, clinical stuff, uh, huh, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Doctory, clinical stuff?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Well, I don't actually know or particularly care about the details. Hoh, hoh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, hmm... Yes... What is that look for? A-Ah, yes. There's a really big general hospital around the corner. Hmm, yes... When they can't accommodate everyone, they move some of their patients here. Uh, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You do surgeries here, right?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes... We do some plastic surgery here, it seems... Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It... seems?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes... Uh, huh... It seems that way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you know about Ms. Ini Miney?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Now you're talking! Hmm, yes. That girl, she was transferred from the general hospital.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">From the general hospital...? To here? What kind of surgery did she need?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes... Well, she needed surgery. It was really bad. Really bad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what kind was it...?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes... Well... No, no... You see, that is something... No, I can't tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So you say with a happy smile on your face... "Mr. Director"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hotti">See, there's this thing about how doctors aren't allowed to talk about patient stuff. It's in all those TV shows too, right? You've seen them, right? Hmm, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm never going to get him to unzip those broken zipper teeth of his at this rate... There's got to be something I can show to this old coot...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please tell me what you know about Ini Miney.</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes... I'll get to that, trust me, I will. That girl... That's right. She was transferred here from the general hospital. This was... hmm, yes... a year ago. She was one of those... "emergency" cases.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was she ill with?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Ill? Nah, nah, nah. She was injured, not ill. With my trained eye, I could see. Yep, I could see it was a huge wound at that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A huge injury?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Her whole body was wrapped around and 'round in bandages and her arm was in a cast.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That sounds... pretty severe, alright...</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes... It was an accident; an accident. They're scary, yes? Cars, hmm, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Car...? ...You mean it was a traffic accident?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Yep! That's what gave her the terrible injuries. I swore it was in the papers, hmm... Yes, I looked it all up, I did. It was terrible... Hmm, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Dare I even ask what is wrong with this old guy...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just now... You mentioned something about a big operation?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm? Are you talking about Miss Ini's operation?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes... Miss Ini's.</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">That... Ah, that was one heck of an accident. Hmm, yes... Her whole face was burned like bad toast. It was bad. Very bad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was it really that bad...?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, it was a good thing that Miss Ini had a picture of herself. I heard that picture was how they put her face back together... Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Picture...?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">That girl, see, she had, uh... She had just gotten her license. So she just happened to have a license photo on her, hmm, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">So, see, I got her picture. As a way to remember her, yes... Well, more like... Swiped...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Um, breech [sic] of ethics...? ...Oh, wait...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hotti">What? What? A pretty girl like her -- I bet she has lots of pictures of herself...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Sure...</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">It's a treasure. My treasure... Preciiiious...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What happened to the actual license itself?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Who knows. I didn't bother to ask. It probably got burned up along with the car. Hmm, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... So you "looked up" information on Ini's accident, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Yep, yep. Sure did... Hmm, yes... I read every paper that covered it at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What kind of accident was it, do you remember?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes... Hold on. I'll go get it for you. The article, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Huh? Y-You have it?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Well, well, well, don't get me wrong. I thought something like this might come up, so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Obsessive to the max... But I bet I could learn about how to stay on a lead from this guy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hotti">According to this, Miss Ini was in the passenger's seat.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The passenger's seat, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">And dozing... Or so it says. A strong jolt woke her up, and the next minute, a sea of fire was all around her. Miss Ini fought with the door, finally got it to open, and somehow managed to get away. ...Anywhoo, you can read all the details in the article. Hmm, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A new clue! I should probably look this over.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm? What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm a lawyer. Right now, I'm investigating a murder.</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, hmm, yes... What is with your angry face? Violence isn't the answer, hmm, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The trial is tomorrow. And I would really like some information from you.</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm... Is that right...? ...Well, you know, I think I can let you in on a little secret...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes... Actually, ... I'm not the real Director.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you kidding!? Anyone with half a fly's brain knew that!</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Eh!? Wh-What do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Do I have to explain this to him...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Well, hmm... Hold on. I'll give you something. Real information, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">I'm actually, this clinic's... See, I'm like this place's... "walking dictionpedia"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean "walking encyclopedia"?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Y-Yeah, that. And my specialty is in young, silky-smooth hottie patients... There's nothing I don't know about them... But I get "embarrassed" talking about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah... How about you keep that kind of information to yourself...?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hoh, hoh, hoh. Anyway, you wanted to know about Miss Ini Miney, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Miss" Ini Miney?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hotti">That girl... Ah, I remember her especially well... Really, especially, very well...</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Now this is what I'm talking about! Hmm, yes... nice. This is nice and exciting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think? Does anything grab your attention?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">There's no mistaking this is nice... Hmm, yes... I like... Yes... I like this picture... Hmm, yes... Mind if I borrow this for a while...? For... "private research" purposes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm, that's okay... <thought>I don't think I should support his "research"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Mmm... Miss Ini is really cute in this picture. You'd agree, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, sure.</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">I wish I could see her again. Maybe the next time she has a big accident. Hmm, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'll tell her for you...</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes... Please... Hmm... I'll be waiting for her... Hmm... Yes... Waiting...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So about this girl...</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm... She is... Um... Not the best... Hmm, yes... But she'd be a great candidate for surgery... Hmm, yes, yes... Hmm... That's really the only thing I can prescribe for her...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...What is he talking about? What surgery...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you please take a look at this person...?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Oooh... This is, this is... ...A superb example of a woman... I'd like to... hmm, meet her... just one time... Bring her to me tomorrow. Hmm... She'll get special attention from me, I promise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-Where does he think he is!? This is a medical facility!!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, about this girl...</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Isn't she the patient down in room 206...? Hmm, yes... I'm sure that cute nurse is taking very good care of her. That nurse said the girl has chicken pox... or was it measles... Maybe the flu...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Um, Pearls is fine and well, although I feel sorry for the nurse now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About this person...</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm... Hmm... I feel like... I feel like... Somewhere... I've seen her somewhere before, I think... Hmm... Hmm... Well, when she comes tomorrow for her consultation, I'm sure we can get re-acquainted...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I don't believe this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This person...</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Ooh, she's nice. That look in her eye... She looks like a queen. She's glaring at me. Hmm... Ah, her stare is making me choke up in tears.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I... I was whipped by her... And it hurt... a lot...</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Oh, wow! I am so JEALOUS! So? Did you cry? How did it feel?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I cried a little... I think...? I can't actually remember...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Oh, it's me. Hmm, yes... My tuft of hair... It's so nice. Shows off my smartness... You should try it too. My new hairstyle that I invented...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ah, that's OK. I'll pass on this one...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, so what do you know about this...?</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">I see this and, um, my mind's blank. Hmm, yes. It's boring, that's why. Boring. Hmm, yes... How do I put it? If you had more... Hmm... More attractive items... Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Attractive...? Huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, I'd like to ask you about this person...</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm... Something tells me... Hmm, yes... Umm... No, nothing. There is no need to bring this person in for an exam. Wouldn't do it anyway. Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even as a pretend doctor, he gets an F from me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hotti">It's been half a year since Miss Ini had her surgery and got better. She was discharged sometime in December last year.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's already been half a year, huh...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes... So, how was I? I was a real help, wasn't I? Hmm, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes... Thank you very much.</line>
<line speaker="Hotti">Hmm, yes... Well, then, I'll be getting back to my room then. Tell Miss Ini I said hi, OK? Hmm, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's time for me to leave too, hmm, yes... Ack! OK, it's definitely time to leave!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey! So how was it!? Didja go to the clinic?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I found out a few things... I guess...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">...What's the matter? Ya ain't lookin' so well. Ah, yeah. So earlier, that ol' granny called the cops.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh? The cops? Why would Morgan call the police?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">She said she had "somethin' to tell 'em". Things are sure gettin' interestin'.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ah, but honestly, I tell ya, that granny sure got her bloomers in a knot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I guess you could put it that way...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">It always starts out small, ya know? Stealin' the Master's seat, and controllin' the village folk... and now ya see what it's turned into? A murder, that's what.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, what a mess. ... H-Hey, hold on!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That stuff you were just talking about... That's the first I've heard of it.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Heh, really? Well, it's old news to everyone else in the world.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, excuse me for not keeping up with gossip while I'm busy saving people!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You said something about "stealing the Master's seat"?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yup. Right now, the Master is this medium named Misty Fey, but... the one that was really supposed to be the Master was that old granny.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Morgan was supposed to become... the Master...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know where Ini is, Lotta?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yeah, I saw her not too long ago. She's hangin' around that garden in the middle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK, thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ya got somethin' to ask her?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah. I've got a whole list of things only she can clear up for me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">So I hear the Master has always been the oldest daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The oldest daughter...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Turns out, that old bat is Misty Fey's older sister...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">They say the older sister is usually the one with more spiritual power.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come to think of it, Maya said the same thing a long time ago... She warned me not to take Mia's powers lightly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well, anyway... somehow, granny there lost to her younger sister, Misty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">This made the townsfolk turn against her, so I hear. Said all sorta things too, like, "She's the oldest, and yet she doesn't have the power to be the next Master. Disgraceful."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow. I had no idea...</thought> ...So what would've happened had Morgan been stronger...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Maya's family woulda been the branch family, I reckon.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Hey! Like, I haven't seen you in a while...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. <thought>I think I have enough to finally unlock her secret...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">...Like, what's with that scary look on your face...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please tell me about the traffic accident.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Huh? Like, whose accident?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your sister's accident, naturally!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Oh... Um, Oh, yeah... So, like, that Dr. Grey guy made my sister fall asleep... And, like, that's all I have to say about that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Interesting... Ini just asked, "Whose accident?"... Which means... She must know something about another person's accident...</thought> Alright, let's change the topic, then. How about you tell me about a certain other person's accident?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Huh? Another person's accident...? Like, you got someone in mind?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Oh wow. So, like, that person had a car accident too?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can't tell me you don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, how would I know if that person, like, had an accident?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Besides, like, I'm an occult fan, not an ambulance chaser like you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright, I get it. OK, then let's see if you know about this person's accident!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I want to ask you about your own car accident.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">M... Me!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">So, wow, like, how strange. I have, like, no idea what you're talking about. Can you, like, prove I was in, like, an accident?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here is your proof.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...Like, this is so totally bringing me down.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I know I'm, like, a little flakey, but do you really, like, think I'm an idiot?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, um, no... I didn't mean to suggest that...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, let's make sure we're on the same page. I, like, want proof I was in an accident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I thought I'd ease into this topic, but...</thought> It doesn't matter what you say, I know you were in a car accident!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you take a look at this? It's a newspaper article from one year ago. It says, "Ms. Ini Miney Holds Interview About Crash".</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You suffered a very bad injury and had to be admitted to a hospital, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">L-Like, wait!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What now?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">... Th-That's not me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I mean, like, this person has, like, the same name, but she's totally not me. My name, "Ini Miney" is, like, pretty common.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What in the world are you babbling about!? Your sister's name, "Mimi Miney" is in here too!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, totally, wow... What a scary coincidence! I'm totally getting, like, goosebumps.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Y-You think I'm going to let you get away with that!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">So, like, now what? Like, do you have something that totally says I was hospitalized?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Um, like, you shouldn't throw, like, truffling things around, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Truffling? <thought>Um, "trifling", maybe?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">So, like, let's use our brains, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is your proof.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...Like, what's that picture supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I got this from the hospital where you were hospitalized at.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">H-Huh? So?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was a certain patient there. He's quite a fan... As a memento of your stay, he stole this. I have to say, this photo looks like you.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...That creepy fake Director!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now are you ready to tell me about the accident...?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, wait a sec. OK, so, like, I was in an accident. Sure. But that's, like, totally not related to this murder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, it is. Look at this article. It says that "one of the women died", correct?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...A-And?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That woman who died -- who do you suppose they mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you suppose the woman who died in that accident could be...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you suppose it could be this person...?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">... Like, no way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, the accident was, like, a year ago, so, like, what's this person got to do with it? I'm totally not interested in stupid people like you. Bye-bye...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Ack, I have to stall her!</thought> W-Wait! Look, I think I know who it is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe it was your sister, Mimi Miney.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Mimi...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were riding in your sister's car while she drove. The two of you were together when your accident occurred, making it one and the same!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Yeah... I was... riding... Riding in that car... with my sister. We were... like, on our way home... I was riding in the passenger seat when I fell asleep... ...and then, it happened. At the time, I grabbed for my purse, and escaped from the passenger-side door.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...And your sister...?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I, like, couldn't do anything... The car was full of smoke... I couldn't see anything...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I'm sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did Dr. Grey really cause that accident by drugging your sister with sleeping pills?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, he was totally out to get my sister... He totally did that to, like, pay my sister back...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, I wonder... This does give Ini a good reason to want to murder Dr. Grey!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Ha ha ha. It seems simple, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">But, it would be very hard to catch me. Actually, I'd say impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I think you get the picture. I'm going to serve you a slice of humble pie! I hope you enjoy it. Ha ha ha...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...? Looks like something's up...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">S-Stop... Stop! Leave my mother alone!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">O-Ow! H-Hey, hold on, OK, pal!? I'm not gonna hurt...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Pearl, dear. It is perfectly alright. I will be out for a short while with this young man.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mother! Please, let me go too!</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">No, you must stay here and protect the manor.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aww, don't make that face. Hey, I'll tell you what! I'll show you something cool. Here, look! It's a real pistol...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Detective! Do not upset me further!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah... Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Poor Gumshoe... Being dragged off by the ear like that by Morgan... Owww...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mother...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mother... This has never happened before...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! ...I have a really bad feeling that I can't shake. I think something really bad is going to happen... I'm scared... ...I'm really scared, Mr. Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Say something, Wright! Anything...! *sigh* I'm terrible at this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick, what about... What about Mystic Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She'll be alright. I think I've gathered enough evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mystic Maya... She must feel all alone. Please, Mr. Nick! Go visit her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, but... I can't just leave you here all alone, either.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I-I'll be fine! Please! Mystic Maya needs you by her side!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Her stare is really piercing... *shiver*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Pearls... Could you take a look at...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...*sniffle*...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Aww... I can't do this to her now. She looks so pitiful and sad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You kept me waiting, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">So, how are the preparations?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think I have enough evidence and information now... I think...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Everything will be on your shoulders tomorrow. Whether Maya is found guilty or innocent... It's a heavy weight to bear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... If memory serves... Mia had a few Psyche-Locks of her own...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia. I'm going to get the last piece of information I need.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Sure. I welcome you to try.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia... You know something, don't you? About the real murderer, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Why... do you think so?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's really trying at times to be able to see other people's secrets...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">It looks like it's time for you to explain your reasoning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... <thought>A battle of wits against Mia! ...*gulp*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia, I want to help Maya any way I can. And to do that, I need to know who the real murderer is...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I know. Now, show me your ability as a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is it... The real murderer that Mia's been hesitant to name all this time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix... You think I'm hiding information about someone from you... Isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Alright, then. Tell me who you think I'm protecting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, I think you're trying to protect this person...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix. Don't let me down like this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Maya's life is on the line! Concentrate harder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mia's especially strict today...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">So? Have you gathered your thoughts?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Morgan Fey, of course. There is no one else you would protect like this, Mia...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well done, but... While the murder was being committed, my aunt was outside with everyone else. Which means she already has an alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's true...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Show me some evidence that would cast suspicion onto my aunt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My evidence is this black key.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At the beginning of the channeling, Maya had possession of this key. And yet, somehow, it magically ended up in the incinerator in the center garden.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...You're right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is only one person who could have done that while I was busy calling the police. The person taking care of Maya -- Morgan.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's that look mean?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your argument is too flimsy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">When did the key find its way into the incinerator? It could have happened long after the murder happened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Long after...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Someone could have found the key somewhere and dumped it into the incinerator.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that's...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That prosecutor would use something this small to shred your case. Do you have something other than just the key to cast suspicion on Morgan?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix, we don't have any time left.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I haven't even said anything yet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You can't pin my aunt as the murderer with one piece of evidence alone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the other piece of evidence that points to Morgan as the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I also found this in the garden incinerator. It's the same material as Maya's costume... Except for the splotch of blood.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">But this piece may not even be from Maya's costume.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But this is what Maya told me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which means that this piece of cloth was a part of Maya's costume.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">But when Maya was arrested, she was wearing her costume.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That just means someone changed her clothes.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Changed her clothes? But why...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know why. But... There is only one person who could've done that.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The one person who was taking care of Maya... My aunt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The proof is this piece of cloth.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I found it in the incinerator near the Winding Way. It's the same material as Maya's costume... Except for the splotch of blood.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You mean, it's from Maya's costume that she was wearing at the time of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">But when Maya was arrested, she was wearing her costume.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That just means someone changed her clothes.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Changed her clothes? But why...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know why. But... There is only one person who could've done that.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The one person who was taking care of Maya... My aunt. ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's that look mean?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your argument is too flimsy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You have no proof that this piece of cloth is actually from Maya's costume.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... this blood...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">And do you know whose blood that is at this point in time? You don't, do you? Do you have any proof that piece of cloth is from Maya's costume?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix, we don't have any time left.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I haven't even said anything yet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You can't pin my aunt as the murderer with one piece of evidence alone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think this is the proof you're looking for.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...The key to the Channeling Chamber, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At the beginning of the channeling, Maya had possession of this key. And yet, somehow, it magically ended up in the incinerator in the center garden.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...You're right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And this is what Maya told me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which means that this piece of cloth was a part of Maya's costume.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It would certainly seem that way...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Someone changed her into a different set of clothes. And then, burned the costume she was wearing in the incinerator. There is only one person who could've done that.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The one person who was taking care of Maya... My aunt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, I think this...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">No. You're wrong. Try again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're really unforgiving today, Mia...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">And I keep telling you... Don't take this lightly. Maya's life is on the line.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mia is really serious...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Now, I'm going to ask you one more time.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You did very well, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">As long as you have those two pieces of evidence, you can cast suspicion on my aunt. However.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-However?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Like I said in the beginning, my aunt has an alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... She was with us the whole time...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Here's my final question. You don't have to present solid proof of this for me. But I want to know. If my aunt is the culprit, then how did she commit the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How she did it, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I want to hear your thoughts. In order for my aunt to murder Dr. Grey, who or what did she need...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>No idea... Just throwing things out now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">...And you were so close too, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">There is no way my aunt could have done it herself. So, thinking logically, where does that leave you? Should be easy for you to figure out...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So, if Morgan couldn't have done it herself... Then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Come on, Phoenix. Think.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ini Miney. She's the answer to the final question.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Which means that my aunt and Ini Miney...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Were in cahoots!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...Something's been bothering me all this time. This crime is something no normal person could carry out. The person would have to know a lot about Fey Manor and the village itself to do this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...But Morgan already has an alibi...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes, which is why I can't figure out how it was done. We can assume that Ini Miney is involved somehow...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But we have one big problem on our hands.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...A problem? With what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We don't have a motive.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Why would Morgan want to kill Dr. Grey? Why would she have to?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Also, we don't really know for sure that she was cooperating with Ini.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mia doesn't have a clue either, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Hmm... Then, there is only one possibility...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Think about it, Phoenix. Why would my aunt do something like this? And why would she do it in such an underhanded fashion?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... because...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mother... She is the one who holds the key to this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mother? Whose? Mine?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Don't be silly. Mine, of course! Misty Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mia and Maya's mother? Why would she bring her up now...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Now then... Looks like we've gathered everything we could. All we have to do is win tomorrow! Everything will become apparent then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Right, Chief! We won't lose!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think I have enough evidence yet... I should investigate and gather some more clues before I try again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nnrgh! I've made too many mistakes!</thought></line>
</xml>