<xml>
<title>Reunion</title>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor... Shall I make the tea?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Not just yet... They should be arriving soon. Let's wait until they get here, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="???">...Hello? Sorry I'm late...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow, you're here! Please, come on in!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Good day, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey there, Professor! Luke! It's been a long time!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed it has. I'm delighted you were able to come.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hang on... Mr Wright...where's Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, um... She's... How can I put this? She's on a "culinary quest".</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A quest, you say...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She's checking out fish &amp; chips here in London. "Mystic Maya's quest for the best of the best"...as she put it.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...You don't say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She said she wanted to check out all the different places she can find one by one, so she's going to be a little late. She probably has about two or three more left to try before she gets here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm starting to think Maya enjoys eating almost as much as I do!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, why don't we all have a nice cup of tea while we wait? Would you mind making it, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">No problem, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've gotta say, you both seem to be doing well.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Thanks! We definitely keep ourselves busy, don't we, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can imagine you guys have been up to your necks in adventures and swamped with puzzles. Business as usual, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I must admit, that's fairly close to the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Are things pretty much the same with you, Mr Wright? ...Still up to your neck in objections and swamped with contradictions?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh... Sure... I guess so... Say, my job sounds really...underwhelming when you put it that way.</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey! What gives?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're all having tea without me?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh! Hiya, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah, Miss Fey. A pleasure to see you again.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Long time no see, Luke! And I see you're still wearing that classy hat, Professor. How are you guys?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">All the better for your presence, Miss Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So, did you find it? The best fish &amp; chip shop in London?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Even better! I bought a takeout from each one of the places I visited. I hope you guys are hungry!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Now that Miss Fey has joined us, I suggest another pot of tea is in order.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'll second that, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I see... So, once again you're here courtesy of the Legal League of Attorneys?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right... We have a technical exchange trial starting tomorrow morning.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Time sure flies... It's hard to believe an entire year has passed since we left Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I wonder how everyone there is doing...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It would be just great to see Espella again, wouldn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, and Patty. I wonder how they're both doing... I'm curious as to how Barnham's been keeping himself busy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick... I bet you're just DYING to see Barnham's dog Constantine again, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uuuurgh... And I bet he's just DYING to take another bite out of me...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hm...?! Professor, I think we have a visitor.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">At this late hour? I can't say I've been expecting anybody.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'll go and see who it is.</line>
<line speaker="???">Are you...Mr Hershel Layton?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, indeed I am. My dear young lady, how may I be of assistance?</line>
<line speaker="???">I have been asked...to give you a letter. Please, could you read this?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This letter...it's from Carmine.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Um...what was my next line? I forgot! Hee hee! How have you been, Mr Layton?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That was a perfect performance, Espella! I felt like we'd gone back in time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, guys... Talk about putting on a show...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright, Maya! It's so good to see you both again! So how did you like the re-enactment of our first meeting?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Err, yeah... You totally had me fooled... I thought for sure Labyrinthia had come down with another case of "magic water"...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you saying, Nick? They just re-enacted the fateful scene from when they first met!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I bet the fans could recognise that scene in an instant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...How was I supposed to know? I wasn't even there... Hey, wait! Neither were you, Maya!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Incidentally...where is Carmine? I invited him to join us too.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, that's right... He won't be able to make it tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Really? That's a bit of a shame...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Speaking of Carmine, that letter I just gave you is actually a message from him.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Let's read it, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Who'd have thought Carmine would get involved in another car accident?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, he seems to be making rather a habit of it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... <thought>That's one dangerous habit...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I say he should just change his name. Clearly it's totally jinxed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that's how it works, Maya...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Right, then. Now that everyone's here, what do you all say to some tea? Care to do the honours, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What is it, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, um...it's nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, that's great! I'm so glad to hear everyone's doing fine back in Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Everyone's working very hard to create a new town: Labyrinthia 2.0.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So, Mrs Eclaire and Mr Barnham weren't able to come today?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm afraid not. They really wanted to, but they just couldn't take the time off.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, there's no rush. Apparently, these Special Episodes are set to continue for a while yet.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's right! I'm sure we'll have the chance to see them all again soon.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Now then, everybody... Shall we begin?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...begin? Begin what, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Why, that should go without saying, Mr Wright... Now that we're all here, it can only mean one thing...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh...I think I know where this is going.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah...I've got it! You mean puzzles, don't you, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Puzzles?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, puzzles dropped from the main game... Ahem...I mean, specially prepared for our further enjoyment.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh! It's been so long... May I have a try?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm always ready for a new puzzle or two!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Me too! I'm up for this!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well then, puzzle time it is. Although, before we start... why don't we all have another cup of tea? If you would, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Is something the matter, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... N-no, nothing at all...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Nick? Can we, uh...talk for a sec? We've had SO much tea... One more drop and I think I'm gonna burst!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me about it... Any more tea and we're gonna end up with a water problem of our own...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Hee hee... You know, you two can take a little break if you need it.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">How right you are, Espella. Speaking of a break, how about a nice, leisurely puzzle to relax ourselves? Can you blend this, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Luke">She did it, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y'know, I think I'd rather be full of puzzles than full of tea any day!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Speaking of tea... Now that we've solved the puzzle, let's all celebrate... with another cuppa! Right, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ Not this time, Luke. I think we've all had enough tea for now.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh... Have we, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I think it might be time to try some of those fish &amp; chips instead. Wouldn't you agree, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm so full...I couldn't eat another fry-uhh... I mean, "chip"! By the way, Nick... Just how many cups of tea do you think we all got through tonight?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see, now... We all had a cup when I got here. That makes for a total of... three cups, altogether...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then, we all had another one each when I got here, which is another four cups. That makes seven cups in total.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">And when I arrived, we all drank one more, which is another five cups. ...That brings the total to twelve.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And finally, we all had another cup right before solving that puzzle just now... That's another five cups, bringing the grand total to seventeen cups of tea.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Seventeen cups, huh... ............ Say, Nick... Maybe the professor has a rule when it comes to drinking tea.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, something like... "I never drink more than 17 cups of tea during any given puzzle".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Maya... You might want to think twice about using that kind of Ace Attorney reference here...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, that's about it for Episode 1! Until next time!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">In the next episode, we'll be inviting along more of the characters you all came to know and love...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Professor. Is it really okay for everyone to be so, err...self-aware like this?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ease up, Nick! Sometimes a little self-awareness is fun. Isn't that right, avid video game player?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We'll see you all again next time, then!</line>
</xml>