<xml>
<title>Reunion, and Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Maya">I finally get to see you again, and...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not your fault. You didn't do it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No, I... I did it... I killed that person.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that wasn't you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It doesn't matter. It might as well have been me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't believe something like this happened...The events of that gloomy, rainy afternoon that started this whole mess...keep playing through my mind...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">What depressing rain...Do you understand how depressed that makes me!? Do you!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, I guess...</line>
<line speaker="???">But actually, more than being depressed, I'm angry. Angry at that weather girl on TV. "I think our little rainy spell will take a break with a day of sun!"...is what that girl said! I'd stake my life on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it's the weather...</line>
<line speaker="???">But that's why I didn't bother to bring an umbrella today. What nerve, calling herself a weather girl! She's going to hear about my $1500 suit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... About your case... Unless you're planning on suing the weather girl...?</line>
<line speaker="???">... I'm sorry. I thought that before we got down to business, we could have some friendly chatter. My name is Dr. Turner Grey. I'm a surgeon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Remind me never to end up under his knife...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grey">I'm here today because of this incident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Malpractice at Grey Surgical Clinic. Fourteen In-Patients Lose Their Lives!" ...Oh. You're... the doctor at...?</line>
<line speaker="Grey">It's really quite upsetting. Did you hear me!? UPSETTING!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, yes, I heard you. I agree, it's quite upsetting, Dr. Grey.</line>
<line speaker="Grey">The one that screwed up was that nurse! It was her that got the medications mixed up and killed those 14 patients! And yet! Now listen good! And yet! That nurse had the nerve to go and die before admitting to her wrongdoing! She didn't even offer any sort of explanation to me! And this is the kicker! She up and has herself a grand ol' accident and crashed her car! Smash! Crunch! Instantly transforming her car into the accordion model!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's right... About a year ago, all the tabloid shows were talking about it. Fourteen victims of medical malpractice and the nurse's mysterious fatal accident. There were rumors that Dr. Grey had actually caused that crash. People said it was to forever hide the person responsible for the malpractice incident.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grey">Why would I...? Now, I'm just going to say this once -- Why on Earth would I want to kill that nurse? She's the one who killed those 14 patients! Not me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think you need to take a deep breath, doctor, and focus... More to the point, this case is over a year old. Why bring it up now...?</line>
<line speaker="Grey">That's simple! Because the situation is slipping out of my grasp. This just won't do. My clinic isn't seeing nearly as many patients nowadays. Do you understand what that means!? It means they're not coming to my clinic!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You don't say...? If it were me, I don't think I'd want to go either.</thought> So... what would you like me to do about it...?</line>
<line speaker="Grey">I want you to help me prove I'm innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, you do realize I'm a lawyer, not a private investigator, right?</line>
<line speaker="Grey">No, this is something only you can do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Grey">Maya Fey. You know this girl, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>Maya! Why would he know her name...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grey">I heard you were working under her for a little while.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, yes... I mean... Hey, wait a second here! I worked UNDER her!?</line>
<line speaker="Grey">Yes. Am I wrong? She told me, so I'm not quite sure if...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, we worked a few trials together. But she went back to her hometown to undergo more training.</line>
<line speaker="Grey">Ah, yes, I heard. It must be lonely for you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What!? Wait... I'm not...!</line>
<line speaker="Grey">She must be an extraordinary girl to handle such rigid training.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Grey">I have an acquaintance who knows a lot about these mystical sorts of things. She's the one who introduced me to Ms. Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is Maya... really that famous...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grey">And I've already set up an appointment.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">For what?</line>
<line speaker="Grey">What else!? A channeling! I'm going to have her call the spirit of that nurse that went and got herself killed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh. <thought>Maya... I wonder what she's up to right now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">We, the women of the Fey family, have always been spirit mediums. It's because the power to communicate with spirits flows strongly through us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's what she told me...I guess she's learned to accept her responsibilities and become an adult...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grey">Not counting training, this will be her first time channeling a spirit, so she gave me one condition before accepting my request.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A condition...?</line>
<line speaker="Grey">The condition is you, Mr. Wright. She said that she wouldn't do the channeling without first seeing you again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me...?</line>
<line speaker="Grey">And that is why I've searched you out! You want to see her too, don't you!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And so... that is how I ended up visiting Maya's hometown with the doctor...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So this is Kurain Village; Maya's hometown.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Why, hello there.</line>
<line speaker="???">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... What an odd little girl.</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey! Wait up, Pearly!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hm? Someone else is coming this way...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Niiiiiiiick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maya. How are you...? It's good to see you again.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, I didn't think you'd really show up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not that big a deal. You made it sound like you were soooo far away.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, maybe I exaggerated... just a little.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was only 2 hours by train. If I had known you were this close, I'd have visited more.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No! You're not allowed. I already decided, you know. Until I become an adult, I have to work hard and be strong by myself...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... well... Anyway, congratulations. I'm glad to hear training is going well for you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Heh, heh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's an old-style phone booth. I can't say it fits in with this area too well. My cell phone doesn't get reception up here, so who knows. I may need it later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An old bus stop. It says "Kurain Village" on the sign post. The buses seem incredibly inconvenient since they only come 3 times a day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A giant rock that seems to be reaching for the sky. Its origins are written on a beat-up, old sign. It looks like this giant rock is called the "Kurain Boulder". There's a really complex explanation written here, but long story short, it's a big stone for spirits to live in... Or something like that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Rustic, thatch-roofed houses where the other villagers live line the street. They're nowhere near as large or as nice as the manor in front of me. It's kind of odd that I don't see any of the other villagers walking around, though...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The biggest, most elegant of the buildings I can see from here. This is Fey Manor; the place Maya calls home. It's easy to be overwhelmed by its presence...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like you've finally become a full-fledged medium, taking on your first job.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. I didn't think it would be this soon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But this case... Do you know the messy story behind it...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ha ha ha, behold the power of the Maya Intelligence Network! Let's see. Fourteen people died because of malpractice on Dr. Grey's part, right? And to pin the blame on the nurse, he killed her in what appeared to be a car accident!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Um, so what is this "Maya Intelligence Network" anyway...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The tabloids.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Ha ha ha. I'm just pulling your leg, Nick! What really happened is the exact opposite. I heard all about it from Dr. Grey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, come on, Nick! I wouldn't take a crazed killer as a client! That's too scary, even for me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Y-Yeah, I guess so.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this is your hometown, huh, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup! Kurain Village... But I've heard people call this place "Medium Valley", too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Interesting... So everyone that lives here is a spirit medium?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pretty much. Most of my ancestors were too, I think...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's probably true since the Fey ability to communicate with the dead is so strong...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Actually, only the women of this village are mediums.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what do the men do?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They usually work someplace outside the village.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh yeah, I wanted to ask you about that girl I saw earlier. Do you know her?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, you mean Pearly?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearly?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pearl Fey. She's my cousin. Isn't she adorable? Just like yours truly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Cousin... Wait, then that means... Is she also a...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup. She's a medium, too. Pearly's a real genius when it comes to channeling!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, I see. I hope I didn't scare her when I tried to talk to her earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nah, it's not you. My aunt drilled it into her head that "if a suspicious-looking person tries to talk to you, run away".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Suspicious-looking...!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, you're not wearing training clothes, for starters...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course not.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pearly is my aunt's most valued treasure, so she's not allowed to go outside of town. She doesn't know much about the world outside of Kurain Village.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aunt?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pearly's mother is my aunt, duh. Come on, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah, it's good to see this tarnished badge again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean by "tarnished"...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, look. This badge is like every other. It's bound to lose its color and shine after years and years. But you know, polishing it up once in a while wouldn't be a bad idea.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ha ha ha. I'm warning you! I'm not the same weak Maya you knew a year ago, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You seem to have a lot of faith in yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You'll see soon enough. I think you'll be totally shocked by how good my hamburgers are now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Were you training to be a medium or a cook?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, it's my client!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Client," huh? You're really serious about your work, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I thought I'd say it once, just to try it out, like how you always say, "My client."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm, nothing really comes to mind, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't say that with such a big smile on your face.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ha ha. What can I say? I'm in a good mood today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think about this person?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, have I told you this one yet, Nick? We have a legend in this village. It goes like this. "All the woman of the Fey clan are beauties." Well?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...And that's a legend now?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, Nick, I've got to get going. It's about time for the channeling to start.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Oh, yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm doing the channeling in my house, so come on in, OK? After I'm done, we can grill up some juicy burgers!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright. Good luck, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well... At least she's still the same perky Maya.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grey">Ah, Mr. Wright. I'm so glad you showed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Some nice weather we're having today. Aren't you happy?</line>
<line speaker="Grey">No, not at all. That stupid weather girl made the wrong call again. "It will rain cats and dogs today!" she said with a straight face. I can't believe they allow such misguided reports on the public airwaves!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like talking about the weather with this guy is just asking for punishment...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grey">...But anyway, this is a splendid manor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No argument there... It's hard to believe that this is Maya's house, though...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grey">I was given a guidemap to this building. Here, Mr. Wright. I have a copy for you too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A door that leads to the Channeling Chamber, the place where spirits and people meet. The iron in this door was tempered, making it very solid. It looks like there is a strong lock on this door to top it off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Someone with a lot of skill wrote these four Chinese characters with a brush. Oh look, here's a translation: "Once in a Lifetime." Its message is people should value their ghostly meetings as once in a lifetime chances.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A piece of cloth with a ton of finely-written characters jammed onto it. Probably esoteric knowledge only mediums should know. ...Hmm, let's see... Here's one in English... It says... "100 Ways to Save Money". ... Being a medium sounds like a rough way of life...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This door leads out to the Winding Way. The weather outside looks really nice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you going to do once the nurse's spirit has been called?</line>
<line speaker="Grey">Isn't it obvious? I'm going to have her write a signed confession.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A signed confession?</line>
<line speaker="Grey">Yes, a confession. Pay attention! I'll have her write this: "One year ago, on May 2nd, 14 patients died due to my negligence. And then, on May 24th, I fell asleep at the wheel and died in a car accident due to my further negligence. I'm sorry and I apologize for being negligent." That's what I'll have her write! With a confession, the rain falling on my soul can finally stop.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, how did you hear about Maya Fey...?</line>
<line speaker="Grey">I heard about her from an acquaintance; a girl studying the occult at the college. That girl introduced me to this village. This is the home of the Kurain School of Channeling.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The home, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Grey">And Ms. Maya is a daughter of the "Master", I hear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Master...?</line>
<line speaker="Grey">Anyway, do you see that door? That's the room where people and spirits meet. Ms. Maya's aunt is in there right now. Would you care to meet her...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, here's my attorney's badge.</line>
<line speaker="Grey">Are you trying to compete with me and my profession with that piece of scrap?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Grey">I am a surgeon. Compared to you lawyers, I'm practically a saint! Yes, well, I don't exactly have any patients right now, but, and listen good! I'm not the one that made the mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This doctor needs his head examined...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow, this manor is really nice, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Grey">Do you honestly think this place is all that impressive? Don't make me laugh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Grey">This is the countryside. Land here is dirt cheap. I will have something much greater one day! I will build my own grand mansion! Did you hear me!? A grand MANSION! This manor will seem like nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh, could you keep that shaking fist away from my face? Thanks...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grey">She's still young, but one day, she'll bear a big responsibility. She'll be the Master, you know. The MASTER!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess there are "Master" mediums, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grey">That's Ms. Maya's aunt. Earlier, she made me eat some sort of traditional dessert the size of a tea saucer! Hmm, I wonder if Ms. Morgan ever performs channelings herself...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you have to say about this person, Dr. Grey?</line>
<line speaker="Grey">...This person... Hmm... Judging by their face...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Grey">They have a weak stomach.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Really...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow... It's such a strange atmosphere in here... These flickering lights... I guess they're candles...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Good sir! Who might you be...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaah! I-I'm, uh, my name is Phoenix Wright...</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh... You must be that good sir...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Good sir"...? Is she talking about me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">You are a lawyer, are you not, good sir? I have heard much about you from Mystic Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that so? <thought>"Mystic" Maya...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">I am Mystic Maya's aunt, Morgan Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-Nice to meet you.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Ah, I had wanted to speak with you about a certain incident, good sir. It would seem that perhaps you ask too much of Mystic Maya in performing your duties. Most unbecoming, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Don't tell me you have already forgotten? That was it not for Mystic Maya and her assistance, you would surely not have won...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>First a girl that runs away, and now an old lady who says I stink at doing my job... When did I become the poster boy for "How Not to Make a First Impression"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">The past is the past though. Let us speak of the present now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ah, thank you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Meditation Room is on the other side of this very heavy-looking door. There is a giant iron lock where the handle is. It feels like a curtain that separates the normal world from the spirit one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is where the medium sits, I assume. There are 4 panels of this flooring. The straw in the flooring feels a little damp, probably from the humidity in the air.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess this is an alter [sic]. Whatever it is, it feels very important. A mirror-like object with a cloudy reflective surface, and some branches of a sacred tree have been set in a pre-determined arrangement.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Good sir! I wonder if you would please not touch the sacred objects. Those objects are being offered to the spirits. If you were to touch them, good sir, they would become cursed. Yes, cursed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She really didn't have to talk down to me. I'm not that much of an idiot...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This folding screen is really showing its age. All of its edges are a bit tattered. The lettering is fading too. I think I recognize a few of the characters on here... ...Ku ...ra ...in... I'm pretty sure that's what it says... Maybe I'll ask Maya about it later...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is some empty space behind the folding screen. The light of the candles can't reach back there, so it's completely dark.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So why do you add "Mystic" to Maya's name. Isn't that a little... strange?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Good sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">How dare you be so rude and disrespectful towards Mystic Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">She must be addressed by her proper title, good sir. You must call her "Mystic Maya"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, uh... So, about Mystic Maya... Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">It is the blood.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me? "Blood"?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Mystic Maya carries the blood of the Master. In actuality, she is the only one remaining.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Only one remaining...? What's that supposed to mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Mystic Maya is the last of the rightful heirs of the Kurain Channeling Technique.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK... Then... where do you stand...?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">That is a little more complicated... Although a woman of the Fey family, I am merely a member of the branch family.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Branch family? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">It is as it sounds. For a member of the branch family, no matter her spiritual power, she can never become the Master of the Kurain School.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... how strong are you...?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">... It is a shame, however I will admit. I can not even begin to compare the lowliness of my power to the Master's.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's how it is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So today's channeling will be her first?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Yes, good sir. Because the spirit of a person who dies in a traffic accident is usually very strong, it is usually easier to call that person to our world.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Traffic accident" indeed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">The channeling will take place here, in this Channeling Chamber, good sir. As you can see, I am in the process of preparing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... this room is the... Channeling Chamber...?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">The place where a spirit medium speaks with those who have departed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't suppose you'd mind if we observed the session...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Do not even think of such nonsense! Only the medium and the client may enter here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">The secrets of the Kurain Techniques can not be seen by just anybody.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That never stopped Maya from doing it in front of me before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">It is also for your safety, good sir, if something were to go wrong. That is why, while channeling is being performed, that heavy door is securely locked...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, that's what the lock is for...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Good sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">When did you... take a hidden picture of Mystic Maya!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-Wh-What!? Wait... It's not like that at all!</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">It is unforgivable!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ow-ow-ow! <thought>Why did she slap me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About this person...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Oh! It is that man, is it not? A man who wishes to borrow a departed spirit's power to hide the lack of his own. What an insignificant man.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Insignificant...?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">That would mean you are that man's insignificant little friend, dear sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Then I guess that makes Maya my insignificant little assistant, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Good sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">We would like to begin the channeling at 3 o'clock. If you don't mind, good sir, would you mind allowing me to make preparations?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, um, sure... go ahead... <thought>She's a Fey alright! Just as odd as the rest.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">... Oh, yes. I wonder if you have yet to meet Pearl, good sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearl?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">She is an adorable, angelic young girl.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, that odd...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">She is my daughter. Now then, what was it you were about to say...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What a cute daughter you have... Ahaha...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">A pure heart that knows not of the evils in this world is a powerful thing, good sir. Please refrain from affiliating with her, I request.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, it's not like I had the chance to anyway...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">I must insist and stress that you not let it occur.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, okay, I get it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow. This garden is really breath-taking. Someone put a lot of love into it. What is that over there...? ...Is that an incinerator? It looks a little out of place in a garden like this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A splendid garden with a small lamp and traditional decorations. It's a bit small to walk around in... Although, that incinerator piques my curiosity...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a small incinerator. I don't think garbage trucks come all the way out here to a little village like this. So every family has to burn their own trash.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like there's a room over there, too. A peaceful feeling is emanating from it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a really old urn. The ashes of a person long dead are inside. It looks like something with a long history... Other than that, it's not very interesting, so time to move on.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So this is... the Side Room. Looks like it's more of a break room. There is bedding spread out on the floor. It looks like someone's sleeping in one. I shouldn't disturb them...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a decorative wooden bear sculpture. There's a plate attached to the base. "Kurain Village - The Heart of Channeling" What the!? It's a souvenir. So does this mean it's easy to spot bears here... And for them to spot you...? *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a small alcove. I have no idea what it's supposed to mean or symbolize. If I had one of these in the office, it would end up as storage space. But here, it's decorated with some pretty flowers and a beautiful hanging scroll.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the first time I've seen a sliding door like this in person. From here, I can see the Winding Way and the little garden in the courtyard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's bedding spread out on the floor. Is that someone sleeping in one over there? She's probably an exhausted medium taking a break and catching some z's. If I wake her up, she might be grumpy and throw a spell on me. It's probably a good idea to not disturb her sleep...</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey! You! Hold on, now! This gal's got a few questions to ask!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I'm sure I've heard that southern accent somewhere before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, well I'll be! It's Mr. Phoenix Wright! How ya been!? Haven't seen you in, what, a year!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... You... are... uh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Lotta Hair, was it?</line>
<line speaker="???">L-L-Lotta Who!? Wait, you best not be making fun of my hair, now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, no, um, I wasn't "making fun"... I was "complimenting" you on your fine hair...</line>
<line speaker="???">Hmph, I dare say yer one heartless man, Mr. Wright. It was cause of my testimony that yer friend got outta being guilty. But looks like you already forgot that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hold up... ou were working with the prosecution at first as one of their witnesses, and came after us as if we were a piece of sirloin steak...</line>
<line speaker="???">Minor detail. Stop being so uptight; lettin' little things get in the way. The name's Hart. Lotta Hart. Don't you go forgetting it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh yeah! That's it!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Now listen here. I'm here to take some pictures today. Gonna get myself a real scoop.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, so I guess you're still at it? Being a photographer, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">You betcha! The hardest working one out there, I reckon! Didn't I say I was gonna make a name for myself as a famous "paranormal photographer"!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're Lotta Hart, right...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Bingo! I'm the one and only "paranormal photographer", Lotta Hart!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, so I guess you're still at it? Being a photographer, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Of course! And today, I'm gonna get myself a real scoop! You wait and see!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but who are you again?</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh Lawdy! I've met some cold men in my days, but you... You're in an icebox of yer own!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come on, am I really that bad...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Put yer noggin to some use! You've gotta remember who I am! It was cause of my testimony that yer friend got outta being guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah! You're the one from that trial!</line>
<line speaker="???">See, I knew you could remember if you tried!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were working with the prosecution at first as one of their witnesses, and came after us as if we were a piece of sirloin steak...</line>
<line speaker="???">Why don't we let bygones be bygones, now. It's yesterday's news, right? Name's Lotta Hart. Don't you go forgetting it, ya hear!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... So what brings you here today?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hah! You should already know! I'm here for the big scoop! I can feel it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, so I guess you're still at it? Being a photographer, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">You betcha! The hardest working one out there, I reckon! Didn't I say I was gonna make a name for myself as a famous "paranormal photographer"!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Oh, that's right! This ain't no time to be wastin' time! The channeling's about to get started!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is it that time already!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">We all should hurry up and get to the Meditation Room. ...What are you waiting around for!? Come on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Lotta Hart, huh? I've been judging her harshly because of that case, but, I guess looking back, we had some good times, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">We will now begin the channeling. Mystic Maya and honored guest, please proceed into the Channeling Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Grey">With this, I can finally swat all those pesky flies, once and for all! You hear me!? They won't be able to say a single bad thing about me after this! You would love to hear them apologize, wouldn't you? Wouldn't you, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me!? Oh, uh, yeah, I sure would.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Mystic Maya, do you have the Channeling Chamber key?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup, right here.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">That is most satisfactory. That key is one-of-a-kind, so please take care of it well.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It'll be fine, Aunt Morgan. I won't lose it, trust me! OK, Dr. Grey. Let's get started.</line>
<line speaker="Grey">Finally! Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Now let us wait patiently out here for them. Please have some lovely bitter green tea and jaw-droppingly large strawberry desserts...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hold on, now, granny!</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">...Granny?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">How come we ain't allowed in that room!?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Dear madam, you have an "impressive" grasp of English. From where did you learn it?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">What!? I'm from the heart of the heartland!</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Is that so? Then I humbly request that you return to this "Heart of the Heartland".</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Wh-What are ya...?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">This is Kurain Village. If you can not follow our traditions and rules, we request that you leave!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">...! ... Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow. She shut Lotta up! Now THAT's impressive!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Now then, let us wait.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey now! Wh-What was that just now!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It came from inside the Channeling Chamber...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey! Th-That's a gunshot!</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">E-Excuse me!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I've heard that sound before. It's a gunshot! I'd bet my afro on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>M-Maya! Maya's in there!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well, Mister Lawyer! What's the plan!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What else!? We're going to break in!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">What!? But... But there's only one key and that kid's got it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We're going to have to break the door. Is that alright, Ms. Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Well, yes... But there is one matter... That is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't try to stop me! You can send the repair bill to the Wright &amp; Co. Law Offices later!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Fey! What should we do!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yellow-bellied chicken liver! What are ya waiting for!? Kick it down already!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... The key...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">That key is one-of-a-kind. In this world, there is only that one. Even I am powerless to open that door.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, there is really no other way...</thought> Alright. Stand aside! I'm going to break the door down!</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">W-Wait! Please! That sort of recklessness...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yeah! Now that's what I call being a man!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Dr. Grey!!</line>
<line speaker="???">...I... ...I was... murdered...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maya?</line>
<line speaker="???">That man... ...murdered me... ...so I killed... him...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lotta! At a time like this!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Times like this are perfect for snapping up shots! But anyway... what's going on here!? This gal... Is she... ...Maya!?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Please leave this area to me. Go quickly and inform the police!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, but...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Hurry! Before there are more victims here!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey, let's go, City Boy! Leave this to the granny!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>My cell phone doesn't get reception way out here... So I ended up using the phone booth to call the police...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">And...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They're on their way.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">That's good. Lawdy, I saw a genuine "mysterious phenomenon"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She seems really on edge because of all this... Not that I blame her... I'm scared to death by what's going on...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey, Mister. That gal... Maya. She wasn't the one that pulled the trigger, was she...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, yeah... Lotta doesn't know that when Maya is channeling, her whole physical appearance changes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Then again... Weren't there only the two of 'em in there? I reckon she musta done it then...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lotta, what do you know about Dr. Grey?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Not much, but I did some digging... That's one gent with a bad reputation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I hear he's good at surgery and stuff, but his personality stinks like wet sheep.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I sort of got the same impression myself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">He's real controllin'. Soon as his nurse or patients don't do what he says, he starts a-hollerin'. Musta been real rough to work for him.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey, they'll be here soon, right? The police, I mean. I reckon you should be gettin' back to the crime scene, now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, I guess so...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Ah, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Fey! How's, um... Mystic... Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">She has returned to "this world". The Spirit Severing Technique was successful.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let me see her, please!</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">She is still unconscious. I humbly request that you wait outside for her recovery.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess I just have to wait... *sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The police are here! Sorry to keep you waiting! Huh? ...You again!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you doing all the way out here, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's actually kinda funny. I was in the area for a business trip, pal. Well, time to check out the crime scene. I'll have to question everyone here later on, so just sit tight, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why is he grinning at me...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Shall I show you to the scene of the crime, Detective Gymshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um... My name isn't Gymshoe...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The two of them went into the Channeling Chamber... I guess all I can do for now is see what everyone else has to say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's probably scared out of her wits after having a murder take place right near her.</thought> Lotta?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">GAWDDON'TLETITBEMENEXT!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eek! Don't scare me like that!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">What do you mean!? Yer the one scaring me! If I weren't so tough, you'd have another dead body on yer hands -- mine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you see or notice anything that stuck out at you?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Nah... Well, maybe one thing...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Turns out my poor stomach's not good at handlin' this kind of thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh-what?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Curses and ghosts and stuff comin' back to get ya... This is just too much, I say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is too much?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Being an occult photographer. That's some scary stuff, so I think I'm gonna try being a celebrity photographer, now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Going after photos more within your reach from now on? More glamour, less gore?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's up?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Oh, yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I took some hot pictures earlier!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Remember!? I took some pictures at the murder scene inside!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ack! She did! Two even!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">"The Séance Murder"... I sure like the ring of that. It'll be a sensational story!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">L-Lotta!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Sorry, but my journalistic sense is burnin' inside me! Hate to cut and run, but I'm headin' back in! Gotta beat those cops to the scoop of the century! UWAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAhahahahahahahahahahaha... ...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Must be an awful thing to see each other again and have this happen. Never woulda guessed that gal would end up being a murderer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That wasn't Maya! She was being controlled by a spirit...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Come on, now, City Boy. Ya really think the cops'll believe that?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey, it's that Dr. Grey guy. Pity what happened to him. Pretty scary what ghouls and ghosts can do to a man, huh? Gawd rest his poor soul.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Since when was Lotta so religious...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">That old lady sure can be forceful. She scared me back there. ...Well, only a little, now, ya hear?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I swear I've seen his face before. Maybe during that last case... Whenever something happens, this detective guy is always there. I wonder if he's the real baddie behind everything?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Somehow, I highly doubt it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Nope. Don't know nothin' about that. Things that don't catch my eye, don't catch my interest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And she calls herself a journalist??</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't know who's scarier... Lotta or the spirits... And why does it feel like we've been through this before...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The police are busily running here and there, and I don't see Maya anywhere...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-Hey, you! Don't touch anything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, I really need to ask you some questions!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm... Don't look at me like I'm some sort of uncaring jerk... Tell you what, pal. I'll let you ask me a few questions, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal! No touching without my permission!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm just looking at it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, I can't be too careful if a kid like her can be a murder suspect, now can I?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess if I want to search this room, I'm going to have to come back later...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, about Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I hate to break this to you, pal, but... with the way things look now, that girl's the only one who could've done it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah. Only Maya and the victim were inside this room, after all...</thought> But Maya is...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You can ask more about her later, pal. Right now, I've got a job to do and that's collecting evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Detective Gumshoe looks like a real professional. And yet, something about his expression still looks the same...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... Dr. Grey was shot with a gun, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He was shot in the forehead. But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But he was also stabbed in the chest with a knife.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...A knife?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">After being stabbed, the final blow was a shot from a gun.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah, I'm really busy right now. I can take a look at it later, alright, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He didn't even take a glance at it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, I'm pretty sure there was someone sleeping here earlier...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Like, how can I help you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! Ah, I'm, uh... That is... I...</line>
<line speaker="???">Um, like, so isn't it about time to start?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Time to start what?</line>
<line speaker="???">You know, like, the channeling!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Channeling...? Oh, oh, oh, oh!! No, actually, the situation has kind of changed...</line>
<line speaker="???">Huh? Like, what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please stay calm, but... a murder has taken place!</line>
<line speaker="???">... Um, so, like... A murder is that thing where, like, one person kills another, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes! A person has killed another person!</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, that's... Uh... What are the words I'm looking for...? It's like... ...like totally a bummer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah... <thought>After all that effort, that's all she had to say?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Oh, I'm sorry. I forgot to, like, introduce myself. My name is Ini Miney. Um... At the college, I'm researching and studying "parapsychology".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Parapsychology"?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">That's right. Um... I think people, like, usually call it, "occult studies" or something. Like supernatural phenomenon, ESP and psychic powers. That sort of stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's pretty out there...</thought> I'm Phoenix Wright, attorney at law.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You left the blanket a mess. Are you going to fold it?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like I had a really good nap, and, like... I was thinking of leaving it like this, so, like, it's all set for tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what brings you here today?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Um, like, so... I was the one who told Dr. Grey about this place. He asked me, like, "Do you know of a good spirit medium?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, Dr. Grey did say something about being introduced to this place.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Cause, like, talking to dead people and, like, multiple personalities are my thing...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... Then why were you taking a nap here?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like... I wasn't feeling good.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I'm, like, allergic to sesame seeds. They, like, must've put some in the food they served for lunch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, that doesn't sound fun.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">So I, like, felt sick, and came in here to, like, sleep. I totally feel, like, I've wasted my time 'cause I, like, slept a long time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you were sleeping here the entire time?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Yeah. Ever since lunch...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you don't know anything about the murder that took place?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, what? Oh, that! I, like, totally know nothing. So who was, like, you know, killed...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The surgeon that requested the channeling, Dr. Grey.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You and Dr. Grey knew each other, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...! I don't know any Dr. Grey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh really...? That's not exactly what Dr. Grey said...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Huh!? ...Well, uh... Like, a long, long time ago... I was, like, a patient, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She sounds like she's trying to hide something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Oh, hey! That's, like, Maya Fey, right? She's, like, totally waaaay famous! Like, well, for people like us, like, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Waaaay famous"? Maya?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">I mean, like, she's, like, the daughter of the Master, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Well, at least she remembers some things.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Um... This face... Like, I think I've seen it somewhere before...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!? ...Y-You're joking, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Ha ha, like, of course I am, silly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, thank goodness...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, I'm really sorry, but I'm not all that smart... so I don't, like, get it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm. Why does it feel like she's just putting on an act?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">I'm, like, totally bad at remembering people's names.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">But I, like, remember seeing that face somewhere before, like, I think...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, thanks for trying. <thought>I didn't think it was possible for someone to be this much of an airhead...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's no one here... as usual.</thought> Ack! ...H-Hey... How are you?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're Pearl, right?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm. Silent as ever... ...? What's that she's got in her hand? I've seen it somewhere before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...What is it!? Is it my hair? Is it too spiky? Not spiky enough!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...What is it!? Is it my hair? Is it too spiky? Not spiky enough!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Oh, dear madam... You have such impeccable timing.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, what's all the buzz?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ahem. Alright everyone, listen up! You too, pal! I'm going to give you all a brief update! Right now, it looks like the investigation's not going to be done until real late...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">That is a terrible shame. I propose that everyone sleep here under the roof of the Fey Manor tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What a mess. I can't believe how crazy this day turned out... Maya was arrested and taken away by the police. And I don't see myself getting any sleep tonight...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*yawn* Uuugh... Morning... I guess I must have nodded off at some point... I hope Maya's OK. I should hurry and get to the Detention Center, ASAP!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">N... Nick! Nick! I...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What am I going to do!? I never imagined it would turn out like this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Calm down, Maya! Take deep breaths. <thought>Come to think of it, the first time I met her... It all started right here, in this detention center...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I finally... I finally get to see you again, and...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not your fault. You didn't do it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No, I... I did it... I killed that person.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that wasn't you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It doesn't matter. It might as well have been me. I was too weak... and I... I couldn't control the spirit's power, so...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't want to bring up the case quite yet, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...You don't have to be nice to me. I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Smile, you're on candid camera.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitors the visitor's room. I wonder if he's bored. Not that I can tell since he never looks over this way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you're the Master or something of the Kurain School of Channeling...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Actually, my mother is for now. But since that title is passed from mother to daughter, I guess I will be someday...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But many people think that channeling isn't real, that it's all just an act.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You believe in us, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... because I've seen it with my own eyes. <thought>When Maya's channeling a spirit... not only her voice, but her whole physical appearance changes. It's a supernatural phenomenon that occurs every time. It happened this time, too... Dr. Grey said that he wanted to call the nurse, so... Maya's body must have taken on that nurse's appearance...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What exactly happened in the Channeling Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... I went into that room with Dr. Grey, locked the door... and sat down across from him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We closed our eyes...and I began the channeling.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is sounding kind of creepy... like the beginning of a scary story...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">And that's the last thing I remember...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">After a spirit comes into my body, I lose my self, my consciousness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then, you don't remember a single thing?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">When I came to, I was being held in my aunt's arms. And there was blood... all over my clothes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! But... I do remember having a dream.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A dream...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What kind of dream did you have while you were channeling...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um... I can't remember it all that well, but... I was dead and buried in the ground. I couldn't move... and it was unbearable... Really suffocating... ...It went something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I see... <thought>I have no idea what to say to that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">There was a really familiar smell too...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Under the ground?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, I can't quite place it, but I know I've smelled that same scent before...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Make sure you show that to Pearly, OK, Nick? I'm sure she'll be a big help to you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I... I can't face myself...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should've known better...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">!! T-The... That's the guy I k-killed...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! I'm sorry! <thought>Why did I pull this picture out!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pearly... She definitely has more than me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Who I think the next Master should be... I mean, she's got more spiritual power than me, and she really works hard at her training...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Talk about bringing the mood down even further... *sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I... I can't face my aunt right now... Not now... that this has happened...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's alright, Maya. I'm sure she understands. She's on our side, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, I know... But still...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's Lotta Hart... right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That girl is still after the next sensational photo.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ha ha. I guess some things never change.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I felt terrible during the questioning session... I mean, Gumshoe kept looking at me... with these really sad eyes... ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sorry, Nick, but there's nothing really special about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... what do you think about this person...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I can't expect her to know anything about this person.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>...I guess this is about all the information I'm going to gather for today...</thought> I'll be back later, Maya. In the meantime, please make sure you prepare it, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? "It"? What is "it"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The document requesting me to be your attorney, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...! But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Are you sure? I mean, I'm guilty! I'm a murderer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No one's decided that yet.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But I did! I killed that person... with these... two hands...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's enough, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's hopeless! If you defend me, you'll lose, I'm sure...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Stop it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... ...Help me... Nick, help me... I'm scared...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry, I will. When is the trial?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It sounds like tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>As usual, zero prep time...</thought> Alright. I'm going now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This jewel... This is called a Magatama. It's a magical charm and it's always protected me. Give this to Pearly... And I'm sure she'll lend you her spiritual powers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phew. It feels like I've been gone forever. But it's only been one day... <thought>Oh, that's right!</thought> Where's that newspaper Dr. Grey brought the other day...? ...Ah, here it is. Right on top of my desk. <thought>This is the only thing he left behind that's going to be of any help...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is a giant building just outside the window. It's the Gatewater Hotel, a high-class, luxury hotel. Until recently, it had been a normal, business-class hotel.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Charley. A quite decorative plant. It's a memento of my boss, Mia... who passed away. The rest of the room may be in shambles, but I always manage to care for this little fella.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A poster of the TV action hero, the Steel Samurai. Maya stuck it up here right before she left. I wouldn't say that the Steel Samurai and an attorney's office are a good match, but Maya threatened to curse me with some magic spell... so I guess it can stay.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Difficult-looking legal books stand in a formidable row. They mock me. ...Actually, I've neglected them for so long, a layer of dust has started to form. One of these days, I should try to build up the courage to read one... Maybe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's my desk. I keep it neat for those rare occasions when I actually have a client in the office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya must still be in questioning... I hope the detectives are taking it easy on her, but... these kinds of cases aren't taken lightly. I guess I'll come back later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to save Maya, no matter what! It's her life on the line! What in the world happened in that room yesterday?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The Meditation Room nurtures all mediums young and old. Even mediums in training, I'd wager. But it's pretty deserted today... ...probably because of the murder yesterday...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like Detective Gumshoe isn't here today... I should take this chance and thoroughly check this room. If I'm lucky, I might uncover a clue or two...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Oh, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good morning.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">I am on my way to go meet Mystic Maya, and I thought to bring her some items to make her feel more at home. Namely, tea so bitter you lose your tongue and jaw-droppingly large strawberry desserts.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure Maya will be very grateful...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">That's "Mystic Maya", good sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Urk. She is one scary lady.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Oh, dear, sweet Mystic Maya... Pearl wept constantly for you last night, as did I.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I know it's important for me to search the site, but I should ask her some questions too, while I have the chance...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Meditation Room is on the other side of this very heavy-looking door. The lock on it is broken, because, well... I broke it. It doesn't seem possible, but I managed to break it pretty badly. When we want to do something bad enough, people can do the most amazing things.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is where the medium sits, I assume. There are 4 panels of this flooring. The straw in the flooring feels a little damp, probably from the humidity in the air. No matter what I do, my eyes keep getting drawn to the pool of blood in the center here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess this is an alter [sic]. Whatever it is, it feels very important. A mirror-like object with a cloudy reflective surface, and some branches of a sacred tree have been set in a pre-determined arrangement. I'd guess they're used during the channeling...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a beautiful and expensive folding screen. It also looks quite old. There seems to be some sort of sacred text written on it, but I can't read it. ...&#160;! Th-This is... It's a hole! Could this have been made by a bullet?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is some empty space behind the folding screen. The light of the candles can't reach back there, so it's completely dark. I hope no one is hiding back there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I would like to ask you a few questions about what happened yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Do you mean that awful tragedy?</line>
<line speaker="???">That man... ...murdered me... ...so I killed... him...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Please leave this area to me. Go quickly and inform the police!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What happened here in this room after I left?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Well... First, I struck Mystic Maya on the head.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To make her go unconscious, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">That is correct. Next, I performed the Spirit Severing Technique.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Spirit Severing Technique"?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">The spirit of that nurse was inside of Mystic Maya's body. I used the technique to send the nurse's spirit back to the other world.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if this kind of testimony is even admissible in a court of law...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By the way, what is this room exactly...?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">The Channeling Chamber? This room was created for the sole purpose of preventing such a tragedy as yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Sometimes, when an inexperienced medium calls an especially strong spirit, that spirit may become violent and revolt, as you witnessed yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Revolt? But how?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">When a spirit enters a medium's body, she loses her will and her self steps aside. To put it another way, the spirit is borrowing the medium's body, good sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But isn't that extremely dangerous?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">An experienced medium has little problem controlling a spirit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But Maya... I mean, Mystic Maya... That was her first channeling...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">And that was why I insisted on locking the door. However, I never thought that would be calling danger upon the client himself... I am grateful that one of our heirlooms was not damaged in this horrible incident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that is...?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">It is that folding screen there. It is the Kurain Sacred Writings. Along with the Kurain Sacred Urn, they are this village's most treasured possessions. If I ever found out that something had happened to either one... Oh, the inhumanity...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Odd for her to be worrying about the folding screen at a time like this... I guess this isn't just some dilapidated old screen after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... How is Pearl today...?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">In this world, Pearl is my most treasured possession. When compared to even Mystic Maya, Pearl has the spiritual power to become a Master.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That's very impressive.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Until now, the women of the branch family have thought themselves to be inferior. .. But. Pearl is different! Her spiritual strength is so great; even greater than some of the main family! Yes, Pearl is a channeling prodigy and is the pride of the branch family!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow... She's really fired up now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">In any case... Our world is so different from yours, perhaps it is best for you to quit, good sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Quit"? Quit what?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">...Oh my!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">That... That is Mystic Maya's Magatama. Why would you have this in your possession!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Return it to Mystic Maya at once!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, madam! <thought>Why did I feel like I was being scolded by my own mother just now...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Ah, so even someone such as yourself can take interest in something like this. This is the Kurain Channeling Technique Sacred Writings. There are 6 panels in all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... But that's not what caught my eye. You see this hole here...?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">It is an old screen, you see. It is only logical that perhaps a bug or worm of some sort is the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even though this looks nothing like the eating patterns of any bug I know...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">I can hardly believe Mystic Maya has become like this. Directly influenced by the likes of you, and becoming caught up in a situation such as this...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry... <thought>...Hey, hold on! How is all this MY fault!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">I told her so many times, as I have also told Pearl, "Do not associate with strange old men you don't know".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, that shouldn't apply to me then, especially since I'm hardly an "old man" yet!!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">That doctor was one of those people. Those who intend harm upon the spirits receive harm in return; it's karma at work. It seems that he was the one to take the nurse's life, wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess that's possible...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Good sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">When did you take this picture!? This is one of those... what are they called...? Those... "hidden camera" pictures!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No!! It's not one of those at all!!</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Such an unforgivable offense! You will hand it over to me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No! I won't! <thought>If I ever want to talk about Pearl again, I should be much more careful...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">It shows the same face as the one I see in the mirror every day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And? Anything else?</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">No. That is all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why in the world did I bother to show this to her!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">I will be leaving shortly to meet with Mystic Maya. I simply do not have the time to look at such trivial matters.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">We usually do not welcome strangers into our village as they disturb the aura here. Especially people like you, good sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Hey, what do you mean, "especially people like me?"</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">You selfishly make Mystic Maya help you with your work... You should be thankful I have not taken your life for such a disrespectful act.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, madam...</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">And even more importantly, remember that if anything were to happen to Pearl...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is that supposed to mean!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Morgan">Well, then, I do believe it is time for me to take my leave.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright. Please tell Maya I said hi.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">What was that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, I mean, Mystic Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Morgan">I will tell her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...*sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Little Pearl isn't here today... Maybe she's at school?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Oh, hey! Like, you're that guy from yesterday... The, uh, dentist guy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, I'm a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">That's right! Um... Mr. Smith, Esquire.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's "Wright". Wait, I mean, you're wrong. My name is "Wright".</line>
<line speaker="Ini">"Smith", "Wright"... Well, I got, like, three letters, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think she gets the point...</thought> Anyway, why are you here?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">So, like, I study this thing called "parapsychology" at this college and...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, you told me about that yesterday. The sesame allergy, too. What I'd really like to know is why you're still here today?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Oh! So, like, that's what you meant! Like, you shoulda been more, like, clear about it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry. My bad.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">No, it's OK. Like, it's really...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's it? Why'd you stop mid-sentence!?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Did I? ...So, like... what was I talking about again...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>If Lotta ever wanted another "genuine mysterious phenomenon", it's right here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a decorative wooden bear sculpture. There's a plate attached to the base. "Kurain Village - The Heart of Channeling" What the!? It's a souvenir.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Isn't it cuuuuute? I, like, totally bought that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... so it's yours, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Yeah. So, like, this village is really famous for, like, channeling and bears.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Heh. <thought>...Wait. Famous for bears!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">But it's, like, OK. If you ever, like, see a bear, you just play dead, and they, like, leave you alone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-Is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Yeah. Cause, like, fighting back is totally of no use.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Has she actually tried to fight one!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, now where did this box come from? I'm sure this wasn't here last night. It looks like a box for storing clothes... But it's pretty big for just clothes... It's mostly empty, but a few folded pieces of channeling costumes sit at the bottom.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So? Why are you still here today?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, there's so much for me to, like, study here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Like what?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, the medium's training, or like, how they inherit their spiritual power.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I suppose... This village is the real thing, after all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">So, like, I asked if I could stay here for, like, a little longer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She sure seems like the care-free type, at least, on the surface...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you heard about the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">It's, like, totally scary.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...she says, with a silly smile plastered on her face...</thought> ...So do you know anything about it that might help?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Somehow, I don't think she has a grip on reality, let alone what's going on here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About the victim, Dr. Grey...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I don't know who you're talking about. ...Like... Wait, I think you asked about him, like, yesterday, too...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's right... Her reaction yesterday when I asked was...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You and Dr. Grey knew each other, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...! I don't know any Dr. Grey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh really...? That's not exactly what Dr. Grey said...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Huh!? ...Well, uh... Like, a long, long time ago... I was, like, a patient, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>OK, she is definitely hiding something from me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">...Like, is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Hey! It's, like, one of those little badges people in Congress all wear...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, no. I'm a lawyer. L-A-W-Y-E-R!!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...? Like, so is that what you are?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Wow! It's a Magatama! Aww, you shouldn't have!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's so totally not for you!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Hey! Like, it's not nice to freak me out like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That should be my line...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wanted to ask you about this girl...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Oh, that's, like, Maya Fey. She's, like, the Master's daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You surprise me. You knew that?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Well, like, I totally know everyone related to the occult. Maya is, like, an idol among spirit mediums.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya an idol? I guess stranger things have happened.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">That's Morgan Fey. Like, she's been totally helpful.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Did she just bow to the picture...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">So what about her?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, nothing in particular. I just wanted to know what you knew about her.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Um... Well, she's, like, a really good person.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like totally.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK. <thought>This is going nowhere...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Um... This face... Like, I think I've seen it somewhere before...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!? ...Y-You're joking, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Ha ha, like, of course I am, silly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, thank goodness...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, I'm really sorry, but... And I know, like, you totally had your heart set on it, but I can't, like, take it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who said anything about giving this to you!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you know about this person...?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I'm, like, sorry, but it's totally, like, time for my nap...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*yawn* <thought>Ack! She's even got ME yawning!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">And I, like, totally don't care about that person anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! Y-You surprised me!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And how are you today?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I guess she isn't open to friendly chatting... Huh? She's still holding something in her hand... ...It looks like the same thing she had yesterday...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Aaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Huh?? <thought>If only I had something that would catch her interest. Maybe then she'd talk to me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you take a look at this? Please?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Urk... She's really scrutinizing my face...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Th-That's enough already! I'm not that shifty-looking, am I!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh yeah. Maya said to give this to you...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ack! I'm in trouble now!! If Morgan sees us like this, I'll be the next one they're channeling...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Th-That's... That's Mystic Maya's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh!? <thought>Sh-She actually spoke!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Who are you...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm Phoenix Wright. I, uh, worked with Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Y-You worked with Mystic Maya...? You... You're Mr. Nick, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Uh, excuse me? <thought>I bet I know who she picked "Nick" up from...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I know who you are. You're... You're Mystic Maya's... "special someone"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WH-WH-WH-WHAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So then... Of course! You're going to help Mystic Maya, aren't you? That's what you're going to do, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well, yeah... I will...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh wow... It's like a beautiful fairy tale! That earnest look shining brightly in your eyes... It must be true love...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Wh-What!? <thought>Why am I being boiled into a bright red lobster by this little kid!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm so jealous of Mystic Maya! Ah, what a wonderful relationship...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait... I... uhh... I mean... We aren't... Things aren't like...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hee hee, I can tell you're a good person. Alright, Mr. Nick! I may be small, but I'm going to help you in any way I can!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearl, are you friends with Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I feel very grateful to be friends with her... She's so great. I want to be like Mystic Maya when I grow up. I really look up to her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow, I had no idea Maya was so... revered.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Usually when people don't use Mystic Maya's title, I get mad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh, sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But if it's you, Mr. Nick, then it's OK. Because... Because... you're "special" to her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Where in the world did she get an idea like that??</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">By the way... this may be rude, but which channeling school are you from?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which channeling school?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes. For example, I study the Kurain technique.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Ah, I get it! No, no, no. I'm a lawyer. A lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Law...yer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Is that related to spirit mediums in any way...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Um... None that I know of...</thought> Wait, are you telling me you don't know what a lawyer is?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm sorry, but I have no idea.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya did say Pearl doesn't know much about the outside world...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what's that you've got there, Pearl?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, this? I found it yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">If you want it, I can give it to you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't take something this important from you, Pearl.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But I'm sure I've seen that key somewhere before... ...and it might be an important clue later on...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright, well, if you really want to give it to me...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hee hee. You look like a child at a toy store, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...She not only speaks in a refined manner, but laughs in one, too!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this is...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That is Mystic Maya's Magatama. It's one of the most important heirlooms of Kurain Village. Please make sure to take good care of it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, I will. <thought>Is it really OK for me to have such a priceless object?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Are you interested in Kurain's traditional things too, Mr. Nick? The Kurain Sacred Writings are on this folding screen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? Is that what's written on it? Actually, what caught my eye was this "hole" in it...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It's a very old screen, so I think that maybe bugs made it by eating through it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...It sure doesn't look like something bugs can make...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About this key...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I found it while I was playing in the garden yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've seen it before too, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I look up to Mystic Maya a lot. She's my role model. She's so smart, and pretty, and kind, and loving. She's always cheerful, never gets sick, isn't picky, and has good sleeping habits. She always wakes up before me, and always eats breakfast before me too. And she has you; such a wonderful person with whom she can share a lo-</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! OK, OK! I get the idea! <thought>She really thinks the world of Maya, doesn't she?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">To tell you the truth, I really want to grow my hair out, just like Mystic Maya. But my mother won't let me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your hair now suits you quite well, though, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">R-Really? Th-Thank you! *fidget, fidget*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*fidget, fidget*</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, it's my mother! She takes really good care of me and loves me very much. She says I'm the "pride of the branch family"... But I don't know what that means.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Branch family"... That concept is probably still too hard for little Pearl...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm sure it is helpful to you in some way, but I'm still in training, so I don't know anything about it. I'm really, deeply sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, no, it's OK. I shouldn't have shown you something so trivial anyway. I'm very sorry. <thought>This feels so weird, talking to a kid like this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hmm, I'm sorry I don't know who this person is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess that makes sense... You've never left Kurain village, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm really sorry, Mr. Nick. I just don't really know anyone outside the village.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, Mr. Nick...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Pearls? I can call you that, right? You're too cute to just call you Pearl.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Sure, Mr. Nick... Umm... Are you sure it's OK for me to have this Magatama?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, it's OK. I was told to give it to you.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But, I can't accept something like this! ...All I really should do is charge this Magatama with spiritual energy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Spiritual energy?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Please take this. I'm sure it will be helpful.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It will let you see people's secrets.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">See people's... secrets...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes. ...If it's alright with you, I would like to accompany you for a little while. I can explain the Magatama's power to you when we meet someone hiding a secret.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, it's you, pal! So you're going to be her lawyer, I bet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh... I really feel bad for you, pal. Just this once, I wish I could be on your side.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, but I shouldn't be saying that kind of stuff to you. Hey! You're a cute kid.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ha ha ha. I'm not scary. Honest!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, I never knew Gumshoe liked kids...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-Hey! I know! I'll show you something cool! How's this? It's a real, genuine pistol...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Detective Gumshoe!! What are you doing showing her something that dangerous!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about Maya and the charges against her?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't think you can win, pal. If you're talking about proof, we've got a few pieces.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've got proof...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, pal. That puffy-haired photographer's going to testify tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He must be talking about Lotta. Actually... speaking of Lotta...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I took some hot pictures earlier!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Remember!? I took some pictures at the murder scene inside!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Lotta's "hot pictures"... I wonder what her camera captured...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Besides, you must've realized by now, pal. There's no way anyone other than Maya Fey could've done it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What am I supposed to say to Pearls now...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About Dr. Grey...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The victim wasn't super famous, but people still knew who he was. His face was all over those tabloid shows last year.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I know.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I was looking through some newspapers from last year, and... ... Huh? I could've sworn I had... I cut an article out, but I guess I must've lost it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's searching through his pockets... And boy, are those big...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm... It looked really interesting, too. Hey, do you have a copy, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A copy of that article...? I think Dr. Grey might have brought a copy to the office when he came by...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About Maya's trial tomorrow...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I've got two pieces of news for you, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Two?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. "Bad news" and "even worse news." So which do you want to hear first?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I don't really care... It doesn't change the fact that I'm not going to like it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Alright, pal. Well, the prosecutor for the trial is Prosecutor von Karma.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAT!? Von Karma!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Manfred von Karma... He was an awe-inspiring veteran prosecutor. He never lost a case in the 40 years of his career, and he raised a fearsome disciple. The horrible aftertaste of the evil he force-fed me is something I'll never forget.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Wait a sec. But didn't Von Karma stand trial and...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's where the other piece of bad news comes in... The Von Karma you're facing tomorrow is actually his successor...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Successor...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, um... Who is this "successor" to Von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Literally, pal, it's Prosecutor von Karma's kid. His kid became a prosecutor real young... like 13, and hasn't lost a trial since. That's what they call a "prodigy," pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Kid, huh... ... W-W-Wait a sec! Th-Th-Thirteen!? The kid became a prosecutor at the age of THIRTEEN!? I mean, a prodigy like that... I would have heard something about...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, no, no. The kid was born and raised in Germany, pal. That country's got a lot of stuff and is a great place to develop a person's talents.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Germany, huh? That's probably why I've never heard of this person. Ugh... Still, all it takes is someone mentioning the name "Von Karma", and I get terrible flashbacks to that case. Stop it! Get over it, Phoenix! That person is already gone...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, look. It's my attorney's badge.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ha ha. Good one, pal. You're always good for a laugh with your little badge. But a real man... A real man has a police badge.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Uh, um... Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it, Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I was wondering if I could see it, too?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, no, it's OK. It's not that important anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think about this...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, that's a pretty nice-looking brooch! You should stop wearing that ugly old attorney's badge, and start wearing that, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hee, hee. That detective is so nice! Aren't you happy, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Happy?... About what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Dr. Grey brought this over to my office the other day, and...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! It's that news story! The one about the malpractice suit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Fourteen patients died and it caused a huge stink.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, but that's not all, pal. Things only got worse after that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean the car accident the nurse died in?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Hmm... Oh, here we go. I brought my own clipping with me today. Here, pal, this is for you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright. Thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The nurse that killed the patients ended up getting killed in an accident. Dr. Grey wound up on a lot of tabloid shows because of that. Now, there was a smart man. I'm sure that was a great way to advertise for his clinic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh, huh. Scaring people off is always the best way to get more patients.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So about this key...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, is that your house key or something, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come on, does this look like a house key to you?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Then what's it for?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's... ... <thought>Hmm, actually, I should probably keep that a secret...</thought> It's my bicycle key.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh. Nothing special, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm sorry things had to turn out this way, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's too early to give up! No one's proven her guilty of anything, yet!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Look, even if there were a zillion of you, pal, this is a case you... *sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now why is he sighing?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, so that's little Pearl.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know her?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Only that Ms. Fey was looking for her earlier. Something about being worried that she'll end up talking to the weird guy. So, you have any idea who this "weird guy" is, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Nope. Not a clue.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's Maya's aunt, right? I got to eat one of her giant strawberry desserts earlier. It was really good!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Aw, I didn't get to eat one yet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Boy do I look scary in this picture. I guess if I want people to stop thinking cops are scary, I have to change myself. Gotta smile, gotta smile!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's that classic Gumshoe goofy smile again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ooh, I'd better shut my mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, what?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm not gonna give you any information about evidence, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't have anything to tell you about this one, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't have to be so mean about it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Not. A. Word.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-H-Hey! Don't look at me like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That girl has one intense stare... *gulp*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hello again. We seem to be seeing a lot of each other today.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Aww, she's, like, tooootally cute! Is she, like, your daughter?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-What!? NO! <thought>How old do you think I am!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I want to ask you about the victim, Dr. Grey.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I, like, totally don't know him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaack! What is that!?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You can see it, can't you, Mr. Nick? You can see the "lock" on that person's heart.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh, what...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">This is the power of the Magatama. Only you can see these "Psyche-Locks", Mr. Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Psyche-Locks, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">The more someone wants to hide their secret, the more locks you will see. If it's only one, I think you can easily unlock it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Unlock"...? But how?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Please use Mystic Maya's Magatama on this person, and let's remove the lock.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have no idea what she's talking about, but... Guess I'll give it a try.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You must be careful, though, Mr. Nick. If you make a mistake, it will hurt you. If you don't think you have the proof you need, you must have the courage to stop.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I've got to start somewhere. Let's give this Psyche-Lock thing a try.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Iim going to ask you again. Did you know Dr. Grey?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I totally don't know that guy. Like, you're totally more presistent than a roach!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This girl is hiding something! I'm sure of it! I guess I have no choice but to remove this lock. Alright, so first, I have to use Maya's Magatama...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ini Miney. I believe you do know who Dr. Grey is!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">I told you! Like, how many times do I, like, have to repeat myself? If you're, like, so totally sure, then where's, like, your proof?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">While it may be possible that you never actually met Dr. Grey in person, I do believe you might have at least, indirectly known of him.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, what do you mean, like, "indirectly"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should try to show that the possibility existed for now...</thought> <thought>Hmm, so, something that shows a possible connection between Ini and Dr. Grey...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here is your proof!</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, what is that...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ouch... I guess it doesn't have anything to do with it, huh? <thought>Pearls did warn me... "If you make a mistake, it will hurt you," she said. If I don't have enough evidence, I should probably "stop". I should take another look at the Court Record and think it through one more time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a look at this newspaper clipping.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Like, what is it? ... A story about an accident?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please read the victim's name.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Um..."Mimi Miney"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Miney" is a pretty rare last name, wouldn't you say? Ms. Mimi Miney wouldn't happen to be a relative of yours, would she?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...! So you noticed. Sh-She was my older sister.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry about your loss... Your sister... Was she a nurse... Perhaps at Dr. Grey's surgical clinic?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Grey Surgical Clinic... I don't think I need to tell you that the clinic was run by the victim, Dr. Turner Grey. Which is how you knew of Dr. Grey; you knew him through your sister!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please, tell me all you know about Dr. Grey.</line>
<line speaker="Ini">My... My sister's name was Mimi Miney. She was, like, a nurse at Dr. Grey's clinic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's what I thought...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ini">I heard that, like, Dr. Grey was really tough on people. Like, a total slave driver. My sis was, like, always coming home totally wiped out 'cause she was overworked.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wiped out? So is that why she fell asleep at the wheel?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">That guy, like, drove my sis so hard, so, like, that's why the accident happened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The one where 14 patients died from malpractice?</line>
<line speaker="Ini">Yeah, like, I think that was the doctor's fault, too. My sis was pushed by, like, everyone's expectations and, like, her duties and stuff. And that pushed her to her death.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... I'm sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Ini">So, like, are we done? I've, like, already told my story to, like, everyone...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Do you understand now, Mr. Nick? This is how a Psyche-Lock works.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well, I don't plan to pry into people's hearts unless I absolutely need to...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">The lock this time was pretty easy, but... you might meet people who aren't as willing to give in later on. If you don't have enough proof, be careful and know when to stop trying.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm? What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I have never left Kurain Village.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Really? Wow, that's, um, pretty amazing...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You are going to meet with Mystic Maya... aren't you? Please tell her I said hi.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, wait! <thought>She ran off... Again. Well, I know Ini's secret now, but... I still don't have any idea how I'm going to save Maya. I don't even know if I should go in there with a smile or a straight face... *sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What am I supposed to do!? I'm almost out of time! Can I really do anything? Can I really save her...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Sorry to keep you waiting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? Must be Maya...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">It's been a long time, hasn't it, Phoenix?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>That voice...</thought> M-Mia!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Even without me being here, it looks like you've learned to stand on your own.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mia... She's Maya's older sister, and my mentor. She was a top-notch defense lawyer, but a certain case forced her into "retirement". But... whenever I'm in trouble, she comes to help, just like this. Her spirit comes back from the other world and borrows Maya's body for a bit...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix, you can't make that kind of face in front of your client.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">A lawyer is someone who smiles no matter how bad it gets, and especially when it's bad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You can't smile at the end if you haven't been smiling the whole way there. In any case, the face you're making now is no face to show a client, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">So, tell me all about it. I'm going to guess that my sister is in a lot of trouble again...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I told her everything about what had happened in the last two days. Mia closed her eyes, deep in thought, while she listened...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">...I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia... What am I supposed to do?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... It's pretty clear what a good lawyer does in this situation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-And that is!? Tell me, please!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Believe in your convictions. And fight for the complete acquittal of your client.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You think Maya's not guilty!? How can you be so sure!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I know she is. And I'll give you a hint as to why.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mediums can't have dreams.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can't have "dreams"...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">From what you told me, it sounds like Maya was having a dream while channeling.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... She said she dream that she had died and had been buried in the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">But that is impossible. You've heard it from her, I'm sure. When a medium channels, her own spirit disappears. Which means that it's impossible for her to dream during that time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! Then... What does this mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I think it's safe to bet that Maya was set-up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A set-up!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's up to you to blow the lid on this case tomorrow and show how she was set-up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How am I supposed to prove her innocence when I have nothing to go on!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">If you're looking for a clue, it's already in your hands.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-It is!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Just as it sounds, Phoenix, you already hold the "key".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>R-Really...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Come on, show me the "key" to this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The "key", huh? Alright, I'll show it to her; the "key" I hold.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">*chuckle* Wow, this badge brings back a lot of memories, doesn't it...? I would love to stand with you at the defense table one more time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mia...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">This is... Maya's Magatama, isn't it? Why do you have it...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya gave it to me, but...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I see... ... This is something very important to me. Take good care of it, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She looks at it with such a soft look in her eyes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia, have you seen this key before?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ahh, the key... It's literally, the key to understanding everything that's happened in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This key?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix, listen. Right now, that key is sitting in your hand. However, it shouldn't be. ... It contradicts the "facts".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What does she mean...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">I'm certain this key will be the piece of evidence that makes your case tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I can't see Maya... when I'm in her body like this... But I can tell. She's very lonely and sad. Take good care of her, will you, Phoenix?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I will...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Pearly! She's really grown up... I left Kurain Village a long time ago. She probably doesn't remember a thing about me by now...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I'm afraid I might have caused Aunt Morgan a lot of stress. When I left Kurain, I left Maya in my aunt's care. And now something like this happens...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I've seen this man somewhere before... He had a strange name... and I'm almost sure I've questioned him before. I remember him making a show of confidence at first, but after five minutes, he breaks down and... ...you end up feeling bad for the poor guy...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's right. I'm already dead. But I feel very grateful to have been born a Fey... so I can talk with you like this...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...Do you have anything more useful? There's no time left. Try to show me something that will help you in tomorrow's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I'm sorry, but I don't remember who that is...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... ... You already know everything you need to know. You know what the "key" to this case is... That is enough...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... But! How can I win tomorrow without knowing who the real murderer is!? Who... Who could have...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>At the time, I didn't know, but this day was going to end with a turn for the surprising...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mia!? Wh-What...!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's right. Only I can see the Psyche-Locks... Which means... Mia must know something about the real murderer! But for this to be something that she would hide under lock and key from even me... What in the world is going on!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think I have enough evidence yet... I should investigate and gather some more clues before I try again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nnrgh! I've made too many mistakes!</thought></line>
</xml>