<xml>
<title>Rise from the Ashes</title>
<line speaker="Ema">Uh... um, Mr. Wright! So... What's going on with the case, anyway!? I... I'm a little confused.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!? W-well, um... let's see. <thought>What is going on?</thought> The victim, Detective Bruce Goodman, was stabbed to death after&#160;5:00 PM on the 21st. He died in the Prosecutor's parking lot... and the Police Department's evidence room.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What's this "and the evidence room" part!? The Prosecutor's Office and the Police Department are 30 minutes apart by car.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Well... that's what we're going to find out. <thought>Or try to, at least...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">... Alright! Let's do it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Glad she's in good spirits, but I'm not sure she's going to be much help with this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Don't be so sure, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Would you mind coming with me? I'll prove that these thick- rimmed glasses of mine aren't just for show! Let's go! Science awaits us!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You know, I really don't think we should worry about the Police Department murder! There wasn't even a body found there! Who cares?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Of course it was our victim who was killed at the Department...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">And my sister would never do such a thing! I know it...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That oil drum... Was it empty?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">The oil drum kicked over by the Chief Prosecutor... was brimming with water!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">My sister, erasing evidence at the crime scene? Never!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even though she says they don't get along, Ema really likes her sister...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's not it at all! It's just... We're both professionals at what we do... and I trust her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Big words for a high school student.</thought> Well, whether there was blood stains or not... The water in that oil drum washed it all away.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He he heh. Ignore the strength of my science at your own peril, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What's that grin for?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This situation calls for one thing, and that is... Luminol testing fluid!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">L-luminol?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Blood is sticky stuff, you know. You can't just wash it away with a little water. Even if you can't see it, it's still there...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But wouldn't the police have already done those tests?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Never trust anyone's eyes but your own, Mr. Wright! Just give it a try!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-me? Why do I have to do it!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm a minor! I can't even drink yet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We're testing blood stains with this stuff, not drinking it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Here, look, I'll lend you these glasses.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? You had an extra pair of those things?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">To test for a blood reaction, just spray the luminol on it. Like this, see? Touch the screen to spray it on. Okay! Let's find us some bloodstains!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can see her eyes shining behind those glasses...</thought> So, is this a bloodstain?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Uhhhh... It's so... ugh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ema, you're shaking.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's just... this is my first time seeing real blood!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Scientific investigation in action...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">O-okay, well, we definitely know that this is a bloodstain. But, doesn't something strike you as odd? Scientifically speaking, of course?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's odd about this... scientifically?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why, the blood stain's location is odd! Elementary!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">H-huh? Why is that "elementary"? I mean, I would think that if there was a fight, you'd expect some bloodstains here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I suppose you might think that.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">C'mon, Mr. Wright! We're all counting on you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There is something odd about this bloodstain... But if it's not the location of the blood, then maybe...</thought> Maybe it's the amount of blood that's odd?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The perpetrator and Detective Goodman fought here, right? Don't you think there'd be a little more blood?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I definitely think so! I mean... Look at all the blood on the sole of the victim's shoe!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's strange! If they fought here, there'd have to be more bloodstains than this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Uh, h-hey, Mr. Wright! See how I'm marking up the floor plans when we find a blood stain? See... I'm pretty handy to have around, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, yeah. That's very... useful information to have.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I saved up my allowance to buy this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Luminol Testing Fluid information received from Ema.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">We can't be sure that the police will reveal all their evidence in court. Sometimes they fail to mention evidence that doesn't fit with their view of the case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And we'll drag that "hidden evidence" out into the light of day!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah! It feels like we're really investigating a crime now, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This luminol stuff is going to come in handy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Hah!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I wonder how that fluid of yours would react to a nice Deli Box?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ms. Starr!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">You only trust your own eyes, hm? Not bad,&#160;you two... This day-old Deli Box is on the house...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, it's just, that kind of lead in doesn't really get my mouth watering.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So that's where Ms. Starr saw the incident from.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can probably see quite a lot from up there. <thought>Hmm... That probably means she wasn't lying when she saw Ms. Skye stab him...</thought> Where's the security guard, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, this is just something I heard... But apparently he went out to buy coffee for Ms. Starr.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That woman is a force to be reckoned with...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, this is the famous divider.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It sure helped us knock a hole in that testimony today. Come to think of it, this divider helped our case more than the actual witness.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The great divider! A chip off the old parking block!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's just a wall. <thought>Scientifically speaking...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, this is the famous oil drum.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, no time like the present! I'll try to kick it over myself! Hii-yah! ......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-that's okay. Don't cry. <thought>That Lana Skye must be a powerful woman...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's about as red as a sports car can get.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup, it's pretty red alright. <thought>The body was found in Edgeworth's car trunk... And the lock on the trunk was broken too... So, the question is why did Ms. Skye chose his car?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, what model car is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I think it was called a "Sedan" or a "Coupe." Something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Those are car types, Mr. Wright. Not models. You're a guy, aren't you, Mr. Wright? Your supposed to know these things!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe it is about time I got my driver's license...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's where we found that note.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"2/21 SL-9"... The SL-9 Incident.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A case that was due for transferal the day of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And the detective in charge of the case was the victim.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I wonder what kind of case this SL-9 Incident thing was?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's kind of hard to guess just knowing the case number.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"B Block" is through there. That's where visitors park.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So... Ms. Starr climbed over this fence!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-it seems so, yeah. <thought>That fence is 9 feet high at least!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well no time like the present! I think I'll give it a little try! Eeeek! ......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-it's okay, don't cry. <thought>Maybe there's a Lunchland Olympics team?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">That looks like a petrified piece of provolone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? I-it's not! It's my attorney's badge!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">... I'd think a petrified piece of provolone would fetch more on the open market.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, my badge isn't up for sale. Not yet, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I had one of those up until two years ago...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Back when you were the Cough-up Queen, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We found this ID card here in this parking lot...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Well, there's no mistaking that. It's definitely Goodman's.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... It's the same ID as the man who was killed at the Police Department.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">... That's impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wish I could be so sure...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A body with Edgeworth's knife stuck in it was found in Edgeworth's car.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I'd think he owes me his gratitude.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gratitude?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Why, if I hadn't witnessed the crime...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Edgeworth would have been the suspect!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I wonder.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">Still, it's strange. Why didn't our Chief Prosecutor have her own murder weapon ready?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um... What do you think about this?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">"SL-9 Incident"... On that knife... And on that note... Goodman... Goodman was the head detective on that case, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">That knife was evidence from that case... the murder weapon. It was due for transferal the very day that Goodman was killed. As I suspected... SL-9 isn't over! Not yet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you think you could tell us more about the SL-9 Incident?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">It was when I grabbed the Chief Prosecutor on the shoulder... She dropped that phone on the pavement.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's when you heard her talking about the "muffler," right?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Little did I know... it was a trap! The red car's muffler, and the prosecutor's red muffler!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What was Ms. Skye really trying to say, I wonder?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">If you think about it, I could have taken that picture from the guard room. But... even I get flustered sometimes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you went straight to the scene of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">And climbed the chain link fence in an effort to stop the murder? That's when I took this photo, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">In other words... five minutes after the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Those five minutes are the whole problem... The hole in my testimony, as it were.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The five minutes weren't the problem, Ms. Starr, you lying was the problem!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Listen, little girl. I've had my testimony "disregarded" before... And I wasn't going to have it disregarded again! Just like that time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That time...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">You!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">You said you wanted some hot tea, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, no, but thanks. <thought>She didn't even look at it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mmm! You must have to brew the leaves a long time to get rich flavor like this!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">We "pre-infuse"&#160;the leaves with steam before brewing.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I knew it! So that's the secret to their aroma! Exquisite!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The only thing I'm smelling here is wasted time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Someone used a marker to write their name on this.</thought> "Ema Skye" Don't tell me you bring this with you everywhere you go.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, you never know where something might go down!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just what kind of a world do you think we live in...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This blood must be from when Lana...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No! My sister isn't the murderer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But she did call you, didn't she? At the time of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And her right hand is bandaged.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey! Just whose side are you on!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This has nothing to do with "taking sides." <thought>So... This means that Lana's hand had blood on it. This just keeps getting worse...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Difficult-looking legal books stand in a formidable row. They mock me.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, I tried studying one of those just now. Remember what they were talking about in the trial today...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right, evidence law. So, did you learn anything?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, when I tried reading it made my head hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Then, when I closed it, it slipped out of my hand and fell on my foot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oddly enough I find myself identifying with her on this one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia's plant, "Charley." I've been taking care of him in Maya's absence. Huh? He looks a little yellow today...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, I watered him just now. I mixed in a lot, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mixed in... what?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Why my very own scientific additive! Well, Charley? You like it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I told you, he's turning yellow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia's desk. I sit here even less now that I've stopped taking cases.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Uh oh! I have a history test coming up next week! I'd better study! I'm borrowing this desk, okay? Let's see... George Washington was the first king of America...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sorry, Mia...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like it's cleaning day again at the hotel across the way. I hear they're planning a second branch outside the city. Egad! The bellboy was staring right at me.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He looks wimpy, but you can tell, there's a sharp edge under that facade. That bellboy is going to be someone someday.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wish someone would say that about me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... where should we begin?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, well, isn't it obvious? We should begin with that, y'know... that thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The mystery of the victim I guess. How could one man, Detective Goodman... be killed in two places simultaneously?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, well, you see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We should go to the Police Department... the evidence room was it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Uh... I'm not being very useful here, am I...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No, no! You're being very... helpful.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Poor Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Gant">You are becoming a thorn in my side, Worthy... There've been rumors... After all, you were in the defendant's chair just last year...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There was that business with him not reading that officer's report...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, about the killing at the Police Department, right. <thought>The Chief of Police was right about that... But I can't help but think... Someone at the Police Department doesn't like Edgeworth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">That number was the clincher, wasn't it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">5842189... It's in the record.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The ID number of the detective killed at the Police Department that day at 5:15. But... we found this card in the parking lot at the Prosecutor's Office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Something to think about later when I'm not so busy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Don't leave me here to do all the thinking alone!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I bet you'd be pretty happy with a "King of Attorneys" shield, too, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We defense attorneys are a scattered, unrecognized bunch.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Still... I wonder why the trophy shield is broken?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It is pretty odd, huh? <thought>I doubt it has anything to do with this case though...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So... Mr. Edgeworth's knife was the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right... or so the witness, Ms. Starr, claims. She saw your sister stab Mr. Goodman with this knife.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ugh... You know, all of this is that Angel Starr's fault!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She's not the one on trial here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, no, but she must have seen it wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Her eyesight isn't on trial here, either.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to Ms. Starr's testimony... Ms. Skye used her phone right after the murder... she called you, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">B-but...! She hung up right away. And it was a bad connection. I couldn't hear anything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Because it was an underground parking lot, I suppose...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">She did say something about a "muffler"... but got cut off...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Th-this photograph... Ms. Starr must have been seeing things!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And photographing things? <thought>This proves Ms. Skye was there at the scene of the crime! She is connected to this crime somehow... but how?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why would this have been in the car's exhaust pipe?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's evidence from an old case, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right... the SL-9 incident. It was already solved, apparently. <thought>This knife was stolen on the day of the evidence transferal... Maybe I should look into this "S-L9 ([sic]</thought> Incident"...)</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This stuff is pretty expensive.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't say. How much does it cost?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'd say about $10 per gram! I save up my allowance to buy it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your allowance...? Does your sister give you that?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes. We don't have parents...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-right...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sometimes she even gives me a bottle instead of my allowance!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A bottle of luminol testing fluid...? <thought>Man, I'd just take the allowance myself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like Ms. Skye is in questioning...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I hope the detectives aren't yelling at her... "How did you kill him in two places at the same time!" Can you imagine?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How's she supposed to answer that! <thought>Wait a second... The Chief said they'd caught the criminal at the Police Department!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Let's come back later!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitors the visitor's room. One murder at the Prosecutor's Office... one at the Police Department... He must be frozen with fear thinking that he might be next...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Don't scare the poor guy!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, this place is certainly tidy today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And it will be tidy tomorrow, too. Incidentally, he's not here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm sure he's off doing important investigations!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I hope that's what he's doing.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess we'll have to come back.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Whoa! What a view! It must be nice to have an office on the 12th floor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess you would feel... important.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Incidentally... Were you to jump out this window, the speed at the time of impact would be... ... Got it! Approximately 70.71 miles per hour!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's handy to know...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">He won such a prestigious award. Why would he just leave it on the couch?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Better this than that giant Steel Samurai. <thought>Edgeworth has always been like that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Really? Hey, I should write this down. Tell me what he was like as a kid!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Back in elementary school, he won awards for all kinds of things. Speech contests, essays, playing the flute, golf tournaments...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That doesn't exactly sound like typical elementary school stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But he always hated receiving awards. He'd make some smart remark like,</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"I know the path I've walked. No one else needs to tell me."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's how he's always been.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Kind of gets under your skin, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What? It looks like some blood has dripped down here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judging by the amount, my guess is it's from a nosebleed.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A nosebleed, hm? Maybe in his wrath, Mr. Edgeworth slapped someone for their incompetence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why does Detective Gumshoe's face come to mind...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's even busier here today than it was yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The detectives are running around so fast they're blurring.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I suppose it makes sense--a detective did get killed in their own department.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So... the evidence room. The scene of the crime! According to the pamphlet we got at the front desk... Here it is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's like a kid at an amusement park.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ooh, a real crime scene! Let's go take a look!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The Blue Badger is still writhing around today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's give him the benefit of the doubt and say he's dancing. <thought>Speaking of "dancing"... The whole Police Department has been dancing around like crazy since yesterday...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Can I take out his batteries? I just can't help but feel he's going to do something naughty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, that patrolman is saluting the other guy. He must be a detective!</line>
<line speaker="Police">You idiot! What were you thinking!? Where's your head?</line>
<line speaker="Patrolman">S-sir, it's r-right here sir.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">... I guess he wasn't saluting, he was showing the detective where his head was.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They make a good pair.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow, everyone looks deadly serious here...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, there was a vicious murder of a detective in this department, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, but the same detective was also killed at the same time in the Prosecutor's lot.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ugh... It makes my head hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, first things first. I want to check out the crime scene here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes, you sound "dead"-set on investigating! But don't mess up, or we could wind up... dead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I doubt anyone wants more mysteries or dead bodies around here right now. <thought>But... it doesn't look like anyone's going to help us much, either.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A poster of a female police officer... Wait, no. That's the latest "Babes in Uniform" calendar. My bad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Police">"I know! The killer used dry ice! If you put it between the latch and the door, the room could be sealed shut!" This is good! I'll win a writer's award for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He's not writing a report... he's writing a novel.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These are the detectives' desks. There are computers and files on each one. Funny, they're a lot tidier than I'd expect. I guess the detectives don't spend a lot of time at their desks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this is the police mascot, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Chief">The Blue Badger! The future star of the police force!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The design's a little changed from the one outside...</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Ah, well, the Dancing Blue Badger<thought>tm</thought> is still under development, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You have it trademarked?</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Absolutely! It's cutting edge stuff. Very "now." I showed this doll here to my daughter and she burst into tears!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Don't show her the moving mock-up outside then, you'll give her nightmares.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be the Head Detective. He's glued to his computer screen.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Wha...!? "Detective killed in the evidence room"! "Tell no one outside the Police Department"!? Nooo! I told the old lady at the restaurant everything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Someone's getting a demotion...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's with the decor in this place? It's very... eccentric.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">According to the pamphlet, this is the guard station for the evidence room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, beyond that door is the evidence room... the scene of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It sure seems that way... Oh. Ohhh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's those cacti! They're so prickly... so imposing! It's hard to think straight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If you can't handle the cacti, stay out of the desert...</thought> What I want to know is, if this is a guard station, where is the guard?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I have a feeling I know who this guard is already...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's a security guard uniform hanging there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks more like a costume than a uniform, honestly.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A leather jacket, leather pants, a leather... What was that called again? A punchy? A paunchy? A pinchy? I know! A poochy! Hmm... Wait, maybe that wasn't it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's a "poncho," but I think I'll keep that information to myself for the time being.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yipes, that sure is prickly. It must be the real deal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I would think just one big one would be sufficient.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This cactus... is a lot like my sister, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Ms. Skye?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Encased in a cold, rigid shell, with thorns pointing in every direction... Just like her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... You know, I've been looking at this cactus a while now, and I don't see the resemblance.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">... It's more an attitude thing than a physical similarity.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like there's a video feed from the evidence room here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's a light blinking below the monitor. It says "Recording"! I bet we could use this computer to check on who went in and out of here!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This swinging door makes the place look like some kind of saloon!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But look, it's nailed shut. You can't get in that way.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Of course not! If you went in through here.. The cactus would fall over. Ouch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd say it'd be more of an "Yeeeeaargh," myself.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Look, on the floor, a lasso!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... looks like it's set up to trap something.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A trap, here? Wait, I know! Maybe someone was trying to catch a wild bull in here... But the lasso missed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You sure have an active imagination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The evidence room is beyond that door.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Let's just walk in! ... It won't open.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You thought it'd be open? <thought>I think we'd need someone's permission to go in there first...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wow! We got a reaction!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm. There's clearly blood around the thorns here. This room's pretty messy. Someone must have tripped over something... and planted their head right in these thorns.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">... I think that might be more painful than being murdered.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">You certainly put me in a tight spot today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My apologies, Ms. Starr, but...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">No, no, it's okay. It was my fault.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, we know.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I witnessed everything from that security room right there. But... I was afraid that wouldn't sound convincing enough, you see... I was wrong to think that. I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sorry? You lied on the witness stand! That's unforgivable!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">... Little girl, don't forget what's important here. Even if the place I witnessed the events from was different, I still saw what I saw. I saw Chief Prosecutor Skye stab a man in cold blood, and that testimony still stands!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I swear it on my honor as a detective! She stabbed Goodman!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I know this photograph has something important to tell us... but what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So... you were a detective, weren't you, Ms. Starr?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Yes... It was a long time ago. Well, two years ago. No matter how hardened the criminal, when they faced me... They coughed it up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Coughed it... up?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">They confessed. They babbled like babies. You know, I may seem like a demon sometimes... But I can be an angel, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wouldn't doubt it.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Every day, I dragged the dirt out of the mouths of suspect after suspect... And before long, they called me... The Cough-up Queen!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, and here I had thought someone had gotten food poisoning from your lunches.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And... you were "let go"? Er... fired?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I felt that I had found my dream job when I became an investigator... And if these prim and proper prosecutors hadn't let me go, I'd still be one today.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">It's all because of that case... The SL-9 Incident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ess... el..? <thought>Wait! She doesn't mean...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">That's when I learned the truth. We're nothing to them. Disposable.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Disposable?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Two years ago... it was the biggest case I'd ever handled. The police and the prosecutors were desperate for decisive evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So... they didn't solve it?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">On the contrary. It was solved quite cleanly. The criminal was caught and executed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>E-executed...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">Yes, the criminal got what was coming to him. It doesn't get any cleaner than that. The only problem was... they never did find decisive evidence. Not even a little.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!? But the criminal was executed, right?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Evidence... of a sort. Made up evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wh-what? You mean they executed someone with fabricated evidence!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">... The best part came several months after the trial. Every detective involved with the case was dealt with. Some were demoted to patrolmen, others found themselves out of a job...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">And... you were one of those?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Myself, and one other person you know well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait, could it be...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">Exactly. Officer Jake Marshall. He's on security detail in the Police Department, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">As professional detectives, we investigated that case from every angle. Jake was particularly determined. And then... it was over. And he was demoted. However... He hasn't forgotten. And neither have I!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You haven't forgotten SL-9?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">There was another side to that case, a hidden side. That's what we're after now. And no one up in their fancy offices can stop us.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wait! Th-those lunches you sell...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">There is only one reason I come to sell lunches in this accursed office. I come here to meet old friends... boyfriends that can help me investigate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ms. Starr's old boyfriends... How many does she have, anyway?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just when the detectives on this case have disappeared, we find new evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">There has to be a connection!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">So, Rookie...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">It seems like you're serious about investigating this case...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Then you should take this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A... Salisbury Steak Lunch?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I know a certain guy who might help you if you tempt him with this treat...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um, Ms. Starr...? Officer Marshall... is he your... uh, are you his...? Are you g-g-g-going out!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Why do you want to know?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I was just wondering what happened to him? A long time ago, when he was helping my sister do cases, he was so nice. He got along so well with my sister, it made me jealous. And... he was nice to me too, back then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This would be when Officer Marshall was a detective.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">But now... now he's so cold!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">... Jake and I are merely cooperating on this investigation. We're putting the past to rest, as it were. Nothing more than that.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I... I see. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Officer Jake Marshall... Hmm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">You'll give that to Jake like I asked, won't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um...! Y-you, and Officer M-Marshall, you... uh... A-a-a-a-are y-you... Are you going out!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">... Jake and I are cooperating on an investigation, that's all. We're just putting the past to rest.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wow, my mouth is watering! I can almost hear the sound of steak frying on the grill!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No doubt it's all cold and tough by now.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No, I'm sure it's delicious! Ms. Starr poured her heart into making this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So long as she didn't put any other organs in there...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see... "Ingredients: Meat"</line>
<line speaker="Ema">She must mean "beef." She probably just wrote it generically.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... yeah. Let's hope so.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Of course, as a scientist I have to check what additives she used.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Go to town.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh? It says here... "Hours of sweat and labor."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that's why the sauce is so salty...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This place is charge with frantic energy, as always.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Please!!!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh? Wasn't that...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">One steak lunch, please! Oh, it's you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Now's no time for chit-chat, pal. I'm a busy man! What I really need is a steak lunch from Lunchland.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh... you mean one of these? Actually, it's not for sale...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I just heard the sound of his heart breaking.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Now's no time for despair! We've caught our criminal! Now we just need evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The criminal... you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You heard about the stabbing in the Police Department evidence room, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the same day that a detective was killed in the Prosecutor's parking lot... Another detective... was killed at the Police Department!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And the perpetrator? Do you have a suspect?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Well, there was a suspect. Just arrested 'em, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's the biggest scandal to hit the station in ages! Everything's topsy-turvy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, Detective Gumshoe, who was it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Listen, pal, all I know is I need me a steak lunch, pronto! Standing around here talking isn't going to fill my belly!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">W-wait! Don't leave!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If you want to know more, head on down to the detention center, pal. Questioning should be over, so I figure he's down there having a good cry. Later!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He ran off to the evidence room...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, this investigation is off to a running start.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, that patrolman is saluting the other guy. He must be a detective!</line>
<line speaker="Police">Answer me! How many fingers do you see!?</line>
<line speaker="Patrolman">... I-I'm sorry! I don't know!</line>
<line speaker="Police">Well, that's 20 for the left, but nowhere near that for the right... Get glasses, officer!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">... That wasn't a salute... it was an eye test!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They make a good pair.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Still, I do feel better about things. A little. I mean, they caught the person who stabbed Detective Goodman, didn't they?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, yeah, I guess they did. <thought>Best to not go too far down that road right now. Things will just get confusing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wh-what was that!?</line>
<line speaker="???">Sir! That's what I'm saying! Me, a perpetrator? I-I-I'd say I-I-I was the perpetrated against, sir! That's what I'd say! Ah, oh, uh. Hi. Greetings, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wait, I know who you are...</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Excuse me! But is Mr. Edgeworth, uh... anywhere on the premises? I'm here, sir, at the request of the Chief, sir! I've got your report, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Officer Meekins! So you're a guard here at the detention center?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">No, sir! I'm not, sir! I'm a little lost patrolman, like a little lost lamb, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, I get it. You're here to deliver a report?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">No, sir, I, uh, how should I say this...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait... he isn't... is he?</thought> You... Officer Meekins... You didn't... did you?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Err..........</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Perpetrator Officer Meekins reporting, sir!!!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What...!? Whaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now this is an unexpected turn of events...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Smile for the camera... Poor Officer Meekins... I think he knows he's being watched.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitors the visitor's room. Seeing a fellow patrolman in here must make him worry about his own fate in life.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No comments from the peanut gallery!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir! I'm a patrolman with General Affairs, sir! SIR!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ow. I can hear you fine, Officer Meekins.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I had some business that day, sir, and so I went to the evidence room, sir... The guard office in front of the room was empty, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, normally there's a guard at the evidence room?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">That's right, sir! Because evidence is kept in the evidence room, sir! Now, the security officer... was none other than Officer Marshall!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>M-Marshall!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Then, sir, I happened to glance at the security room monitor! That's when I saw him, sir! A suspicious person in the evidence room! A suspicious person, sir! A suspicious person! Yowwowowowowowow!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What the heck is this guy doing?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So what happened then?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">After that, sir, I... I... everything went white! I saw red! I blacked out! And... when I came to, I was here. In the detention center.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How long were you out!? Days!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um, might I ask... what happened to your hand?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir! There was no one to bandage me, sir! So I did what I could to wrap it up, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A bandage on his hand... just like Ms. Skye.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yet another similarity between this case and the one at the Prosecutor's Office...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">First things first... tell us how you hurt your hand!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, I don't mean to pry, but you are the perpetrator, correct? You killed Detective Bruce Goodman in the evidence room... right?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir... Please don't look at me with those sad puppy dog eyes, sir! If you have to label me as persecutor or victim, sir... Then label me victim!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, I would, but you happen to be in detention. And alive and well at that.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Ah, yes, well, that's true, sir. I suppose you could say that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you know the victim, Detective Goodman?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Well, sir, if I had to label him as a "stranger" or a "total stranger"... Then I'd say he leans heavily on the "total stranger" side!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... you didn't know him?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir! I work in a tiny department, devoid of light or other creature comforts! I don't know any detectives!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, if he was a total stranger, why did you stab him?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir! I had n-no intention of killing him, sir! None! N-nor do I have any recollection of k-killing him, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>At least someone around here is more confused than I am.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you tell me what it is you do "remember"?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Well sir, you might say I'm a lost little patrolman. A lost little lamb, if you will! I didn't know Mr. Detective Goodman who was in the evidence room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's why you thought he looked suspicious...</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir, I entered the evidence room, and asked the man to display his ID card!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, that sounds pretty much by the book so far.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Th-that's right, sir! That's what I've been trying to tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you asked Detective Goodman to show his ID card. What did he do?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">That's the thing! Suddenly he pointed a knife at me!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What...!?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir, I assure you I was as flustered as you are right now! So I whooped and leapt at him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Detective Goodman pointed a knife at him?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">"Do unto others before they do unto you"! My father's own words, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wh-what happened then?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Well... My eyes, sir... everything went white. When I awoke, I was here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And your hand... that happened when Detective Goodman was stabbed?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Well! You see, sir, I, er...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Don't you think you should just confess?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">But, sir! Sir! But! There was nothing I could do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Nothing you could do"...?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir, to tell the truth, sir, when it happened... When the detective pointed that knife at me, I just hollered, sir! And the next thing I knew, I was unconscious!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The next thing you knew you were... huh?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Then, when I opened my eyes... I was alone in the evidence room, sir! All alone! Alone, because... Because Detective Goodman had disappeared!!!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Then when I looked down, I was gushing blood from my hand, sir! Oh, the shock! Oh, the sorrow, sir! Can you imagine how I felt?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The victim's body... disappeared...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm... That's some story.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, Officer Meekins, why was it that they arrested you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean, Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Let's look at what we know. Now, Officer Meekins didn't know Detective Goodman... And the "victim" whom he met at the scene of the crime didn't show his ID card.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In other words, we have no way of knowing if the victim was really the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">And if this "body" just "disappeared" from the evidence room... We don't even know if anyone actually died!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">That's it, sir! That! That's what I wanted to say! That is... I did say something along those lines.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh? But you still ended up here...?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">They told me that it had to be him, sir. "On that day, at that time..." Detective Goodman was definitely in the evidence room." That's what they said.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... you don't remember the events clearly?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">No... but the video tape is quite clear.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh? Video tape...?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">From the security camera. The crime, my crime, the crime I swore to stamp out! It's there! It's me! It's on tape!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">And you wait until now to tell us this!?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I'm sorry, really sorry, sir! I'll hand over my badge! I don't deserve it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no thanks, I have my own. <thought>Well, guess we'd better go check out the crime scene.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Officer Meekins, have a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">... Go ahead, sir, laugh! Laugh at me, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha... huh?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I know what you want to say! You're going to tell me how she has one just like it!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">M-me? Why would I...?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I know, sir, I know. I'm the only one without a girl with matching badges! Nowhere! I'm alone! All alone! Is that so wrong!? Life isn't all about high school sweethearts and youthful romance, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is he talking about those badges on her coat?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd like to think there's a difference between my badge and a fashion accessory...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um... do you think you could take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">... Hey! That's it, sir! That's it! That's it!!!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's what!?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">My head was a blank until this very moment! But, sir, now I remember! I remember, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean you remember what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Correct! That card, that card was the cause of it all!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This... ID card?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Exactly, sir! That's exactly it! Nothing could be more exact, sir! Nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better pry into this one a little deeper.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Officer Meekins, this is for you!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Eeeek! I-I'm scared of knives, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's okay, I just wanted you to take a look at it.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">That's it, sir! Last night, sir! That's the one! I was an apple sir, in my dream, sir, and I was... I was being peeled!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">On second thought, you don't have to look at the knife.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... He's overreacting to the knife, but I guess he's been through a lot.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Hey! Why do you have that? That's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">From the day... It was taken at the Prosecutor's Office.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The day that Detective Goodman's body was found in the trunk...</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">So this means... This means I'm a free man! Innocent! If this is a dream, sir... Then I hope I never wake up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If this is a dream you'd better wake up right now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Officer Meekins, could you take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I'm sorry, sir, really sorry, but I have no idea what that is. Maybe you should ask Mr. Edgeworth, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He's passing the buck, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It takes a special kind of man to pass the buck to Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">H-hey, Mr. Wright! Look who's standing at the Head Detective's desk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's Chief Gant!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gant">Are you sure this is all, hmm? You know what it means if there is anything missing!</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Sir! I'm sure it's most likely totally perfect! We checked the drawers, the lockers, the garbage cans, the coat pockets... the pillowcases, behind the computer monitors, the coffee machine...</line>
<line speaker="Gant">I see. Well, if anything does turn up, you call me right away, deal?</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Y-y-y-yessir!!! We'll scour the place again, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The Head Detective looks a little flustered...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gant">Ah hah! Wrighto, my boy! How ya been? Swim much?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh ho ho, Chief Gant! Reporting for duty, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Why are you saluting him, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Police">"I know! The killer used a cassette tape! What a crafty trick! That gunshot was a fake!" This is good! No one will expect a cassette tape in this day and age!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He's not writing a report... he's writing a novel.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Ooh, sorry you had to see that.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Uh... what exactly did the Chief of Police want you to do?</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Well, see over there? That's Goodman's desk. He wanted me to check it for anything that might be a clue... They took away every last piece of garbage in the trash can.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, nothing belonging to Detective Goodman is still here?</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Of course not! Well, except for this.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What!? You kept something!?</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Sure, why not? It's not important. He didn't even finish writing it! It's a lost item report but it's only half complete.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A lost item? Did Detective Goodman lose something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The date on it is February 21. <thought>I'll make a note of that just in case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should probably get a quick look around the crime scene...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... is Edgeworth going to be okay?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Oh, Worthy? Oh, you know, they're doing a little inquiry committee with him.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sounds like an inquisition...!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Yep, well, we've had no end of trouble with the boy since last year...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean... the incident on Gourd Lake?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">It doesn't look good having one of our top people sitting in the defendant's seat. Now, you got someone else found guilty in that case, right, Wrighto?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>von Karma...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gant">A legend he was, undefeated in his forty year career! But in court you fixed it so he was caught for forging evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-wait! I didn't do anything wrong! He did forge evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Gant">In any case, the Prosecutor's Office is in a bit of turmoil, you might say. Why, they'd do just about anything to restore their reputation. Now, depending on what that inquiry committee decides... It could be bad for Worthy.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wh-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">It's downright odd, I tell you. I mean, it happened at exactly the same time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The murder at the Prosecutor's Office...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Scientifically speaking, it's impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Yes, but that's what the evidence is saying. "Goodman was stabbed in two locations at the same time!" That's what it says.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What evidence is this...?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Now, now, Wrighto, I can't give away all our secrets just like that! And this in particular, well it's a little sensitive... and I can't talk about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wasn't expecting much anyway.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gant">You know, one thing I hate most of all is hiding stuff. Secrets. Can't stand 'em! But you know... It's a full time job just keeping the Head Detective's trap shut!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah, he was the one you were picking on earlier?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Huh? You saw that? Whoops!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder what it was that he wanted the Head Detective to do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Let's see if we can kind of discreetly ask him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, I was wondering if I could ask you a favor?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Hmm? Well, I never thought the day would come when Wrighto asked me for help!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was wondering if we could investigate the evidence room?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Now, Wrighto...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-actually, I'm sorry, I d-don't need to investigate after all!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Wrighto, please, do I look like a selfish man?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Heck, if anyone asked me "sir, can I borrow $50?" I'd give them $50, no problem. So, go ahead! Investigate that room to your heart's content! Knock yourself out!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It just goes to show, you never know until you ask!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">And for you, here, you can borrow this.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh... hey! This is a detective's ID card, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">That's a special card for guests, so don't lose it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Y-yessir! It's an honor!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">You just run along and do your best, now. Later, folks!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was wondering, could you have a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Ah, sorry, Wrighto. I'm through with that stuff. Through, I say. Go find that guy who can't seem to sit still out there. The busy one...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The guy who can't sit still... does he mean Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Either him or the Dancing Blue Badger.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Heh heh! It looks pretty cool on my lapel, doesn't it? Just think, a real ID!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You seem... happy.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes, sir! Because, sir, we get to go into the evidence room now, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think this place is a bad influence on the girl.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The evidence room is beyond that door.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">And we have the ID card from Chief Gant! Let's just walk in! ... It won't open.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah hah! The card reader is turned off, see?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What is that security guard thinking?</line>
<line speaker="???">Howdy, pardners. Well, well, what's made my bambina's skies so gray?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Officer Marshall! <thought>Somehow, I knew...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">What's that "somehow I knew" look for? As you may have surmised, this here's my saloon.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um... we're here to investigate the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">... Yeehaw! That card you got there on your chest. That's better than a sheriff's badge in these parts.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Y-yeehaw?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Well, what ya standin' there for? Get along, little dogies. The crime scene's a waiting!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like the card reader's on again.</thought> While we're here, I was wondering if we could ask you some questions?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Sorry, cowboy, but I got no mind to tangle with you hombres.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're... busy, then?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Did I say that? I only said I didn't wish to speak with you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Actually, you said you had "no mind to tangle with us hombres."</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">A leather jacket, leather pants, and a leather...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Those aren't pants, those are chaps. And that's a poncho up there.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah hah! A poncho! It sure looks cool, but the name is a little silly.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This cactus sure is prickly. It must be real.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Best keep your distance from Billy there. You're liable to get hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Billy... The cactus has a name?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Billy, you're wearing your cowboy hat on your hand.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Ah, my rawhide cow skin 10-gallon hat! I just picked that up, but Billy took a fancy to it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like it got stuck on the thorns and he couldn't get it off.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">You sure have a lot of monitors in here!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">There's eight cameras in the evidence room in all. One for each section.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Which monitor shows the section where the crime took place?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Why do cattle sit before the rains come? It's not for man to know.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Unless you're the security guard responsible!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Look at this swinging door! Just like a wild west saloon!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Ah... Sorry, pardner, but we're closed for the day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Y'all get along home now!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I think Officer Marshall really wanted to be a wild west bartender.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I always wanted to say that.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Look, on the floor, it's a lasso.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... looks like it's set up to trap something.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I just roped me a steer with this here lasso.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">It was a' bellowing "moo, pal! moo!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Detective Gumshoe, I presume...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The evidence room is beyond that door.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I turned on the card reader. Go have yourself a ball, pardners!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">And I have the ID card! A real ID card!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Let's get this investigation started already...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um, I was wondering if we could talk to you...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Sorry, bambina. But I'm off to roam the lands, like a tumbleweed on the wide prairie. Like a gunslinger loading his six-shooter, I say a little prayer. GRROOOOORRK</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What was that all about, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think he was just too hungry to talk.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You're just saying that because his stomach was growling! You have no idea what he was talking about either!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, in any case, we need to get cracking on this investigation, pronto!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Officer Marshall, you're in charge of security for the evidence room, right?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">You got good eyes, pardner. It's an easy job, and I'm grateful for it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, Officer Meekins at the detention center told us.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Ah, that poor little dogie? Poor guy, I keep getting his name wrong and calling him "Meekly."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He told us something. He said that, when the stabbing occurred... you weren't at your station.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">... Well, maybe I shouldn't be telling you this... But since I got demoted from detective two years ago... Well, it might not look it, but I lost my fire for the job, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So... what were you doing around 5:15 when the murder took place?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Well... I reckon I was galloping down the highway on the back of my steed, Zippy.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Note: he was riding down the highway on his horse named "Zippy."</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">There's no need for people here, anyhow. These newfangled machines do a bang-up job of keeping an eye on the place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean the security camera system?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I don't take to machines much. Kinda like that stewed broccoli they sneak in next to your steak, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ms. Starr told us something... She said that you were a detective until two years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">It was always my dream to be a rawhide wrangler on the scene of the crime... That's all gone now... Like a drinking hole in a prairie fire.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You're still investigating the SL-9 Incident with Ms. Starr, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">That was my case... It's all "solved" on the record books. But it smells like a bad game of poker. I can't let it go... That's all there is to it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What kind of case was it, anyway? We've heard the name so many times, but no one tells us what actually happened.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">... There are some things you're better off not knowing, Bambina. Anyway, that case is officially dead as of two days ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Two days ago... the day of our case!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">That's right... The evidence transferals.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Edgeworth was talking about the transferals, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I know what maybe two of the machines in here do.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">O-only two of them? There must be a dozen!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Like I said, bambina, Me and machines, well... I like them about as much as I like stewed cauliflower with my steaks. The easiest ones to understand are these here security cameras.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Those are the ones that Officer Meekins mentioned.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">If nothing happens, the tapes are automatically erased every few hours.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">And Officer Meekins and Detective Goodman, are they on one of those tapes?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I reckon they might be.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You're the security guard and you "reckon"!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">One more thing. When you go into the evidence room... You need an ID card.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Thus the card reader by the door.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">The card reader leaves a record of every ID card passed through.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So this is the ID card record...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey! I've seen that somewhere before!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Sorry, Bambina. I can't show you more than that.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I haven't heard whether this is related to the case, yet.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! I saw a number on that record just now! I've seen that number before!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe there's some way I can prove that record is tied to the stabbing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but could you explain what this whole "transferal" thing is about?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">We keep only evidence from solved cases in this room. They're kept here under the presiding detective's supervision for two years. So we can re-investigate them if it turns out there was a mistake, see?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what happens to the evidence after two years?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">It goes to sleep forever in the underground vault at the Police Station. That's what we call "transferal." We do it every February.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I see now...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">"Transferal" is like a funeral for old cases. Two years after a case is solved... it's closed forever. Dead. Never to be reopened again. Never to be reinvestigated.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And that happened to SL-9 two days ago...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">See this? This is the victim's ID card.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Ah, the one that was on the ground in the parking lot?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The number on this is... "5842189."</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Officer Marshall! Show us the ID number on that ID card record! Look, the fourth number! It's a perfect match!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was used at... 5:14. Right before the stabbing!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">What's more, there's only one of them cards in the world!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, when the incident occurred, Detective Goodman was in the evidence room!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But wait, what did Officer Meekins say?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir, I entered the evidence room, and asked the man to display his ID card!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you asked Detective Goodman to show his ID card. What did he do?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">That's the thing! Suddenly he pointed a knife at me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If he had his ID card then... Why would he have pointed a knife at Officer Meekins?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Alright, compadre, you win. I guess I can give you this ID card record.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've got an idea... Maybe I should show this list to other people with IDs here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">......... That smell... Ah! Reminds me of Texas!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, Officer Marshall... You're from Texas?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">No, I just saw a special on television the other day. Is this from my baby?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Uh, yeah, Ms. Starr...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Wh-what's this!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What? What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">A filet steak lunch! I see... I see!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I don't see. I wonder what it means?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Alright, bambina. You win. Ask mmph mmph munch munch Anything mmph munch snack.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Finally, it seems like...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">He's willing to talk!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">The sheriffs back in the wild west didn't place much faith in evidence. About the only thing they trusted was their shooting hand.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um... this is neither "Wild" nor "West" here...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Ah hah! But that and this are two different things entirely!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">... I... guess so? Huh? I'm lost.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like we need some evidence to get anywhere with this guy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's quiet... the investigation must be over here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So this is the evidence room? It really is kind of like a graveyard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Graveyards are supposed to have grass and trees. This feels more like a morgue.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">N-nice try, M-Mr. Wright. Y-you can't scare me! Eeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whoooooah!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">S-sorry, I thought you were a ghost!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I wouldn't recommend going around smacking ghosts on the head, pal. So, is it true what I heard?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Wrighto, please, do I look like a selfish man? Heck, if anyone asked me "sir, can I borrow $50?" I'd give them $50, no problem. So, go ahead! Investigate that room to your heart's desire! Knock yourself out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, it's true.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So, Chief of Police Gant... will loan anyone 50 bucks? Even me!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, so that's what you were talking about...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Actually, I was put in charge of the investigation for today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just for today?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Boss for a day...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But guess what!? You got permission from the Chief... So now you're boss for a day!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gee, thanks...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">First of all, you'll want to have this.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's the door we just came in through.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like you don't need an ID card to get out.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I wonder what would happen if Officer Marshall cut the power while we were inside?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Let's hope he remembers we're in here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wow! Look at this big pile of junk in the corner!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That looks like... a car door.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's a pair of handcuffs attached to the frame.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe the guy they caught was some sort of escape artist and he got away.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, that's one of those human profiles for range testing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's been shot square in the forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Better him than us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's something sticking out of here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Looks like a shirt. I guess it must be evidence for some case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder if Detective Gumshoe put this here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There you go, pal, making me out to be some kinda slob! I'm not responsible for the evidence here. That said... I bet that evidence locker was opened recently.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">How do you know?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If you leave things hanging out like that, the evidence gets dirty or ripped. The guard checks on that kind of stuff and notifies the detective responsible. How many times have I had him breathing down my neck about some silly evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sounds like Detective Gumshoe leaves evidence hanging out a lot, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet he doesn't tuck in his shirt under that trench coat, either.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If you're going to talk behind someone's back, don't do it right in front of them, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This place is stuffed with evidence... stuffed with dreams.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not so sure about the dreams.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mmph! It won't open.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess I should have known.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal, our security is high-tech around here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Some sort of bulky equipment is gathering dust here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What a sorry looking fishing pole that is.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! That's my personal pole! I never did get around to using it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, I've seen that somewhere before...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Right, pal. That's that metal detector! The one that led to the solving of that case out on Gourd Lake, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right! Wow, that feels like it was ages ago. And... hmm, I don't think I've seen this one before.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, that! That's a radiolocator! I'm sure it will come in handy in solving some case sooner or later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That cheap-looking box?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You can't judge a person or a machine by their cover! You gotta look at their heart!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what's this...!? Blood!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's a little worn... but there's definitely a handprint here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like someone tried to wipe it off.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! What if there are other bloodstains left in the room!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We should use her testing fluid to check it out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wow, someone must have broken something big to make all these pieces.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There you go, pal, making me out to be some kind of hooligan! That's apparently from "the" case.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">"The" case?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The SL-9 Incident, pal. See the sticker on one of the pieces there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Another piece of SL-9 evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Let's not waste too much time with this now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">We can check it out later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder what shape these pieces were in before whatever it was broke?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You want to try to put it back together?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hah! Good luck, pal. That's no job for amateurs. Why, I spent a good three hours on that before I had to give up!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's why I always carry around a tube of glue!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, this piece looks like the bottom. Let's try putting the rest in place!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's no use. These pieces just don't add up to anything!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Maybe some of the pieces are missing? Let's just try to put as many of the pieces in place as we can!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... maybe I'll give it another shot later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">H-huh? Well, I think we did it. But some of the pieces are missing.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That only took me two minutes to do! The problem is finishing it!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Were some pieces stolen?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet they were missing to begin with.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Still... It doesn't look like the most stable kind of jar.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I kind of understand how it got broken.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you put these pieces together, it makes a jar.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There are two things that bother me. One: why are some of the pieces missing? Two: doesn't it seem a little unstable!? No wonder it broke!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll make sure to remember that next time I make a jar.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Look, this one's open! And there's a indicator tag stuck on it still!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That locker is coded with Detective Goodman's fingerprint.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Detective Goodman's locker!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Are you sure it's okay to leave it open like that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, it'd be hard to get it open again if we closed it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's empty... they must have taken the contents elsewhere.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Someone left a glove here... but only one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There you go, pal, making me out to be some kind of absent-minded detective! That's evidence from "the" case, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean SL-9? <thought>It does have a tag on it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">What is a saw and paint doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Since the dawn of time... True art has always been a war against oppression.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">True art...? I noticed that there's blue and yellow paint here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Perhaps we're witnessing the birthplace of the Blue Badger?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well... You might say this is my studio...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Here? In the evidence room!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, Detective Gumshoe, you're boss for the day?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's right! It's an honor! After all, the murder took place right here, in the Police Department!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But, if you're boss... why are you all alone!? Where are your underlings?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... They're using our findings from yesterday's investigation to prepare for the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>In other words, Detective Gumshoe got kicked out of the investigation again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm adamant, though! I'm going to take control and put this case to rest! And in my own evidence locker, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You have a locker in here, too, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hah hah, of course! I am a detective, after all. They gave me a locker that only I can open, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">"Only you can open"...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'll always believe in Mr. Edgeworth, no matter what happens.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So... Mr. Edgeworth is with the inquiry committee now, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">They're trying to figure out who's responsible for the mess-up in court today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I guess this is what you call "fate." Mr. Edgeworth just can't get away from that case...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That case...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, that case! The SL-9 Incident, of course! That was the beginning of the end for Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe we can get him to tell us more about the case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This place is more high-tech than you might think. Every locker is fixed so that only one detective can open it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Using this ID card?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, that's the thing, pal. ID cards can be lost. Why, I'm on my third card since entering the force already.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That sounds like a lot.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, but even I can't lose my own right hand!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">"Right hand"...? Oh! You mean, your fingerprint?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Exactly, pal! The lock for each locker is coded with a fingerprint! And that's the only locker we can open.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Funny, they look like normal lockers...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">These are the latest model! There's a trick to the handles, see?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The handles?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">On the other side of the handles is a sensor, and if the wrong person touches it...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Bzzzap! You get a shock!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If that's what happened, my hand would be black and smoking every day! In any case, the locks aren't that obvious. There's even some people in the force that don't know about the fingerprint locks!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Now that was a bloody, violent case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Violent... so it was a murder?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A serial killing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A serial killing... Maybe I don't want to get involved in this after all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But the killer made a mistake, and Mr. Edgeworth built his case around that to nab him.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">And this was two years ago?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That put Mr. Edgeworth right in the spotlight... and started the rumor mill.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Rumors... <thought>About forged evidence?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It was supposed to be all cleaned up with the "transferal" the other day. It was the last job he ever did... Detective Goodman, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Detective Goodman was the detective in charge of the SL-9 Incident, see.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, so... That switchblade knife...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim took the knife out of the evidence locker himself?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective... here's my attorney's badge.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You show this to me every time we meet, pal. Real men show their police badge. 'Nuff said!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I wish had a badge... Even an ID card would be nice...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's the victim, Detective Goodman's ID card. These days, everything's cards and secret numbers. I can never relax!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's only because you always lose your card.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I always forget my secret number, too. Scary, huh? My face should be ID enough! What's the world coming to!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Detective Gumshoe, rebel against the system.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, that's it! That's the "King of Prosecutors" award that Mr. Edgeworth got recently!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Were you at the awards ceremony, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course, pal! I got an award for diligence, myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... congratulations.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I was wondering, why is the award a shield? And... why is it broken?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, there's a reason. Erm... I'll tell you what it is later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Apparently, he's forgotten.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Found in Mr. Edgeworth's car, stabbed with Mr. Edgeworth's knife, huh... What would drive Chief Prosecutor Skye to do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">W-wait, I didn't mean... I mean, sure, of course someone else really did it! Someone who must have, um... Someone who must have a grudge against Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is my crowning achievement, my masterpiece, you might say. But... art is always misunderstood, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Art...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He was dancing proudly on the day of the awards ceremony... But there were a lot of people coming and going after the ceremony... So they took the Blue Badger away for a while!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, they said it was "shameful" or something like that. "Shameful"! I toiled night and day...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I sympathize with Detective Gumshoe... but I can see why they moved it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Detective Goodman's note... and that switchblade knife. I bet Edgeworth was the most surprised of anyone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because of the SL-9 connection?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That was Mr. Edgeworth's first big case you know, two years ago. That was the first time the world knew Edgeworth was a man to be feared!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, why would evidence from that case turn up now?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I guess it's not over, pal. Maybe there are some loose ends left on that case...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's the photo that Ms. Starr took.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anything you can tell us about it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That Ms. Starr is quite the lady. Why, I remember it was winter... I was 16. She was the only one who ever got me to talk about what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">16... that's how old I am now! I wonder what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if Detective Gumshoe wore a trench coat in high school, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you take a look at this? This is the ID card of the person who came here on the day of the stabbing.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah, I heard the rumors. So it was Goodman who came in here at the time of the murder... Whoooooooooah!!!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wh-what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Th-th-th-th-th-th! That second number...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not your ID number is it, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The second number on this list... belongs to Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What... Whaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why would Edgeworth have come to the evidence room!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You can't open the lockers if your fingerprint doesn't match. If you can open it... they'll give you 50 cents!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Note: the Police Department lacks faith in its lock system.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">After all, Detective Goodman was stabbed here after opening his locker... But at the same time he was found dead over at the Prosecutor's Office!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Allow me to say one thing, speaking as a detective. If I see a piece of evidence I know nothing about, I say nothing! Nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's... fine.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You bet it's fine, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...! Why am I getting a reaction here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no reason for the murderer to touch this spot if he fled out the door. <thought>This just might be something significant!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey... That's some pretty amazing stuff you got there, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What, this? It's called "Luminol Testing Fluid"!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Where'd you get your hands on that!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'd like to get some too! I'll just borrow 50 bucks from the Chief!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Where do you get this, Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I always buy it by mail order.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I'd better jot this down on the floor plans.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I knew it! This is someone's right handprint!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">WHAAAAAAT!!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's the matter, Detective? Th-this locker... It's mine!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's yours?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Please! You have to help me... When they come to take me away... Promise you'll testify that I wouldn't harm a fly! You'll do that for me, won't you, pals!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is an important clue! I'll jot it down on the floor plans...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm counting on you guys! Believe me, you can't trust the police!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What? But you're a detective!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There must have been a massive amount of blood here. <thought>I've never seen so much before...</thought> I'm not a professional. What's your opinion, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm... Pale blue blood... Maybe Detective Goodman... was actually an alien?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This proves that something really happened in front of this locker.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll make a note of it on the floor plans.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! If you didn't want my opinion, you shouldn't have asked!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The tag says, "SL-9 11." I guess this is another piece of evidence from that case.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You know, I never did care for the word, "tag." It's confusing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What's so confusing about that?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Do you know how many other words sound like it? "Bag," "Gag," "Nag," "Lag," "Xag"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Xag"...? Is that a word?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Do you challenge me...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What, are we playing a word game now?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, look here! It's hard to make out, but there's a dark red stain here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Looks like blood.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Do you think Detective Goodman's blood somehow got on it when he was stabbed?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not likely. This blood looks like it's been here for months, maybe longer. <thought>This jar was evidence in the SL-9 Incident... That might be when the blood got on it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh? This thing doesn't have a bottom!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's weird.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I wonder which side is "up"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Better yet... What's the purpose of a bottomless jar?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">... At least it doesn't collect dust inside, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal, look at the time!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was there something you needed to be going to?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's just that Mr. Edgeworth's inquiry committee should be letting out soon. I'm going to go give them my report for the day. It might help, you know...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">R-report? You mean the note written on the back of that flyer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The one that says nothing but "No problems"!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, it's Mr. Edgeworth we're talking about! I'm sure he can use a report like this. I believe in him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who needs enemies when you've got friends like Detective Gumshoe..</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm off, pal! Later!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should probably see what Edgeworth has to say, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A piece of white cloth is sticking out... looks like a shirt.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You'd better tidy it up or it will get wrinkled!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, don't look at me! I didn't leave it hanging out like that!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This place is stuffed with evidence... stuffed with dreams.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not so sure about the dreams.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mmph! It won't open.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess I should have known.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A pile of junk lies battered, worn and forsaken!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aren't you being a little dramatic? Looks like a fishing pole... and a metal detector. Not sure what this one is.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">They cast a withering gaze in our direction that screams, "dust me!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can't junk just be plain old junk?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Detective Goodman's evidence locker. It's empty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Only Detective Goodman himself can open this locker.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, the person who took out this knife had to have been Detective Goodman.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And why was it wrapped in the "scarf" muffler stuck inside the "car" muffler?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">That yellow crime scene tape! You know, yesterday was my first time seeing that! It was always my dream to push through the crowd and just step over the tape! It's a little daunting to encounter it again so soon!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think maybe you're overreacting a little...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's blue and yellow paint here. This is all I'd need to paint a portrait of you, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I am wearing a red necktie, you know...</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Ah, guests! My apologies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh! It's you!</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Have we met somewhere...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Mr. Edgeworth! I beg your leave. So long!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is Edgeworth here...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">There, standing by the window, a teacup in his hand!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, it's you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He has the hotel bring him tea service!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Edgeworth... you're back from the District Prosecutor's Office inquiry?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By the way, Detective Gumshoe was looking for you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh yes... He brought me some information, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Really? Was it helpful?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Apparently, a new French restaurant is opening near here. I think he was trying to console me, somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Er, I think the report is on the other side, Edgeworth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Poor Mr. Edgeworth... I think this whole thing is really taking a toll on him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, how did the inquiry committee go?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Actually, they decided to treat this not as a case of concealing evidence... But as a communications error during the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">"Concealing evidence"...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Apparently, there are some who believe... that I concealed evidence. They gave me a warning. "You were lucky this time... again."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Again"...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've heard them say that so many times. Ever since that case two years ago...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you okay for the trial tomorrow?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, I'm still the presiding prosecuting attorney. However...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something happened?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They gave control of the investigation over to the Police Department.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The Police Department!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Any further investigation for this case will be directed by the Chief of Police Gant. I can do nothing but wait for his results...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... see.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why, I ask you? Why!? All along, I've done only what I believe is right. I have nothing to be ashamed of! But still...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, I've never seen him this out of sorts...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The SL-9 Incident was a heinous serial killing case. The head of investigation was the Deputy Chief of Police at the time... Damon Gant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That wacky old coot was involved in the case two years ago too then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He was the best we had, and it was my first time working with him... I was nervous.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wow, you get nervous, too, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What I want to know is why was a Deputy Chief of Police on the investigation?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In truth, I used slightly more... extreme methods than normal. We were dealing with a vicious murderer. If I let him go, the blood would be on my hands. We won our guilty verdict, and the killer was executed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, you didn't...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course not! I didn't touch the evidence. Yes, I will do anything in my power to win a trial. However... I do have a code, and I follow it faithfully.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I know you. You've probably got a hold of some information already, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It all has to do with that case you were on... the SL-9 Incident. And some "dark suspicion" you were wrapped up in.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You are the man who revived the worst memory of my life, as I recall. I figured I'd be telling you about this sooner or later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A bad memory... he's talking about the murder in the elevator...</thought> Okay, Edgeworth. Why don't you tell me about it. Tell me the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right! I'd better check this now...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As I was saying, I...&#160;! What's this? A record of ID card usage?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth, you went into the evidence room that day, didn't you? Just before the incident occurred, no less.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">W-why, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please don't look at me like that. I was asked to go. By Chief Gant no less.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The Chief of Police...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He wanted evidence for a case that wrapped up half a year ago. He told me he wanted me to keep it here in the Prosecutor's Office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... it was solved, right? It would have to be if the evidence was already filed...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Chief is never one to explain himself. In any case, on the day of the stabbings, I brought this back here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Can I ask what kind of case it was?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I... can't say. It really has nothing to do with the current case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now I'm curious about this other case. I'd better make a note of it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Stubborn as always. I told you this has nothing to do with the current case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Wright, please. I'm the prosecutor on this case! You don't expect me to sit here and discuss the case with you over a cup of tea!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll pass on the tea. Just tell me about the case...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! Mr. Edgeworth just told you "no" in a very polite manner!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whose side are you on, anyway? Maybe if I just show him my best evidence I can get some reaction out of him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The tag says, "AI-16."</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What's that got to do with anything?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nothing, apparently. At least, that's what Edgeworth said.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hm. That makes it seem all the more suspicious. Who knows? This might turn out to be the clue that breaks the case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wouldn't that be nice...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">By the way, Ema. The Chief Prosecutor wanted to know something...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">M-my sister? What?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You still working on that scientific investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh? Y-yes! Of course! Why, just today Mr. Wright and I were using this...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Luminol testing fluid... Hm? Well then... You might have use for this.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Aluminum powder for taking fingerprints!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's been chemically treated for better adhesion.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">F-for me? Are you sure? We are the "enemy" you know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've no say in today's investigation... do as you will.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth... I'm really--</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No need to thank me. Here, take your powder and these fingerprint files for everyone involved.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, uh, th-thanks! <thought>How about giving these to Detective Gumshoe as well!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, let's get going! One last investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right! <thought>I do seem to remember seeing a suspicious handprint somewhere...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Our investigation turned up a suspicious handprint.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Here, in this blood on the detective's evidence locker.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's use the secret weapon we just borrowed!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Right. Let's get started! First... choose a finger.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A finger...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Each finger leaves behind a slightly different imprint. So let's choose the finger that will have left behind the clearest print!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I really can't tell the difference at a glance...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Quit procrastinating and choose a finger!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Okay. Now it's time to check for prints! Let me show you how it's done.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ema's starting to get that sparkle in her eyes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">First, we sprinkle the aluminum powder around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? How do you do that?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Just touch the screen... See?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... it looks like that did the trick.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The aluminum powder adheres completely to the print. Once the powder is well spread... just blow away the excess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? How do I do that?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You just blow With your breath. Imagine you're blowing out the candles on a birthday cake. See?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow... that looks like fun! <thought>It might take some getting used to though...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's fine! It won't go up your nose or anything. You just pour the powder on thick, and blow away the extra! Those are the basics of fingerprinting, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I'd better give it a try...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Aha! You did it! You found one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... this looks nothing like a fingerprint.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm... now that you mention it, I guess it doesn't...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What does it mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It think it means... we're out of luck.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Out of luck...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The person who left this handprint must have worn gloves.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Don't tell me we've been wasting out time here!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, calm down. That's just the way it goes sometimes with scientific investigations. But... it does seem a shame. While we're at it, why don't we look for other prints?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Other prints...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Looking at the locker door again closely...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">it seems like there are fingerprints outside the bloody handprint as well. Let's see if we can find a clear print!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... fingerprints outside the blood...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yay! A print so clear it's dazzling!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-dazzling...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Anyway, this print took a lot of effort to find. Let's match it up right away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So we're not over yet? This is quite a process...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, there's no point in finding a fingerprint... and not knowing who the owner is, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess she's right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Look at the fingerprint data we got from Mr. Edgeworth... and point out the person you think left these prints!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? How am I supposed to know who it was?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I could make a pretty good guess. The bloody handprint and the fingerprints are in different places right? That means that the prints probably don't have anything to do with our case. So, whose fingerprints would we most likely find on this evidence locker?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm... no match.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">C'mon! How am I supposed to guess whose they are?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Isn't it obvious? The bloody handprint and the fingerprints are in different places right? That means that the prints probably don't have anything to do with our case. They most likely belong to the owner of this evidence locker.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">S-something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was just thinking, if you're so sure who it is, why don't you match the fingerprints?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! I was doing this for your benefit, so you'd learn!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">F-fine, fine! <thought>Let me think... who could have left these prints...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah hah! So these prints belonged to Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Something wrong, Mr. Wright? You gave me this "so what?" look.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess that's probably because I was thinking "so what?"</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Okay, so we came up with nothing this time, but there's always next time! Sometimes you hit, sometimes you miss! You gotta roll with the punches, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks for the sympathy. <thought>Wait... If I remember correctly... there was one other handprint in this room. Let's check it out!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is where we got a luminol fluid reaction, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Right! There was a handprint here! Okay! Want to try using this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There go her eyes sparkling again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, let's not check.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What!?&#160;Why not!? Try my patience any longer and I'll dump this powder over your head!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... maybe I better check for those prints after all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, let's check for prints!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's the spirit! Oh! But I have to warn you about something first.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The area with the blood was wiped away, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We only ended up finding it using chemical means.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Any prints in that area will have been wiped away too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... right. So... that means no prints.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Would you say the probability of your hypothesis is high?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-don't ask me!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Anyway... We must try to find prints that weren't wiped away.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Prints other than the ones left by the bloody hand...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... I gave it my best shot.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That kind of result won't be any good for matching prints, will it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But it doesn't look like we'll get a clearer result from this print.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ok, let's try a different finger, then!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, these fingerprints, they...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Whose are they? Whose!? Is it someone I know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's Officer Marshall!!!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh? O-Officer Jake Marshall!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Th-that's got to be a coincidence! He's not involved in the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ema. This* <thought>[sic]</thought> are decidedly different from Detective Gumshoe's prints.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh... Oh!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So, we have Jake Marshall's fingerprints... on a wiped bloodstain!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">But why would Officer Marshall...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like our investigation is finally turning up some results!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess this is what you'd call "decisive evidence"!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I... I don't believe it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I'd like to try one of the other fingerprints.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Okay, let's move on to a different finger!</line>
</xml>