<xml>
<title>Rise from the Ashes</title>
<line speaker="Lana">How did the investigation go yesterday, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Frankly, there are still a lot of... gray areas.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Or rather, the whole thing is one big gray area...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Don't worry about me, no matter what the outcome. I'm ready to accept my fate.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I believe in you, sis.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Mr. Wright, let me offer you a word of advice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">A defense attorney should never "believe" their client.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...!</line>
<line speaker="Lana">The defendant is called to trial because they are suspected of wrongdoing! Never forget that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Skye, you... You remind me a lot of Mia. But there is one decisive difference between you and her.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">And that is?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're not a defense attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">... I believe it's almost time for the trial. Good luck, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>My first trial without a Fey helping me... No one's going to bail me out this time... I'll be alone in there... So I have to discover the truth all by myself!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Let's do it, Mr. Wright! I'll be with you the whole way!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court is now in session for the trial of Ms. Lana Skye.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution has been ready for a while, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Edgeworth... I haven't been in court since Edgeworth's trial... It's been a while now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I hope that personal feelings will not be a part of the proceedings today, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I will choose the path I think is right, regardless of what those around me might say. The judgment to be made here is in our hands, not those of anyone else.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Edgeworth, your opening statement please.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Chief Prosecutor Lana Skye has committed an unpardonable crime. Not only this, but she was rash enough to commit it in the Prosecutor's Office lot!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wow... He's much more forceful in person. I suddenly feel like confessing to everything!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, she will now pay for her rashness with her life. There was a witness to her crime... A "professional" witness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, call your first witness, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution calls its first witness, Ms. Angel Starr, to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The "Cough-up Queen"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm? Haven't I seen you somewhere...?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">You ordered the Caviar Lunch, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho! Caviar! I've never eaten caviar before!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The judge is really wolfing it down...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">Ah, and for you... I have a Fiesta Bowl.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Will the witness state her name and profession?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Ah, and you, sir... Did you order "The Fingerprint" lunchbox?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is too early for lunch. Your name and profession, please.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">... Well, Your Honor? How does it taste?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So this is why everyone raves about caviar! It's so tasty it hurts! I always thought caviar would taste like pickled tapioca.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What the heck does pickled tapioca taste like!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Name. Profession. Now.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Me? The name is Angel Starr. Don't go forgetting it. I find myself running Lunchland these days. Is... that what you wanted me to say, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very well, witness. Please describe the incident to us.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The prosecution will wait! I'm not finished eating...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hurry it up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mmmm... Very well, Mr. Edgeworth. As you know, we usually call on the police to provide a description of the crime...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Your Honor, as Mr. Edgeworth has said to the court... I am a... "professional."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... Huh? What exactly does that mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Until two years ago, Ms. Angel Starr was a special investigator with the police. She was a first-rate homicide detective.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wh-whaaaat!? Ms. Starr was a detective!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa-hah! I-I know who you are!!! Cough-up...!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Cough-up Queen Angel Starr, Your Honor. Long time no see.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">V-v-very well! Y-you may continue with the description, Ms. Starr!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just who is this lady!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">If I might have the court's attention over here... The parking lot at the Prosecutor's Office is divided into two blocks. A Block is for the Prosecutor's Office personnel. B Block is for visitors and clients... A chain divider separates the two blocks.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suppose that's to keep visitors from taking up prosecutor's spaces, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">The crime took place by a car in the back of A Block, in the car's trunk. The killer stabbed the victim with a knife and went to drive the body out. Unfortunately for her there was a witness, and an arrest was made on the spot.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And who was this valiant "witness"...?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Why, it was me, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, did you see the very moment of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Of course, Your Honor. Immediately after that, I apprehended the Chief Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It seems rather cut and dry, doesn't it? Well, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... I can't agree on principle, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">It seems that some poor losers are unwilling to accept the truth, Your Honor. Shall I proceed to crush what little hope they have remaining?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait, are they talking about me...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">Somehow, I always knew a day like this would come.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Bringing a lunchbox to your boyfriend? How touching!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. As you can see... There is no room for doubt.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The key "point" of your testimony seems to be nothing other than... the point of the knife which you saw being stabbed into Detective Goodman!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">So... how does it feel to be so utterly crushed?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I'm still thinking about that.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I-it's merely a flesh wound, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Wright. You may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Somehow, I always knew a day like this would come.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How did you know!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I respect the prosecutors' basic abhorrence of crime. Yet their methods are ugly and twisted. Twisted methods will always lead to tragedy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The lunchlady's uninformed opinion is duly noted.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Given that they are used to erasing inconvenient evidence at their whim... Killing off a detective that knew too much is merely an extension of that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ms. Starr... do you have something personal against prosecutors?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I felt that I had found my dream job when I became an investigator... And if I hadn't been laid off by those prosecutors over there, I'd still be one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Laid off...? <thought>She was fired...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">To me, prosecutors are nothing more than worms. That said, I am a pro, as you know. My testimony is unbiased... and flawless.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. You may continue, Ms. Starr.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I was on my way to deliver a lunchbox to my boyfriend...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This boyfriend... he's the detective?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Not that boyfriend. The security guard.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-"that" boyfriend? You have... several?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Yes. "This" boyfriend, "that" boyfriend, and "the other" boyfriend. Care to join? The "yet another" boyfriend position is still open for applicants.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I-I'll stick with the lunch, thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Note to self: the judge had to think before replying.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">The security guard room is in the lot, in A Block. It's up on the second level so you can see everything from there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That would be the room with the "SECURITY" sign.</thought> Incidentally, did you bring your lunchboxes by car?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Since I'm a visitor now, I parked in B Block.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So... she was in B Block when she witnessed the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">When I sensed something... perhaps it was my finely-honed detective instincts working.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You "sensed" something? So, you're saying you had a premonition of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">It felt like... how would you say... Oh yes... It was like the feeling you get when you view a pumpkin chock full of seeds!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I have no idea what that means.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Speaking of a "detective's instincts"... Wasn't the victim, Mr. Bruce Goodman, also a detective?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Yes, well, he was like a young cheese.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A... young cheese?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">A pale white cheese, not yet tangy with experience on the streets. A greenhorn.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I, of course, am hard, yellowed, sharp as a tack.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I bet you stink, too.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">In any case, there, in the lot, I felt something stirring in the back of my mind...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Then, through a wire fence, I saw the chief prosecutor standing next to a garish car.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By "garish car," you mean...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Mr. Edgeworth's car, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Edgeworth's!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Incidentally, the knife with which the victim was stabbed was also Mr. Edgeworth's. Wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Indeed, it was.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm! What an odd case this is. And the person you saw... you are sure it was the defendant?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I saw her from no further than thirty feet away. I am certain it was her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If she's telling the truth, we're doomed!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Let's just do what we can! Even if we don't have any proof, we can always complain!* <thought>Let's just do what we can! Even if we don't have any proof, we can always nitpick! in the Trilogy release</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We're dealing with Edgeworth here... I need better material before I start pressing this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Can you tell us what the suspect was doing when you saw her?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Witness! In your testimony, you clearly stated the following: Prosecutors are nothing more than worms. Ergo! You are a biased witness!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">You might want to keep those silly opinions to YOURSELF in the future, rookie.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Rookie?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Unless you're willing to risk the consequences of doubting me? I'll fry you like a fritter! Crispy on the outside... chewy on the inside!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That... That was inspiring!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I believe I've heard that tag line elsewhere... you could cry plagiarism?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I may be relegated to the lowly post of lunchlady... But my instincts are honed!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-a photograph! You took this!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">The moment I witnessed the crime, my reflexes took over and snap! I took a picture. In fact... One of my lunchboxes is rigged with a camera.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I suppose that's more exciting than just hanging it around your neck.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Er... this is my first time seeing this photograph.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">You think I'd show it to you, a prosecutor? Think again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">My boyfriend works in the photography division of Criminal Affairs.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... This is most certainly the defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh, that is unmistakably Lana Skye!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, what was the defendant doing at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">The chief prosecutor was holding a knife in her right hand....</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me more about this knife that the suspect was carrying.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Well, I'd say the blade was about 10 centimeters long. Is that right, Mr. Edgeworth? It is your knife, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Er... Ahem, yes, that's about right.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Prosecutors are, by nature, well-versed in the location of a man's vital organs. I'm sure it was easier than boiling an egg for my egg salad surprise set.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-you can't testify as to her ability to kill an egg! I mean, a person!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Hmm? Perhaps a chicken salad set would have been a better metaphor?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, the defendant was holding a knife. What then?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And you witnessed this? You saw Ms. Skye stab the victim with the knife?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">As I've already said, yes! I swear it on my finest "Salmon Swirl" lunch!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm!!! I'm sure that is a fine lunch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... isn't that odd? Look at this photograph! This is the photograph you took of the very moment of the crime, is it not? Then why is Ms. Skye not holding a knife!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Ahem. Mr. Edgeworth, your thoughts?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Objection.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's be a little more careful with our evidence, shall we?* <thought>That had to be the weakest objection ever, Edgeworth. in the Trilogy release</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is you that needs to be more careful, Mr. Wright!* <thought>Yet, it was still stronger than your ever feeble mind, Mr. Wright. in the Trilogy release</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This photograph was not taken the moment before the stabbing... This was taken the moment AFTER the stabbing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-how can you tell that!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Blood splatter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">See the dark crimson stain on the Chief Prosecutor's coat?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's a black-and-white photograph!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah... yes, it's hard to tell, but this could be blood.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, Mr. Wright? I see no problem here. No problem... except you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! Are you going to just sit there and take that kind of abuse!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh... You got a better idea?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now that you mention it, I see no problem here. Other than myself.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">M-Mr. Wright! You can't just let him walk all over you! Th-that's just sad!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Feeling sad, Mr. Wright? Perhaps a special "Lover's Lunchbox" would cheer you up?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, that was a waste of time. Let's continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Perhaps I should have dug a little deeper...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait! That contradicts what the witness said in her testimony! Namely, that she took the picture the "moment" she witnessed the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Well, it seems I was slightly unclear. My apologies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-that's it!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">If you run out of lunch, you order seconds. Problem solved! If you don't like it, try ordering the jumbo sized lunch from the get-go!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Good advice. I'm not sure I understood it, but... good advice.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I didn't have time to stop her. Prosecutor Skye was cold, calculating, like a robot. She killed without pain or remorse! It was a premeditated murder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-premeditated!? How do you know!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Look at the chief prosecutor's hands in that photograph.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well...! Are those... gloves?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Surgical gloves made of thin rubber, most likely. Why would she have those on?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If it was not premeditated, she would not be wearing those gloves!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Waaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">These gloves do seem to tell a tale of premeditation!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Premeditated murder... a serious offense.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! Add this to your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Change statements">"The chief prosecutor was holding a knife in her right hand...." and "Then, she thrust the pointy tip of the knife into Detective Goodman's chest!" to "The murder was planned! The rubber gloves prove it!"</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Then, she thrust the pointy tip of the knife into Detective Goodman's chest!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell the court why you didn't try to stop this crime! You did see her raise the knife to strike, no?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... The defense has a point.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Unfortunately, by the time I realized what was going on, it was already too late.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Too late...?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Yes... the next moment... The chief prosecutor brought down the murder weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And you witnessed this? You saw Ms. Skye stab the victim with the knife?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">As I've already said, yes! I swear it on my finest "Salmon Swirl" lunch!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm!!! I'm sure that is a fine lunch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... isn't that odd? Look at this photograph! This is the photograph you took of the very moment of the crime, is it not? Then why is Ms. Skye not holding a knife!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Ahem. Mr. Edgeworth, your thoughts?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Objection.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's be a little more careful with our evidence, shall we?* <thought>That had to be the weakest objection ever, Edgeworth. in the Trilogy release</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is you that needs to be more careful, Mr. Wright!* <thought>Yet, it was still stronger than your ever feeble mind, Mr. Wright. in the Trilogy release</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This photograph was not taken the moment before the stabbing... This was taken the moment AFTER the stabbing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-how can you tell that!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Blood splatter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">See the dark crimson stain on the Chief Prosecutor's coat?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's a black-and-white photograph!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah... yes, it's hard to tell, but this could be blood.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, Mr. Wright? I see no problem here. No problem... except you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! Are you going to just sit there and take that kind of abuse!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh... You got a better idea?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now that you mention it, I see no problem here. Other than myself.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">M-Mr. Wright! You can't just let him walk all over you! Th-that's just sad!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Feeling sad, Mr. Wright? Perhaps a special "Lover's Lunchbox" would cheer you up?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, that was a waste of time. Let's continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Perhaps I should have dug a little deeper...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait! That contradicts what the witness said in her testimony! Namely, that she took the picture the "moment" she witnessed the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Well, it seems I was slightly unclear. My apologies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-that's it!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">If you run out of lunch, you order seconds. Problem solved! If you don't like it, try ordering the jumbo sized lunch from the get-go!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Good advice. I'm not sure I understood it, but... good advice.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I didn't have time to stop her. Prosecutor Skye was cold, calculating, like a robot. She killed without pain or remorse! It was a premeditated murder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-premeditated!? How do you know!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Look at the chief prosecutor's hands in that photograph.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well...! Are those... gloves?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Surgical gloves made of thin rubber, most likely. Why would she have those on?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If it was not premeditated, she would not be wearing those gloves!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Waaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">These gloves do seem to tell a tale of premeditation!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Premeditated murder... a serious offense.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! Add this to your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Change statements">"The chief prosecutor was holding a knife in her right hand...." and "Then, she thrust the pointy tip of the knife into Detective Goodman's chest!" to "The murder was planned! The rubber gloves prove it!"</line>
<line speaker="Angel">The murder was planned! The rubber gloves prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What if she was just in the habit of wearing gloves? Like, driving gloves?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The gloves were admitted as evidence when the defendant was arrested! They were rubber gloves, of the kind used for autopsies!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">In other words, when the chief prosecutor came to the crime scene... She came to do murder! It's the only possible conclusion one can make. Everything was planned, it was a premeditated crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arrrrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Impressive! I'm sorry they took you off the force, Ms. Starr!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is bad... She's got them thinking this was all planned... If she can prove this claim, the trial's already over! I've got to think of a way to show that this wasn't premeditated!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I-it's only a flesh wound, Mr. Wright! We can make it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You said that before. Anything else?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Scientifically speaking... Ms. Starr's testimony... is flawless.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds pretty fatal to me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wh-what do we do!? Is this it? Is my sister guilty!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's just keep our heads cool and press the witness a bit, shall we? <thought>For some reason, having her panicking next to me makes me calmer...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">D-don't smile like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Witness, do you know what this is?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Are you trying to test me? I sell box lunches for a living, you know. That's a knife. THE knife. The knife that was in Mr. Edgeworth's trunk!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed, it is my knife.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense has a request. We ask that the witness provide an ACCURATE testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">What's that, Rookie?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In your testimony... You stated that Lana Skye planned this murder. And that's why she was wearing those special gloves.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Seems like a natural conclusion to me! The gloves do indicate planning...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However! Why would she not also prepare the most important thing... the murder weapon!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This knife just happened to be in the trunk of that car. Ladies and gentlemen, if you're going to plan a murder, you don't forget the weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Ugh... Woooooooorrrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great! Now the tide is turning in our favor!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Great show, Mr. Wright! My sister's as good as free!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright. I believe the next lunch you'll be eating is... humble pie!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I hope you weren't deluding yourself into thinking that the "tide has turned." Not over such a trifling detail!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-but this shoots a hole in the whole premeditated theory!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Bah! The prosecution could care less if it was premeditated or not. The only one who seems to care is that lunchlady over there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The defendant, Lana Skye, murdered a detective with a knife. That is the only thing the prosecution need prove. Nothing else.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Very good, Mr. Prosecutor... I suppose you think you're clever now? But you know as well as I do that she planned on killing him! It was planned! If it wasn't, why would she have been wearing...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe I'd like to hear your testimony again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Witness, please tell us only what you "saw," not what you "thought."</line>
<line speaker="Angel">How dare you! My powers of deduction are not to be underestimated!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Really now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">Lana Skye intended to murder Detective Goodman!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The victim was summoned from the Police Department to the Prosecutor's Office.. It does sound a lot like premeditation, doesn't it!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, if I order pizza, does that mean I'm planning to kill the delivery boy?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In any case, the defense may now cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Lana Skye intended to murder Detective Goodman!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've said that, but you haven't told us how you know!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">That's what I'm about to tell you, Rookie!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe what she just said was a mere prelude to the story she is about to tell. Try not to interrupt her again.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Rookie... Never interrupt a storyteller! It's like pulling a bun out of the oven half-baked!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something's half-baked here alright, and it's you!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Try not to confuse the defense, witness. They're not very quick on their feet. Now, why did you believe the suspect had intentions to murder the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Her actions speak for themselves!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">That's why she called the victim all the way to the Prosecutor's Office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You have no proof that Ms. Skye called him there!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">You have no proof that she didn't!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Mr. Edgeworth, thoughts?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is no record of a call mad on the defendant, Ms. Lana Skye's phone.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">She might have written him a letter!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>C'mon! You could have tried "public phone" first, at least!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In any case, the victim came to the Prosecutor's Office, where he was murdered.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sure he had a reason to be there. Witness? Why do you think it was the suspect who summoned the victim that day?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I'm sure the Chief Prosecutor had a grudge against the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What kind of "grudge"!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Well, I wouldn't know that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course you don't! That's because she didn't have a grudge!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Rookie... I have a lunchbox here. Now... what's inside?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-how am I supposed to know!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">See? We agree there is a lunchbox here, but we don't know what's inside! A person's life is like a lunchbox with pretzels. Don't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I get it! That's why my lunch was so salty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This judge isn't very good with metaphors...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The suspect had a grudge against Detective Goodman. Will you tell us your basis for thinking this?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">It's simple...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Nothing else could drive that human machine to plunge the knife in again and again...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A "human machine"!? That's a contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please... Can't you find fault with something of substance, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Note to self: Mr. Edgeworth's sighs smell like citrus fruit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... You say "again and again"... how many times did she stab him, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">We often say "chop into a thousand pieces," but we don't actually mean 1,000 pieces. What difference does it make if the deed is done!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How come she's getting mad at me!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's just say she stabbed him several times and leave it at that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Leave it at that!? This is a murder case, people!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright, you should speak up if you have an objection, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You say she stabbed him again and again... But you couldn't have witnessed that!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Are you testing me...? Then I'll test you! With my Moss Surprise!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm afraid the moss is growing under our feet as we wait, Ms. Starr.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">...!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I shouldn't have to explain this... But, take a look. The autopsy report states that death was due to a loss of blood... from one stab wound.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah hah! You're right! Good show, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What a hunk! He's my hero, really.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What about my objection? No one noticed?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">You got the Crime Scene Set, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... oh, thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I always believed that no one could ever mistake ketchup for blood.... But now, I realize that such mistakes are possible.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So... You're saying you mistook something... for blood?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">When she lifted her knife, I thought I saw blood at her breast... Splattered blood from her victim! That's why I thought she must have stabbed him at least twice.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then tell us what you saw that you thought was blood! Testify!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">...</line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"Nothing else could drive that human machine to plunge the knife in again and again..." to "Her red muffler looked like blood to me... that's how ghastly the whole scene was."</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Her red muffler looked like blood to me... that's how ghastly the whole scene was.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Her red muffler?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Yes, like a scarf. The Chief Prosecutor always wears one around her neck. So she can be easily hanged at a moment's notice, I suppose...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's right... Ms. Skye was wearing a red scarf... wasn't she?</thought> But wait... Isn't it odd that you mistook that for splattered blood?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, people often mistake my beard... For a bib.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A judge with a bib. That's why this place feels so much like kindergarten sometimes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">Actually... I do think I saw some traces of blood on her chest...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, the autopsy report is clear on this matter. There was only one knife wound.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Apparently, Ms. Starr isn't entirely sure of her own testimony.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! This is our chance!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Chance for what, I wonder...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ms. Starr has turned out to be as short-tempered as she looked when we met her. Challenging her abilities as a detective really set her off!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">The short wick burns out the fastest! It's a scientific fact!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder... wouldn't it depend on the size of the candle? I mean, add more wax and even a really short wick will burn longer...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...&#160;Obviously, more scientific testing is required!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Starr! I demand an explanation...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The witness is clearly not suited for detective work.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">W-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The suspect was not wearing a scarf or muffler of any kind when she stabbed the victim. And you've proved it yourself! With this photograph!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Huh? B-but that... That can't be!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Only a true professional could be so clueless. I'm sure you'll make a good lunchlady, have no fear.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm! Harsh words! But good!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">In the end, Mr. Edgeworth prevails!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What was my objection, chopped liver!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">B-but it was there, a scarf, no, not that, but something red! Really!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well now, where were we? The witness has given us an entertaining interlude, now back to business.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Wh-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, witness, continue your testimony. You saw the crime, and apprehended the suspect... Tell us about that.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">...... Very well. I do remember some things accurately, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ultimately, we couldn't shake the most important part of her testimony.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">The most important part...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The part where your sister stabs the victim! <thought>This next testimony might just be the moment of truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">After the murder, the suspect attempted to run behind a partition off to her side.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You are quite determined about this scarf, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I strike like a snake and bite like a cobra! That's me. Angel Starr.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That wasn't a very good metaphor. First of all, a cobra is a kind of snake.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Don't bother me with details, unless you want to get bitten!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Note to self: Attorney Wright gets bitten by snake.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">The chief prosecutor tried to resist, but her efforts were in vain. She knocked my hands aside, kicked over an oil drum...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-oil drum? <thought>Hard to imagine...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">Oh, she's beautiful, but deadly! A predator, this one! A leopard woman! Rowr!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Wright. Your cross-examination, if you will.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">After the murder, the suspect attempted to run behind a partition off to her side.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So where is this "partition" on the floor plans?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sure she means this wall next to the car.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's right... There was a wall there... about 6 feet high.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">She was obviously trying to hide herself. Quite a natural thing for a criminal to do!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what did you do then?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I quickly caught her, explained her rights to her, and arrested her on the spot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You say "quickly"... were you close to the suspect?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">As I just said! I was only 30 feet away from her the whole time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... maybe I should press her for more details?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How far away was she when she witnessed the murder? I guess I could just look at the picture to find out.</thought> Very well, you may continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd like to see this on the floor plans, just to be safe. The Lunchland car was...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">She was a "visitor," thus, she was parked in B Block.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you witnessed the murder from... here?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That would make it about 30 feet from the car, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that correct, Ms. Starr?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Y-yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But, there was a chain link fence in front of you...?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I went over it, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Amazing! The Cough-up Queen, lunchlady athlete, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It would have taken her a little time to climb over the fence. So she couldn't have gotten to my sister THAT fast...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, that fence was about nine feet high, too. How come Ms. Skye didn't get away?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">Ah, yes. When I arrested her, she mentioned the muffler!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She mentioned the muffler? What exactly did she say?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">If I remembered exactly I would have told you in my testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Cheeky!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">Anyway, all I heard her say was the word "muffler."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Just that one word?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So... what you heard wasn't the suspect talking to you, but to someone else?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Yes. The chief prospector was talking on her phone!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Her phone? You mean... this cell phone?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ms. Skye's cell phone... The last number she called was her sister, Ema! Hmm... if I press this too hard, who knows who the snake will bite...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The witness may continue with her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By phone... do you mean this cell phone, discovered at the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Yes, ultimately.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ultimately?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">My memory... it's like a salmon, heading upstream, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">N-no, the court doesn't see, Ms. Starr.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">The chief prosecutor first attempted to use the phone hanging on the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">On the wall?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's right! Near the car... there was an emergency phone on the wall!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">Apparently, it was out of order.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And so she used her cell phone?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed, the emergency phone was out of order that day.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Good witnessing, witness!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Good witnessing? What ever happened to good testifying?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You should of course add this to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">The things I do to please this rookie defense attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"That's what had me confused in my earlier testimony!" to "She gave up trying to use the phone on the wall and just used her cell phone!"</line>
<line speaker="Angel">That's what had me confused in my earlier testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you never saw this muffler?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As the photograph proves, she couldn't have seen it.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">... That's true.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ms. Starr... is acting strangely. First she mistakes a scarf for splattered blood... And now she says she didn't see any scarf!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She doesn't strike me as the kind of witness to make careless mistakes, either... I'm sure she saw something red... but what!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">She gave up trying to use the phone on the wall and just used her cell phone!* <thought>I saw it all -- how she tried the phone on the wall but had to use her cell instead. in the Trilogy release</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... do you think you could restate your testimony for the court?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah hah! I was going to ask the same thing!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I'll only say this one time, so listen close, Rookies. The chief prosecutor stabbed the victim, and ran behind the partition. Then she picked up the emergency phone on the wall, but it was out of order. So she pulled her own cell phone out of her pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And during that time, you climbed over the chain link fence...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Then, when I boldly grabbed her arm... The chief prosecutor hung up her phone!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And you saw her doing this?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...? What is it, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Angel">The chief prosecutor made to escape, but against Angel Starr, resistance is futile!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She "made to escape"... Can you be more specific?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">She brushed aside my hand and ran! It was a terrible sight to see, like a dollop of lard on a pate of foie gras!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">She even kicked over an oil drum at me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-an oil drum!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There was an oil drum lying on its side at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But, it's strange...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If she wanted to escape... why didn't she run the other way?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The other... ah! The car entrance!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Th-that's right! It doesn't make any sense that she would run from behind the partition to the oil drums!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Excellent! More mysteries!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wish we could solve a few before finding more, though...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So Ms. Skye tried to run?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm sorry my sister is so suspicious, Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not as sorry as I am.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But she didn't do it! You have to believe me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have to conclude that you have a personal grudge against Ms. Lana Skye.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The witness is a former detective. Her testimony is unmarred by personal bias.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Well, who would have thought you would be my knight in shining armor, prosecutor? You who, together with the chief prosecutor, kicked me out two years ago!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Ms. Starr... This is a fatal contradiction with your testimony... How do you explain this?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Hmph! I don't know what you're talking about. Mess with me... and I'll make you cough it ALL up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ahem. Let's look at the floor plans. You said you witnessed the crime from this point. However, if that's true... You couldn't possibly have seen Ms. Skye making that phone call!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe you see what I'm getting at. That emergency phone was on the back side of this partition. If, indeed, you were in B Block... You couldn't have seen it!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Wha... Waaaaaaaaaaarrrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! What is the meaning of this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's simple, Your Honor. She's not coughing up lunch...&#160; she's coughing up lies!!!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Grrr!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's quite a claim, Mr. Wright... perhaps you will allow me a question? Tell us exactly what lie this witness has told the court!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Here's where the counterattack begins! I can't afford to get this wrong!</thought> The witness lied about...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She lied about what she saw! In other words, she didn't see Ms. Skye using that emergency phone!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It does seem hard to imagine how she could have! Very logical!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's the matter, Starr? Cat got your lunchbox?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um, Mr. Wright... I hate to bother you while you're celebrating your victory... But why would Ms. Starr lie like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Why would she say that my sister had tried to use the phone, but failed? It doesn't make any sense! Why lie about something so insignificant?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... <thought>Dang, she's right!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I mean, maybe she really did see her try to use the emergency phone.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see no room for doubt here.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">You ordered the P'tooey on rice, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! And I thought you had something there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh. <thought>One... one more try!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. I see it in your eyes. You haven't learned your lesson, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She lied about the order of events! Ms. Skye used that emergency phone BEFORE the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I see! I hadn't thought of that!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That took the wind out of her sails!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um, Mr. Wright... I hate to bother you while you're celebrating your victory... But... why would anyone use the emergency phone before the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just when you think he can't sink any lower, he amazes us. I applaud you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">You ordered the Orange-peel Lunchbox, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I guess that teaches me to not get excited BEFORE the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh. <thought>One... one more try!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. I see it in your eyes. You haven't learned your lesson, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She tried to use the emergency phone... but it was out of order. What is significant about this fact? Nothing. It would be pointless for her to lie about it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Pointless to lie... I see!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness did actually see Ms. Skye using the emergency phone. In other words... Ms. Starr witnessed the crime from a different location!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A different location!? Now that's a pointless lie if I ever heard one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Before you call my lie pointless... at least let me tell it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let me ask a question to our clever wordsmith, Mr. Wright. Just where was the witness when she saw the crime!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All the testimony we've heard until now points in one direction...</thought> The place from where Ms. Starr witnessed this crime was... here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If she was here, she could see the emergency phone!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-that's true! That solves the mystery!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That would allow her to see the emergency phone, yes... But if she was there... She would have been able to arrest her well before she dialed her cell phone!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">You doubt my speed? I can run 150 feet in nine seconds, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is that really that fast?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not as fast as your witty rejoinders!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... uh, yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think! I mean, it's highly likely that's where she was.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">You "think"?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's "highly likely"?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Your cavalier attitude stands in stark contrast to your feeble argument, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Her being there wouldn't change a thing!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please, Mr. Wright, think before you speak.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... uh, yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the only place where she could have been.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The security guard room?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed, the security room in the underground parking lot is well positioned... It's built on the second level, so you can see the entire lot.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... She would have been able to see the emergency phone from there. But why there? There are many other places where she could have seen the phone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not in this case, Your Honor. The witness, not being part of the Prosecutor's Office, couldn't park in A Block. The only place where she could have seen the crime and the back of the partition is here. I remember in your testimony, you said... You brought a lunch to your&#160;"boyfriend" in the security guard room, yes? Well, Ms. Starr?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">... How many years have I been getting the better of men...? To think that the tables could be turned... Today, a man has got the better of Angel Starr!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Witness! What have you done!? You used to be a detective! You should know better!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I'm not turning back. The guilty will be punished. And I'll do what I must to make sure justice prevails.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The guilty... is she talking about Ms. Skye...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um, Mr. Wright? Doesn't this strike you as odd? Why did Ms. Starr lie? It doesn't make sense!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">She could have just said she saw the crime from the security guard station. It wouldn't change anything!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Exactly! This photograph tells all! It was the defendant who stabbed the victim! That truth still stands!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It "still stands"? I disagree, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If a witness is found to be lying, they're guilty of perjury. She knows this. She wouldn't risk that without a good reason!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, tell us what her reason was, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Huh? M-me?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who else!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! Let's review what we know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ms. Starr witnessed the crime from the security guard station... But she lied and said she saw it from B Block... It must make a vital difference... but what? What would change...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why, the angle at which she saw the crime occur would change!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The angle...? What do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, um, well... The security guard station is on the second floor... and um... She would have sort of a more 3-D view of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And this is important... why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps you'd like to reconsider, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a difference in lighting!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Lighting...? What does that mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it means, uh... See, the security guard station is on the second level... So, uh, she would have seen the crime in better lighting conditions.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And this is important... why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps you'd like to reconsider, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It changes the distance between her and the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">My condolences, Mr. Wright... But one look at the floor plans and it's quite clear. The distance between the scene of the crime and the guard station is 30 feet. I don't see how that would change what she could see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What she saw is not in question here. What matters is the time it would take her to reach the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Starr! You witnessed the crime from the security guard station! Now, how long did it take you to go from there... to the scene of the crime, where you arrested Ms. Skye!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">You...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">You ordered the Squid Wheels, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The quality of my lunches has gone from low to inedible.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">I was bringing a PB&amp;J lunch with fresh boysenberry jam to my boyfriend.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Boysenberry for the boyfriend!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">He wasn't in the station, so I waited. I witnessed the crime from the glass-walled station... and before I knew what I was doing, I found myself running towards the scene. But... the door was locked. I couldn't open it. That's why I had to go through the visitor's parking in B Block.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's quite a detour.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">It probably took me at least five minutes to get to the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">F-f-f-five minutes!? Hmm... This changes things considerably!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">But, it was that woman over there in the defendant's chair who stabbed him! I know it! I have photographic evidence! I swear it... I swear it on my finest plastic spork!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You have a point. And the spork is a wonderful invention.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Would you like another Caviar Lunch...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Absolutely!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! You have to do something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Do I have any evidence to stop this...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I need more evidence before I go sticking my spork in this mess...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Woo! Caviar! Ah... how it makes my eyes tingle!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! No evidence can win against the raw power of caviar! It's a scientific fact! The only thing that's left... Is your strong presence and deft powers of deduction!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Let's screw the lid back on those overpriced fish eggs!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Five minutes between the witnessing of the murder and the arrest! Think about it! You could make pasta in that amount of time! If you like it al dente!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I've got lunchboxes that tie pasta into knots, Rookie!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A five minute "blank"... Isn't that strange!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Strange...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you were a criminal... What would you do with five minutes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, um... I guess I'd flee the scene. Hey! D-don't get the wrong idea! I didn't kill anyone...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you have the instincts of a killer! You would run! But this time was different! Ms. Skye dawdled at the scene of the crime... she even had her picture taken! No true criminal would act this way! It's inconceivable!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Y- yeeeaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then. It seems we've come to the end of this testimony. She has a grudge against the defendant, and there is a blank in her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth, is the next witness ready to go?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unfortunately... I appear to have overestimated this witness on account of her professional history...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">We did it! We screwed that can shut, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Th-that was too close!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid that the Cough-up Queen has been dethroned. And with that, court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Mr. Edgeworth, you ordered the Squid Wheels, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's the one she tried to foist off on me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I prefer to not take the defense team's leftovers. Anything else to say?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I... might be able to save you. I have decisive evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what was that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is this another one of her trick lunchboxes!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">My apologies, but we have no further questions to ask of you, Ms. Starr.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Ah... Is this your jumbo lunchbox?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whoo hoo! A triple-decker! Out of deference to the witness's determination, I'll allow one more testimony! Let's hear about this decisive evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Like the Lunchland motto says, you won't be disappointed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's she going to pull out of her lunchbox this time!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">I should have mentioned those five minutes when I wasn't looking at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what!? There was blood found on that shoe!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Try Lunchland, for all your lunch and decisive evidence needs!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Witness, what's the meaning of this? Why is this the first time I've heard of this evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Simple. As I've already said... I don't trust you with evidence, Mr. Edgeworth! That's why I took the liberty of investigating this myself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And... you had blood tests performed?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Didn't I mention? I have three boyfriends in forensics.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In any case, Your Honor, I can't accept this as evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You should know the two rules of evidence law, Ms. Starr! Rule 1: no evidence shall be shown without the approval of the Police Department! In other words, this shoe is illegal evidence! At least, for the time being!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I-is that right, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seems so. Edgeworth sure is celebrating.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Not so fast, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Don't forget... I used to be a detective! As I mentioned previously... This shoe has already been tested by a member of the forensics department! As you can see, it was approved by the Police Department as of... today. Even the general public can produce official evidence, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nuh... Ungh!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I-is that right, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seems so. Edgeworth is looking pretty sullen.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You could at least study some evidence law! Really!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The prosecution's complaints notwithstanding... It appears that this evidence satisfies the first rule of evidence law. Well... It seems you have yet another count against you, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Anything to ensure that the guilty are properly judged.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Wright, you may cross-examine the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This blood... It's my sister's, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It appears so. <thought>Lana's right hand was bandaged when I saw her in jail. She must have cut herself at the time of the crime...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Poor Sis...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">AAAH! There's blood here too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the sole of the shoe? It's got to be the victim's. He must have stepped in a puddle of his own blood.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">All this blood... It's horrible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... This blood might be an important clue...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">I should have mentioned those five minutes when I wasn't looking at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did you lie about those five minutes?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I guess you could say, I just wanted people to look at the results.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The... results?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">How many times do I have to say this? I saw the chief prosecutor stab the victim before my very own eyes! Compared to that... A five minute "blank" means nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then why didn't you just tell the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Don't make me laugh! We're dealing with the most untrustworthy of the vile lot known as prosecutors! Falsified evidence, arranged testimonies, erasing and manipulating evidence... When you fight monsters, you need to use every trick in the book!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This when the suspect is admitting she did it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">False testimony is the most despicable crime of all, Ms. Starr. Let's just get this over with.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">And now, to the matter of the victim's shoe... Did I not bring this up...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And, you found this shoe at the scene of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I detained the chief prosecutor, and notified the Police Department... I wanted to make myself useful while I was waiting for the police to arrive.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, like an ill-trained pooch, you snuck off with a shoe!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I was afraid someone would erase the chief prosecutor's crime. This shoe was my secret weapon if that should happen. See this fashionable basket I have here...? It carries more than lunchboxes, gentlemen!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm happy for you and your lunchbox bag, really.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">In any case, you removed valuable evidence from the scene of the crime.Now, tell us what you did next.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Two types of blood were found on this shoe! One was of course the victim's.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you brought it to the forensics department?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">If you're going to submit something as evidence in court, you need it approved. To do that, evidence must be analyzed... by a forensics expert.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And she got away with her little coup because she used to be a detective...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The shoe does appear to have bloodstains on it.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Makes sense. After all, a man was stabbed here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that blood belonged to the victim, Detective Goodman?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">As I said, there were two types of blood found on the shoe.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">And the other was...! The defendant, Ms. Lana Skye's blood!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can't say for sure the blood belonged to the victim with a blood test!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">You claim to know something about blood tests, Rookie?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Well, speak up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, well... Blood comes in four types... A, B, O, and AB... However! You can't tell from a blood test whether a murder was performed... in cold blood!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... That's just a figure of speech, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Actually, if you combine all the various blood tests, there are millions of types! It's practically impossible to narrow a blood sample down to one person! Or so I hear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-millions of types?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">If I had a little more time, I would have gotten DNA test results... But they said there's very little doubt it could be anyone's but Ms. Lana Skye's.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So the suspect's blood was found on the victim's shoe...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That ties her directly to the death of Detective Goodman!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I was afraid he was going to say that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">This shoe proves it! It's flawless, decisive evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't let this evidence go through without a fight!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">You ordered the peppered fish guts, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Some like it hot, Mr. Wright. Some, like your client. She's in enough hot water to make a whole batch of soup.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! Do you or don't you have a problem with this shoe!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A problem...? <thought>This is critical! What's wrong with the victim's shoe?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No... there's nothing there. And if I just stab blindly at it, I'll hurt my case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">C'mon, Mr. Wright, I know you can find something! Some kind of off-the-cuff contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm trying to avoid saying things off-the-cuff today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If I'm not imagining things... I'd say there is one critical problem with this evidence... A clear contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">That gleam in your eyes... You're still young, Rookie. I'd give you a peppered fish gut now, but you couldn't take the heat, could you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's hear what Mr. Wright has to say! What is contradictory about the victim's shoe? Show us the problem with this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The problem with this evidence... is here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Where?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Take that finger and point it at your own head, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... guess that wasn't it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright, let's be scientific about this! Examine the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As I thought, a waste of time. Well, that was a nice break. Let's return to the testimony, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder if you noticed... there's blood on the bottom of this shoe!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Don't mess with me, Rookie... Or it'll be your blood on the bottom of my shoe!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Indeed, there is quite a bit of blood on the bottom of the shoe.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It makes sense. The victim was stabbed with a knife! What could possibly be contradictory about blood on the bottom of his shoe!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I'm guessing your shoe has blood on it too... you just shot yourself in the foot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arrgh...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Would you like a grinder, or a grind from the heel of my boot, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Man... tough crowd.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright, let's be scientific about this! Examine the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As I thought, a waste of time. Well, that was a nice break. Let's return to the testimony, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's pretty sly, hiding evidence like that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's nothing sly about a lawyer using the law as a weapon! In any case, science is always on our side! Don't forget! Scientific investigation is the wave of the future!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... maybe I should "investigate" this evidence a little more closely...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The problem lies... in the footprint.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">The... footprint?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Note that the bottom of the victim's shoe is covered in blood. Then... isn't it strange? Why weren't any bloody footprints found by the scene of the crime!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah hah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As you can see... There were no traces of any such footprints at the scene of the crime! That contradicts your claim about this shoe!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This picture only shows part of the floor, so there could have been bloody footprints.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If there were bloody prints they would have been found. We checked the scene and found nothing of the sort!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! Well, witness!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">What!? Huh? I, uh...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Great going, Mr. Wright! But... It's true that the lack of a footprint is a contradiction... But then we have to ask why there wasn't a footprint!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's true! There has to be a reason why there wasn't a footprint!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Think, Mr. Wright, think!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Hey, I don't know why it's not there. I'm just good at finding contradictions.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... Now I get it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Get what!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Our witness is more devious than I gave her credit for! We were hoodwinked to the very end! But she slipped! There is one vital hint to the truth in her testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Think back to when she told us about apprehending the suspect...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">The chief prosecutor tried to resist, but her efforts were in vain. She knocked my hands aside, kicked over an oil drum... Oh, she's beautiful, but deadly! A predator, this one! A leopard woman! Rowr!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I thought that was a strange thing for the normally cool-headed chief to do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No kidding!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, witness. Allow me to ask a very simple question. This "oil drum"... was it empty?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">... Oh, that, hmm? I'm not sure I like your attitude, Mr. Edgeworth. Though apparently you're not the slowest conveyor belt in the lunchbox factory.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! W-well? Was the oil drum empty...?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">The oil drum kicked over by the chief prosecutor... was brimming with water.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-water? <thought>What does that mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Still don't get it, Mr. Wright? Do you want to know the reason she knocked it over? The REAL reason?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aaaa haaaaah! You don't mean...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, the suspect knocked over that oil drum for one reason and one reason alone! To erase the blood stains that would become evidence against her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaaaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That ties things up quite nicely! The blood stains left on the victim's shoes tie her quite clearly to this murder! Then, after the deed was done, she knocked over the oil drum to erase the telltale signs!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Why, that's a prosecutor's specialty... erasing evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That reminds me... Ms. Skye's right hand was hurt... Didn't she say she'd cut herself when she stabbed him...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So my sister's blood on the shoe... That's when it happened?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... I see no reason to prolong this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">M-Mr. Wright! Do something! Please!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-what!? What can I do? Your sister has confessed to the crime, and she tried to conceal it!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">B-but...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Enough. There is no need for further debate. The verdict, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But Angel Starr is on the prosecution's side! She could have been lying about the water!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court finds the defendant, Ms. Lana Skye...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Little girl... What did you just say?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh...? M-me?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Did you say that I, Angel Starr... was on the prosecution's side?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">W-well, yeah, you are! You're saying my sister hid evidence by erasing the bloody footprints!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Well. I thought you'd had your fill, but here you are, demanding a second helping! Another lunchbox... A lunchbox called "evidence"!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-wait... Witness, don't tell me you have something else?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You've reached your verdict, Your Honor! Any further comments will be held in contempt of court!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Your threats don't scare the Cough-up Queen! Look at this!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A photograph...?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I had this just in case anyone had the gall to suggest... that the white shoe didn't belong to the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see no room for error in this evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">M-Mr. Wright, wait! Look at the asphalt in this photo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! It's clearly wet!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Erasing the last trace of doubt from the court's mind. Immediately after the murder, the crime scene was washed with water!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I-I'm sorry, Mr. Wright. I guess I... I couldn't help after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's not your fault... I knew I couldn't win this case from the beginning. And... it seems this is what your sister wanted anyway! ... I'm sorry, Mia...</thought> ... ... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is the last piece of evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well! This time I'd like to declare a verdict for good!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor, wait!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it with you people!? Can't I hand down my verdicts in peace anymore!? Whatever it is, can it wait?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no it can't. Then it will be too late! Look at this photograph, the last one submitted... This trial isn't over... until we give each piece of evidence proper consideration!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, Wright... Are you saying there's a problem with this latest piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah! <thought>I'll think later!</thought> Yeah, there's a problem! <thought>Right or wrong, I've got to go ahead with this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suppose since we've come this far, we should give every claim a fair shake. Very well, Mr. Wright. Show the court the problem in this photograph!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... it's probably here! Don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As your elder, Mr. Wright, let me give you a piece of advice... When you point at something, at least remember to keep your eyes open?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I believe he's trying to say that no one's falling for your bluffs, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Open your eyes, Mr. Wright! Think scientifically!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The problem in this photograph... is here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's this...? There's something poking out of the car's muffler!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wait just a moment, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You just said "muffler"... However I see no trace of a muffler or scarf of any kind in this photograph!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... A muffler is also a part on a car or motorcycle, Your Honor. Just think of it as... part of the exhaust system. A pipe...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see! And... I see! What's that suspicious-looking cloth sticking out of the car's muffler?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Hmph! So what if there is something sticking out of the muffler! What does that have to do with this case? Nothing! Absolutely nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, Ms. Starr... But it's not going to be that easy! In fact, you've already told us why this is important to the case... You said as much in your testimony!!!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Wh-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's hear what Mr. Wright has on his mind! Tell us why you think this piece of cloth in the muffler is related to this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Your Honor? How do you feel about that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Actually, I don't feel well at all. I have this pounding headache...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, I meant, what do you think about the...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid the reason for that headache is you, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That cloth was found in the car's "muffler," right...? Muffler... muffler... Where have I heard that word recently? Muffler...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Starr! Recall your testimony for the court...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Ah yes. When I arrested her, she mentioned the muffler! That's what had me confused in my earlier testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Muffler! argh! Yeearrrrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could it be that the "muffler" you heard mentioned... Was actually this exhaust pipe!? If so! That means this piece of cloth is vital evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Oh... Whooooooooooo ooooooooooooragh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... It seems we will have to suspend the proceedings.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Sus... Suspend!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I find myself wondering about that piece of cloth. If we leave any question unanswered here we do a disservice to the law! Have the car at the crime scene inspected at once, and bring me that cloth! The verdict will wait until after we've seen all the evidence. Agreed...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I suppose so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whew... that was close. But... we made it... at least for now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will adjourn for a thirty minute recess! It's lunchtime after all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's still hungry!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um... Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Are trials... always like this with you? Like you're swimming up from the bottom of a lake, about to reach the surface... But no matter how hard you paddle you never seem to get there...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pretty much. Except today we're swimming in quicksand. So what happened to your sister, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Apparently she got called off to the judge's chambers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Probably something to do with that piece of cloth.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So! This is where we turn this trial around, right? Our only weapon, a tiny, insignificant piece of cloth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm the one who's starting to feel tiny and insignificant to tell the truth.</line>
<line speaker="???">Hola, Pardner!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">They say you show a red cloth to a bull, it'll fire up its temper! That's what they told me when I was a young'un, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Officer Marshall!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Thought I'd come take a look-see at how the trial's going. Looks like I'm late. They've got the place locked down tighter than a fort in enemy territory!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is going on over there, anyway? All the police I've seen these last two days have been really on edge.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Don't you got enough on your plate without worrying about other people, compadre? You could be worrying about the chief prosecutor's taste in mufflers, for example.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um... Officer Marshall? The whole "muffler" thing didn't have anything to do with scarves... She wasn't even wearing a scarf!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">You don't say? Now don't that just beat all.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I've seen the red breeze blow at her slender neck many a time... I saw it that day, too. She was wearing a red muffler.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">At the awards ceremony that afternoon. Edgeworth's seen it too, I'd reckon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What does that mean!? In the photograph taken at the crime scene... she wasn't wearing a scarf!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, Ms. Starr wasn't mistaken...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Well, it's about time. Remember, pardner, sometimes you gotta grab the bull by the horns... and sometimes you just gotta let that bull go where it will. Time will tell!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... I have a bad feeling about this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So... what are we swimming in now, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">If it's steak sauce, I can hook you up with some fine ribs! Ooh-wee!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'd... like to... resume...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's up? The judge keeps looking over at the prosecution...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is something wrong, Mr. Edgeworth? Your face is blue, your lips are purple, you're sweating bullets... That furrowed brow, those grinding teeth, those watery eyes... What's more your eyes are unfocused, you're doubled over, your back is bent...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It... can't... be!! This... can't... happen!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I wonder what happened to Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, I believe it is time we continued on with this trial. During our recess I had requested that the prosecution conduct an investigation...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-this is unacceptable!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It seems our prosecutor is quite beside himself.</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, er, excuse me. Knock knock?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? Who's there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's with this guy? A strange, stuffy aura seems to be filling the courtroom.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey! The temperature rose 5.7 degrees when that man came in!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who on earth is he...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, it's you...</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh! Oh, heh heh. Sorry I'm late, Udgey! The roads were packed. It's just me! Long time no see, eh, Udgey? How ya been? Swim much these days!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah! Hello, hello. No, I've been so busy...</line>
<line speaker="???">Busy! Busy-smizzy, Udgey, my boy! You have to make time to relax!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-yes, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Udgey... seems to be his nickname for the judge...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm afraid you're right. Very afraid. Um... sorry, but... who are you?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah hah! So you're Wrighto! The attorney! I've heard good things about you, son!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eh? Uh, th-thanks...?</line>
<line speaker="???">So sorry about our little Worthy giving you all that trouble, eh? You know, we should all go swimming together sometime! Jolly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Little... Little Worthy...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! You don't know the district Chief of Police!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Chuh....? Chief of Police...!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He's the top ranking police officer in the entire district!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Name's Gant, Damon Gant. Pleased to meet you, everyone!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, uh, to what do we owe this honor today? It's been over... two years since you last came to this courtroom, hasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Well, it's Worthy, here. Look at the poor fellow! I just thought I'd help out... by bringing this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! Th-that's...!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">My sister's muffler!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So Ms. Starr wasn't just seeing things! When the crime occurred, Ms. Skye really was wearing that muffler!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gant">But to think that it was stuffed into that exhaust pipe... On little Worthy's car, no less! It's really quite embarrassing, even for us.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what's this!?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">It's what you'd call a switchblade knife. Quite perplexing, this.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Chief! What kind of outfit are you running!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How could they miss such a vital piece of evidence!? If your investigators are this lax, how do you expect us to do our job?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">N-now wait a minute, Worthy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've no desire to hear your excuses!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">I'm telling you to wait! Or didn't you hear me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Have a look at this document, where it says "person in charge of investigation"... There's no mistaking that signature... Miles Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-that's no fair! The day of the crime, I-I had...</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Your head in the clouds because you got that award! I know how you feel... But you're the person in charge. I'll expect a written apology.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What? Are you serious!?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Don't be too upset, we'll find a way to clean up this mess... that you made.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This is the first time I've seen Mr. Edgeworth at a loss for words...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This kind of major blunder is unlike you Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gah...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court accepts this new evidence. But, I'd like to ask the defense a favor first.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Just to be sure... I'd like to take a look at the blade of this knife.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The b-blade, Your Honor? Well, I don't see why not...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Could you open it up for me, I wonder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, well. I think all you have to do is push that switch, and...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If I cut my finger Mr. Wright, I wouldn't be able to pound my gavel anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah. But if I cut my finger, I wouldn't be able to point it at people anymore...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Come on! Just hurry up and open it!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's a small tag on this knife.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seems to say "SL-9 2"...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What does that mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... <thought>I've heard something similar... "DL-6"... of "DL-6 Incident" fame...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">But... it's strange.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What is?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm not certain... But I get the feeling I've seen this somewhere before! Letters like this... or letters that looked a lot like this... somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's a small tag on the knife.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It says, "SL-9 2."</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure... <thought>But it reminds me of a similar code... "DL-6." Maybe it's a case number?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's weird.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I don't remember where... but I think I've seen something like this before. Something similar to what's written on this tag. It wasn't that long ago either...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe I should check the Court Record again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Waaaah! D-don't scare me like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm the one who's scared!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Look at this knife blade... the tip is broken off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And this dark red stain... blood?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This does not excuse the actions of the Police Department! I would like to hear an explanation from the Chief of Police himself!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm terribly sorry, but could I ask you to testify for us? About the split between the prosecutors and the police... and this knife.</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Sure! Sure thing. Not a problem, not even a little one! Really!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">This knife is special... but I can't say how here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There... There was a murder at the Police Department!? A detective!?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">That's hush-hush information, Udgey! We haven't exactly announced it yet.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-wait a second! You said "5:15"... That's the exact time that Detective Goodman was killed at the Prosecutor's Office!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Anyway, we at the Department were all a-flustered, as you might well assume. We're in the middle of a top-top-secret investigation. Don't tell anyone, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think we understand the Police Department's situation... Well, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Two detectives killed at the same time in two different places...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">The chances of that are really slim. Scientifically speaking, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd... like to exercise my right to cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well... however! Keep your questions focused on the case at hand!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">This knife is special... but I can't say how here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me... "special"?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Mmhmm. Hard to come by this particular knife anywhere else.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Might that special thing... be this little tag?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Oh! Sorry, Wrighto! But I can't say that now. Not that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We've established that the knife in Goodman's chest... was this knife. Now why was there another knife at the scene of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's quite a mystery!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">And like a mystery, it's wrapped in something... a muffler!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">This knife was evidence in a case. It was stolen from the Department's evidence room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this knife... was stolen?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Yes, but on the day of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was evidence, you say. Was it, in fact, a murder weapon?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Nice! Nice! Nice! Good show, little Worthy! It was a murder weapon, as it happens. It was evidence from a case long-since solved...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So this knife was stolen on the day of the murder... And it was found in the exhaust pipe of Edgeworth's car...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hard to think there isn't a connection there!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Unless there's evidence to prove a connection between this knife and Goodman...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This knife was found on the scene of our crime! I think that makes it connected to the case, don't you!?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">See, there's a lot of things that go on at the Department I can't explain... It's... delicate, okay? Sorry, Wrighto!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Maybe there's something about the knife that will give us a clue! Let's examine that knife while we can, Wrighto!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmmm... evidence that links this knife to Detective Goodman... I think perhaps the pieces are falling into place... I should try presenting the piece of evidence that's had me stumped all this time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, how were things down at the Department...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a second!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Ah, at last! An honest to goodness "objection"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This knife... This has to have something to do with Detective Goodman!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Ah hah! An honest-to-goodness what do you mean from the judge! This is great!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at the tag on this knife! It reads "SL-9 2"...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And this is important... why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Over here we also have... A memo that was on the body of the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... what's this? 6 minus 7S... 12/2...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor... It's upside-down.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Upside...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The printed name on the memo makes it look like it's right-side up... But turn it around and what do you get!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah... Ah haaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When he wrote this note, he was holding the paper upside down!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">SL-9... That's the same thing that is written on the knife's tag! Order! Order! Well, Chief?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">... Ah, well. I guess the cat's out of the bag... You win, Wrighto!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... win? Ah... <thought>What game is this guy playing!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Change statements">"This knife is special... but I can't say how here." and "Unless there's evidence to prove a connection between this knife and Goodman..." to "This knife was evidence in a case. It was stolen from the Department's evidence room."</line>
<line speaker="Gant">That was a bad day for the Department. We weren't in any shape to do an investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something didn't happen at the Police Department too, did it...?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">You got a good look in your eyes, there, Wrighto my boy. Sharp! Hungry!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Chief... did something happen? And why haven't I heard?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Why haven't you heard? Or why didn't you ask?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">No matter, I understand. You were busy, what with Lana's case and all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, what happened!? What happened at the Police Department that day?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">A detective was killed at the Police Department, see... what a mess!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the same day that a detective was killed in the Prosecutor's parking lot... Another detective... was killed at the Police Department!?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">That's a fact. Surprising, isn't it, Udgey?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm at a loss for words.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And the perpetrator? Do you have a suspect?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Well, there was a suspect. Just arrested 'em, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just arrested! That was quick...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gant">But... there's still a lot of unanswered questions. Maybe you could help, Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I suppose I could help... if you help me by giving me data on your case?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Oooh, good one! This kid's sharp! Okay, here's the deal. I'll tell you one thing and one thing only...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, how was the detective killed?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">How was he killed? Now that's the interesting part! It was what we in the force call a "stabbing." With a knife!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A kn-knife...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's exactly the same as Detective Goodman!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">That's the spirit! We're cooking now! But you know... That's not the only thing that was exactly the same...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">There were more similarities between the two cases than the cause of death!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It seems like I'm going to have to press this a bit harder...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... when did the murder at the Police Department occur?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Now that's a sharp question, Wrighto! Very sharp! Well, my boy... You're gonna love this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, tell me... where was the victim found?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">... Well, I can't speak on where the corpse was found. But I can say the crime took place in the evidence room at the Police Department.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The evidence room!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gant">You wouldn't know about the evidence room, would you, Wrighto?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't say I've heard of it. <thought>I guess I should ask again once I learn a bit more about this "evidence room."</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gant">There's something stranger about this than the place where the body was found!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>W-wait a second... I have heard of that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">The evidence room... Didn't he mention that in his testimony just now?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">This knife was evidence in a case. It was stolen from the Department's evidence room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's the connection between the two cases!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">You seem happy, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Happy? We just got handed our ticket to go to town on this case! <thought>With the link between the two cases established, we finally have some leverage. Now we can get Gant to testify about the details!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gant">The time of the crime? 5:15. Scary coincidence, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Five... 5:15...!? B-but that's... That's when Detective Goodman was killed in the Prosecutor's Office!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Funny, isn't it? A murder at the Prosecutor's place, and a murder at our place at the very same time! What are the chances!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Coincidence!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">This is just my gut feeling... but I'd say there's a 0.001% chance of that happening!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Chief Gant, please tell us more about the incident!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">It's not officially linked to this here case, so I can't talk much about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How can you say there's no connection!?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">How? Because I'm the Chief of Police! I can't just say anything I please, Wrighto. You understand!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Try to understand, Wrighto.</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Well, if you can prove there is a connection, more power to you. Maybe there is something that ties the two murders together?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whatever it is, I'd better find it and get to the bottom of this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Chief... The defense's position is simply this: The connection between these two cases has already been proven!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Heh, you don't say? Well, out with it Wrighto! What's your connection?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, out with it, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The connection is a place, mentioned in the testimony we just heard. The knife found in the lot was stolen... from the Police Department's evidence room.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not to mention the victim had written down the numbers on the knife's evidence tag.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And we also know that the detective murdered at the Police Department... was killed in that very same evidence room!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed... There do seem to be too many connections for it to be a coincidence.</line>
<line speaker="Gant">You two make a good pair. It took my men two days to find out what you deduced right here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Chief! I request that you release your information on the victim at the Police Department!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">See, that's the tricky part. It hasn't been announced yet, and all...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can we get the information... unofficially?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Hmmmmm... Sure! Why not? It's unofficial, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What? Really!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Who would have guessed?</line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"It's not officially linked to this here case, so I can't talk much about it." to "I'll cooperate, but I can't reveal the name of the victim at the Department, okay?"</line>
<line speaker="Gant">I'll cooperate, but I can't reveal the name of the victim at the Department, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you're going to tell us a little, why not tell us everything?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Ah, well, case information is sticky stuff. You have to do everything properly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh well... I guess I might as well try to get what I can out of him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, well... What division was the victim stationed in?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Oh? You want to know that, do you? Do you? Ah hah... Criminal Affairs, Division 1. The detectives responsible for homicide cases.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Homicide... that would be the same division as Detective Gumshoe!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Detective Goodman who was killed in the underground parking lot was homicide, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's almost like a serial killer was after homicide detectives...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Except that the serial killing happened simultaneously, scientifically speaking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I sure hope Detective Gumshoe isn't next on the list...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay... how about the gender of the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">You want to know that!? Um... Hmm... Okay, a hint. Let's see... first hint! The gender that's NOT female...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah hah! He was a guy!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">What did I tell you! The boy's sharp!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Stop goofing around, Mr. Wright! This is serious business!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-sorry, Your Honor. <thought>Hey, tell that to the Chief of Police!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay... How about you tell me the victim's ID number?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Hmm? Sure, why not. It's not like you'll be able to tell who it is from that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course not. You won't tell me their name, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Gant">We keep a tight lid on ID numbers, so don't go getting your hopes up. The number is... 5842189.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well! That's quite... long!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">And we have to remember these! It drives me nuts!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">8... 2... I can't do it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You didn't even get the first number right!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright? Does this tell you anything?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The ID number of the victim at the Police Department... 5842189...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Absolutely nothing, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah... well, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">First of all, it was too long! I've forgotten it already!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-sorry! I mean, why are you getting mad at me!? I didn't come up with those numbers...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm... 5842189...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, it does, Your Honor. It does...! I think!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Meaning?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It has to be what I think it is... But what does this mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, let's hear what the defense has to say. You say the ID number of the detective who was murdered at the Police Department... tells you something? What does it tell you!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The ID number tells me...&#160;this!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">My dear boy, you shouldn't believe everything ID numbers tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... Maybe I misheard. You know?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright.... The court respectfully requests that you clean out your ears and pay attention!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And I'd like to request some straightforward information for once!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! Don't listen to them! Look at the Court Record, scientifically!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Two detectives were killed at 5:15... One at the Prosecutor's Office... And one at the Police Department... that can't be a coincidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">And that knife! What was it doing there...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better check this knife out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Witness! ...</line>
<line speaker="Gant">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... What is it, Mr. Wright!? You're grinning like a schoolgirl on prom night!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I... it's just, I got confused...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And this is news?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just come out with both guns blazing... like you always do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The Police Department... the Prosecutor's Office... Two places, two detectives murdered... at one time.</thought> Actually, I happen to have a police ID number here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh hoh! Is it yours?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no, Your Honor. I'm a defense attorney... remember? This is the ID number of our victim, Detective Goodman.</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Shame on you, Wrighto! Personnel IDs are top secret!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Goodman's ID number is... "5842189."</line>
<line speaker="Gant">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... And...? This means... what, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wait... That ID number we heard from the Chief earlier.. That started with "82..." Hmm. I've forgotten.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You even got the first number wrong!</thought> The number the Chief of Police gave us was... 5842189.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-wait a second, Wright! What does this...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mean? That's what I want to know! The two ID numbers are identical! In other words... The detective killed in the Police Department's evidence room was Bruce Goodman!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What does our witness think about that!?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">... Oh! Ho ho ho, sharp as a tack, Wrighto! Sharp as a tack!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-but wait! Detective Goodman is OUR victim! He was killed at 5:15 in the underground parking lot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yet, a Detective Bruce Goodman was also killed at the Police Department... In the evidence room... at the exact same time!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-that's impossible! So, what we're saying is... The same person was killed at the same time!? And in a completely different location!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! Chief! What does this mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>No... what I want to know is... why didn't I hear about this!? Yes, it's top-secret, fine! But I'm the prosecutor in charge of the case!!!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Now, just wait a second, Worthy. No need to get all flustered.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor! The Police Department has made a grave error in this case...</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Wait. I said "wait." Or didn't you hear me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">The oversight... the grave error...? Mr. Edgeworth... They're yours.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-what!?&#160;How... how dare...</line>
<line speaker="Gant">We informed you yesterday. I believe it was our Officer Meekins who brought you the news?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">O-officer... Meekins?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! Where have we heard that name before? Wait... Ah hah!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Erm...! Excuse me! But is Mr. Edgeworth, uh... anywhere on the premises? I'm here, sir, at the request of the chief, sir! I've got your report, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You don't mean... him!?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">According to Meekins, you didn't accept the report?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Hard to believe.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">B-but your officer, he told me! He said that report had nothing to do with the Lana Skye incident!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">[Detective Bruce Goodman murdered in the Police Department evidence room...] Mr. Edgeworth. The victim's name is written right on the top of the report.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gaaaaaaah! Wh-why didn't your officer tell me!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Honestly, I'm not sure if that officer was capable of making the connection... He did seem... challenged.</line>
<line speaker="Gant">In any case, this is a serious error, a gross negligence of duty on your part, Worthy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">B-But, sir!!! You could have submitted that report this morning to the court, as evidence! Then, I...</line>
<line speaker="Gant">No such luck this time, Worthy... or should I say, un-Worthy?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Now what was the second rule of evidence law, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Oh, well, it's, uh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Rule 2: New evidence may only be submitted if it concerns the case on trial. And how is this relevant!?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Normally, you submit a list of evidence to be used in court before the trial. This report wasn't on that list...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So... What does this mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">I couldn't submit this evidence until a connection was proven in court.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">That connection was just proven by Wrighto over here. Good job, Wrighto, my boy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Uh... I... I was just doing my job.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No... Noooooooooooooo!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems... we have come to the end of this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Gant">You are becoming a thorn in my side, Worthy... There've been rumors... After all, you were in the defendant's chair just last year...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...! I apologize for this terrible lack of due diligence on my part...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please... Just give me one day. I'll get to the bottom of what happened... If it's the last thing I do!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">You'd better get results this time. Really.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Poor Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't think there's ever been an error this serious in the history of this court. We will grant one further day as the prosecution has requested. Will this be sufficient, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, Your Honor. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whatever your punishment for this is, for your sake I hope it's not... decisive. Very well! Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't sound very convinced, Mr. Wright. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This evidence clearly reveals the contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are that evidence and the statement just now related...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They aren't, are they...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Wright, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness's statement is clearly faulty, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry, but I can see nothing faulty. Unfortunately, I will have to penalize you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh. I must be on the wrong track?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! This court sees no reason to further prolong the trial. The defense has failed to give the court sufficient reason to doubt the prosecution's claim! This court find the defendant, Ms. Lana Skye...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accused will surrender to the court immediately, to be held pending trial at a higher court within a month from today's date. That is all. The court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>