<xml>
<title>Rise from the Ashes</title>
<line speaker="Ema">So, what do you think, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think the prosecution is as confused as we are. After all...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">the victim was murdered in two different places at the same time, and a different suspect was arrested at the other crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Lana!</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Good morning, Mr. Wright. I apologize for yesterday. I was... indisposed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I hope they didn't hold you too long for questioning.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">We just finished, actually. I'm used to all-nighters, though.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, how'd it go?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">It's as Mr. Wright suspects. The police are clueless. I figured as much, so I struck a plea bargain.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A plea bargain? What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">We agreed that if I told them the truth behind this "simultaneous murder," they wouldn't seek capital punishment. That's what I mean, Ema.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But Lana! Don't tell me you...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Much to my regret, I'm as much in the dark about this as they are.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Skye.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We discovered traces left by a certain person in the Police Department's evidence room. They belonged to Officer Jake Marshall.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">You found Officer Marshall's... traces?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Blood-stained fingerprints, to be exact.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's the trump card I have up my sleeve today. You do understand what this means, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">In order to defend my sister, you're going to accuse Mr. Marshall?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We have to play the cards we're dealt. Isn't that right, Ms. Skye?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">... Do what you have to do, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Ms. Lana Skye.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution is... Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Hmph? I'm afraid you'll have to clarify.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It takes 30 minutes by car to reach criminal affairs from the Prosecutor's Office. The victim, Bruce Goodman, was slain at both places at the same time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But, that's not physically possible, is it? What's more, I hear the victim from the evidence room just "disappeared"!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes, and the body eventually reappeared in the trunk of Mr. Edgeworth's car.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow... this is one messed up trial...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">One of my duties as prosecutor is to present impartial evidence. Today I will present evidence relating to the murder at the Police Department. In so doing, I believe the way in which we should proceed will reveal itself.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Now that's what sets Mr. Edgeworth apart. He sounds so on top of things... even though he doesn't know what's going on himself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's supposed to be an admirable trait?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, let the trial resume. On the day of the crime, what exactly transpired at the Police Department? Mr. Edgeworth, you may call your first witness of the day to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For its first witness, the prosecution calls... the suspect of the murder that occurred at the Police Department!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The suspect!? You mean, the so-called murderer!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hoo boy. Things are getting wild from the get-go.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Will the witness please state his name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! I am Officer Mike Meekins, sir! My occupation is, um... that would be murderer, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Er... So you're telling us you're a "professional killer"...</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir. It was me, sir! I'm the one who did it! I'll never kill anyone again, sir! You've got to believe me, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... Actually, what we'd like to hear from you is...</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir! I'm what you would call part of the "younger generation," sir! A person whose actions adults can't possibly comprehend!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please, Mr. Edgeworth, sir! Help me, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Officer Meekins.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Y-yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Give us your report of the crime. Consider that an order.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! As you wish! After all, I am part of a generation that must be told what to do, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You can't fault him for a lack of enthusiasm.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Although it's not my normal duty, I was assigned to guard the evidence room that day!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. So the victim, Detective Goodman, attacked you?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">"Do unto others before they do unto you"! That's the Meekins family motto, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Then you fainted, and a colleague helped you regain consciousness.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! He knocked me upside the head, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The defense may begin its cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What I need here is more info to work with!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Although it's not my normal duty, I was assigned to guard the evidence room that day!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Meekins. You work in the General Affairs Department, do you not?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! I am in charge of hiring new recruits, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yikes! Now there's a scary thought.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Evidence transferal was taking place on the day of the crime, which meant many officers were given special tasks not ordinarily performed.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I was in charge of guarding the Blue Badger, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The Blue Badger?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir. The lovely police mascot created by the Head Detective, sir! I was to ensure it wasn't broken during the transferal process. That was my sole mission for the day, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Sounds like a very... uh, important mission.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">After the awards ceremony finished that day, there were so many people running around that I relocated the Blue Badger to the evidence room!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh... So that's why you went to the evidence room.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tell us... what did you see when you got there?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I spotted a suspicious man on the security screen, and rushed into the room!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In order to enter the evidence room... you need an ID card, am I correct?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Precisely, sir! I have one right here around my neck!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So then... your ID number should be listed in here, right?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">... There it is! I found it! This is the one right here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Could you please read us the number?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! It's "4989596." That's my number, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... Huh? But the number 4989596... is shown as being used twice!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please explain, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">It's n-no real mystery, sir! The first time is when I relocated Blue Badger to the evidence room, and the second time is when I went to go get him after everything settled down.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. So it was during that second time when?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! That was when I spotted the man on the security screen!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I was only doing what I was trained to do, sir! I was suddenly attacked!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you were attacked... Can you please tell us exactly what happened to you?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">It was a knife, sir! A knife!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Detective Goodman pulled a knife on you? What happened then?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Well, with me charging in on him like that, he looked as surprised as I was!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You aren't exactly the kind of person someone would want to run into...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">That's when I reacted, sir! I swung my arms like an octopus, struggling to detain him! That's how I got this gash on my hand.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Maybe if you'd just kept your cool your hand wouldn't be...</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">When I saw the blood trickling down my arm, I panicked! I grabbed the man by his collar!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I fought for my life! Then I... I did it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What exactly do you mean when you say you, "did it"?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I know I don't look the type, but I'm really into kung fu films, sir! The man let his guard down for just an instant, so I snatched his knife from him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You took his knife?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I spun him around and performed a disarming maneuver! I made sure to close my eyes like a man!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, uh, see... <thought>He must have been desperate.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">The next thing I knew, his white coat was drenched in a sea of my blood, and then... Then, the next thing I knew...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">He punched me right in my face, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">After that I passed out... until another officer smacked me awake!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About what time did you regain consciousness?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">No offense, sir, but how am I supposed to know that? I was unconscious!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... right.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">According to the report from the officer that woke up the witness, it was about 5:30.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">He hit me right in the head too! I woke up crying tears of pain!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's nice... Er, I mean... it's nice that you recovered, that is...</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">When I came around though, I made sure to finish my mission, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your "mission"...?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! The Blue Badger, sir! I returned him to the entrance before things got out of hand!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, we can all rest easy now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">This is what he was telling us yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, we need to try and skim some more detail from him. For starters, what was an officer from the General Affairs Department doing in there in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Right! Let's press him for all he's worth!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe we now have a fairly accurate picture of what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, Your Honor. Only one thing remains unclear. Was the man this officer "murdered," really the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's got a point...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Officer Meekins?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">With regard to that, sir... Take a look at this. It was sent to my cell. Chief Gant delivered it to me just this morning sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Chief?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Delivered it...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is that? A... videotape?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! That's absolutely right, sir! A videotape, sir! It contains footage from the security camera in the evidence room.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!? But I specifically asked if there was such a tape, and was told it had been mistakenly erased!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's quite a mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I just do what I'm told, sir. It's the only thing I'm really good at.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like communication with the Police Department is as good as ever...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, let's have a look! Show us the video of you murdering the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Oh... Please stop using that word, "murder," sir! It scares me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A video of a real murder... Just what are we getting ourselves into...?</thought> ...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I believe we're all thinking the same thing. How can we deal with these unsettling feelings stirred within us...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What the hell was that wriggling piece of plywood!?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir! That is the pride and joy of the entire Criminal Affairs Department, sir! It's the Blue Badger, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why am I not surprised this isn't going smoothly?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, well anyway... this tape seems to prove that that the witness did indeed encounter... er, "someone" in the evidence room, and some sort of... er, "activity" did take place...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor... instead of relying on clearly incomplete footage, the witness's testimony will suffice. Is that alright with you, Officer Meekins?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! As you wish, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">His face can't be clearly seen in the video,</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this about a fingerprint?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Each detective has been given a locker, equipped with a fingerprint-activated lock. These locks ensure that each locker can only be opened by the detective it belongs to.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Intriguing... That would mean... the victim at the crime scene would have to have been Detective Goodman. Very well! The defense may begin its cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't know where this cross-examination will lead, but everything begins with contradictions. That's where I have to start!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">His face can't be clearly seen in the video,</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me, were you able to get a good look at him? At the face of the man who attacked you with a knife?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">S-sir! If you must label people as having "seen" or "not seen" the man's face... I believe I would be classified as... the latter?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The latter? But you were standing right in front of him, were you not?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">More to the point, you are the person who fought him, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Oh, yes sir! But... I didn't get a clear look at his face, sir. I'm not the kind of guy who looks directly at people when talking with them, you see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, that's a good trait for a police officer...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Still, I'm sure it was him! I'd bet my badge on it!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">but there's no question that the other person was Detective Goodman, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you don't know that for sure, do you? You never actually saw Detective Goodman's face.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Well... I suppose you might say that. That is, if you must label people as having "seen" or "not seen" it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Since his face can't be identified in the video, only you can verify it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Meekins!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Having been shown a questionable video at best, we are not in the best of moods. Now please be more certain when you testify!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Y-y-yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You claimed the man who brandished a knife on you was Bruce Goodman. Tell us why you are positive it was him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Regarding the video contained on this tape, there is one thing in particular that seems rather strange.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Strange?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This contradiction leads to the possibility that... the man may not be Detective Goodman.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What? This video contains such a contradiction?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Interesting... Your Honor, I have a proposal.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I propose we have the defense... point out to us this alleged "contradiction" in the video.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He would want me to point it out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, proposal accepted. Let us further inspect this piece of evidence. I will now play the security tape. Mr. Wright. Please show us this contradiction you speak of.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to point out a problem in the video? This is the first time I've ever had to do that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">You can do it, Mr. Wright! It's set up so you can Fast Forward, Rewind or Pause the video. Just take a good look and be sure to point out the right thing!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Please don't play it too many times. I-I can't stand watching this video!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How did this guy ever become a police officer?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Wright. Please enlighten us! Where is the contradiction that indicates the man may not be Detective Goodman?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The thing that's strange about this video... has got to be this!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes, that is strange. Something certainly seems unnatural about that. What could it mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry to interrupt, Mr. Wright... but you seem to have forgotten the point of this exercise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The point...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What you are looking for is one thing and one thing only: Something that indicates the man may not be Detective Goodman.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whew... I almost walked right into the defense's trap!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I'll place him under arrest, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Rats... I need to slow down and tackle these things one piece at a time. Now what do I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Very well. Let's try this again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just remember one thing, Mr. Wright: Every time you point your finger, someone gets hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But he's the one pointing his finger...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It seems I've been taking the wrong approach.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, the defense may resume its cross-examination. Assuming the witness is still willing to continue, that is. Officer Meekins?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! It is my duty as a police officer to help those lost, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great. Now they think I'm lost...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The thing that's strange about this video... would have to be... uh, this?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Hold on a second. I need to use my eye drops. ... Well, I don't get it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Um, would you mind if I borrowed your eye medicine?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Don't look at me with those bleary eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Before your eyes get too teary, perhaps you should think this through again, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now what do I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Very well. Let's try this again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just remember one thing, Mr. Wright: Every time you point your finger, someone gets hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But he's the one pointing his finger...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It seems I've been taking the wrong approach.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, the defense may resume its cross-examination. Assuming the witness is still willing to continue, that is. Officer Meekins?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! It is my duty as a police officer to help those lost, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great. Now they think I'm lost...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I mean, he opened the locker, which required Detective Goodman's fingerprint to do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About these lockers... Is there no other way to open them?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">No, sir! I myself tried all kinds of methods in the past! They only respond to registered fingerprints, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder what kind of methods he's tried...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">If the man opened the locker's lock, which only responds to its registered fingerprints, then he must be the person the locker was assigned to.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Exactly my point, sir! And this too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Regarding the video contained on this tape, there is one thing in particular that seems rather strange.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Strange?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This contradiction leads to the possibility that... the man may not be Detective Goodman.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What? This video contains such a contradiction?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Interesting... Your Honor, I have a proposal.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I propose we have the defense... point out to us this alleged "contradiction" in the video.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He would want me to point it out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, proposal accepted. Let us further inspect this piece of evidence. I will now play the security tape. Mr. Wright. Please show us this contradiction you speak of.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to point out a problem in the video? This is the first time I've ever had to do that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">You can do it, Mr. Wright! It's set up so you can Fast Forward, Rewind or Pause the video. Just take a good look and be sure to point out the right thing!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Please don't play it too many times. I-I can't stand watching this video!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How did this guy ever become a police officer?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Wright. Please enlighten us! Where is the contradiction that indicates the man may not be Detective Goodman?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The thing that's strange about this video... has got to be this!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes, that is strange. Something certainly seems unnatural about that. What could it mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry to interrupt, Mr. Wright... but you seem to have forgotten the point of this exercise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The point...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What you are looking for is one thing and one thing only: Something that indicates the man may not be Detective Goodman.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whew... I almost walked right into the defense's trap!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I'll place him under arrest, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Rats... I need to slow down and tackle these things one piece at a time. Now what do I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Very well. Let's try this again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just remember one thing, Mr. Wright: Every time you point your finger, someone gets hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But he's the one pointing his finger...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It seems I've been taking the wrong approach.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, the defense may resume its cross-examination. Assuming the witness is still willing to continue, that is. Officer Meekins?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! It is my duty as a police officer to help those lost, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great. Now they think I'm lost...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The thing that's strange about this video... would have to be... uh, this?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Hold on a second. I need to use my eye drops. ... Well, I don't get it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Um, would you mind if I borrowed your eye medicine?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Don't look at me with those bleary eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Before your eyes get too teary, perhaps you should think this through again, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now what do I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Very well. Let's try this again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just remember one thing, Mr. Wright: Every time you point your finger, someone gets hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But he's the one pointing his finger...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It seems I've been taking the wrong approach.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, the defense may resume its cross-examination. Assuming the witness is still willing to continue, that is. Officer Meekins?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! It is my duty as a police officer to help those lost, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great. Now they think I'm lost...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">The locker he opened is unquestionably Detective Goodman's locker, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How do you know that information?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I've heard rumors, sir! From people in the know, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"People in the know"?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">The workers in the department cafeteria, sir! They keep me informed! They also listen to my... romantic troubles, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For the record... the opened locker did indeed belong to Detective Goodman. I verified this information through a more... reliable source.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So the victim opened the locker with his own fingerprint.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Regarding the video contained on this tape, there is one thing in particular that seems rather strange.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Strange?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This contradiction leads to the possibility that... the man may not be Detective Goodman.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What? This video contains such a contradiction?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Interesting... Your Honor, I have a proposal.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I propose we have the defense... point out to us this alleged "contradiction" in the video.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He would want me to point it out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, proposal accepted. Let us further inspect this piece of evidence. I will now play the security tape. Mr. Wright. Please show us this contradiction you speak of.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to point out a problem in the video? This is the first time I've ever had to do that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">You can do it, Mr. Wright! It's set up so you can Fast Forward, Rewind or Pause the video. Just take a good look and be sure to point out the right thing!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Please don't play it too many times. I-I can't stand watching this video!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How did this guy ever become a police officer?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Wright. Please enlighten us! Where is the contradiction that indicates the man may not be Detective Goodman?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The thing that's strange about this video... has got to be this!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes, that is strange. Something certainly seems unnatural about that. What could it mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry to interrupt, Mr. Wright... but you seem to have forgotten the point of this exercise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The point...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What you are looking for is one thing and one thing only: Something that indicates the man may not be Detective Goodman.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whew... I almost walked right into the defense's trap!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I'll place him under arrest, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Rats... I need to slow down and tackle these things one piece at a time. Now what do I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Very well. Let's try this again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just remember one thing, Mr. Wright: Every time you point your finger, someone gets hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But he's the one pointing his finger...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It seems I've been taking the wrong approach.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, the defense may resume its cross-examination. Assuming the witness is still willing to continue, that is. Officer Meekins?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! It is my duty as a police officer to help those lost, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great. Now they think I'm lost...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The thing that's strange about this video... would have to be... uh, this?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Hold on a second. I need to use my eye drops. ... Well, I don't get it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Um, would you mind if I borrowed your eye medicine?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Don't look at me with those bleary eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Before your eyes get too teary, perhaps you should think this through again, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now what do I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Very well. Let's try this again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just remember one thing, Mr. Wright: Every time you point your finger, someone gets hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But he's the one pointing his finger...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It seems I've been taking the wrong approach.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, the defense may resume its cross-examination. Assuming the witness is still willing to continue, that is. Officer Meekins?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! It is my duty as a police officer to help those lost, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great. Now they think I'm lost...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">So it must be him! No one else could have unlocked it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However, the most important detail is not shown in this video... the man's face!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">S-sir! If I may say something, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please do. After all, you are the one being examined.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I don't understand why the man's face is so important in this case, sir! I mean, it was his hand that opened the fingerprint lock... and it was his hand that tried to thrust his knife into my body, sir! My unsettled state can testify enough to this, sir! Yes, you have a point. The footage doesn't lie.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That is... unless the defense can find a problem with it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! Let's check the Court Record again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is there a problem with the security video?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The tape was provided by the Police Department, so there's no problem with it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I admire your trust in the Police Department Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But if you ask me, I think there's a problem with what's shown on the tape... rather than with the actual tape itself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Regarding the video contained on this tape, there is one thing in particular that seems rather strange.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Strange?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This contradiction leads to the possibility that... the man may not be Detective Goodman.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What? This video contains such a contradiction?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Interesting... Your Honor, I have a proposal.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I propose we have the defense... point out to us this alleged "contradiction" in the video.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He would want me to point it out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, proposal accepted. Let us further inspect this piece of evidence. I will now play the security tape. Mr. Wright. Please show us this contradiction you speak of.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to point out a problem in the video? This is the first time I've ever had to do that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">You can do it, Mr. Wright! It's set up so you can Fast Forward, Rewind or Pause the video. Just take a good look and be sure to point out the right thing!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Please don't play it too many times. I-I can't stand watching this video!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How did this guy ever become a police officer?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Wright. Please enlighten us! Where is the contradiction that indicates the man may not be Detective Goodman?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The thing that's strange about this video... has got to be this!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes, that is strange. Something certainly seems unnatural about that. What could it mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry to interrupt, Mr. Wright... but you seem to have forgotten the point of this exercise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The point...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What you are looking for is one thing and one thing only: Something that indicates the man may not be Detective Goodman.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whew... I almost walked right into the defense's trap!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I'll place him under arrest, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Rats... I need to slow down and tackle these things one piece at a time. Now what do I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Very well. Let's try this again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just remember one thing, Mr. Wright: Every time you point your finger, someone gets hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But he's the one pointing his finger...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It seems I've been taking the wrong approach.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, the defense may resume its cross-examination. Assuming the witness is still willing to continue, that is. Officer Meekins?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! It is my duty as a police officer to help those lost, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great. Now they think I'm lost...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The thing that's strange about this video... would have to be... uh, this?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Hold on a second. I need to use my eye drops. ... Well, I don't get it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Um, would you mind if I borrowed your eye medicine?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Don't look at me with those bleary eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Before your eyes get too teary, perhaps you should think this through again, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now what do I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Very well. Let's try this again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just remember one thing, Mr. Wright: Every time you point your finger, someone gets hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But he's the one pointing his finger...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It seems I've been taking the wrong approach.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, the defense may resume its cross-examination. Assuming the witness is still willing to continue, that is. Officer Meekins?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! It is my duty as a police officer to help those lost, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great. Now they think I'm lost...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Regarding the video contained on this tape, there is one thing in particular that seems rather strange.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Strange?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This contradiction leads to the possibility that... the man may not be Detective Goodman.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What? This video contains such a contradiction?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Interesting... Your Honor, I have a proposal.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I propose we have the defense... point out to us this alleged "contradiction" in the video.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He would want me to point it out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, proposal accepted. Let us further inspect this piece of evidence. I will now play the security tape. Mr. Wright. Please show us this contradiction you speak of.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to point out a problem in the video? This is the first time I've ever had to do that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">You can do it, Mr. Wright! It's set up so you can Fast Forward, Rewind or Pause the video. Just take a good look and be sure to point out the right thing!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Please don't play it too many times. I-I can't stand watching this video!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How did this guy ever become a police officer?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Wright. Please enlighten us! Where is the contradiction that indicates the man may not be Detective Goodman?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The thing that's strange about this video... has got to be this!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes, that is strange. Something certainly seems unnatural about that. What could it mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry to interrupt, Mr. Wright... but you seem to have forgotten the point of this exercise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The point...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What you are looking for is one thing and one thing only: Something that indicates the man may not be Detective Goodman.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whew... I almost walked right into the defense's trap!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I'll place him under arrest, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Rats... I need to slow down and tackle these things one piece at a time. Now what do I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Very well. Let's try this again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just remember one thing, Mr. Wright: Every time you point your finger, someone gets hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But he's the one pointing his finger...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It seems I've been taking the wrong approach.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, the defense may resume its cross-examination. Assuming the witness is still willing to continue, that is. Officer Meekins?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! It is my duty as a police officer to help those lost, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great. Now they think I'm lost...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The thing that's strange about this video... would have to be... uh, this?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Hold on a second. I need to use my eye drops. ... Well, I don't get it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Um, would you mind if I borrowed your eye medicine?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Don't look at me with those bleary eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Before your eyes get too teary, perhaps you should think this through again, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now what do I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Very well. Let's try this again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just remember one thing, Mr. Wright: Every time you point your finger, someone gets hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But he's the one pointing his finger...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It seems I've been taking the wrong approach.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, the defense may resume its cross-examination. Assuming the witness is still willing to continue, that is. Officer Meekins?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! It is my duty as a police officer to help those lost, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great. Now they think I'm lost...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This all sounds true enough, but the victim's body was found at the Prosecutor's Office. There has to be a mistake somewhere...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">The real thing's so much more intense than in the movies! Here, you can use the player to watch it as much as you'd like.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The security video... <thought>Maybe I should take another look at the footage...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The thing that's strange about this video... has got to be this! Officer Meekins.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir! D-do you mean me, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As I understand it, the locker apparatus works like this: When you grab the handle, a sensor reads your fingerprint. If the print matches the registered data, the light turns on and the lock is released.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">A-according to my very limited experience, that's the way I understand it, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If so, then something is seriously wrong with this picture! When the victim reaches for the handle to open the locker... Let's rewind to a little earlier... Here! Notice the light?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this!? It's... already lit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Precisely my point, Your Honor. The locker was already open before the victim grabbed the handle!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">AAAAAAAAHHHHH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! What's the meaning of this!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's very simple, Your Honor. The locker wasn't locked on the day of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But the locker locks are controlled by an electronic system. When a door is shut, a sensor is triggered... and the locker is automatically locked!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, I know! It must have broken down! Of course, I'm not an expert in this...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's not likely, Your Honor. The sensor would detect and report any malfunction.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh well. It just goes to show novices should keep their mouths shut. So then, Mr. Wright. Do you have an explanation?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes. Why wasn't the locker locked?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me, Your Honor? ... Yes, well. You see... This isn't exactly my field... What do you think, Miss "Scientific Investigator"?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh? Oh, um... Maybe something, like, jammed the electronic system?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something... jammed the sensor? Say... There's something else that seems out of place in this video.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah, I thought so too! There's got to be another clue somewhere in this footage!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Let's inspect the video once more. The locker wasn't locked... Mr. Wright. Please point out the cause for this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The thing that's strange about this video... has got to be this!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh yes, that! I found that quite disturbing myself! Such sloppiness should not be accepted in any law enforcement agency!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, no Your Honour. That's not exactly what I meant...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems yet again you've lost sight of the problem at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The reason the locker was not locked. That is the one and only thing you must point out here, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whew... It seems I almost walked right into the defense's trap again!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Now I'll REALLY place him under arrest, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've got to stay focused on that locking mechanism.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The thing that's strange about this video... would have to be... uh, this?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Hold on a second. I need to use my eye drops. ... Well, I don't get it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Um, would you mind if I borrowed your eye medicine?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Don't look at me with those bleary eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Before your eyes get too teary, perhaps you should think this through again, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please watch closely. This is the continuation of the part I showed you earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this? Something white fell out of the locker!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We can't be sure that item was in the locker to begin with.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The sensor triggers the lock when the door is shut... What if something was inserted, say, between the sensor and the door?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In... Inserted...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This white thing wasn't inside the locker... It was stuck between the door and the sensor!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Oh, I understand now, sir! It's just like my tie! Two out of three times it gets stuck in the door when I get out of my patrol vehicle, sir! Instead of the door closing, My tie chokes me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But the object would have to be extremely thin to fit in the door.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not only that, it would also have to block electrical currents... It would need to be an insulator.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, an insulator! But at the crime scene...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">there just might have been something that fits the description.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">But s-sir! By "insulator," you don't mean...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I've finally got this figured out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well! Will the defense please present the relevant evidence! What was this insulator that was stuck in the door?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Behold! This was stuck in the locker door!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How about sticking your finger in instead?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You are rather thin. It just might fit...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think my own current's just been blocked.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Instead of being sarcastic, why don't you think this through again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something thin enough to slip in the door, yet not conductive to electricity...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I found this near the locker: a thin rubber glove.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But we can't be sure that was in the victim's locker.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It has a tag that says, "SL-9 Incident."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The video seems to depict the victim opening the locker, but that isn't the case! The lit lamp attests to this. On the day of the crime, even I could have opened that locker! Is this not so, Officer Meekins!?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir... It would appear so, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! So are we to believe then, that the "victim" whom this witness stabbed in the evidence room... was not Detective Goodman?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do not be misled, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The defense has merely demonstrated that possibility, and nothing more. The "victim" in the video was indeed Bruce Goodman. The prosecution will offer one more testimony to prove this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Officer Meekins, please testify about this.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir! M-me, sir!? I'm not sure what you're referring too, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">O-oh! You mean that, sir! Of course, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is this a joke...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, begin your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">There's one other thing that proves the man was Detective Goodman, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">An ID card record. I see...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have the ID card record right here, Your Honor. The ID used at 5:14... is that of the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Just before the crime, hmm? Yes, without a doubt this is the victim's ID! However, one thing does strike me as unusual... Several hundred cases should have been due for transferal. Why were there so few people using this room?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This particular evidence room is only used for storing certain special cases.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Special" cases...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Extremely violent cases involving police staff.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Just hearing that makes my hair stand on end!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Me too, although it doesn't make much of a difference...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There were only a few cases up for transferal there, and most were cleared up by noon.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Right... I see. Now, Let us move on to the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">There's one other thing that proves the man was Detective Goodman, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, unlike your earlier testimony, you believe this to be rock solid, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! Solid as stone, sir! If my hand wasn't wrapped in bandages... I'd even give the 'V for Victory' sign, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Couldn't he just use his right hand for that...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's hear him out. The witness can't afford to make any more mistakes.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">To enter the evidence room, one must use their ID card!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that card hanging from your neck one of these ID cards?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! This card right next to my cuffs, sir! I keep it here so I won't ever forget it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But what if someone were to steal it from you, keeping it out in the open like that?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">... Maybe I shouldn't wear it around my neck... Remember when I said two out of three times my tie gets stuck in my car door when I get out? Well, the remaining time my ID card gets stuck. Instead of the door closing, my ID card chokes me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe I should just leave this one alone...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">At any rate, each police officer has only one ID card. Both the Police Department and the Prosecutor's Office can attest to this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please proceed with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">When an ID card is used, there's a record of it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let it be noted that this is the record the witness referred to.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let me see... yes, that would be it. Detective Goodman...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">? <thought>What's the matter?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-according to this... Mr. Edgeworth! Your name is on here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So it is, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You've got the wrong color, kid.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would seem... the inquiry committee will want to speak with you again today.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have nothing to be ashamed of regarding my actions, or their consequences. For now, let us continue with the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Poor Mr. Edgeworth... It must be so difficult for him...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">At the time of the crime, the detective had used his card!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Earlier I believe you testified that when you asked the man to show his ID card, he pulled a knife on you.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! He didn't show me any ID card, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't you think that's odd? I mean, if he had his ID card, all he had to do was show it to you. There wouldn't be any reason to draw a knife!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">... M-maybe he just panicked?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Everything stems from contradictions. Let's point them out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! What do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm... confused.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The problem with this ID card testimony is far too obvious. It's not like Edgeworth to miss something like this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">You're thinking too hard about it. Come on, let's show them what we've got!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait one moment, Officer Meekins.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I-I'm not good at waiting, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have the victim's ID card right here. I found it at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That makes sense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When I say, "crime scene," I'm not referring to the evidence room at the Police Department. I mean the "other" crime scene... The underground parking lot at the Prosecutor's Office!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor... I have one more piece of evidence to present. It's a very important clue regarding the victim's ID card.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A... Lost Item Report? It's only half completed,</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">but it shows that Detective Goodman had lost "something" on the day of the crime. Something important enough to fill out this report.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let me guess. You believe this "something" to be his ID card, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't say for sure... but there is a high probability! On the day of the crime, Detective Goodman was not carrying his card!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! So now... what does this all mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It can only mean one thing. It doesn't require much thought! The man Officer Meekins encountered in the evidence room... was not Detective Goodman, but rather the man who stole his ID card!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! Does the prosecution have a response?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I have only one thing to say to the defense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Bravo, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-bravo...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Allow me to summarize the defense's argument. At 5:15 PM on the day of the crime, the man Officer Meekins encountered in the evidence room was not Detective Goodman. There are two grounds to support this. First, the locker in the evidence room was already unlocked. Second, the victim lost his ID card. Am I correct so far, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... <thought>What's he up to?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That being the case, we must inevitably arrive at a single conclusion: If the "victim" in this video is a fake... then the murder in the evidence room is also fake! In other words, the security camera does not show the instant of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... Th-that is... Well, I guess that's right...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is something wrong, Mr. Wright? Only moments ago you seemed content to be pointing your finger around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This isn't good...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, well... It seems you've finally realized... exactly what you've gone to such lengths to prove!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Explain yourself, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The defense has already done the explaining for me. The victim in this video is a fake... which means a murder did not take place at the Police Department at 5:15 on the day of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So the real crime could only take place at one location: the underground parking lot at the Prosecutor's Office! The murderer being Ms. Lana Skye, the defendant! The evidence is compelling! A trustworthy witness... observed the moment the defendant used the murder weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaah! <thought>I knew that testimony was way too shabby. It was all a trap from the beginning!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The activity in the evidence room still leaves many questions unanswered: Who exactly was the "victim" Officer Meekins encountered? And where did this person disappear to...? However... This trial's purpose is to examine only the murder of Detective Goodman.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just so, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! You have to do something, or else Lana...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What do I do? How am I supposed to get myself out of this mess?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better pace myself. If I rush ahead, I might run right into another trap!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">But Mr. Wright! If you don't do anything...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems the defense is out of ammunition.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The surrender flag has been raised. Your Honor, may we have your ruling now?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Don't give up, Mr. Wright! Get up and fight!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One moment, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What now, Mr. Wright? Don't tell me you're objecting to what you've just proven.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course not. But I almost walked right into the prosecution's trap!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This cross-examination has proven one thing and one thing only. The security video did not show the actual murder. However! It cannot be said that it is unrelated to the murder in the parking lot. Specifically, large amounts of blood traces were found in the evidence room!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense demands further examination into the truth of the matter!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If this court were to examine this further, other witnesses will be necessary. Is the prosecution prepared?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sorry, Your Honor... The prosecution considered the incident at the Police Department to be unrelated. We have not prepared any other witnesses for this incident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This just might be my chance. Time to call a certain Texas ranger to the stand!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright... Do you mean...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor. The defense would like to request a specific witness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh? Whom do you have in mind?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Someone we have reason to believe knows the truth... The truth behind the activities that took place in the evidence room.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution requests to hear this person's name before deciding whether or not to comply.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, then. Mr. Wright! This person whom you would have testify... What is his or her name?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, I'm not even going to bother asking you why. I've never seen a more obvious stall tactic in my entire career!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! Don't you remember what you said this morning!? You know, about your "trump card"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's right! Those bloody fingerprints we found in the evidence room... Now's my chance to bring him in to testify!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Officer... Jake Marshall.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't let him know everything just yet...</thought> He's in charge of the evidence room. I feel we should hear what he has to say.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution agrees to the defense's request. Since he was responsible for guarding the room, we should hear his testimony. Fortunately he works in the Police Department. We shouldn't need longer than 20 minutes to prepare.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court will take a 30 minute recess while the witness is subpoenaed. Will the prosecution please prepare the witness during this time?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We will, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court in recess!</line>
<line speaker="Lana">... There's no stopping you is there, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">You called for Jake Marshall. It seems you've figured everything out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... <thought>I haven't figured anything out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Lana... You're the one who knows everything!</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Ema...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You always know everything! Why don't you just tell us!? Mr. Wright is trying his hardest to protect you!</line>
<line speaker="Lana">I... I don't recall ever asking for his "protection."</line>
<line speaker="Ema">How can you be so cold... Don't you trust us? Don't you trust... me?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hope I'm not interrupting anything, pals.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh... Guess I am. I'll come back later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, Detective Gumshoe! What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You've got a lot of nerve, pal! Making a detective run all around while on duty, and to top it off you call me here... I've seen happier people at funerals!</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Sorry, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You better be, pal...Hey... Hey! Hey!! Hey!!! Hey!!!! I didn't see you there, Ms. Skye!</line>
<line speaker="Lana">That's ok. So... Have you brought what I asked?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh... Oh ho! Oh ho ho! Oh ho ho ho! Oh ho ho ho ho ho ho! You mean this, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">My apologies, Detective. Due to my present circumstances, I was forced to use Mr. Wright's name when making my request.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My name!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Never in a million years would I have thought it was you who asked me, "Could I bother you to bring me the SL-9 Incident files?" "I'll need them by noon." Talk about crazy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The "SL-9 Incident"?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But Lana! That's...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">I thought Mr. Wright might need them, so I had them brought here. Here. You might do well to read them.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't believe you, the Chief Prosecutor, were a witness in that case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Skye... was a witness?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Take it from me, you don't want anything to do with serial murders.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, what? Now that I've brought you your stuff, you're just gonna ignore me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Ema! But why... Why is your name in here?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What? My name's in there!? I don't know... Unless... No, it couldn't be... Lana! This "SL-9 Incident"... Is that...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">... That's the classification number the police filed it under. Two years ago, the rest of the world knew it as... the "Joe Darke Killings."</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The... Joe Darke... No... No, Lana! That's over with! No!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ema, wait! <thought>She ran away...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A number is engraved on the back of the badge. I wish they'd put my name on it instead...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His name and ID number is written on it. "Detective Bruce Goodman, ID# 5842189"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"King of Prosecutors." The names of past recipients are etched on the plate. Manfred von Karma's name appears too... How ironic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim Bruce Goodman's blood still remains on the blade. I wonder if Edgeworth got this knife because the handle matches his clothes...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Miles Edgeworth - 17:12"... It's dated the day of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come to think of it, I don't have a strap on my mobile phone at all. I hate having useless things dangling off it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The redial button. It dials the number of the last person called. The last call was to Ema. I wonder what they spoke about...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Blood is splattered over the white enamel surface. It must be Lana's blood, form the cut on her right hand she now has bandaged.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These blood traces are from Bruce Goodman, the victim. He must have tried to run after he was stabbed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"SL-9" is written on a small tag attached to the knife. It was the weapon used in that incident two years ago; and has known many victims.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ema Skye is written on the side in permanent marker. She seems awfully possessive about a can of luminol.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"AI-16" is written on the tag. That means it has nothing to do with the current case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"SL-9 11" is written on the tag. It seems this is more evidence from that incident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a trace of old blood on this jar. This was evidence in the SL-9 Incident... The blood must be from back then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The jar has no bottom, so the hole goes right through. I wonder if it's really jar, or some kind of weird telescope...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Uh, ya know what? I just remembered... I gotta be somewhere. Sorry pal, but I'm outta here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Jake Marshall, Angel Starr, Damon Gant, Miles Edgeworth... Not to mention Lana and Ema...</thought> Everyone involved in this case is connected to those killings two years ago... This can't be just a "coincidence."</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Knowing you, you just might be able to figure it out. Time to get back to the trial, Mr. Wright. Best of luck.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better take a good look at this file...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will now reconvene for the trial of Ms. Lana Skye.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ema didn't come back...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Allow me to call the next witness to the stand: the officer in charge of guarding the evidence room on the day of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Witness, please state your name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Me, pardner? Oh, I'm just a man, same as you, wanderin' the trails of civilization,</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">occasionally helping the elderly cross intersections when needed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, I know! You're a "patrolman"!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">As for my name, if you listen hard 'nuff, you can hear the howling wind calling it out.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To be exact, it's Jake Marshall... Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Howling wind"...? I've never heard Edgeworth described that way before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, Mr. Marshall. Let me ask you something. You were in charge of guarding the evidence room on the day the crime took place. Is this correct?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">According to the papers, pardner.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">A desperado's soul is as boundless as the desert sands. No "paper" can sum it up.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Maybe it's best we get on with this quickly. Please share with us your testimony of the day of the crime... in English!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">My job was to keep a wary eye on that bone orchard.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can't say I particularly care for your attitude...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I can't say I care for your beard, but you don't see me complainin'.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a minute... What do you mean by "two security systems"?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I mean the security cameras and the ID card reader. I reckon even a cowpoke like you knows about those.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, well, what about the fingerprint activated locks inside the evidence room?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Fingerprint activated locks? What kind of new-fangled doohickeys are those?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's not being very helpful...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He's not that good with machines... or with following orders.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Everyone's got their weaknesses, now don't they, Mr. Prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This one seems like trouble. Okay Mr. Wright, he's all yours.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">My job was to keep a wary eye on that bone orchard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How exactly did you "keep an eye" on the evidence room?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I just made sure nothing moved in the security camera monitor. That room's so still, even time dies in there. I was just a caretaker who interred the recordings.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You "interred" them?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Videos of nothing aren't that useful. When the time would come, I'd erase the tape.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If nothing unusual is recorded, tapes are to be erased every six hours.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Each time I'd erase a tape, it felt like I was erasing a part of my life.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This guy has a flare for the dramatic, but it isn't going to do him any good.</thought> So, in actuality you don't physically enter the evidence room?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">They said I was supposed to make rounds three times a day, but that ain't my style.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you made your rounds on the day of the crime, right?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Ain't you heard a word I said, pardner? I told you that ain't my style.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Um, I'm afraid I don't understand.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">No desperado I know lets "rules" get in his way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No desperados I know join the police force...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, Officer Marshall. On the day of the crime...?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Just between you and me, I didn't set foot in the evidence room that day.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There was a rubber glove stuck in the victim's locker. Do you know anything about that?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Sorry pardner, can't say I do. I haven't been in that crypt in weeks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How does this guy avoid being fired...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Besides, the room's protected by two security systems, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You used to be a detective, so you've used the evidence room in the past, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Of course. Back in the day my locker was a goldmine of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And yet... you didn't know about the fingerprint locking mechanism?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Sorry, pardner. I ain't good with machines. I couldn't even tell you how a bike works.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's quite, uh... incredible.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The sensors on the locker handles cannot be seen. It's well known that some detectives are unaware of their presence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that he mentions it, Detective Gumshoe said something like that too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">At any rate, it doesn't seem that this is relevant to the crime. Can you tell us what you were doing when the crime took place?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">If I remember right, I was at a street-side saloon at the time it went down.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What were you doing in a place like that?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I was eating spaghetti. Not even Angel's steak lunches can beat that parlor's vongole sepia pasta.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you mean to tell us... you abandoned your police duties to eat some noodles?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Not all desperados eat tacos, pardner.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's not what I meant... I hope this has at least taught you a lesson!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's strange... This is usually where Edgeworth says, "Did you not want a raise this year?"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I'm just an innocent travelin' man, so if you're out of ammo it's time I hit the trail.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Out of "ammo," officer Marshall?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">That's right, pardner. Or as you'd call it, "evidence." If you plan to pin me to this crime, then you'd better draw. Otherwise, you're just wastin' my time. My steel horse is waitin' to carry me back west into the sunset.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... One thing seems clear. Despite being responsible for guarding the evidence room, the witness doesn't appear to have seen anything.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Texans don't take orders from anyone. Everyone knows that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Apparently your superiors don't...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay... I have a trump card up my sleeve, so I'd best keep my cool. Before I use it though, I'd better up the ante...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Officer Marshall. Doesn't it strike you as odd? That is, you being called in to testify like this?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">After all, you weren't in the security room at the time of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">And yet you dragged me down here. Explain yourself, pardner.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's quite simple. You left a very large trail behind at the scene. Or, to be exact... a handprint.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Hmph! Listen real good, pardner. Like I said, I'm the caretaker of that crypt. I pay my respects... that is, make my rounds, about once a month. It's only natural my fingerprints would be in there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I only wish it were, Officer, but you see... your fingerprints were covered in blood!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! What's the meaning of this!? Your bloodstained fingerprints were at the crime scene...!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The blood was wiped away. However! A luminol test clearly revealed this! Well, Officer Marshall?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">... It seems to me... there ain't a person in this room with a head on his shoulders.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I take it you have an explanation then, Officer Marshall? About the "bloodstained" fingerprints?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, you may begin your testimony about your fingerprints, found at the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Like I said, it's only natural for my fingerprints to be in that evidence room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... The witness's explanation appears valid, although there's room for doubt.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Life wouldn't be any fun without any doubt, pardner.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense may now cross- examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This guy's hiding something, I can feel it! Now's my chance to prove it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Like I said, it's only natural for my fingerprints to be in that evidence room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's because you... how did you put it... "pay your respects," once a month?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Yeah, that's right. That, and one more thing... That locker happens to be mine.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What!? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I mean what I said. That's the locker I used when I was a detective... the locker I still use. All that's in there now though is a heap of broken dreams.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">It'd be strange if my prints WEREN'T all over that locker.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Apparently his fingerprint data was never changed. He must have been using the fingerprint lock without even knowing it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Are you starting to get the picture, pardner?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The picture...?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">This seal of blood... in the desert, it's just food for the buzzards.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">There's only one reality, and that's this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The security tape...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">So long as my trail isn't in there... you can't say otherwise.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This isn't getting us anywhere, Mr. Wright. Please consider carefully where you're going with this cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, continue your testimony, Officer Marshall.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"Too bad it wasn't me in that video, right, pardner?"</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">One of them just happened to be at the same place as the bloodstained handprint.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So then... What about the bloody handprint?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Wasn't mine. It's no mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please explain.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">My locker is covered with my fingerprints. It just so happened...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">The murderer touched the locker where my fingerprint was by chance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The chances of that happening are a million to one!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">On the contrary, one could argue just the opposite. The chances of that not happening are a million to one! Get one thing straight, pardner. You ain't gonna get no reward for me with a mere fingerprint. You wanna know why?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">The bloodstain and the fingerprint are completely unrelated.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Unrelated?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">They're as different as night and day. Kinda like "cereal" an' "serial." One's got to do with breakfast while the other's a type of murder.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He's right... although seemingly alike, they're totally different.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't see what homonyms have to do with this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Or didn't you know the murderer was wearing gloves?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How do you know that!?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I may be a loner, but I still do my job. I keep up on the reports.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There was a bloodstain at the scene, thought to be left by the murderer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right, it was found on Detective Gumshoe's locker.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, no fingerprints were detected on that handprint.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh yeah, I think we tried that too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...So that would mean... the murderer, wearing gloves, happened to place his hand on top of Officer Marshall's fingerprint.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">That's the only logical conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Are you starting to get the picture, pardner?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The picture...?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">This seal of blood... in the desert, it's just food for the buzzards.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">There's only one reality, and that's this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The security tape...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">So long as my trail isn't in there... you can't say otherwise.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This isn't getting us anywhere, Mr. Wright. Please consider carefully where you're going with this cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, continue your testimony, Officer Marshall.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"Too bad it wasn't me in that video, right, pardner?"</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Too bad it wasn't me in that video, right, pardner?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">You want to tie me to this crime, isn't that right, pardner?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">If so, that video is the only direct evidence you have.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that video is next to useless! It's full of blind spots!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Blind spots?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Places you can't see! The camera's panning back and forth, the floor isn't shown... If someone was familiar with the camera's position, he could leave the room without being caught on tape!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We don't have time for your speculations, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright. If you can show us evidence in this video that indicates Officer Marshall was present, please do so now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I might be walking right into Officer Marshall's trap. It's better to find out a little more information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems we should be moving back to the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Officer Marshall, can you please give your testimony again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Very well. Allow me to point out your mistake, Officer Marshall!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tread carefully, Mr. Wright, or you might wind up being the one making the mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, let's have another look at the video. Show us this incriminating evidence of the witness... Officer Jake Marshall!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There! How's that for evidence!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please allow me to apologize for my colleague, Your Honor. He gets carried away sometimes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, well, this certainly isn't a first.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Will you forgive him too, Officer Marshall? He's not a bad man, just a bit... disillusioned.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Of course. I'm not one to gun down unarmed boys.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh great, now Edgeworth is defending me. Guess that means I missed the mark.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, let's get back to the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't let him squirm out of this one. I've got to find something, something decisive, to tie Officer Marshall to this crime!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Bringing our attention back to the security camera... is a mistake I'm afraid you'll soon not forget, Officer Marshall.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">... The days are short in Texas... and so are our tempers. Could you sum up what you have to say in eight words or less?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Very well. You can clearly be seen in this video!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Exactly eight words... Not bad, pardner.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The key... lies in a certain locker shown in the video.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">See this locker that has a white cloth sticking out? This is the witness's locker.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now then, let's rewind the video a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! The white cloth... it's gone! What's the meaning of this, Officer Marshall!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When the crime took place... The white cloth wasn't there. Then... it suddenly appeared! There's only one explanation: Officer Marshall! You were in the evidence room at the time of the crime! What's more, you opened your locker when the camera was turned away!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! It would seem that's the only-</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Hold your horses! Sorry, pardner... but you got the wrong man.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">So what if my locker was opened? That doesn't mean I'm the one who opened it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">The murderer needed to hide something, so he opened a locker and stuck it in. It's not my fault he happened to choose mine!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">... Why's everyone staring at me like I'm a wanted man?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This guy isn't just playing dumb... He really doesn't know!</thought> Uh, I hate to rain on your parade, but you're the only person who can open that particular locker.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Oh yeah? I call your bluff. You say I opened that locker... Now prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">... You can talk the talk alright, but you got a long ways to go before you can walk the walk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright... I think even I could prove this one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-sorry, Your Honor... <thought>If that's Officer Marshall's locker... Then only he can open it. I should know this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Come on, pardner. A revolver only holds five bullets. The question is, how many you got left?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">A... "fingerprint" sensor?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We talked about this earlier today. The lockers can only be opened by the detectives they belong to.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">W-what kinda crazy talk is this!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, Detective Gumshoe did mention something about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">In any case, the locks aren't that obvious. There's even some people in the force that don't know about the fingerprint locks!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, sheriff! What do you have to say... in eight words or less?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I only got one word for you, pardner. NOOOOOO!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! Witness! Explain yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">If this is a joke, it's the worst I've ever heard...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I assure you this is no joke, Officer Marshall. Now then, please tell us what you were doing in the evidence room at the time of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ol! Please answer the question!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is he now, a bullfighter?</thought> That's alright, Officer Marshall. I believe we can figure the rest out from here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We can?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have a look at these floor plans. There is no place for someone to hide in the evidence room. Yet, Officer Meekins didn't see Officer Marshall.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that's so, then... where was the witness?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems Mr. Wright has an answer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's right. The only possible conclusion!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then? Let's hear it. Where was Officer Marshall at the time of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Officer Marshall was standing right here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So Officer Meekins didn't notice him standing there... That's almost as credible as Meekins's warp theory.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Your chamber's empty, pardner. Better reload.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now they're ganging up on me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps... You should think a little more about where Officer Marshall was.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Officer Meekins should have seen him in the evidence room. That means the only place he could have been would be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Officer Marshall was standing right here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There? But that's... That's where the victim, Detective Goodman, was!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Correct... unless the man wasn't Detective Goodman. I believe the "victim" in the video is... Officer Marshall! It was you, dressed up like Detective Goodman!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But that's preposterous! Officer Meekins witnessed the detective at the crime scene! Once he saw the man's face, he'd know for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">May I point out though, that Officer Meekins did not know Detective Goodman. He also testified about the man's reaction when confronted.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">When I entered the evidence room, I asked him to show his card, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes? And how did Detective Goodman respond?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">He suddenly pulled a knife on me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something about the Officer's story puzzled me. If the man had his ID card, why didn't he just show it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, he would have needed it to enter the evidence room, so he must have been carrying it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The answer is simple. He couldn't show it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As you can see, Detective Goodman's picture is on his ID card.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, I get it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If he showed that, his cover would have been blown! Officer Meekins would have realized the man wasn't Detective Goodman. Do you have anything to say to this, Officer Marshall?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">... You've got quite an imagination, pardner. We got a term for that. It's called "circumstantial evidence."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Circumstantial evidence...? <thought>He's still denying it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">You're gonna have to do better than that to break a detective. Unless you have hard evidence proving I dressed up as the victim...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I can't say I particularly care for your uncooperative disposition...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I can't say I care for your beard, but you don't see me complainin'.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright? Do you have any evidence? Any evidence proving beyond the shadow of a doubt that Officer Marshall dressed up as the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... <thought>Who am I kidding? I don't have anything like that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I can see the fear in your eyes, pardner. Seems you're the one who couldn't take the desert heat!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! <thought>This can't be happening! It's so obvious he's the one! What can I do...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Hmph. It looks like your lack of experience has finally been exposed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll pass onto you what someone told me when I was just starting out. When you've run into a wall with no place to go, return to the basics.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The basics... <thought>For me, that would be what Mia used to tell me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I shouldn't look for proof that Officer Marshall was in disguise... but rather I should look for evidence that came about because he was in disguise!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why do you think this locker was opened in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's no reason for Officer Marshall to open his locker at the time of the crime. Yet he did, despite the chance that it might be discovered later as it has been.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Which means he didn't originally plan to open his locker...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">According to the defense's argument, Officer Jake Marshall dressed up as Detective Goodman at the time of the crime. Then, after the crime was "committed," he opened his own locker for some unknown reason.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The fact that a white "cloth" is sticking out of the locker seems to indicate that he opened it in order to put the cloth inside.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So... just what exactly is this piece of cloth?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Perhaps... Perhaps the video is the key to all our unanswered questions. <thought>I don't have any evidence, so this video's my only shot!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Let's take yet another look at the security tape. After commiting the crime, the witness opened the locker to put away the white cloth. Please show us why the witness had to open his locker!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, what do you have to say to that!?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Alright, pardner. You really want to know the reason I had to open my locker?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">So I could stuff you in there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I'm sure the world would be a better place with you sent off to the boneyard.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unfortunately unsolved cases can't be stored in the evidence room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now I'm an "unsolved case"? Something went wrong in that evidence room... That's why Marshall had to open his locker. The accident itself is the reason! I'd better have another crack at this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">For some reason, you disguised yourself as Detective Goodman, and entered the evidence room. I don't know what that reason was... yet.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">"Yet"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However, something unexpected happened. Officer Meekins barged in on you. When asked to show your ID card, you pulled a knife on him. However! Officer Meekins panicked, and the white coat you were wearing was soiled with blood!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A bloody white coat...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You couldn't just walk out like that, so you hid the coat in your locker.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">... Not bad, huh "pardner"?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Officer Marshall. Are you ready to tell us the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Looks like I underestimated y'all. I hope you're happy now, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Two years ago... if you were only half as persistent then as you are today, we all wouldn't have to be here, now would we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Officer Marshall! Tell the court what you did... all of it.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Alright. It seems the time has come.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I had to do it that day. I couldn't just stand by and let it die.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So the supposed "victim" was really you...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But there's one thing I still don't understand. Large quantities of blood traces were found on the floor of the evidence room. If no one was murdered, then how could that be?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Officer Meekins managed to cut his own hand. My guess is he's the donor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looked like too much blood for that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I had to do it that day. I couldn't just stand by and let it die.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When you say "it," you mean...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Do you even have to ask, pardner?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The SL-9 Incident...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Two years have passed since that case was closed. It was going to completely end with the transferal that day.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Not if I have anything to do with it. That incident's not over!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But what did you hope to accomplish by sneaking into the evidence room?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">When a case is closed, only the detective who was in charge of it can look through the evidence. I wanted to have a look at it myself one more time... no matter what the cost. I don't care what anyone says, pardner. That case is mine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But Officer Marshall wasn't in charge of that investigation. Why does he care so much about it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">That day was my last chance. That's why I...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Officer Marshall. May I ask you one thing?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Fire away, pardner. It's a free country. Just remember, I'm also free to decide whether or not to answer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did you do this? Stealing a detective's ID, injuring a police officer... This is no small offense!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Moreover, you're an officer yourself. This will have serious consequences. It can't just be forgiven with a simple cut in salary.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not that salary cuts are ever a valid solution...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">... Like I said. This isn't your case. This one is mine. And I'll do anything it takes to get an answer I'm satisfied with.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... The witness has an unusual amount of zeal. Let's hear more.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"I can't just forget the SL-9 Incident... You know why?"</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I stole the detective's ID and dressed like him. I planned to take out the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did you disguise yourself as Detective Goodman?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">If I didn't make it look like Goodman was carrying out the evidence transferal... I'd be arrested for stealing evidence, which wouldn't get me anywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you did it to fool the security camera.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And the detective's ID card?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I stole that the morning of the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that really was why Goodman started filling out that lost item report.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I returned his ID card. I left it on the floor in the Prosecutor's Office parking lot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The ID card I found was left there by Officer Marshall!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So essentially... You managed to succeed despite your lack of foresight.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">What do you mean... pardner?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I mean the fingerprint- activated lock, of course. No matter how well you disguise yourself, you can't change your fingerprints. Normally, that locker shouldn't have opened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So it opened because a rubber glove was stuck in the door by chance...? Then Detective Goodman must have opened the locker before Officer Marshall!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Officer Marshall. May I ask you one thing?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Fire away, pardner. It's a free country. Just remember, I'm also free to decide whether or not to answer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did you do this? Stealing a detective's ID, injuring a police officer... This is no small offense!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Moreover, you're an officer yourself. This will have serious consequences. It can't just be forgiven with a simple cut in salary.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not that salary cuts are ever a valid solution...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">... Like I said. This isn't your case. This one is mine. And I'll do anything it takes to get an answer I'm satisfied with.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... The witness has an unusual amount of zeal. Let's hear more.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"I can't just forget the SL-9 Incident... You know why?"</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I wasn't expecting Officer Meekins. I knocked him out...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You pulled a knife on Officer Meekins and tried to drive him off?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Let's just say I was a little surprised. I only planned on being in the evidence room for no more than five minutes. I didn't think anyone would actually come in during that short time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Officer Meekins... certainly is a one-in-a- million type of person. Mistaking a detective for an intruder and demanding to be shown his ID...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll have to think a little more about his raise this year...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>When did Edgeworth get so much influence...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Anyway, he threw himself at me, and I ended up cutting him slightly. I'm sorry it had to turn out that way... with me knocking him out and everything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By the way, what happened to your knife?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Oh, you mean this one?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>I don't know what to say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So, what happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Officer Marshall. May I ask you one thing?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Fire away, pardner. It's a free country. Just remember, I'm also free to decide whether or not to answer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did you do this? Stealing a detective's ID, injuring a police officer... This is no small offense!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Moreover, you're an officer yourself. This will have serious consequences. It can't just be forgiven with a simple cut in salary.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not that salary cuts are ever a valid solution...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">... Like I said. This isn't your case. This one is mine. And I'll do anything it takes to get an answer I'm satisfied with.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... The witness has an unusual amount of zeal. Let's hear more.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"I can't just forget the SL-9 Incident... You know why?"</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">and managed to escape. I knew which areas wouldn't be caught on the camera.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you did your research beforehand.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Those who go into the desert unprepared don't live long, pardner. I didn't think it would make a difference though. The security tape is erased every six hours. If all had gone as planned, no footage would have been left.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However... You bloodied your coat in your struggle with Officer Meekins.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">If someone was in the security room when I came out, the jig would have been up. I opened my locker and stashed it in there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was Officer Meekins doing during that time?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">What else? He was sleeping like a baby.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So what you're saying is, on that day...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Officer Marshall. May I ask you one thing?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Fire away, pardner. It's a free country. Just remember, I'm also free to decide whether or not to answer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did you do this? Stealing a detective's ID, injuring a police officer... This is no small offense!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Moreover, you're an officer yourself. This will have serious consequences. It can't just be forgiven with a simple cut in salary.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not that salary cuts are ever a valid solution...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">... Like I said. This isn't your case. This one is mine. And I'll do anything it takes to get an answer I'm satisfied with.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... The witness has an unusual amount of zeal. Let's hear more.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"I can't just forget the SL-9 Incident... You know why?"</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">There wasn't any murder in the evidence room at 5:15.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the blood found at the scene certainly indicates a crime took place!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">What are you, blind? The "victim" shown on that tape is me, and I'm not dead yet, pardner.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, you stole the evidence from the locker?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Actually... no, I didn't.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">When I opened the locker, the evidence was already gone.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What!? Mr. Edgeworth. Where is that evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's still missing, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Detective Goodman's locker was already empty... Someone else stole the evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Officer Marshall. May I ask you one thing?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Fire away, pardner. It's a free country. Just remember, I'm also free to decide whether or not to answer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did you do this? Stealing a detective's ID, injuring a police officer... This is no small offense!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Moreover, you're an officer yourself. This will have serious consequences. It can't just be forgiven with a simple cut in salary.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not that salary cuts are ever a valid solution...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">... Like I said. This isn't your case. This one is mine. And I'll do anything it takes to get an answer I'm satisfied with.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... The witness has an unusual amount of zeal. Let's hear more.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"I can't just forget the SL-9 Incident... You know why?"</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I can't just forget the SL-9 Incident... You know why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that case was solved two years ago, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's the reason the evidence was stored in the evidence room.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Joe Darke was convicted for those crimes. One thing I can say for sure, he deserved his sentence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I remember the Joe Darke case... It involved serial murders, didn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I don't intend to complain about how it turned out, but there's something that still bothers me. Something went down at that trial. Something no one will talk about.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What happened?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I don't know. That's what I'm trying to find out.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why is he so concerned with that incident? Maybe I should present him with what I think his real reason is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I had a feeling we'd wind up here sooner or later... Everyone involved here is related in some way to that case... I'd better take another look at the files.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Officer Marshall, I think I understand. I think I know why you care so much about the SL-9 Incident.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Sounds like you've been sipping too much cactus juice, pardner.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have the SL-9 Incident file here. The name "Marshall" is mentioned in here...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">in a list of murder victims. "Neil Marshall"... Are you related to this man?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Neil Marshall...?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Yeah, I'm sure you've heard the name. Two years ago... he received the same lousy prosecutor award you got.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What!? A prosecutor...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He must be talking about the King of Prosecutors award.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now I remember... Prosecutor Neil Marshall. He handled the SL-9 case before I did.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">That's right. He was killed... and the case fell into your hands.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But what's his relation to you...?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">He was my brother. He was investigating the murders with Damon Gant, Chief Detective at the time. The group of detectives I was part of worked under them. We were desperate to prosecute the killer. Joe Darke... My brother fought Darke and was killed. That was the first time Darke left behind any evidence. That was all we needed. He was arraigned and incarcerated. The case was finally closed... at least, according to the public records.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">My brother couldn't have been killed by Joe Darke. I knew my brother better than anyone... No one could have beaten him in a fight.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And that's it? That's your reason for your insane actions?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">There's more to my brother's death than what the records say. No matter how much you try to hide it, you can't fool me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... at least one thing's for certain. Now we know what happened at the Police Department on the day of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That was the last day the SL-9 case could be reopened. Not satisfied with its resolution, Officer Marshall planned to steal the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Disguising himself as Detective Goodman, he entered the evidence room. Officer Meekins confronted him, so he rendered him unconscious and fled.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, this mystery has finally been cleared up. No murder took place at the Police Department that day!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The things that happen by chance never cease to amaze... At exactly the same time as the murder at the Prosecutor's Office... this fake murder was going on at the Police Department.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Chance...? It's got to be more than just that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So if no one was murdered at the Police Department on the day of the crime, that means the murder in the Prosecutor's Office's parking lot was the real one.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Which, in turn, means... only one person could have committed the crime: Chief Prosecutor Lana Skye.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-but wait! A verdict wasn't reached in yesterday's trial!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Which is why we examined the incident at the Police Department today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's only one reason the defendant was not convicted yesterday: there yet remained the mystery of the simultaneous murder at the Police Department.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">It seems to me... this boy's got the draw on you, pardner.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">All the mysteries at the Police Department have been uncovered. No contradictions remain. The murder took place at the Prosecutor's Office! The only suspect is Lana Skye. There were no errors in the testimony of the witness, Angel Starr! If you have a response... make it one word or less.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... ARRRGHHHH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I rest my case.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems this trial has reached its conclusion. There's no room for doubt.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well done, Mr. Wright. Thanks to you, I didn't need to waste my time... disproving the alleged "murder" at the Police Department.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's no doubt what I proved today is true... The apparent murder on the security camera's tape really was fake! But I didn't realize... that would end up proving Lana guilty!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, the time for the verdict has arrived. This court finds the defendant...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Y-your Honor! Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ema!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The defense has an objection. A scientific objection! Right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean, "right?"</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Are you this girl's guardian?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! Oh, uh... in a sense...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Please, Your Honor. All I'm asking is for a minute of your time! Please hear me out! Mr. Edgeworth, please...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I don't want to leave any loose ends. You want a minute? I'll give you three.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I... I was kind of in shock. I mean, finding out that the SL-9 incident referred to the Joe Darke Killings!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that she mentions it... the names of both Skye sisters were in that file.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">But that's when I figured it out. I mean, what Officer Marshall was trying to do that day... So I knew his fingerprint had nothing to do with the crime. That left only one thing... the other handprint!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You mean the traces of blood found on Detective Gumshoe's locker...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But no fingerprints were found on it, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No, but I figured if I examined it scientifically... I'd be sure to find a clue! So I ran over there and looked at it again!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um... No!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sorry. I guess I'm not much of a scientific investigator after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Is that all?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Please don't be mad. I'm just a high school student!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And I'm just an attorney...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">But Mr. Wright! Those traces of blood are the only clue we have! If we can't find something wrong with them... Please, Mr. Wright. You're a professional. If anyone can save Lana, it's you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me? Oh boy...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Time's up. Now then, Mr. Wright. With regard to the incident at the Police Department... Does any reasonable doubt remain?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It appears the defense is troubled by the other blood mark. Looking at the floor plans, a handprint was discovered around here. Is there a problem with this?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! I'm sorry I can't be of more use... But still! If you can't find anything wrong with that blood mark, Lana will be...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please answer my question, Mr. Wright. We don't have all day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, Your Honor. <thought>If ever I've needed to concentrate, it's now! What could be wrong with that handprint on Detective Gumshoe's locker? Could there be something I'm missing...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've got to be honest... I don't see anything wrong with it! Still... If I give up now, Lana's going to be convicted for sure...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This handprint left at the crime scene... clearly shows a contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The only thing that seems clear is you're grasping, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You've been staring pretty intently at those floor plans. Tell me... is there a problem with them?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Yes, this is strange...!</thought> Take a good look at these floor plans. Something is missing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Missing"...? You mean, something hasn't been drawn on there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. Something that, when drawn, will completely change the meaning of the blood mark!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let us pray the defense isn't simply trying to buy time. Very well, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>With all this evidence here... there's got to be something I can use!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The question is... which item can prove something is missing in the floor plans?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">As they say back west... "Even a blind man can hit with buckshot." That is... so long as he's facin' the general direction.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems Mr. Wright's not sure which direction to face.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's no use! The more evidence there is, the more wrong choices!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Just calm down, Mr. Wright. Try and remember what the evidence room was like on the day of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is it that bothers me about this blood mark..?</thought> Please allow me another chance, Your Honor. I'll prove it this time!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">What about that piece of plywood?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Blue Badger! Mascot of the police force! Defender of truth, guardian of proof!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Explain yourself, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please look at the floor plans of the crime scene. The Blue Badger is not here.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">So?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So watch what happens when we put him in. This is where he was dancing at the time of the crime. Well...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. So long as the Blue Badger is dancing here... it would be impossible... to place a handprint at this spot on the locker!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Whaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So that means... Uh... just exactly what does that mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It means it can't be done!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What are you saying? Blood traces were undeniably found on that locker!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't look at me, I didn't put it there!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! Think it through scientifically!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ema!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">On that afternoon... Officer Meekins was the one who brought the Blue Badger to the evidence room, right? After he put it down, it would be impossible to leave a handprint on that locker.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! So that must mean this blood mark... was left there before the Blue Badger was brought in...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Just one moment! I will not allow such farfetched balderdash in my courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It may sound farfetched, Your Honor... but it's the only possible explanation! On February 21st... in the Police Department's evidence room... blood was spilled not once, but twice!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">B-but how...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One time was captured on this tape, taken by the security camera. Officer Meekins cut his hand, from which a trivial amount of blood fell. The problem is... the "other" time. Someone bled prior to the struggle shown on this tape. It had to have been... Detective Goodman, when he was really murdered!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's ridiculous! I refute you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The murder portrayed in the security tape has been proven to be a fake. However! That does not explain the blood mark found on the locker!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So then... assuming this "murder" you purport really happened. When did it take place!? I demand you show evidence that proves it occurred!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>When did the first incident occur...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">To surmise, the defense claims that... prior to Officer Meekins being cut by Jake Marshall, who was disguised as Detective Goodman, another "incident" took place in that evidence room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The blood mark on the locker proves this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Then tell us... When did this "first" incident occur? Proof must be presented.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Proof that shows when the murder took place... There's only one piece of evidence that can show that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then. Will the defense please present its evidence? What shows when the "first" crime took place?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the proof! It's quite simple, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If it's so simple, then don't get it wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If "huh" was an acceptable excuse, we wouldn't need police.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The first crime took place before the Blue Badger was brought to the room, right? Say... When was the Blue Badger brought there, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't we have a time chart among our evidence items that lists the time?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If the crime took place inside the evidence room, then the perpetrator would had to have entered the room. In order to do so, an ID card is required.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">An ID card... Oh! The ID Card Record!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Officer Meekins brought the Blue Badger panel into the evidence room at...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's see here... 4:50 PM. If the crime took place before that time, then it would be... 4:40 PM... Ah! AAAAAAAHHH! M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-Miles Edgeworth! Just what have you done!?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I never figured you had nerve, boy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Put off the act, witness. It doesn't take a lot of thought to figure out it couldn't have been me.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Hmm... Nope, I ain't gettin' it...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I'm afraid I don't understand either.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's clear from the luminol test that blood was there. However, when the "second" crime took place... both Officer Meekins and Officer Marshall failed to notice the blood.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That means... the blood from the first crime was wiped away... by the real murderer.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I would have had just ten minutes to murder the victim, carry his body away, and clean up the blood... Unfortunately that's physically impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That would mean... the crime must have taken place before Mr. Edgeworth entered the evidence room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's look at the chart again. There's only one other card number remaining: "7777777"!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Talk about a lucky number...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But wait... That doesn't make sense! How could Officer Goodman have entered the evidence room?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Since there's no record of his card being used beforehand... he must have entered along with the real murderer. That's the only plausible explanation. He went in with "7777777"!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth! Please look into this ASAP! Find out whose ID number is "sevensevensevensevensevensevensevenseven"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's one "seven" too many, Your Honor. Unfortunately... I'm unable to look up the owner of that ID card. At least, at present.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Explain yourself, son.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The ID number "7777777" belongs to someone with a rank of Captain or higher... Someone who is a so-called "executive officer." We don't have the authority to inquire into such a person's identity.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that's ridiculous! Just how...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm not finished talking, Mr. Wright. There is one situation in which we can be granted such authority.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If an official charge filed against an executive is accepted.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An "official charge"...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">You're all alike, aren't you? With your "cover-ups" and your "forgeries"... That's how the Prosecutor's Office operates!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I take pride in my work, Officer Marshall. I would appreciate it if you would keep your slander to yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">"Slander," is it? Okay. Let me ask a question.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">No, not to you. To her, the defendant sitting over there. Your own little "executive."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>L-Lana?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't be stupid. She's been charged with murder. Of course we've looked up her ID number... and it's not "7777777."</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Don't play me for a fool, pardner. That's not what I want to ask. All I want to know is one thing... about that incident.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The SL-9 Incident?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Answer me this, Chief Prosecutor! In that trial two years ago... Did you really only use legitimate evidence!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you need the witness to repeat his question, Chief Prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">I heard him fine, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Two years ago... I was in charge of the prosecution for that trial. At the time, we...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Occasionally... we felt the powerlessness of the law. At least... I did.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">L-Lana...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">I became a prosecutor in order to suppress crime with the law. But before I realized it, we were the ones being suppressed by the law.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defendant! Just what are you saying!?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I'll ask you again, Chief Prosecutor. During that trial two years ago... did you really present all the evidence in court? Can you look me, an investigator in that crime, in the eye and say that you did?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Chief Prosecutor! You didn't...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">... I don't have to, Officer Marshall.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Drastic crimes require drastic measures... That's just the way it is. We did what we had to... in order for him to get the verdict he deserved.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But Lana!</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Even if it involved "forging" evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">See? That's what I'm talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No... NNNNOOOOOOO!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! ORDERRRRR!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't sound very convinced, Mr. Wright. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This evidence clearly reveals the contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are that evidence and the statement just now related...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They aren't, are they...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Wright, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness's statement is clearly faulty, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry, but I can see nothing faulty. Unfortunately, I will have to penalize you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh, I must be on the wrong track?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! This court sees no reason to further prolong the trial. The defense has failed to give the court sufficient reason to doubt the prosecution's claim! This court find the defendant, Ms. Lana Skye...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accused will surrender to the court immediately, to be held pending trial at a higher court within a month from today's date. That is all. The court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>