<xml>
<title>Rise from the Ashes</title>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm so sorry, Mr. Wright. I'm sorry for what my sister said...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Drastic crimes require drastic measures... That's just the way it is. We did what we had to... in order for him to get the verdict he deserved.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I... didn't know. I never knew that the "SL-9 Incident" was just another name for... the "Joe Darke Killings."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like everyone's heard about these killings but me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Lana wanted Darke convicted so badly! That's why she used me... That's why she used what happened to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean, "what happened" to you?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's all there in the file... Joe Darke's last victim was Prosecutor Neil Marshall. When he murdered Officer Marshall's brother, he left behind an incriminating piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But what did you have to do with those killings, Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">On the night Prosecutor Neil Marshall was murdered, Joe Darke... tried to kill me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? He tried to kill you!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Officer Marshall's brother... Neil... was only trying to save me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that means you...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes. I was a witness in the Joe Darke trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I didn't see that one coming!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Difficult-looking legal books stand in a formidable row. They mock me.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, I tried studying one of those just now. Remember what they were talking about in the trial yesterday...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right, evidence law. So, did you learn anything?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, when I tried reading it made my head hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Then, when I closed it, it slipped out of my hand and fell on my foot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oddly enough I find myself identifying with her on this one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia's desk. I sit here even less now that I've stopped taking cases.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Uh oh! I have a math test coming up next week! I'd better study! I'm borrowing this desk, okay?1 + 1 = 21 + 2 = 31 + 3 = 4</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If that's what they're teaching in high school math, we're in serious trouble.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Goodman didn't have this on the day of the crime, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. A few days before he was murdered, he had filed a lost item report. <thought>Although "stolen item" is more like it... Swiped by that lone wolf who dressed up like him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I never would have thought Officer Marshall the type to do something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It didn't come as much of a surprise to me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was something strange about this shoe, wasn't there? Let's see, what was it...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The traces of blood on its sole. There wasn't any blood found at the Prosecutor's Office's underground parking lot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But we did find blood on the floor somewhere, didn't we? Where was that again...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">In the evidence room at the Police Department. Now stop using me as your memo pad!!!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's only one number left to check out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. We now know the other numbers aren't related to the murder. "7777777"... An "executive officer."</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sevensevensevensevensevensevensevenseven...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, I believe that's one "seven" too many... <thought>We can't find out whose number this is unless we have some incriminating evidence. That's going to be hard to dig up by tomorrow...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Edgeworth is so kind, giving us something like this. Hey! You don't think he... he... likes me, do you? ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you okay, Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! Hurry! RUN!!! AHH-CHOOOO!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">... Here, I'll wipe those fingerprints off your face.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Might as well wipe my dignity away too while you're at it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This screwdriver was at Edgeworth's office, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes. He said it didn't have anything to do with the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Then what are we doing carrying it around?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, don't ask me! I'm not the one making the decisions around here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I recall... Edgeworth said Chief Gant asked him to take this to the Prosecutor's Office.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This jar's pretty fragile.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It looks like it's about to break apart!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean, "about to"? It's already broken.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I meant again...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This piece was found in Detective Goodman's evidence locker. That means...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">This is somehow related to that other incident...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This fingerprint was left on the locker when Marshall was stashing his bloody coat.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I guess that blood wasn't Mr. Goodman's after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nope. Just that of an overly zealous patrolman.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So there wasn't a murder at the Police Department at 5:15 in the end.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder what's going to happen to Officer Marshall now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">We owe our entire success in court today to this tape.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At first I thought it was a joke, but it turned out to be a goldmine of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I counted a total of five clues in it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It also gave the Blue Badger some publicity... of the negative sort, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seems everything is somehow related to this incident.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What was it labeled, again? The "SL-9 Incident"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. The name of everyone connected to this trial is listed in here. All that's left... is to figure out just what role everyone plays in this case. If we search hard enough, I think we'll find our answers. <thought>What exactly did, or didn't, Lana do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm not sure I want to know everything...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Looks like they're questioning Lana again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess we're not the only ones who want to question her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, since we've come all this way, why don't we go see Mr. Meekins?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... Let's not and say we did. <thought>I'd rather come back and do that later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No one's here today... Not even Ms. Starr.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Everyone's probably busy looking into what exactly went down in the evidence room. That must be where the detectives are.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But we proved in court today that no one was murdered in the evidence room at 5:15 PM, on the day of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah. I thought we were finally making some headway in our case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But instead it looks like we just ended up making Lana look even more guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hang in there, Lana...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've got to find all the answers by tomorrow!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, this is the famous divider.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It sure helped us knock a hole in that testimony yesterday. Come to think of it, this divider helped our case more than the actual witness.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The great divider! A chip off the old parking block!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's just a wall. <thought>Scientifically speaking...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's about as red as a sports car can get.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup, it's pretty red alright. <thought>The body was found in Edgeworth's car trunk... And the lock on the trunk was broken. So, the question is why did Ms. Skye chose his car?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, what model car is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I think it was called a "Sedan" or a "Coupe." Something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Those are car types, Mr. Wright. Not models. You're a guy, aren't you, Mr. Wright? Your supposed to know these things!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe it is about time I got my driver's license...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's where we found that note.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"2/21 SL-9"... The SL-9 Incident.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A case that was due for transferal the day of the murder. I never knew... The "SL-9 Incident" referred to...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Joe Darke Killings. <thought>Everyone in this case played some part in that incident. This has to be more than just sheer coincidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Edgeworth isn't here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe he's being questioned by an inquiry committee? <thought>He took a real beating in court today...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah, with&#160;Lana admitting to falsifying evidence two years ago...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess we'll just have to come back later.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">My, my, my! What an amazing bouquet! Just right for Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No kidding. Hey, there's a card on it... "To be or not to be -- Wendy" <thought>"Wendy?" ... I've heard that name somewhere before.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">And beside it... A giant Steel Samurai! Wow, I want one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? There's something written on the bottom of his foot. "To every cloud, there is a silver lining. -- Wendy"</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Was this the same message that was here yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Whoa! What a view! It must be nice to have an office on the 12th floor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess you would feel... important.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Incidentally... Were you to jump out this window, your chance of fatality would be... ... Got it! 99.9998 percent!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's a 0.0002% chance you'd live?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Howdy, Bambina.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, Mr. Marshall!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I never thought things'd turn out this way when I woke up this morning. Que serà serà. You never know where life'll lead you, eh Bambina? I should've known my luck had run out when ol' Billy dried up this morning.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Billy...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Must be his pet cactus. Say, where are you headed?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Just over to the Prosecutor's Office for a little interrogation. It's a "voluntary" appearance, but we all know I won't be coming back. Sorry, but you can't go in the evidence room today, pardner.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But Mr. Marshall... Why did you do it?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Why do prospectors head west? If ever there was a case I needed to know the truth about, it was that one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Before you turn yourself in, Mr. Marshall... would you mind telling us exactly what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Hmph... Looks like I won't be getting a steak lunch today.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The Blue Badger is still writhing around today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's give him the benefit of the doubt and say he's dancing. <thought>Speaking of "dancing"... The whole Police Department has been dancing about like crazy since the other day...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Can I take out his batteries? I just can't help but feel he's going to do something naughty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, that patrolman is saluting the other guy. He must be a detective!</line>
<line speaker="Police">So I cuff the lout, right? Then you know what he says? "What are you, a moron? I'm an undercover agent!"</line>
<line speaker="Patrolman">Oh, man. I hate it when that happens!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">... I guess he wasn't saluting, he was just listening to how his friend messed up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They make a good pair.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Something was fishy about that trial from the beginning. It wasn't just me either. All the detectives thought so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean, "fishy"?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Some of the facts reported were inconsistent with the evidence we found. For example... the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The murder weapon? You mean... that switchblade knife with the broken tip?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">That was Joe Darke's, all right. But... in the initial autopsy report, a question was raised.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A question...?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">The blade of the knife was not a perfect match with the wound the victim sustained.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What does that mean?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">It means there is a good chance that knife was not the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">However, in the report that was finally submitted, that possibility had been erased.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Could the facts have been concealed with forged evidence...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">That case left behind scars on all of us.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The "scars" that the SL-9 Incident left behind...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I got the looks, but he got the brains. He was one of the best prosecutors around. I had just made detective when it went down. It was our first case together...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">How old was he... your brother?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">He was 27 at the time. He was awarded the highest honor that very day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The... "highest honor"? You don't mean...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">King of Prosecutors.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not that again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">What are you looking at me like that for? That's an honor for a prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mr. Marshall must have really been close with his brother.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">The day the SL-9 Incident took place, that wasn't the same day as...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">That's right. It was the day of the evidence transferal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! Interesting...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">It was drizzling that morning, and by nightfall there was thunder. I can't believe two years have gone by already. I tried to steal the evidence so the case wouldn't die.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Apparently someone tried to stop you. Detective Goodman was murdered... and the evidence locker was empty.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">There was something going on behind the scenes in that case. We all knew that later. Every detective involved in that investigation, save one, was... taken care of. Ms. Starr was fired and I was demoted and boxed away in a tiny room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about Detective Goodman?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">If they did something to him too, the commissioners would get suspicious. No, they were careful enough not to be too obvious.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"They"...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Who are you talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Don't get upset, Bambina. I mean Damon Gant... and Lana Skye.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Chief Detective Damon Gant and his second-in-command, Lana Skye... There wasn't a person on the force who hadn't heard of that duo. That case was the biggest step in both of their careers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">After the case ended, Lana transferred to the Prosecutor's Office, right?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Yeah. Damon Gant, the new Chief of Police, arranged for that to happen. She's never been the same since she left.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Everyone who knew her said so. "Chief Prosecutor Skye was totally different when she was a detective."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that he mentions it, Ema said something like that too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Tell me... what happened to my sister!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Sorry, Bambina, but her secret is too well guarded. I never found out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Lana's "secret"... It all started two years ago.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Marshall! Could you please have a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Sorry, Bambina. I'm not a patrolman anymore, and I'm certainly not a detective. I'm nothing more than a wanted man, now. These old eyes of mine have seen too much as it is.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">So there you have it. That's my story. Did you enjoy it, pardner?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was certainly... enlightening.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">There's one thing for sure I found out in court today. That boy Edgeworth isn't my enemy. He was the one who used falsified evidence to get a guilty verdict, but someone else was the one who gave him that evidence and planned everything. That someone is Damon Gant. Don't believe me? Well I don't blame you. I won't even be a patrolman after today. Too bad I won't be around to work with you... when you become a real scientific investigator. Adios Bambina!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't see Detective Gumshoe anywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Things seem kinda quiet around here today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're right. <thought>The head of the department seems the same though.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Why don't we go look for some other people to talk to?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. We can come back here later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Police">"That's it! The villain used a time machine! Very clever indeed... That would explain the alibi! The future might not be so far away after all!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He's not writing a report... he's writing a novel.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That man must be the Head Detective. He's staring at the screen so hard it might shatter.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">What!? "Darke Case May Have Been Fabricated." That's what I thought all along... I just never bothered to tell anyone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now there's a guy who cares about his work...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">It happened two years ago... It was right about this time of the year, too. There was a terrible thunder storm that day... Unusual for the season. I was alone in my sister's office. We were planning to eat dinner together once she finished her work. Then suddenly... This terrifying man came bursting into the office!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Joe Darke...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It seemed like he was running from someone. He pulled out a knife and screamed at me. I didn't know what was going on. Just then, Prosecutor Marshall showed up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Jake Marshall's brother...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Joe Darke tried to take me hostage, but before he could... Mr. Marshall tackled him. Then...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What happened?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I-I'll never forget it! Lightning struck, and the lights went out. Suddenly... a bolt of lightning flashed outside the window, lighting up the office for an instant. What I saw then burned a permanent picture in my mind. I... I can still see it now...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A permanent picture...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I don't remember the moment when Darke stabbed Mr. Marshall.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you weren't able to testify about that? No, I was only asked about when I was attacked. That must be why Lana... why she "made up" the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Made it up? You mean, provided bogus evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The Prosecutor's Office wanted that guilty verdict so badly. Lana forged the evidence, and Mr. Edgeworth used it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes. But I'm sure he didn't know anything about it! He couldn't have known he was being given false evidence. Even so... that's when it all started. The rumors about Mr. Edgeworth, I mean. It's all my fault... If I could have just testified properly, none of this would have happened!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So it's true. Even though he may not have known it... Edgeworth really was involved in falsifying evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">After that case ended, Lana was never the same. She became cold, like she is today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She must not have been able to face up to what she did... Especially not to Ema.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What did you see in the instant that crime occurred?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">... Darke knocked down Mr. Marshall and raised his knife.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Neil Marshall was stabbed right in front of this poor girl!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I don't remember what happened after that. Apparently I passed out. When I came to, Lana was cradling me in her arms.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Poor Ema... You've been through so much.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I-I couldn't bring myself to testify about that instant. I tried, but the words just wouldn't come out. I drew a picture, but it wasn't any good.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Two years ago... You must have been 14. That's understandable.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Once it was all over... I made up my mind. I decided that when I grew up, I'd become a scientific investigator. I want to be able to fight crime with my testimonies! And find the evidence to make an airtight case... That way, Lana would never have to forge any.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... <thought>I think I'm finally starting to understand what makes Ema tick. But there's still something that bothers me about that crime.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's something that's puzzling me, Ema.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You said you were in Lana's office at that time, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why then would a serial killer come running in there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not only that, but he was being chased by a prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, there's no mystery there. Joe Darke had been taken in for questioning that day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Taken in for questioning? You mean by the police?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Of course. This happened at the Police Department. He tried to run away halfway through the interview, and fled into my sister's office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But why did he run all the way over to your sister's office?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Because the detective offices and the questioning room are right across from the elevator.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Across from the elevator? But Lana was the Chief Prosecutor, wasn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No, silly! Didn't I tell you? Two years ago... Lana was a detective. She was the best in the entire force!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaaat!? <thought>That's news to me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">After the Joe Darke case, she was transferred to the Prosecutor's Office and made Chief Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Lana used to be... a detective? I'd better have another talk with her!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">L-Lana...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Mr. Wright. It seems I keep causing you trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Falsifying evidence... I didn't think you were the type.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Criminals don't mind playing foul, why should we?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But Lana! If you're wrong... an innocent person might be found guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Believe me... I understand the risks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lana. Ema told me about you.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About how you were a detective two years ago, and how the SL-9 Incident was the reason for your transfer to the Prosecutor's Office.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you fill me in on the details? Especially about that unusual change of jobs.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">... I suppose you have a right to know, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitors the visitor's room. He seems frozen in place, cowering under this room's oppressive atmosphere.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Attorneys and prosecutors have no business showing evidence outside court. It's taboo. Especially when the interests of both parties are involved.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She really means it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Lana...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A lot of revelations were uncovered at the trial today, not the least of which was the fact that this case is largely connected to another one, two years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Evidence from that case was stolen... I expected as much. I know how obsessive Officer Marshall can be.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That trial... it really wasn't "fair," was it?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I believed in you, Lana! I believed that no matter what happened, you'd always stick to the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Lana">It couldn't be helped, Ema. At that trial two years ago... I sold my soul.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, all drama aside, the fact of the matter is at 5:15, there was no murder at the Police Department.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Tell me it's not true, Lana! What the witness... Ms. Starr said! About you stabbing Mr. Goodman with a knife!</line>
<line speaker="Lana">...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Lana! I don't understand! Why won't you tell us?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Ema... This doesn't involve just me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think I've ever seen Lana look so fazed before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lana">It's true. I was a member of the police force two years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">She was amazing! They still talk about all the cases she and Chief Gant cracked together!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Chief Gant?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Then he was the Vice-Head of Criminal Affairs, but he still worked the crime scenes. Damon Gant... he was everything I aspired to be.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">They were the best team ever! They solved crimes before the reports could even be filed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ema really idolizes her big sister.</thought> But now you're Chief Prosecutor... What happened?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">I always planned on becoming a prosecutor. The reason I became a detective was...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">to gain experience investigating crime scenes, so you could later use that experience in court.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Gant's help in the SL-9 case was critical in its resolution. After that, he became Chief of Police, and arranged my transfer to the Prosecutor's Office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe I should ask more about this "investigation" of theirs two years ago.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lana">Two years ago I was second-in- command of the detectives investigating Darke.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Second-in-command"? That means the Chief Detective was, no doubt, Damon Gant?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Yes. Detective Gant and I shared the same office, and the same investigations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>They even had the same office...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lana">We led a team of the best detectives on the force: Detective Goodman, whose case it was, Jake Marshall and Angel Starr. It was the first time Marshall worked with his brother. He was quite... "gung ho." Without a doubt, Joe Darke was the serial killer. We asked him to come in for questioning. We were desperate for evidence. That was when the last murder took place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>When he tried to murder Ema...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Prosecutor Marshall was trying to save me from Darke...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">You see, the first person who happened upon the scene of the crime... was me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>Now you tell us...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lana">Detective Gant and Prosecutor Marshall were the ones questioning Darke that day. The investigation was in its final stages, when Darke must have panicked. He waited until Gant and Marshall let their guards down, then fled the room. From there, he ran straight to... the office shared by Detective Gant and myself.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's where he found me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you were the first person to run to the scene, Lana?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">It appears so. I was filing some papers while Gant and Marshall were questioning Darke. When I returned to my office, I saw three bodies on the floor and smelled blood.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Three bodies? Prosecutor Marshall, the victim, Ema, who had passed out,</line>
<line speaker="Lana">and the suspect, Joe Darke. During the struggle, it seems Mr. Marshall stuck a final blow before he died. Joe Darke had incurred a minor concussion, and lay unconscious.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What did you do?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">To be honest, I panicked. I picked up Ema, carried her out of the room and just held her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Can't blame her, after all her sister must have gone through.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lana">After that, I placed Darke under immediate arrest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let me get this straight. You were all involved in the SL-9 Incident?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">That's right. Quite a coincidence, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't buy it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">W-what are you saying?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no way everyone involved in this trial was also involved in that incident just by "chance."</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But that case was solved two years ago!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At least one person went to extremes because they didn't believe it was truly solved.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Officer Marshall... Yes, his actions came as a surprise to me as well. Ever since his brother died, he's changed completely.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I guess he wasn't convinced with the ruling against Joe Darke.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">... Life doesn't end with the closing of a case. Everyone has to live the rest of their lives with their memories.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That "case" just might not be over yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ema was assaulted by Darke at the Police Department, right?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Yes, in the office that Damon Gant and I shared. The office that Mr. Gant now occupies by himself: the Chief's office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe we should have a look at the Chief's office - the site of the final SL-9 murder!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This place is always pretty empty, but today it's deserted.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That must mean everyone's busy solving crimes.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Oh, if you're looking for the others, they're all in the conference room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... thanks. <thought>Wow, he actually talked to us!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Chief">With the Chief Prosecutor saying what she did and the decision about what to do about Mr. Edgeworth, not to mention our statement to the media and tomorrow's trial... there's more chaos going on than Thanksgiving and Christmas put together!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think "festive" is the word usually used for those...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um, sir? We'd like to have a look around for Chief Gant's office.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Just head across the hall to the other building and take the elevator to the top floor.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Really? You mean, it's okay for us to go in there? I mean, we aren't police officers or anything.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Hey, you're right! You can't go in there! It's off limits!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now I see where Detective Gumshoe gets his unique charm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, what are wating for? Let's head to the Chief's office!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa... Where am I?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">In the Chief's office, silly! At least, that's what it said on the door.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Check out that pipe organ. That's real, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, I used to take organ lessons in kindergarten! They used to call me "Little Miss Bach." I thought I was a genius until they tried teaching me notes. I never could remember where C was...</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Hm? Oh, it's you two.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Chief Gant! <thought>He put that paper he was reading in his desk.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gant">So, Mr. Wright. Have you been swimming lately?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... no, I haven't. I've been kind of busy lately.</line>
<line speaker="Gant">I can appreciate that. I've had my hands full too, with Mr. Marshall's misconduct and Lana's provocative statement.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Provocative statement"... oh, you mean about the forged evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Two years have passed since that incident. My, how time flies! See that big picture on the wall over there? That's a picture of Lana, Neil and me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So this is Mr. Marshall's brother... Prosecutor Neil Marshall...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gant">We took it to commemorate our work together.</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Anyway, I'd like to reminisce all day, but there are matters that need my attention. I'm going to lock up here, so let's go out together.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh... But this office... it was a crime scene two years ago, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">That case has long since been over. There's no need to investigate it any more.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All the same, we'd still like to have a look around.</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Perhaps you didn't hear me. I said there's no need to investigate it any more.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Now hurry up and get out. I have a meeting to attend.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Looks like we aren't welcome.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seems that case isn't over with yet, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Chief Gant denied our request to search the "crime scene." That means there must be a reason he doesn't want us looking around in there.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You mean like, a clue!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's got to be a way we can get inside the Chief's office...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe! Were you in a meeting?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I was uh... just taking a breather. My feet hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">From sitting so long in the meeting?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Actually... I had to serve everyone coffee.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like Detective Gumshoe's still out of the loop...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Say, have either of you seen Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth? No. Why do you ask?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He's under fire from both the Police Department and the Prosecutor's Office. It's almost like the battles between you two in court!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That sounds serious...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Is it because of what my sister said?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's basically what it all boils down to. That falsified evidence two years ago. Now Mr. Edgeworth has the whole world after his blood!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yikes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Police">"I got it! I'm the culprit! Very clever indeed... Who would have thought of multiple personalities? I don't see how else he could have done it. I guess it's time to have my head checked."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I think it's way past time for that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That man must be the Head Detective. He's staring at the screen so hard it might shatter.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">What!? "Police Department Makes Fatal Error" What do I do!? Quick! Someone bring me the classifieds! Help Wanted section!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So much for "duty"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But why would Edgeworth be blamed? It's not like he knew the evidence was forged! Lana Skye is the guilty party here, isn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Regardless, the prosecutor is responsible for the evidence he presents in court. Not only that, but as you know there've been a lot of rumors going around about Mr. Edgeworth. Those who don't like him haven't been able to do anything because of his amazing talent as a prosecutor. But now with this...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Are there really so many people who hate him?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">In our world, only those with talent rise to the top. Mr. Edgeworth not only had that, but he's young. There's no better recipe I know of for making enemies.</line>
<line speaker="Police">Hey, Dick! Keep up the good work!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes sir!</line>
<line speaker="Police">Let's go out for lunch again sometime, my treat!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes sir!</line>
<line speaker="Police">You gotta take me back to that joint sometime, okay Dick?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seems you don't have any problem with enemies.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, well... I'm careful not to stick out. Anyway, I'm a bit worried about him. Under all this pressure, I'm afraid Mr. Edgeworth just might crack.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Actually, I took a look at the file earlier, while the coffee was brewing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He seems geniunely concerned for Edgeworth...</thought> Well? Did you find out anything?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The only evidence Darke left behind was during his final attack.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His final attack? You mean...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">When he killed Prosecutor Marshall, who was trying to protect some girl.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It seems Detective Gumshoe never realized Ema was the girl...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's when he left the most incriminating evidence of all.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well? What was it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, um, let's see... I think it had something to do with the murder weapon... ... Oh, I forget. Look, it's all written somewhere in here, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>His powers of recollection never fail to impress.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Maybe we should show him the murder weapon. It might jog his memory!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Joe Darke was 42 at the time of the crime. He was just your run-of-the-mill businessman.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A businessman? What made him take to serial killing?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">One day on his way home from work, he hit someone with his car.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">With his car? So... it was an accident?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">An accident, yes. But it transformed him into an animal!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">An animal...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He killed a man that witnessed the accident. Then he killed a lady who saw the second crime. A kid walked by just then, so he killed him too. Then, when he was burying the bodies, a jogger came upon the scene and was killed as well! Finally he turned himself in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Seems he was a pretty careless animal.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course, this is all conjecture. There wasn't a single shred of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, he turned himself in...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, but in the middle of his questioning, he fled and murdered his final victim... Prosecutor Marshall. That crime was witnessed by someone too, but fortunately he was arrested on the spot. It's a good thing that last witness wasn't killed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That last "witness"... He must mean Ema...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This knife... it was Joe Darke's, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's right. We traced it back to the store he bought it at, and it had his fingerprints on it too.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But no one actually witnessed him using it to murder anyone, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's where his luck ran out. When you take a good look at the knife... you'll see it's broken!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You don't have to take a good look to notice that.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Yeah, well anyway! Take a guess where the broken- off tip of the knife was found. That's what did him in!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Where was it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The victim, Neil Marshall was carrying it... inside his own body!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It was found deep inside the stab wound.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did it match Darke's knife?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You bet. Down to the last fiber.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's pretty... conclusive.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This ID card belongs to the victim, Detective Bruce Goodman. You can do just about anything these days with a card and a secret number... scary!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's only scary because you keep dropping your card, Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I forget my secret number a lot, too. I'm scared of myself! But... but I'm me, after all! And what could be wrong with that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I'll stay out of this conversation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, that's it! That's the "King of Prosecutors" award that Mr. Edgeworth got the other day!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Were you at the awards ceremony, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course, pal! I got an award for diligence, myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... congratulations.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I was wondering, why is the award a shield? And... why is it broken?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, there's a reason. Erm... I'll tell you what it is later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Apparently, he's forgotten.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guy almost made us lose the case today.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What are you talking about!? He was guarding the bloodstain on that evidence locker with his life! That's more than you can say for most officers nowadays!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It would have saved us a lot of trouble if he hadn't guarded it so well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to admit he's right though... Thanks to the Blue Badger, we were able to prove another possibility today: The possibility that another murder took place prior to 5:15 PM...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, about this...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! Don't tell me that's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It has a tag attached to it, with the label "SL-9 Incident" on it. I believe this would be the broken "murder weapon" you were speaking of?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What are you doing with that!? Ever since that case was closed, that knife's been locked away in a locker.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">On the day Detective Goodman was murdered, this suddenly disappeared from the locker, and was found in Mr. Edgeworth's car muffler.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... That's it! Now I remember what that incriminating piece of evidence was! When you showed me that knife, it all came back to me!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, what is it, Detective? Quick! Before you forget again!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, I just bought some of that stuff! Now I can go around detecting blood traces too!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wow! Is that a new type? I've never seen that bottle before. "Add three inches to your base height."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Base height"? Hey, let me see that! "Looming Tall." "New and improved growth formula."</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You mean this can't detect any blood traces!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Uh, well... It's not quite the same thing as luminol.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So that's why the lady at the counter had that smirk on her face...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's the ID card record, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. There's only one number left to investigate. At 4:20 PM... the victim, Detective Goodman, must have entered the evidence room along with someone else. Someone with an "executive officer" number:</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">"Sevensevensevensevensevensevensevenseven"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's one "seven" too many, Detective. <thought>An executive officer. Hmm... I just might have a hunch.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, that powder's used for detecting fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah, Mr. Edgeworth gave it to us.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He did what!? All I have is some flour... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you okay, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Quick! RUN!!! AHH-CHOOOO!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... If it's any help, one time I took a nap on a bench with wet paint.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why am I not comforted?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, a lost item report, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Very impressive, detective! You knew what is was right off the bat!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I am a master of misplacement, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">"Master"... That has such a cool ring to it!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The way I see it, if things are meant to be lost, then they're meant to be lost. There's a higher power at work here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wow, a higher power...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe I shouldn't let Ema hold any evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No locker can be opened without a fingerprint match. Besides... There's no reason for the murderer to touch his own locker...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, wasn't your locker the one with the blood on it, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The handprint of the real murderer's gloved hand... without any fingerprints...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">SSH! If they come to arrest me, you'll defend me, won't you!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If that happens, I think you'll do better pleading with Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">About that jar... I think I've seen it before somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Somewhere"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Or maybe it's one of those memories people have from "previous lives."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This must be the most uninformative detective I've ever met...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Something about it makes me feel uneasy. It's like I'm in the Chief's office, and he's yelling at me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Chief Gant?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Where could I have seen that before...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't believe Officer Marshall would do something like that...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You know Officer Marshall?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course I do! He was like a mentor to me! When I first started out, he even gave me a small cactus.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He said, "Dick, she'll listen to all your troubles."</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Note to self: Detective Gumshoe talks to a cactus...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hard to believe he's just a "patrolman" now. Someone oughta trade places with him! ... What? Why are you looking at me like that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I've been studying up on those Files. There's nothing wrong with Mr. Edgeworth's presentation. To think people are accusing him of injustice... I for one ain't buyin' it, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You're looking into the case for Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. It was a pretty big deal while it was going on, you know. After all, a serial killer was on the loose!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But Lana was pretty clear in her confession. She forged evidence in order to prove Joe Darke guilty.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Let me share a little advice with you as a detective. If you don't have a clue, keep yer trap shut!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll, uh, keep that in mind.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sheesh!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, there you have it in a nutshell. That's all I know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can I ask you one more thing?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What is it? If it's money you need, you should ask Chief Gant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not money, but it does concern the Chief. His office is a "crime scene," right? It's where Prosecutor Neil Marshall was murdered...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The Chief's out now, and his office is locked, but we'd like to have a look around if that's okay.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Well, any Detective's ID card can unlock the door.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What? Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But if I let a civilian in there, I'd be charged with breach of trust.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Breach of trust...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Simply put, I'd be canned.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry, pal. I don't plan on getting fired because of you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">How about this ID card? It was Detective Goodman's...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That won't work either. The data was deleted the day he died.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So in other words, Gumshoe is our only chance of getting into that office.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I wonder if there's something we could show him that would make him change his mind...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if Edgeworth is back yet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">There he is! It looks like he's writing something.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Huh? What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He sure was quick to throw that paper on the floor...</thought> Tough day in court, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. I've had to live the past two years with rumors flying around. What's another allegation to me?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Cheer up, Mr. Edgeworth! I'm rooting for you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's Edgeworth for you... Always trying to hide his real feelings.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, what do you want? Unlike some people, I don't have all day.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He won such a prestigious award. Why would he just leave it on the couch?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Better this than that giant Steel Samurai.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This is the "King of Prosecutors" award, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course it is. You know that!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I saw something today that looked like this, somewhere...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something that looked like that?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah, only different. What was it...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's right. Something's amiss here. Maybe I should show him a certain item...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder what he was writing before?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Come on, Mr. Wright! Let's take a look!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you crazy? Edgeworth is sitting right there!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Just distract him. I'll check it out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... Hey, Edgeworth. Is that Detective Gumshoe out the window there? Oh no! He's falling to the ground!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hold on. First let me see what this girl's doing crawling around my feet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He didn't even look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">What!? "Letter of r-r-r-r..."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you can't read, I'll read it for you. It says, "Letter of Resignation."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Resignation"!? Edgeworth, you don't mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm tired, Mr. Wright. I feel as if... something inside me has died.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But Mr. Edgeworth! None of it is your fault!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know the path I've walked. You don't need to tell me. And the path I've walked... hasn't been a just one. I can't forgive myself for what I've done... and no one else should forgive me either.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh. I think he's serious!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! Please, you have to do something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This Letter of Resignation... I wonder if I can use it for anything?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's no excuse for what I've done. Two years ago, I used false evidence to obtain a guilty verdict. That's what it all breaks down to, and nothing I do can erase that fact.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you didn't know, did you? I mean, that the evidence was falsified.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Police Department and the Prosecutor's Office share a bond of trust. If that bond is broken, we stand to lose everything. The Police Department's error is my error, my responsibility as the prosecutor in charge. That fact remains the same no matter what excuses I might have.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I take pride in my work. So tell me why! Why has it all come to this...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even Edgeworth can't keep this kind of emotion bottled up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you up for the trial tomorrow?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. First last year's trial, and now this one. It seems all you do is worry about me. To be honest, you're getting on my nerves.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But Mr. Edgeworth! You can't just walk out on the trial...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tomorrow is the last day. It's too late to change prosecutors. I'll bet that's what my superiors are banking on. I never thought that case would come back to haunt me like this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That list of evidence. It seems too short. Most lists... run twice as long.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's only half as long as most lists? <thought>That is odd...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">After Neil Marshall was murdered, I became prosecutor for that case. I may not have been part of the investigation, but at the time there was only one thing on my mind: I'd use the evidence I was given to prove the suspect guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Say, we just saw a picture taken around that time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That picture... Something seemed strange about it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell us again about what happened that day? The day Detective Goodman was murdered? You were participating in a ceremony over at the station, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've never cared for ceremonies, but I had to attend that one.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Because you were awarded this?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Those receiving awards can't exactly skip out on the ceremony. I finished up at the office in the morning, then drove over to the Police Department.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You, "finished up" at the office?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Just odds and ends- clerical stuff. I didn't plan on returning to the office that day. That is, until I was asked to take something back.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Take something back?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh yeah. Chief Gant asked you to hold onto that, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. It was a piece of evidence in a case that was closed half a year ago. He asked me to bring it back to the Prosecutor's Office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's the story we heard yesterday...</thought> So you came back here to the Prosecutor's Office because the Chief asked you to?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This award originates from an ancient Chinese tale. In Chinese, the word "contradiction" is written with two characters: the first means "halberd," and the second means "shield." Have you heard this story?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me? Oh, uh... sure. Everyone knows that! Why don't you tell it though... for Ema's sake.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very well. Long ago in the kingdom of Chu, there was an arms merchant. One day, he presented the king with two items. The first was a halberd he claimed could slice through any shield or armor. The second was a shield he claimed could withstand any weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Wait a minute.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Those claims contradict each other!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very perceptive. But then again, you've heard this story before, right? Anyway, as you mentioned, the very descriptions of these items discredit them both. When the king pointed this out, the merchant was left speechless. And thus, the Chinese word for "contradiction" was born.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, I see! So the "chipped shield" and the "broken knife" symbolize...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely so. They symbolize the merchant's items. The ancient tale ends with the merchant at a loss for words, but it's in our nature to pursue matters to their conclusion... even if it results in something as ugly as this.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wow. Thanks, Mr. Edgeworth! I learned something new today!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's funny... If that's so, then why were you only given a shield?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... You'll have to ask Chief Gant. Two years ago, he had the "halberd" part of the award abolished.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Chief Gant...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I once dreamed of being a defense attorney, a long time ago.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What? You wanted to be a defense attorney, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yet, a clear path is laid out before me. I have no time to look back on what might have been.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know, it wouldn't hurt if you put this up somewhere, like on a shelf.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That has no meaning for me anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean, "anymore"?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's who I was last year. What good is it to dwell on the past?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's asking me?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That makes me kind of mad. Actually, something's been troubling me about this shield. Look... Do you notice anything different?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Different...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah, don't you remember? The other shield in the Court Record?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I'd better present this other shield...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems everything in this case is designed to cast doubt on me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, don't look at me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I went into the evidence room on the day of the crime. Chief Gant asked me to do something.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">To take evidence from a case solved six months ago back to the Prosecutor's Office...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have a locker in there as well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you notice anything amiss when you were in the evidence room?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That room's always dark and I was in a hurry. I didn't see anything out of the ordinary.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Come now, Mr. Wright. You can't seriously expect me to just sit down... and chat with you about the case over a cup of tea.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But this isn't related to the case, remember? You said so yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So I did...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Chief Gant gave this to you that day, didn't he? He asked you to bring it here from the Police Department...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Chief is a very competent man... but sometimes he does things that don't make any sense. ... At least it's better than being incompetent and doing things that don't make sense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A certain detective comes to mind...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This picture was hanging on the wall in Chief Gant's office.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Prosecutor Neil Marshall... He had just started making a name for himself. Looks like this was taken when he received the King of Prosecutors trophy.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Speaking of that, there's something that bothers me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The trophy Mr. Marshall is holding... it's a little different than yours.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, you're right. ... I remember now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Remember what?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That was the official prosecutor trophy used until that time. There's a story behind it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A story?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds interesting.</thought> Would you mind telling it to us?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's simple, really. "Contradiction." That's what the award's based on.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They say where there's smoke, there's fire. Apparently I was so caught up in the smoke, I lost sight of the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The others are right. I have no right to serve as a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But Mr. Edgeworth! You were only doing your job!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've always made my own decisions about what I can or cannot do. That hasn't changed. Forgiving myself... is something I cannot do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh. I think he's serious!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! Please, you have to do something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This Letter of Resignation... I wonder if I can use it for anything?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Wright, please. I'm the prosecutor on this case! You don't expect me to sit here and discuss the case with you over a cup of tea!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll pass on the tea. Just tell me about the case...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! Mr. Edgeworth just told you "no" in a very stylish manner!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoose side are you on, anyway? Maybe if I just show him my best evidence I can get some reaction out of him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">"Due to recent events I hereby announce my resignation as public prosecutor."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He really wrote a resignation letter...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wow! Even when resigning, Mr. Edgeworth is cool and concise! Still, it wasn't his fault...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Someone has to be held responsible. That's how it is in the grown-up world.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah, but that responsibility means nothing if he just quits!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, not everyone sees it that way.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">To truly take responsibility you should have to work the rest of your life for no pay.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sometimes the "grown-up" world can be tough...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Would either of you care for a quarter pound of roast beef?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Starr! <thought>I guess she's out of lunches.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">You certainly are the curious sort, aren't you? Kind of like the first person who sucked a cow's nipple to discover milk. Still, I never thought you'd go digging up that case from two years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Everyone in this trial was involved in the SL-9 Incident. Not only that, but the murder occurred on the very day the evidence from that case was due for transferal. This can't all be attributed to mere "coincidence."</line>
<line speaker="Angel">... Aren't you forgetting something? You know, that little scene I happened to witness?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The instant Lana stabbed Detective Goodman with a knife.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">No matter how much of the past you dig up, it won't change what I saw. Roast beef is meant to be savored when eaten.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ms. Starr's hatred toward Lana... It all dates back to two years ago!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">Joe Darke... That's a name I'll not soon forget! We trailed him for half a year. Oh, the pressure! Still, I don't think I was ever more alive than I was then. Those days were steamier than a bowl of hot gravy! Poor old Jake Marshall, though, must have been going through hell.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean, because of his brother's death?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">They were close, those two. After Neil died, something took over Jake. He became obsessed. Seeing Jake like that made her all the more desperate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Her"...?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Lana Skye.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">My sister...?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">The best of the best were put on that SL-9 case. Of course they were lead by that legendary duo.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Lana... and Chief Gant!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">That legendary pair was the reason we were able to keep up our investigation. That's why we're so shocked over how it turned out...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean, with the forging of the evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Don't get me wrong. Joe Darke got what he deserved. Still, it was obvious the evidence produced in court was being manipulated. Items our team never found would suddenly appear, while other items were kept secret.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But you didn't have proof anything illegal was done...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I'm proof enough of what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">After that case, all of us save Goodman were relieved of our duties... most without even so much as an explanation. Then Lana Skye transferred to the Prosecutor's Office and became Chief Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Lana always wanted to be a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Nothing's quite as simple as it appears.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Lana Skye was merely being used as a pawn. That's my take on the matter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She was being used?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Damon Gant and Lana Skye... Two years ago Gant was Chief Detective, and Lana second in command. They were the best.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">They solved all kinds of cases together, didn't they?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Damon Gant's magnetism in particular was almost unreal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His "magnetism"?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">By that I mean his ability to attract evidence. He'd produce the most incredible evidence in the cases he handled.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Incredible evidence"? You mean...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">Oh, yes. There were rumors about him even back then. No one dared confront him, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I take it she's talking about forged evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">Back then, everyone looked up to Lana. All the detectives wanted to be like her.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Oh yes... myself included. I was a fool, really. She hated anything crooked, and always watched out for the other detectives. That's why she was so concerned for Jake.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Marshall...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">When Jake's brother was murdered, she felt as if she had lost her own brother. If it wasn't for her, I don't think Jake would ever have recovered from his shock. That's what makes it all the more infuriating.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ms. Starr...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">That's why... I'll never be able to forgive her. Why did she have to turn so cold after that...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lana transferred to the Prosecutor's Office two years ago, didn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Yes, thanks to "Chief" Gant's powerful influence.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Chief...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">That's right. Having solved the SL-9 case, his position as chief was secured. There was only one thing left for him to control, and then no one could stand in his way: the Prosecutor's Office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? You mean... That's why Lana was transferred!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">If he could control the Chief Prosecutor, he could control the Prosecutor's Office. That must have been his goal all along.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">B-but how could he control Lana?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I don't know, but one thing's for sure. Ever since that case ended, she's never been the same. It's only logical to conclude... there must have been a reason for her change.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>At last... I'm finally getting close to the bottom of this ugly mess.</thought> Thank you, Ms. Starr.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">You listen to me, Rookie. It takes more than just ingredients to create fine cuisine. I hope you turn out to be a better chef than I've been...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I don't have anything else to tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ms. Starr...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">The only thing I can give you now, is a poppyseed rice set.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Talk about cheap...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">Eat this, and maybe you'll be able to tell black from white in court tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, you're back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're still here?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I gotta make 150 copies of these files. Brewing coffee, copying files... I'm turning into a regular DJ!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You're a "DJ" as well?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If I'm not mistaken, I think he means "Desk Jockey."</line>
<line speaker="Ema">... Oh, that DJ...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I gotta admire your persistency, but my answer's still no.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm not letting you in the Chief's office, period. It'd be my neck on the line.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That office is the last crime scene in the SL-9 Incident. I have to take a look in there!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's got to be something we can do to make the Detective change his mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Police">"Oh, Francesca. You're more lovely than a marsupial in... Quiet, Jean Marc. Words will just spoil the moment. Now hold me close..." Yes, this approach allows for much more intrigue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... It seems he's given up on the mystery genre.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, that's it! That's the "King of Prosecutors" award that Mr. Edgeworth got the other day!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Were you at the awards ceremony, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course, pal! I got an award for diligence, myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... congratulations.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Say, this design's based on an old Chinese parable, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Uh, yeah! Everyone knows that! There was this, uh... dragon, yeah, that's it. A dragon! He had a thing for shields, see...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's not exactly the version we heard.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No, but this one sounds more exciting!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Anyway, it gets kind of gory after that. I'll spare you the details.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What's this crumpled up piece of paper? ...... N--no way! Mr. Edgeworth can't be serious!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is he ever not serious?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't believe they've pushed him this far...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Edgeworth really feels responsible.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">At first I thought he was as cold as ice, but now I know different! He trusted us detectives to provide him with sound evidence, but we just... we betrayed him!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Detective...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">......... That's it. I've made up my mind!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Here, take my ID card.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We can't do that. If someone found out...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">they wouldn't let you off the hook with another lost item report!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Look at me. It's no secret I'm already out of the loop. After all, I'm friends with Mr. Edgeworth. Depending on how this case turns out, I may already be as good as terminated...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So at least let me do this... for Mr. Edgeworth's sake!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, Detective. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Detective Gumshoe isn't very photogenic, is he?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whatever you do, just don't say that to his face.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Look, his eyes are half shut!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... and his mouth is half open.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey! Each of his shirt buttons is off a notch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And he's got the narrow end of his tie in front. ... I think this goes beyond being a "photogenic" issue.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Here goes, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Open sesame. If anyone finds us now,</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe's a goner.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If that happens, I'm counting on you to bail me out!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">EEEEEEEEK!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">GAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sorry, I thought you were a ghost.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I didn't even know you could slap a ghost.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AAAAH! Detective Gumshoe! What are you doing sneaking up on us like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-I-I wasn't "sneaking." I was just worried something might go wrong... so I came too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you're here, then what's the point in giving us your ID card!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, don't do that to my card!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I hardly ever get a chance to come in here, so I figured I'd have a look around myself! Besides, we're all in this together now.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You really do want to get fired, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Not if we're lucky. Now come on, let's see what we can find out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've got a bad feeling about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Look at that giant window... Makes you want to crash through it and jump outside.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, this is the 15th floor.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I know! I was just saying...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Saying what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ever since making detective, I've always dreamed about doing something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Note to Self: Detective Gumshoe has a lot of dreams...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So long as he doesn't go crashing through that window when he gets fired.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Don't say that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These shelves are mostly empty. Lana must have cleaned them out when she transferred over to the Prosecutor's Office. There's a small picture frame on the left shelf.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey! This is when Lana and I went to that theme park... ...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This was taken on that day two years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The day Joe Darke ran out of the questioning room and tried to kill Ema...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">After receiving his award trophy, Mr. Marshall took a picture here, then went along with Chief Gant to question Darke. I bet he never knew he'd be dead just a few hours later...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gee, you think?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This was Lana's desk. It sure is tidy.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Lana's always been a meticulous cleaner.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's not even any dust on it! Looks like someone's still keeping it clean. Does Lana ever come back here?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No. Chief Gant must still keep it clean in memory of their partnership. They were the stuff legends are made of!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Does he keep it in memory of her, or in memory of the crime...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The Chief's organ sure is a sight to behold. Occasionally we hear him playing it from the Criminal Affairs department.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's on the 2nd floor, and this is the 15th!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">When a detective screws up, the Chief calls him to his office... and makes him listen to the organ for hours.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What's so bad about that? Music soothes the soul!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">After that, the detective can't hear anything for days except for the ringing in his ears.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So it's an instrument of punishment... literally.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">But aren't the Chief's ears affected?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... He never listens to anyone anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's besides the point...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">This mark looks like some kind of flower.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Word is, it's designed after the insignia on the prosecutor's badge.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Prosecutor's badge"...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, like the one hanging from your collar.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!? They have badges too!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The design's supposed to portray the severity of the punishment system.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Now that you mention it, it does look all pointy and kind of painful.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But Mr. Edgeworth never wears a badge.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's because he's a sharp dresser. A badge like that wouldn't go too well with his outfit.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So sharp dressers don't need to wear badges?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I guess everyone just kind of lets it slide.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't see how that's supposed to signify severe punishment...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is a safe, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">"Safe"... that word is ripe with intrigue!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, okay. If you say so...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It looks like a code needs to be entered in this panel to open it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A seven-digit number. I think I just might know what it is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not sure what will happen if we enter the wrong code. I'd better wait until I find something more definite.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">A seven-digit number... Didn't we see one of those somewhere?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">How about we try entering my birth date?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Do you know what it is?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have a hunch...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, I know! You want to try my birth date? It's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have a better idea. Here goes nothing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I guess that wasn't it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was so sure that was the number!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Maybe we should check the Court Record again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A seven-digit number...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Bingo.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What number did you enter!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whose birthday was that, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"7777777." The final ID card number on that record.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The number of the mysterious "executive officer" who entered the room that day.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You mean, "Sevensevensevensevensevenseven"? That ID number!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think you're one "seven" shy this time. This can only mean one thing: That's Chief Gant's ID number!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Say... Anyone care to look inside?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Is there any money in there? How much does he have stashed away!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Look! It's a... a...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">a shard from a broken cup.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This somehow looks familiar. Where have I seen this before...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's something else in here too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this? It looks like a piece of leather cloth...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This is a handprint, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! I saw someone wearing a shirt like that once! You think the Chief made up the design?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Uh... I don't think so.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh. Well, it was just a thought.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Is that it? This is all that was in the safe?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apparently so. It's empty now.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A piece of cloth with a handprint on it, and a broken shard from a cup.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They look like pieces of evidence,</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">but unless you can prove they have something to do with this case, I'm afraid I can't just let you take them. After all, it's my neck on the line here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great. Now I have to prove their "relevancy" to get them. How are these two items related to the SL-9 Incident?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Come on! There's got to be something we can show the detective!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is a safe, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">"Safe"... that word is ripe with intrigue!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, okay. If you say so...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wow! Look at the size of Chief Gant's desk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Speaking of that, when we were here earlier...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gant">Oh, it's you two.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Chief Gant! <thought>He put that paper he was reading in his desk.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder what he was reading?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This looks like a list of evidence... used in a case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A list of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">In most cases the list runs twice as long as this.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, look at the case name!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? "SL-9 Incident"! I wonder what this is doing here...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hold on, Detective! What did you just say?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I said, "I wonder what..."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, about evidence lists. Normally they're twice as long?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's right. I guess there wasn't a lot of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A half-sized list of evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That list of evidence. It seems too short. Most lists... run twice as long.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What would the other half of the list be doing here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I knew it! The Chief must be hiding something about that case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It would appear so.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wow! Look at the size of Chief Gant's desk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We found this inside the drawer. A list of evidence from the SL-9 Incident.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Edgeworth had the other half of that list!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What would this list be doing here...? We'd better look a little more into this list.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the real deal, isn't it? This armor and these weapons?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure is, pal. The Chief doesn't care for imitations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">First the pipe organ, now this armor... Do you know how many taxpayer dollars must have gone into this room?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What? You mean we're paying for this!? That's it. I'm not paying one cent of my taxes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You don't have any taxes to pay.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ssh! Be careful of what you say! Who knows? The Chief may be hiding in this armor as we speak!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think he'd fit in there.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Even if he did, he'd never be able to get back out.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Cut it out! You guys don't know how scary that guy can be!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You can see pretty far from 15 stories up. If you were to drop that suit of armor from here...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">At first the Chief wanted to use stained glass for this window.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Really? Why didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">They say he changed his mind because he wouldn't be able to see the view.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Stained glass or not, it's a huge window...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That desk on the other side of the room... Was that your sister's?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes. That's where I was waiting for Lana... on that day two years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is anyone using it now?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No sir. This is entirely Chief Gant's office now.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He practices a strict policy of "preserving the crime scene."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's a strange reason to leave it there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He leaves it as a warning to everyone else. He wants us to always be alert. He told us so himself at our New Year's party. Of course, he was pretty intoxicated at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So ever since Lana left, no one ever touches that desk?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No one except Chief Gant... and the cleaning lady who's in here each morning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Still, two years have passed since that incident. There can't possibly be any clues remaining.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Can I ask you something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You only came here to look around, right? Because it's one of the SL-9 crime scenes. I mean, that's your only reason for coming here, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Why do you ask?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You don't think... Nah! You wouldn't be... No. ... No, there's no way. Never mind. Don't worry about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay. Now then, let's look around a bit more.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, hold on! Not so fast, buddy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">When someone tells you "don't worry about it," it's supposed to start bothering you, pal! You don't just let it go at that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-sorry. <thought>This guy's starting to get on my nerves.</thought> Okay, so what's bothering you?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You two don't think... Chief Gant... might be a suspect, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What!? Yeah, Mr. Wright! What do we think of him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Chief Gant... So it's finally come to this. What do I think of him? Perhaps it's best I don't divulge my feelings... yet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There he goes, ignoring me again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This knife belonged to the murdered, Joe Darke, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You bet. If it wasn't for that piece of evidence, he wouldn't have been found guilty! The broken tip of the knife was found inside the victim's body.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ever since that case was solved, this knife's been in Detective Goodman's locker. How could it have possibly gotten to Mr. Edgeworth's car?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Not only that, but it was wrapped in Lana's scarf.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What's even more mysterious, is whether that's called a "scarf," or a "muffler." Answer me that, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe. I'd like you to have a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, I know what that is! So, you want to take some fingerprints?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's a great idea, Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">All right, go to town. Sheesh! ...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you doing? Why are you sticking out your hand like that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Go ahead. Take my fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">... Um, it's not your fingerprints we want to take.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come on, this isn't the time for jokes. We're talking about that cloth we found in the safe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! Heh heh! I knew that. The one with the hand print on it, right? Sheesh, where's your sense of humor?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Okay, Mr. Wright. Let's check for prints! Sprinkle the powder on the cloth, then, once they've been absorbed into the prints, blow the rest away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What are you, my mom? I don't have to be told a million times.</thought> All right, let's get this over with!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... I gave it my best shot.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That kind of result won't be any good for matching prints, will it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But it doesn't look like we'll get a clearer result from this print.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ok, let's try a different finger, then!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No, that doesn't match.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like we're out of clues this time.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah... But it was inside the Chief's safe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right, along with that shard.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So that means it's got to have something to do with that incident!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The one that happened right here in this room... She's right! We should check the fingerprints of everyone who was in here that day!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The way I see it, there's a higher power at work here. You just gotta have faith.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No... How can this be!? What are Ema's fingerprints doing here!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, you found a match? Whose fingerprints were they!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Oh, uh... it seems the prints are too old. They aren't clear enough to get a match.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh... That's too bad. I thought they'd be Darke's prints.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Psst! Hey you. Over here. What's going on here? What are that kid's prints doing inside the Chief's safe?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't ask me! Let's just keep this information from Ema for now.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Here. Maybe you should hold onto this.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Now I know where I saw that before... It was right here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Here"? You mean, in the Chief's office? </line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If I recall, it used to sit right on top of that shelf... two years ago. I used to stare at it while being forced to listen to that organ.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You would stare at it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'd try to use my telepathy to knock it over. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your telepathy... </line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, there it is! Right there in that picture, see?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe. Could you have another look at this jar?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">All of us put that back together. Oh, those were the days...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's kind of early to be nostalgic.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wasn't this jar a piece of evidence from that case?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's right. One of the shards had an "SL-9 Incident" sticker on it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Doesn't this ring any bells? You know, that fragment we just found?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You mean this one, that was in the safe?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes, that one... that was in the safe.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...&#160;! Now that you mention it, it's ringing a lot of bells! Let's see if it fits!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe we shouldn't do this right now.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What!? Look, bud. You don't get someone all worked up, then just leave them hanging! You're as bad as that girl I met back when I was 16...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sixteen... That's the same age I am. I wonder what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's hard to imagine Detective Gumshoe had a childhood.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, if we don't do it now, then let's at least do it later!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here, let me see that shard. I'll take a crack at this.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Go ahead, pal. Show us what a rookie can do!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! Here's some glue!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I can piece this together again... it'll prove Chief Gant was knowingly hiding evidence! Here goes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't get it! This piece doesn't fit anywhere in this jar!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What? But it has to!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I need a breather. I'll try it again later.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">If you don't, I'll switch your eyedrops with my special solution!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There! It fits like a charm. That of course means... Chief Gant willingly and knowingly hid a piece of this jar in his safe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In other words, he concealed a piece of evidence from the SL-9 Incident.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey guys! Get a load of this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This piece you just attached... it's different from the others!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's a reddish line on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A reddish line... That's blood!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't get it! Why would Chief Gant hide this in his safe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I feel a lot better now that this jar's complete.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But it only raises another question: What was a piece of it doing in the Chief's safe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">More importantly, why wasn't there any money in there? Isn't that what safes are for anyway!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have a feeling the outcome of tomorrow's trial just might hinge on this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's what the Chief was reading before, isn't it? You know, when we first came in here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. It looks like the right side of the form's been torn off.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So Mr. Edgeworth's list really was only half of the whole thing!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Something else is buggin' me more than that. Take a look at the back of that form, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The back...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is this strip of cloth, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's smooth, and sort of feels like vinyl. I think I've felt something like this before... ... Nah, I can't remember.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seems this is becoming a habit with you.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't keep anything in my head lately!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Note to Self: Detective Gumshoe is going senile.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ema's fingerprints were found on this cloth. I have a bad feeling about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If I'm fired, I won't be able to give you any information! So that's why I have to get it all out of my system now! You understand, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Don't be so negative, Detective! We do want you to share your information, though.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, who am I fooling? I've never had anything useful to share to begin with.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Argh! Got... to stay... positive!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Whoa! This area must have been covered in blood!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is this from that incident?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It must be. When Prosecutor Neil Marshall was murdered. Two years have passed, so the reaction's kind of dull.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So a murder really did take place here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, look here! It's hard to make out, but there's a dark red stain here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Looks like blood.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This piece the Chief has is different, though. The blood stains on the other pieces are just spots, but this one's a line!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That is odd...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder what this is? <thought>It looks like someone drew some kind of sketch here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">What is it? Did you find something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't make it out. I'd better keep quiet about it for now.</thought> Huh? Oh. No, it's nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Why are your eyes moving about like that, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better not forget about this picture!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">This is a handprint, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. Someone left behind an oil stain on the fabric. Whoever it was, they must have had a really oily hand.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright, think about it scientifically!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A more likely explanation is... the person slipped and fell on a freshly waxed floor, getting wax all over their hand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, that would account for this amount of oil I guess. <thought>I don't see what's so "scientific" about it though.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">It happens, you know. I always slip on the floors at school after they're waxed.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well? Was I any help?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course! Thanks to your ID card, we were able to get some hard evidence.</line>
<line speaker="???">Now that's not very kind, is it? In other words, if it wasn't for his ID card, he would have been useless...</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Isn't that right, you in the coat?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">EEEEEEEK!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">C-Chief Gant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We didn't think you'd be back so soon.</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Fortunately I'm a man who believes in signs. As I was walking to my meeting, I happened to look out a window and saw a stray dog run right into a pole. Just then I thought of a certain detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Do you mean... m-me, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Now then, I'm afraid I'm going to have to ask you all to leave.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Y-yes sir! Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Oh, you in the coat.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Me, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Drop off your ID on the way out. You won't be needing it anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But sir...</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Now get out!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-y-yes sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We'll be on our way too, then.</line>
<line speaker="Gant">Wait. You, the one without the spiky hair. Don't go yet.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">M-me, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Gant">I'd like a word with you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But sir! I'm not a licensed scientific investigator yet!</line>
<line speaker="Gant">You with the spiky hair. You're free to go.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">M-Mr. Wright!!!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Look, pal! If I've told you once I've told you a thousand times...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The dark red stains must be blood traces from the incident two years ago. Only the fragment found in Chief Gant's office still has lines remaining on it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A picture is drawn on the back of the evidence list in magic marker. I've got a very bad feeling about this...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A clear handprint can be seen on the leather cloth. The print belongs to Ema... I think I'll keep this information to myself.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The Chief's office is off limits! But no, you just had to go sneaking in there like that, didn't you!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I thought you said you didn't care anymore if you were fired.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, but if I knew it'd be like this, I never would've said it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that I've seen the evidence Chief Gant was hiding in his office... I think I'm finally starting to get the picture... It's hard to believe anyone could keep quiet about it all this time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Anyway, you listenin' to me!? I'm gonna try to smooth things over with the Chief again! Later, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">After that, I heard from Ema. She said the police want to ask her some questions, so she'll be busy for the rest of the day...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">I see. So the Chief asked Ema to come in for questioning...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's no use thinking about it. Tomorrow's the final day in court. I'm committed to doing everything I can to defend you, which is why I'm here.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">But I've already told you all I can...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What you've told me over these past couple of days... is absolutely nothing. Not a single, useful thing.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Really? I believe I did mention something quite important. Something I told you right at the beginning. I said that I was the one who stabbed Detective Goodman.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know, I think I've finally figured it out... Who it is you're hiding behind those words.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">... Mia did a good job mentoring you. I'm rather jealous...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">It seems Edgeworth was right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth...?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Once you're convinced you know something, no one can persuade you otherwise. "Thick headed" is the term he used, I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now's my chance to get her to tell me the rest of the story!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have to admit I was more than a little perplexed at first. You insisted you "did it," yet there was no incriminating evidence. That's when it hit me. It's not that you're unwilling to tell the truth, it's that you're incapable of doing so, because of a certain individual.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">What an intriguing notion. A certain, "individual," you say? So you think I'm... protecting this person?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Protecting? No. I think "afraid of" is more like it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If I'm not mistaken, the person in question may have persuaded you to silence.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">... For argument's sake, Mr. Wright, whom may I ask is this person you're speaking of? The one I am supposedly so "frightened" of? What is this person's name?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The person whom you fear... is this!</line>
<line speaker="Lana">To be honest, there's someone a bit scarier.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-who would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Why you, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Yes. You seriously believe what you're saying, don't you? Now that's scary.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, uh...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">You seem to have the makings of a criminal in you, what with all your fallacious accusations. Care to spend tonight in the next cell?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If you ask me, you're the scary one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Ms. Skye?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">... Mr. Wright. You are addressing the Chief Prosecutor. Do not forget your place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I take it she's still not ready to spill the beans.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lana">My apologies. Could you please tell me a bit more about the circumstances?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">We were partners until two years ago. I respected him as a detective.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Assuming he is respectable, then tell me something... Why would he try to hide his crimes?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">His "crimes"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Both you and Edgeworth will be brought before a board of inquiry for what you did. Specifically, hiding and forging evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Of course, these are serious offenses...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why is it, though, that Chief Gant's name was never mentioned?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Chief Gant...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth didn't know the truth behind the forgery. The only party who could have possible <thought>[sic]</thought> investigated that evidence was...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Me. I had access because I was second in command of that investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes you, but also one other: Damon Gant.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">... If you intend to accuse Chief Gant, you'll need more than just words. Show me proof that Chief Gant falsified evidence in that case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You want proof of the Chief's wrongdoings? Here it is!</line>
<line speaker="Lana">That "evidence" proves someone is doing something wrong all right, but it's not the Chief.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-who would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Why you, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Yes. You seriously believe what you're saying, don't you? Now that's scary.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, uh...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">You seem to have the makings of a criminal in you, what with all your fallacious accusations. Care to spend tonight in the next cell?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If you ask me, you're the scary one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I just found this in a safe in the Chief's office. This jar piece, and this strip of cloth. Do you know what these are? They're pieces of evidence from the SL-9 Incident!</line>
<line speaker="Lana">I...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The person concealing evidence was none other than Chief Gant himself. Now tell me! Why are you taking all the blame for him!?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">... Touché, Mr. Wright. It's as you surmised. I cannot disobey the Chief's orders... even if it means being found guilty for murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Come now, Mr. Wright. You can't possibly expect me to be able to tell you that. Three days ago... I had no choice but to cooperate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>In the murder of Detective Goodman!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lana">Or perhaps I should say, "follow orders." Yes, that's more accurate than "cooperate."</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Although I can't tell you the details, I can say that I was given an order that day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just as I suspected. Despite what everyone believes... you were not the one who murdered Detective Goodman!</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Correct. I was trying to take the body out of Edgeworth's car. The trunk was broken. I discovered that murder weapon while inspecting the body.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The murder weapon... You mean, Edgeworth's knife?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">No. When I found the body, this was the knife stuck in it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The knife from the SL-9 Incident... serial killer Joe Darke's knife!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lana">I couldn't just leave that knife in him, so I took it out and stabbed him with another knife.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That would be Edgeworth's knife?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">That's right. Even though he was already dead, my hands were shaking at the thought of stabbing him. That's why I ended up cutting my hand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that is the reason for the bandage on your right hand?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Yes. It seems that I got blood on the victim's shoes as well. And then... she saw me just as I plunged the knife in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ms. Starr...</thought> Why did you need to hide Darke's knife so badly?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Showing evidence isn't going to do me any good now. I've got to get Lana to tell me everything she's hiding!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lana">Mr. Wright. You're evolving by leaps and bounds. I'm starting to see the hunger in your eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I need to hear what Lana has to say. Then I can finish up the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">It took a lot of work to finally close the Darke case two years ago. It was over with. I didn't ever want it to be opened again. My intent was to prevent that by whatever means possible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... you hid Darke's knife?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">The weapon used to stab the detective was evidence in the Joe Darke case... If word got out, which it would, the reporters would have a field day with that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you wrapped the knife in your scarf, and hid it. In Edgeworth's exhaust pipe...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Right. Then I called my sister, to tell her what happened, and to ask her to hide the knife that was inside my muffler.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You asked Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">I didn't want anyone on the force to know about this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That would explain why Ema is so confident... about Lana's innocence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lana">Speaking of phone calls, I had a bad feeling about one of them that day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A bad feeling?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">The truth is, after I received those orders from Chief Gant. The first thing I did was make a phone call. A phone call to Patrolman Jake Marshall.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To Marshall? Why on earth would you call him?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">The lead investigator for the SL-9 Incident had been murdered. I wanted that fact to be kept hidden, and I needed help. He was the only other person I could trust. Or at least, I thought I could trust him at the time. However, it seems that after I spoke to him he went off on an escapade of his own...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh! You mean...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Not wanting the case to die, he decided to take things into his own hands.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He disguised himself as Officer Goodman and tried to steal the evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lana">He had already stolen the ID card... but it seems he still hadn't made up his mind to break into the evidence room. After my phone call, any remaining doubts he had must have disappeared.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So your phone call caused the incident in the evidence room!?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">I'm afraid that's all I can tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But Lana...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">You've earned my respect, Mr. Wright. Both as a defense attorney and an investigator. Now please... Don't pursue this any further in court tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Tomorrow's trial... There's only one way to drive off Lana's demons...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've got to get to the bottom of everything! Detective Goodman's real murderer... and what went down in the Chief's office two years ago...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I'd like to try one of the other fingerprints.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Okay, let's move on to a different finger!</line>
</xml>