<xml>
<title>Rise from the Ashes</title>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's been two months since Maya left the office... Two months without a single trial. I've had offers... But none I took. That is... until the day that girl showed up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I come here to the office every day? It's not like I want to work...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">There you are! Finally! Where have you been!? My sister's trial is tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... ... Um... who are you?</line>
<line speaker="???">It doesn't matter who I am! It only matters who YOU are! You're the famous defense attorney, Mia Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="???">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, uh... You're not Mia Fey, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, but Ms. Mia Fey no longer... works here.</line>
<line speaker="???">So you are...? The coffee boy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm Phoenix Wright... A defense attorney.</line>
<line speaker="???">Wright... Wright... Wait! You're THE Phoenix Wright!? The Phoenix Wright from the Edgeworth murder case!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, yes, that's correct. <thought>It wasn't Edgeworth who was murdered, though...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">That's a relief then! You're better than nobody!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry... I'm afraid I'm not taking cases right now.</line>
<line speaker="???">But, you are Phoenix Wright, right? The undefeated defense</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, I'm not accepting any new cases. I'm sorry, but you'll have</line>
<line speaker="???">Please! I'm out of time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But...</line>
<line speaker="???">Please, you have to help! I-it's my sister!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>Maya...? Could it be...?</thought> ... Okay. I'll hear you out.</line>
<line speaker="???">R-really!? Thank you so much! My name's Ema, Ema Skye. I'm a scientific investigator.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Scientific investigator?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Difficult-looking legal books stand in a formidable row. They mock me. I tried reading one, and it made my head hurt. When I closed it, it slipped out of my hand. Then my foot hurt too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia's plant, "Charley." I've been taking care of him in Maya's absence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia's desk. I sit here even less now that I've stopped taking cases. I ought to at least dust it off once in a while.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a poster of the Steel Samurai on the wall. Maya stuck it up here on the day that she left. I didn't have the heart to take it down.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I do sometimes get strange looks from the clients, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like it's cleaning day again at the hotel across the way. I hear they're planning a second branch outside the city. Egads! The bellboy was staring right at me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ema, was it? So you're a "scientific investigator"?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes! That's right! Is... something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, it's just, you seem kind of, er, jumpy. Or maybe just... young?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Young? I'll be sixteen years old this year!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I see... wait! Only sixteen!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm set to be formally assigned to Forensics in three more years. My work is becoming quite well known... At my age, no less!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, so what exactly is your current position, then?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, legally speaking... I guess you'd call me an "Eleventh Grader." But I'm ready to do my job! At my age, no less!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great, another future professional in training...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what's this about a case? You said the trial's tomorrow?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">My sister didn't do it! She wouldn't stab someone with a knife! She wouldn't!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... it's a murder case.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I don't care if there's a witness who saw her do it! She didn't do it! I know she didn't do it! It's a scientific fact!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And... there's a witness.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">J-just talk to her! You have to talk to her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right... I suppose I will.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I promised her I'd bring Mia Fey, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's interesting... How would she know Mia?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you want to be a scientific investigator when you grow up, then?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">E-excuse me? I'm not a child, I'll have you know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Still, it's good to have a goal. Albeit a very unusual one.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I believe investigations should be done scientifically! Don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, yeah. <thought>Sure can't fault her for a lack of enthusiasm.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">If this case is handled scientifically, I'm sure my sister's name will be cleared!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your sister...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I've been doing research, you know! I'm developing a new scientific method of case investigation! I'll show you when I'm done!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm looking forward to it. <thought>Guess I should get down to the Detention Center and talk to her sister.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">My sister asked for her specifically. Mia Fey... was a few years below her in school.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So she went to the same school as Mia.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">She always told me to go to Mia if I ever needed a defense attorney... And, well... I need one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, incidentally, Mia is a woman.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mia... Yeah, I thought it was a little strange when I saw you, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it's nice of you to help your sister out like this. You must be close.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well... Actually, when she gets like she is now, I kind of hate her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">But... But she's my only family.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your only family? What about your parents?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">They died in a car accident when I was little.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">See this? It's my Attorney's Badge.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ahh! Well! I've never seen a real one before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You're the first one who's actually been interested in mine, believe me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Its composition is mostly silver. The gold plating is flaking a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She analyzed it. Scientifically...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">There doesn't appear to be any corrosion due to sulfides. I'd give you $50.00 for it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but it's not for sale. Yet...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...</line>
<line speaker="???">Guard... I thought I told you I didn't want visitors.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">S-s-s-sorry, ma'am! It's j-j-just, your sister...</line>
<line speaker="???">No excuses! Or did you not want a raise this year, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">U-u-u-understood, ma'am!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-wh-wh-what was that all about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">H-hi, Lana.</line>
<line speaker="???">Funny. I seem to remember specifically telling you NOT to come here. Perhaps my memory is failing?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">L-look... I didn't want to come here either, okay? But your trial's tomorrow and you still don't have a defense attorney!</line>
<line speaker="???">I'll be the one in court tomorrow. This has nothing to do with you, Ema. Isn't that right, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! How do you know me?</line>
<line speaker="???">Mia mentioned you. I've heard... quite a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Er, I'm sorry. What exactly is it that you do...?</line>
<line speaker="???">My name is Lana, Lana Skye.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">I'm Chief Prosecutor for this district.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-you're a prosecutor!? <thought>Two sisters... one a lawyer. Could this be a coincidence? Ema... Lana... I mean, they're just like...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Is something wrong, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Smile for the camera...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitors the visitor's room. He's frozen in fear of the frigid Miss Lana. I'm feeling a bit chilly myself.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">There's something you should know from the start.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-which is?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">The suspect in this case has confessed to the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">W-wait! But the suspect... The suspect is...!</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Me. I did it. Well, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... why don't you begin by telling me exactly what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">The crime took place yesterday, February 21, at 5:15 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's quite specific.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">It was in the witness's deposition. A witness clearly saw me committing the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... My, that was a bit of bad luck, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">The crime took place in the underground parking lot at the Prosecutor's Office. The body was found in the trunk of my subordinate's car.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Prosecutor's Office, huh? <thought>In your subordinate's car trunk? Classy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lana">I was arrested on the spot. Caught red-handed, as it were.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>My, my...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, who was the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">An investigator with the Police Department. I suppose the correct term is "Detective."</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A detective...?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Death was due to a loss of blood. He was stabbed once in the stomach.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By... you?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Death wasn't immediate, but the wound was fatal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Allow me to repeat myself, Mr. Wright. The victim was a detective. You know what that means, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh oh!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What? Mr. Wright? What does it mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it means...</line>
<line speaker="Lana">The police department will consider it a matter of pride to have me found guilty. They will use any means at their disposal to do so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This case gets worse and worse with everything I learn.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you're the Chief Prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">That is correct. I'm responsible for overseeing every trial handled by prosecutors in this district. I make sure the prosecutors have what they need to do the job, and manage every aspect. Those are my responsibilities, in a nutshell.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's an awfully large nutshell.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lana">Still, I'm a little surprised. I would think you'd recognize the district's Chief Prosecutor, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">In fact, it seems impossible you wouldn't...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um... Lana? What happened to your hand?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Oh, this? I cut myself by accident. When I stabbed him, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">I'm not very good at being a criminal, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How am I supposed to defend this!? Time to change the subject... Wait, she was in the class ahead of Mia, wasn't she...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, you were in school with Mia, correct? A few years above her?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">... Ema told you that, too, did she?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">W-well, why not? I did drag him all the way here from his office!</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Although it seems he has very little in common with Mia...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lana">It was in law school. I was in my third year, and she was auditing the class. She was different than the other students.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Different?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">She was strong... She'd do anything to become a defense attorney. Anything. That... was probably why she was attracted to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-excuse me!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Intellectually attracted! Lana was top of her class in school.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">I was the best there was.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm doing pretty good in school too, by the way!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It sounds a bit different when Ema says it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lana">Your badge looks new.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I polish it daily.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">In a few years, the gold plating will flake off. Then we'll see the real you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gah! What ever happened to innocent small talk!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lana">Give it three years. Then we'll see what you have become.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Well, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">As you can plainly see, I am admitting my guilt. I think it's safe to say... there's no way you can take this case. None.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">B-but, Lana!</line>
<line speaker="Lana">...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You... you were always this way, weren't you? You never think of anyone</line>
<line speaker="Lana">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I know you didn't do it, Lana, I know! So... So how can you say you did!?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">If I lose you... I'll be all alone! I... I hate you, Lana!</line>
<line speaker="Lana">... Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">I believe our discussion here is ended. The rest... I leave to you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! Um... you mean, you're requesting my services as your defense?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">Don't lose any sleep over it. Your client has confessed, after all. The case is over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right... I'll do what I can to get to the bottom of this.</line>
<line speaker="Lana">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Lana has confessed to the crime, yes... But something doesn't fit. It's that look in Ema's eyes. There's something else going on here... and I'm going to find out what!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm sorry, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? About what?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">My sister... She's not always like that you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I just never expected to be defending another prosecutor again.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">She's changed a lot. She used to be so gentle, always smiling. Everybody liked her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... <thought>Sorry, but I'm having trouble imagining that.</thought> What happened to her?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I don't know for certain myself... I think maybe she... Well, maybe not.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like there's something there that defies a simple scientific explanation.</thought> Let's go check out this underground parking at the Prosecutor's Office, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">O-Okay!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this is the lot where it all happened?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Looks like they're still investigating...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Funny that my first visit to the Prosecutor's Office should be like this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey everyone! Keep up the good work!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-hey! What are you thinking?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, they are going to be my coworkers three years from now after all. No harm in saying hello...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, there is. You know attorneys aren't supposed to examine crime scenes? I'm trying to not stand out too much, here, see?</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey there! You 'specting to go unnoticed here, pardner?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">P-Pardner?</line>
<line speaker="???">What do we have here? Looks like a bambina got loose from the ranch and is up to no good! Folks gotta learn to keep them dogies tied down, pardner.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">M-Mr. Marshall!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Marshall? Looks more like a sheriff to me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Lookie here, bambina. I know how you feel. But this is my gang's gold strike, see?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Strike...?</line>
<line speaker="???">This is our claim, our territory. And the goldmine is... evidence. If you're fixin' to mess with what's ours... You'll regret it, pardner! You know what dreams the cacti out in the desert dream? You want to?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's this guy talking about!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">You head along home now. Happy trails, bambina!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was that uh, hombre, a friend of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Uh... kind of... sort of... Yeah. He's a detective.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who thinks he's a sheriff from the Wild West it seems.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Look! A stylish, glass-walled room! Very nice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You could see the whole parking lot from in there.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It says "SECURITY." Perhaps it's a cafe?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">"Cafe Security"... Yeah, that must be it. Let's check it out later!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um. I hate to break it to you, but I think that's probably just a security guard office.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">... You know, I scored a 97 on my science test the other day!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Too bad they don't have a test for common sense.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">This is where the cars leave the lot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The arrow on the ground makes it look more like an entrance.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What are you talking about? It's plainly an exit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, maybe it's both. Kind of a dual purpose?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah hah! The theory of relativity!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I've got to write this down. Ah! Hey, hey, Mr. Wright! Maybe you know... Was Mr. Relativity, German? Or was he British?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Relativity? Are you sure that was his name?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Look! A door! This must mean something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure that doors "mean" anything.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No! It won't open! A mysterious lock!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I fail to see what's mysterious about it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright... You need to learn to enjoy life more.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's finish our investigation first, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah hah! A ladder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... That's a stepladder.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What's the difference? In scientific terms, please.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-scientific, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Look at the basic nature of things, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This all seems so horribly familiar somehow...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Here, a phone. Let's see if it works...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey. Don't touch stuff we don't need to be touching.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">... I can't hear anything! My ears! No, my ears! Maybe it's due to the barometric pressure...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is she babbling about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey!? What did you just say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">See? You can hear just fine. The phone's broken!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This wall is in our way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's got a faucet for water.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wait! I know! This "wall" is merely a facade, hiding the truth... This is no wall, but a water tank!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I fail to see how it makes any difference either way...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An oil drum. Looks like it's filled with water.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I-it's heavy! I can't even budge it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The drum over here is on its side.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wait! I know! I'll hide in here and do a stake-out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think you'll probably just get arrested. <thought>In fact, you may not even have to hide in the drum to get arrested.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">What? I'm not suspicious!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this? A wallet?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, excuse me! Officer!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">W-w-waaaait! What are you doing, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What am I doing? I just found this wallet, so I'm handing it over to the police...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I don't believe it! This is real basic: anything at a crime scene is evidence! Let's be scientific about this, please! Just put it in your pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-how is that scientific? <thought>Sounds like theft to me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm called to duty already, and at my tender age! Here, I'll teach you the trick to examining evidence in detail, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>By the way her eyes are sparkling, I can tell she's been waiting for this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Okay, okay, now. Look at the Court Record! You have to be sure to examine evidence carefully on all sides! Now. Let's start examining! From every angle!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh look! I think there might be a clue there. You should check it out! Press the Examine button.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This... This is an ID card. <thought>Detective Bruce Goodman, ID # 5842189...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">See? Well? Isn't scientific investigation useful?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess... Though I don't see what "science" has to do with it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Let's be sure to examine every piece of evidence we find!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I've got to be on my toes from now on...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, no time to waste! Let's get hunting for clues! Hmm... I wonder what this is?</line>
<line speaker="???">Well, pardner. Looks like you got no intention of going home quietly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The sheriff!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Like I said before, this here's our claim. You'd best be moseying along. Unless you're fixing to bite the bullet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gah! Scary!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">C-could you just tell us one thing...? Who owns that car?</line>
<line speaker="???">Well, well. The little filly's got a good nose on her! You want to know who rides that red mustang with the body in her saddle, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Please!</line>
<line speaker="???">No problem, pardner. 'Bout time for vittles anyway. Get yourself to the saloon up on the 12th floor of the Prospector's Office. Might just find you a cervesa you like.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Prospector's Office? Where does this guy think he is? And when, for that matter!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Note to self: look up vittles, saloon, cervesa.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe we should check out room 1202... the High Prosecutor's Office!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">In any case, stay away from the car. You can look around here all you like, just keep your paws off our claim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right... great.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Great! Maybe there are some clues around here, Mr. Wright! Let's check it out!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So this is what the back of the badge looks like! And I always thought it had a safety pin!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Each badge has a number carved into it. That way, you can tell which attorney it belongs to.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You mean you couldn't lend your badge to anyone?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I'd be found out right away.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well that's no fun!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A name and ID number are written here. "Detective Bruce Goodman, ID# 5842189"</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I wonder why they only use numbers for IDs.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What else would they use?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Letters, silly! They're the reason we have a written language in the first place!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">True...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">"Detective: Gruce Goodman, ID: YABADAB" See? Wouldn't that be better?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"YABADAB"? Well, it does have a certain ring to it...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Exactly my point! Tee-hee!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It doesn't take much to amuse her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Excuse me? Were you two all set?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Us?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's this? She couldn't be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Y-you're selling lunches? Here? This is a crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="???">Hello! Half n' Half, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh. Uh, thanks.</line>
<line speaker="???">And you, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes?</line>
<line speaker="???">Some Crunchy Goodness coming at you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... thanks. <thought>Interesting way of doing business.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">This area is off limits to anyone without clearance. Especially passers-by. Or are you officers?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Uh... no, but you... You don't exactly look like the type to have clearance.</line>
<line speaker="???">Well, that's hardly a way to greet someone! Even if my days as the "Cough-up Queen" are over...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">C-cough-up? Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You know, I'm feeling kind of full. Maybe I'll pass on lunch...</line>
<line speaker="???">I'm quite connected to this case, you see. The images are burned into my eyes, you might say. Yes, all the sordid secrets...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Secrets...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Dear me. You are a slow one, aren't you? I'm referring to the murder. The stabbing of that detective.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Lana">A witness clearly saw me committing the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You mean you're the witness my sister was talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please! Cough-up Queen! Tell us what happened!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">The name is Angel Starr. Don't you go forgetting it. Or before you know it I'll have you whimpering at my heels.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-y-yes, ma'am! <thought>Yipes! She means it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here, see this?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ahh! I've noticed that defense attorneys have a tendency to want to show people things.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is this? A behavioral study of lawyers?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">This... this is quite the place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can say that again.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But, you know Mr. Wright, you could do your office up like this too! All you need is money and a little design sense...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not doing so well in either of those areas.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">In any case, it looks like the prosecutor is out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's come back later.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's a jacket framed on the wall like a painting! The fabric is high-grade cashmere... Italian styling... Silk ruffles, turquoise buttons, and a gold thread collar. I'm guessing it's worth around $5,000.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">F-five thousand dollars!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Speaking of which, your suit would be about...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-that's enough of that. I don't need my life appraised thank you very much.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Whoa! What a view! It must be nice to have an office on the 12th floor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess you would feel... important.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Incidentally... Were you to jump out this window, the time until impact with the ground would be... ... Got it! Approximately 3.23 seconds!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's handy to know...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Whoa! These are all case files!? They're stacked up to the ceiling! There's even a ladder...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">With them already packed in so tight like that... what's he going to do when he gets new case files?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">... Splendid, Mr. Wright! What an unusual observation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think that was a compliment...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ooh! What a soft and comfy sofa! It makes you want to say, "sofa, so good!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">"Sofa"... "So far"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I got it. <thought>I'm glad she's not an aspiring comedienne...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this? It looks like a shield of some kind... It's broken. Maybe it's made out of chocolate, and he took a bite out of it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It appears to be made out of bronze with gold plating. It's not worth much. $70 tops.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This girl has a thing about pricing everything, doesn't she?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I wonder what that big "K" means? Mysterious...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wow! What an amazing bouquet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No kidding. Hey, there's a card on it... "Back from the Dead -- Wendy" <thought>"Wendy?"... I've heard that name somewhere before.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">And here beside it... A giant Steel Samurai! Wow, I want one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? There's something written on the bottom of his foot. "Between a rock and a hard place. -- Wendy"</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Is the prosecutor in this office named "Wendy"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... I don't think so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A work desk. It's quite tidy, as one might expect.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What a nice desk! Easy to use, and easy on the eyes! It's polished so high I can see my own reflection.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd prefer not to have to look at myself while I work...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oooh! Cute!&#160;What a pretty tea set!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I go more for the instant tea bags myself.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Amazing! The drawer below is filled with packets of tea leaves! They're all sorted by place of origin and flavor! Look at this Royal blend! What an exquisitely splendid concoction!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's such a thing as taking a hobby too far...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, a chessboard!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not too up on my chess but it looks like Blue's in a bit of a tight spot.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The Red Knights have surrounded the Blue Pawn...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Those horses are mounted knights. Their swords have really sharp "edges!" And check out that poor pawn, his head is kind of spiky... Kind of reminds me of you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, I know, but isn't the point to surround the King?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">Somehow... I knew. Yesterday was a day of destiny... I knew something was going to happen... Just like I know that the Daily Special on Friday every week is salmon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Destiny...? Was yesterday special for some reason?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">You're a defense attorney, right? You should know then. You should know the foul misdeeds of the evil ones who haunt this den of inequity!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">E-evil ones?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Prosecutors! They have no qualms at all about blackening the name of innocents! And yesterday they paid homage to the most evil one of all! They gave an award for "King of Prosecutors"... What a farce!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, she's saying... There was some sort of prosecutor's convention yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I was almost compelled to lace their lunches with something foul...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Do you have a personal grievance against prosecutors, or something? Or is there some kind of scientific evidence of this, um, "evil"?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Young miss... Mock me at your own risk! You'll soon find out why they call me the "Cough-up Queen"!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ew!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">The most heinous of all the evil ones, the one they awarded yesterday... It was in his car that they found the body! Proof that he devours the evilest lunches of all!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">R-really!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Really what? I'm totally confused... One thing's clear. This lunch lady has a thing against prosecutors.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what exactly was it that you witnessed, Ms. Starr?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">It was a fascinating spectacle, to be sure! I now feel I know what they say when they talk about a "woman's wrath." To see Lana Skye wield that knife so...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Her knife flashed in anger, bringing him to a sad end. It was truly a sight to see.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Y-you mean you saw the very moment of the crime!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">The sound of his silvery ties to this world being cruelly cut still rings in my ears. And the rhythmic beat of Lana Skye's knife...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a second! You know Lana Skye?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Hmph. Of course. It's quite a feat... becoming Chief Prosecutor. How many lunchboxes of sin did she pack to make that journey, I wonder!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">She... always travels light.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now why would this pretty lunch lady know the Chief Prosecutor's name?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um... Could we ask you a bit about yourself, Ms. Starr?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I come here every day to sell lunches. I import only the freshest and best from the Far East. For some reason, the box lunches are a hit here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Why not make the lunches here rather than import them?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Did you say something?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">N-no...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Only true connoisseurs can understand... The kind you can only tell someone who has tried General Tso's Trilobite lunch set.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah... Nevermind... You win.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't even want to appreciate part of a trilobite's flavor.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">Anyway, I come here every day to sell lunches. My boyfriend works in the security room here at the Prosecutor's Office.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Y-your boyfriend?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">See the security room over there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The glass-walled booth?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">I sell my lunches and, since I'm here anyway, I drop in to see him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Since you're here anyway... I guess selling lunches is more important than romance.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, to scientifically analyze the data available so far... You, Ms. Starr, are a lunch vendor with an ulterior motive for coming here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Useful analysis. Not.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you have a bad experience with a prosecutor, Ms. Starr? I sense some... hostility.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Hostility? Hah! Perhaps. Prosecutors are all alike. And the bigger they get, the worse they smell. Kind of like 10-day old clams in the chowder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if Ms. Starr was involved in some sort of legal trouble in the past?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">That'd be a sure cause of food poisoning! Scientifically speaking, of course. I mean, now you're talking "Cough-up Queen"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I thought she was just a lunch vendor, but now I'm not so sure...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Angel">A defense attorney must be able to fight... How about you? Do you think you can win? How about tackling Lunchland's Pickle Supreme lunchbox!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wow! It's really crunchy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A box of pickles...? Kind of a sad lunch if you ask me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About this card...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">... Lunchland vendors only accept cash. No cards. Especially not a card belonging to someone else!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, this isn't a credit card. It's an ID card. It belongs to a detective...</line>
<line speaker="Angel">And you're showing this to me, the lunch lady, why? That's like showing a fine honeyed ham to a detective!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I always feel like I'm being mocked?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">This is the kind of room that just screams "I can do the job." Quite a change from your office, really.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Look, look! There's a trophy or something here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A trophy? What, that shield?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">It takes real nerve to display stuff like this. Whoever's office this is, he must be a real stuck-up jerk!</line>
<line speaker="???">Mr. Phoenix Wright... You never tire of prying into other people's business, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That voice...!</thought> Long time, no see, Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh? Aaaaaaaaaaaaah! M-M-Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! You know him from somewhere?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">O-of course! I'm his biggest fan! My sister introduced us once, and...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right... her sister was the Chief Prosecutor, after all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well? What brings you here? I'll warn you... I've been known to be a real stuck-up jerk...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">N-no! Did I...? No! It was just, Mr. Wright here, he...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! Don't blame me!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">W-we're just here to investigate a murder case!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Murder...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A body was found in this nasty, bright red sports car in the parking lot...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm? That would be my car. What of it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Whaaaaaaaaaaaa!? Y-y-y-your car!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll say one thing, she certainly can scream.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wow! This jacket is even lacier than his usual ones! This must be his lucky trial jacket!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lucky jacket, right... I've never seen him wear it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm sure there's a story behind why it's in a frame! Maybe I'll be naughty... and take a picture!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's getting way too excited bout this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Whoa! These are all case files!? They're stacked up to the ceiling! There's even a ladder...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Odd... I thought Edgeworth wasn't good with heights.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He must have someone get them for him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Strange... Why did I just picture Detective Gumshoe?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">He must study these case reports so closely... He's so cool!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You wouldn't say that if you saw him sweating bullets up on that ladder.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Edgeworth has such a comfy sofa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sofas like this make me want to curl up and take a nap.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I bet he pours over his case files here until the wee hours of the morning... Then he takes off his jacket, rolls up his sleeves... And goes to sleep using his arms as a pillow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't believe it. She's actually daydreaming about Edgeworth working...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I bet in the morning he has sofa hair, and little creases in his cheek from the seams! He's so cool!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sofa-hair is cool!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've been wondering... what the heck is this?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It has a big "K" on it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the "King of Prosecutors" trophy.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">K-K-K... "King of Prosecutors"!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a great honor. They send that shield to the best prosecutor each year. What! So?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that "K"... that's...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">"K" stands for "King"?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yeah, you got a problem with that? I didn't design the thing!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">"King of Prosecutors"... Kind of like "Employee of the Month," only better!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So that's the "King of Prosecutors" shield, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well done, Edgeworth. You must be proud to be the King of Prosecutors!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Congratulations! King! Of! Prosecutors!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please, stop saying that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That still doesn't explain one thing... Why is the tip of this shield broken off?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">My, my, my! What an amazing bouquet! Just right for Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No kidding. Hey, there's a card on it... "Back from the Dead -- Wendy" <thought>"Wendy?"... I've heard that name somewhere before.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">And here beside it... A giant Steel Samurai! Wow, I want one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? There's something written on the bottom of his foot. "Between a rock and a hard place. -- Wendy"</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wendy? Is she Mr. Edgeworth's fiancee?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... I don't think so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A work desk. It's quite tidy, as one might expect.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What a nice desk! Easy to use, and easy on the eyes! It's polished so well I can see my own reflection.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Strange... Why did I just picture Detective Gumshoe?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Maybe I'll take that name plaque as a souvenir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't. He'll sue you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, a chessboard!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not too up on my chess but it looks like Blue's in a bit of a tight spot.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The Red Knights have surrounded the Blue Pawn...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Those horses are mounted knights. Their swords have really sharp "edges!" And check out that poor pawn, his head is kind of spiky... Kind of reminds me of you. Mr. Edgeworth must be an avid chess player! What's wrong, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Edges... surrounding a pawn with spiky hair... Nah... It's nothing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, the body was found in your car?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Go ahead, say it, Wright. You think I did it, don't you? After you went through all that trouble to help me last year, no less.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">N-no, we don't think you did it! I mean, it was my sister who stabbed him... Uh, wait, no, she didn't do that! I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait... So you're the Chief Prosecutor's little sister, then?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Y-yes sir! Ema Skye! It, uh... It's nice to meet you again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that didn't sound forced at all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, now I remember. You've... really grown. I'll admit, it was a surprise to me, too. To think that my own car would become the scene of a murder. More surprising still... Now I'm forced to prove my superior's guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can understand... W-wait!... What did you say!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Lana Skye is the Chief Prosecutor... the top prosecutor in the district. She can't prosecute herself, so I'll be the prosecutor at the trial tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You!? Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To be honest... It's a bit of a miracle I'm still here at all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Rumors. You've heard the rumors about me, haven't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Miles Edgeworth... It's hard to remember a time when there WEREN'T rumors about this guy... Forging evidence, arranging false testimony, illegal searches, you name it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thanks to you, my innocence was established in the trial at the end of last year. However, there are some who say I'm the one responsible for the current incident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what? That's crazy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Some people need very little excuse to think ill of others. It's a fact of life. Impossible to stop.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Some of them even go so far as to present me with toys like this... They think it's funny.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Toys? That bronze shield? There's got to be a story behind that one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Chief prosecutor Skye? Yes...We first worked together on a case two years ago. It was my first big case.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's right, I remember.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Two years ago... I wasn't even a lawyer yet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Since then, I always felt that she was looking out for me... It appears I was mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">M-mistaken!? Why? I mean, I know she's not the warmest person... But I'm sure she felt some responsibility for you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then... why? Why did she stab someone in the trunk of my car? Not only that... She stabbed him with my knife.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wha... Whaaaaaat!? Mr. Edgeworth! Your knife was the murder weapon!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To be specific, it was the knife kept in the toolbox in the trunk of my car.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure you didn't do it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>C'mon, can't he take a joke?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">You have a strange sense of humor, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me more about yesterday... the day of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yesterday was the annual cleaning day at the Prosecutor's Office.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Cleaning day?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Working with the Police Department, we sort and file all evidence for solved cases. We call it "evidence transferral."</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wiping your hands of old cases, in other words.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh, and another thing... A ceremony was held at the Police Department. There's an annual review and awards for outstanding police officers and prosecutors.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's when you got the shield?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was at the police department yesterday afternoon... I got back here at 5:12.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's... very precise.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">People like myself and Mr. Edgeworth pride ourselves on our precision, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, I place little faith in my memory. The only thing I trust is solid evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the parking stub from the underground lot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The murder took place around 5:15...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So the murder happened right after you got back.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What, Wright? I'd appreciate it if you'd direct that suspicious glare elsewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I once dreamed of being a defense attorney, a long time ago.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What? You wanted to be a defense attorney, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yet, my path is laid out clearly before me... I have no time to reflect on what might have been.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Say, Edgeworth, I was wondering about this...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">M-Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Are you sure you should be showing that to Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh. <thought>He'll take it for sure, won't he.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If she sighs any deeper I'm going to start getting depressed...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, in other words, you were the best of the best this year, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You can take that foolish grin elsewhere, Wright. I lost a day of work to receive that travesty.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh? Why's that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I had to go to the Police Department ceremony to receive that broken shield.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Police Department?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Right next to the Police Station downtown. You've been there, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Where Detective Gumshoe works? Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um, I was wondering something about your shield... Why is it broken?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What does it matter? I've got more important things to worry about.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh. Right...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He doesn't seem too concerned about his award, for better or for worse.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yesterday was a very busy day for the Prosecutor's Office.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Maybe... we should ask him more about yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's against my policy to discuss evidence with the defense. Especially with you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He doesn't like you much, does he, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nah. With Edgeworth it's never personal... It's all about winning tomorrow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, check it out! There's a metal plate here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm. It looks like the names of all the previous recipients are engraved on it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wow. One guy's listed a bunch of times! "von Karma"... I guess he must be a foreigner?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, yeah. That's probably it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well wherever he's from, he must have been an amazing prosecutor! I'd like to meet this Mr. "von Karma" sometime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>When she says it, his name does have kind of a ring to it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Miles Edgeworth - 17:12"... This is dated the day of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The murder took place three minutes after Edgeworth parked his car. If only he was held up at a couple extra lights... he wouldn't have been caught up in this whole affair.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Perhaps.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It just goes to show you never know what'll happen when you run a yellow light.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This must be the victim's blood, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Either that, or Edgeworth cut himself peeling an apple. What's Edgeworth doing with a knife like this anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey! Maybe he spends his weekends roughing it in the wild!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth? In the wild? I think my fruit-peeling theory is more likely.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Are you kidding? I always pictured him as an outdoorsman!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now there's a scary thought...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Um...! Excuse me! But is Mr. Edgeworth, uh... anywhere on the premises?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm Edgeworth. What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">I'm here, sir, at the request of the Chief, sir! I've got your report, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Report? What? Did you find new evidence in the case against Chief Prosecutor Skye!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't like the way this conversation is going at all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Officer">Er... Skye, sir? No, sir! No name of that kind, sir! Not in this report, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I just heard Edgeworth's lid blow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Edgeworth's lid isn't on very tight, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I made a clear request to the Police Department, did I not? I need to focus on the trial tomorrow, so don't bring me anything unrelated!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Sir! But, but sir! I'm just following orders, sir! They told me to bring this to you! I wasn't aware of the peculiars of your arrangement with us, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Give me your name!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">U-uh, yes... yes, Sir! M-M-Meekins, sir. Officer Meekins!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Right. Officer Meekins? Take your report and leave. And good luck with that raise next month.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor guy. Looks like he was absent on the day they gave out brains and good luck.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, sir!? <thought>Gah! He caught me off guard!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As you can see, I'm busy. You may leave now.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">L-let's do as he says, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The victim was a detective from the same department as that patrolman just now. Go down to the Police Department. You can ask more there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">U-uh... Thanks. <thought>He seems to have finally calmed down at least.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm busy preparing for tomorrow. And I'm not in the mood for idle banter. Especially not with you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">L-let's go, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Fine. I'll just have to talk to him when he perks up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm busy preparing for tomorrow. And I'm not in the mood for idle banter. Especially not with you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">L-let's go, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Fine. I'll just have to talk to him when he perks up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm busy preparing for tomorrow. And I'm not in the mood for idle banter. Especially not with you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">L-let's go, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Fine. I'll just have to talk to him when he perks up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">You!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes!?</line>
<line speaker="Angel">You said you wanted some hot tea, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, no, but thanks. <thought>She didn't even look at me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mmm! You must have to brew the leaves a long time to get rich flavor like this!</line>
<line speaker="Angel">We "pre-infuse"&#160;the leaves with steam before brewing.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I knew it! So that's the secret to their aroma! Exquisite!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The only thing I'm smelling here is wasted time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Whew... We're finally here. Why would they put the detectives so far away from the Prosecutor's Office?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That took almost 30 minutes by taxi... and traffic wasn't even that bad. This is my first time to the Police Department, actually.&#160;? Hold on, what's that?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Disturbing! Why does it undulate like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, wait I know. This is the "Blue Badger." They're trying to make him the police mascot.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wow, Mr. Wright! You know a lot about the Police Department! Still, he does seem familiar, somehow...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Forget the Blue Badger! Who's that next to him!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Someone appears to be... dancing with the Blue Badger... Uh oh. He noticed me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He sure is running over here fast...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-h-h-hey, pal! W-w-w-what're you doin' here!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's my line, Detective Gumshoe. Specifically, why were you dancing over there?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What!? Um, well...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, at least he doesn't seem to be busy. This is our chance to get information!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! I'll have you know I'm a very busy man, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The usual wanted posters are hanging up on the bulletin board here. &lt;&lt;Do you know this face!? If you do, dial 911!&gt;&gt;</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You know, Mr. Wright, I've always thought it was kind of funny... I've never seen anyone who looked like the people in these posters. They hardly even look human!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>She has a point...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Uh, I was wondering about that...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What? The Dancing Blue Badger? It's my masterpiece!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You made this, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The chief threw together some designs and I just did my thing, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">N-nice work...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's battery-powered, so it can go anywhere! There's no switch, so it just dance dance dances until the batteries die!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Poor Blue Badger... fated to dance until he drops.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I always get excited when I come to the police station.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why is that?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It just feels like I've jumped into a movie.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You know, with all the police and criminals.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-well, I don't know if this is all that exciting.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sure it is! Look at those two officers over there. They're probably talking about the latest bust!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Funny, I thought they were talking about the weather.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The detectives in there look pretty busy.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Just imagine! Right now... Behind those doors...! A police drama in action!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Somehow the thought fails to excite me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, that patrolman is saluting the other guy. He must be a detective!</line>
<line speaker="Police">And then I said "hey, you do that, your soup will get cold, buddy."</line>
<line speaker="Patrolman">Th-That's hilarious, sir! I laughed so hard I cried!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">... I guess he wasn't saluting, he was wiping tears from his eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They make a good pair.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The banner here is announcing the "Crime Fighting Campaign."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nice slogan...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I wonder if they'll be selling fingerprinting sets.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think it's that kind of campaign.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What family wouldn't want a set at home? It's good for finding out who snuck into the cookie jar.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think most families can figure that out without the extra help.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! Do you know why patrol cars are painted black and white?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No idea. Why?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, I think they're designed after a panda!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A panda...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Not that I have scientific proof. It's just a theory.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... do you mind me asking how you came up with that theory?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It was when I was on a school trip! I saw a patrol car and it came to me! We had just been at the zoo, see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... What about zebras? Or did they not have those at your zoo?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'll give you one word of advice, pal. You'd better not agree to defend the suspect in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wh... Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? Well... It's just that the Chief Prosecutor has confessed to the crime. She says she summoned the detective to the Prosecutor's Office and... she killed him.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But, what if she's not telling the truth!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, well... no! C'mon, pal! There's plenty of evidence against her!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">B-but what if the evidence was faked?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal. Can I speak to you for a second?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Me?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Why is this little girl so peeved at me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She's a relative of the suspect. Lana Skye's sister.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whoa!!! The Chief Prosecutor's little sister!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Just, please investigate this case carefully, okay? Scientifically!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yessir! Oh, by the way. You might want to keep your voices down. You don't want to be overheard using words like "faked"...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's just... it's a sensitive issue with us these days.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So... what are you doing here, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Me? Oh, well... nothing, really. They kicked me out of Criminal Affairs...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe! What did you do this time?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whaddya mean, "this time"!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Then, what happened? I know things are busy right now... I mean... with my sister's case and all...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's true. We've never had a Chief Prosecutor murder anyone before! Only the highest-ranked people are being let into Criminal Affairs now... The lowest ranking guy in there is our chief of detectives. They're not letting any of us rank-and-file detectives in at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">None of you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I know this is an important trial, but isn't that a little odd?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So, anyway, I thought I'd spend the day getting the badger dance down pat.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um... Isn't there anything else you could be doing?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The Chief of Police himself is directing this investigation, pal. And Officer Marshall was assigned to the underground parking lot.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Officer Marshall...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that I think about it, Ema did seem to know that Marshall guy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A patrolman in charge of a crime scene... It's unheard of, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... this ID card belonged to the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He was a detective, like myself. Detective Bruce Goodman.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm... Don't you think it's strange? I mean, why would the victim's ID card be lying on the ground where we found it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, Detective Goodman should have been at the Police Department yesterday. There was an evidence transferal for a case he handled two years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Evidence transferal... Mr. Edgeworth mentioned that too. But... Detective Goodman was killed at the Prosecutor's Office...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, that's the thing... It's hard to say this, but... Word is that Chief Prosecutor Skye called him out there, to the parking lot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And Lana's confessing as much...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He's in a tough spot, again...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Again"...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, it all started with the murder of that defense attorney, Hammond.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But Edgeworth was found innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Listen, pal, there have always been rumors about Edgeworth. Forging evidence, making deals with witnesses... Nothing outright, but there were always whispered rumors. Ever since he was accused of murder, no one's whispering. They're practically shouting!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But... but there's no evidence against him!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, Mr. Edgeworth has always had unusually strong ties to the department higher-ups. It's only natural that people would be suspicious.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I had no idea he was under the gun...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Anyway, this latest case has started a new rumor. People say the only reason he took this case... is because he's aiming for the Chief Prosecutor position himself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But I know the truth, pal! Nobody wants to be the one who has to prosecute the chief prosecutor! Mr. Edgeworth is biting the bullet on this one! He's doing this for all of us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective... here's my attorney's badge.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You show this to me every time we meet, pal. Real men show their police badge. 'Nuff said!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I wish had a badge... Even an ID card would be nice...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait... Speaking of ID cards, I found that detective's card, didn't I...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Detective Gumshoe? What can you tell me about this?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? Hey, pal! This is a detective's ID card! You can't just keep that! You have to turn it in to the police! It's people like you that get me into so much trouble all the time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Meaning Detective Gumshoe must drop his card a lot.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm... let's see... "Bruce Goodman"... Goodman... Sounds familiar... ... Nah, my mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But, don't you work together with him in Criminal Affairs?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whoa!!! Now I remember! Bruce Goodman! He's the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's what I thought...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Can you tell us more, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This ID card belongs to the victim, Detective Bruce Goodman. You can do just about anything these days with a card and the right secret number... scary!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's only scary because you keep dropping your card, Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I forget my secret number a lot, too. It's scary! But... but I'm me, after all! And what could be wrong with that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I'll stay out of this conversation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, that's it! That's the "King of Prosecutors" award that Mr. Edgeworth got yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Were you at the awards ceremony, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course, pal! I got an award for diligence, myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... congratulations.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I was wondering, why is the award a shield? And... why is it broken?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, there's a reason. Um... I'll tell you what it is later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Apparently, he's forgotten.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But, I was proud of Mr. Edgeworth for winning that award. He's even got naysayers in the Prosecutor's Office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, we've heard about the rumors...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Found in Mr. Edgeworth's car, stabbed with Mr. Edgeworth's knife, huh... What would drive Chief Prosecutor Skye to do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">W-wait, I didn't mean... I mean, sure, of course someone else really did it! Someone who must have, um... Someone who must have a grudge against Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The car and the knife do seem a little too well-organized to be a coincidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Poor Mr. Edgeworth... What could have happened?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We have to find out a little more about what's going on with Edgeworth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">As a detective, I have to keep my mouth shut on that one. I know better than to go blabbing on about things I don't know about...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I wouldn't want you to do that either...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Good.&#160;</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... And that's all I know about that. I'm not officially on the case, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why aren't you handling the case, Detective Gumshoe? We met the guy who is... what was his name? The guy in the parking lot...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That'd be Officer Marshall. He was appointed directly by the Chief of Police...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Officer Marshall... Is he some kind of Wild West sheriff or something?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No, Jake Marshall's just a regular officer... From West LA.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">For a moment there, I wasn't sure.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Look, pal, let me try to make things a little easier for you. Show them this and they'll let you examine the crime scene... maybe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll be surprised if this gets us anywhere...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Just act like you're supposed to be there, and nobody will look at you twice, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, look here! It looks like something's been erased.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe it was a letter or something to Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Let's see... "Annual bonus: $20." Um... I think a couple zeros are missing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, that sounds about right. <thought>At least in that detective's case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">... Maybe I should rethink my career as an investigator.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like the investigation is still going...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">I have to be getting back to the shop...</line>
<line speaker="???">Sorry... Looks like I'll be stuck in this pit 'til the sun sleeps.</line>
<line speaker="???">I'll see you in my dreams tonight, then, baby.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Oh! Still here?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah, h-hello.</line>
<line speaker="Angel">Why the surprised looks? Didn't I mention...? I've got a boyfriend in Criminal Affairs, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What happened to the security guard!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Hey! What's wrong, bambina? You're lookin' like a dogie that's lost its herd!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Jake Marshall... Strange guy to put in charge of a crime scene.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">If you want to take a closer look, you'll have to deal with me first, pardner.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">A duel at sunset... The winner leaves the loser in the dust and takes all. The blood law of the gunman!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Note to self: jurisdiction squabbles are settled by dueling.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think one body per murder case is enough, thanks.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's something I wanted to ask you!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">The scene of the crime... a cold grave for men who've lost their dreams... And me? I watch over them as they sleep... dreaming of the desert's harsh judgment. ...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He's asleep.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... should we show this hopeless case something to catch his interest?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Officer Marshall? Could you take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Whoa, pardner! If you're fixing to draw on me, you best be ready for a shootout! You ready to become food for the vultures, compadre?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Are you ready, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Somehow I don't think he's going to help us.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Alright, compadre! Count to three!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">You gotta do that if you're going to draw evidence on someone. That's what we do in Texas.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Remind me never to visit Texas.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you mind reading this for me?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">What's this? I warn you, fan letters to me go right in the spittoon!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a letter of introduction from Detective Gumshoe. May we investigate?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Gumshoe...? Ah, that old cowdog? Hmm... He holding a birthday party or something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Look, where it should say letter of "introduction"... It says "invitation."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... I think he just miswrote it. <thought>Great, Detective Gumshoe. I owe you one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">No worries. This proves it's from Detective Gumshoe, better than a blood test. Guess I'd better let you in, then.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Th-thank you, Officer Marshall!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Officer Marshall isn't a "detective"... he's a "patrolman"... That reminds me of something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">That is odd! Isn't a crime scene supposed to be handled by a detective or higher?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Well, folks. The clues are calling! Welcome to our gold strike. Be like the settler! Strike out for lands unknown! Manifest Destiny! Let's have a hootenanny!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Note to self: police investigations are like settling land. Well, Mr. Wright, what do you say!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I say I won't be needing this anymore...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That looks like a cell phone.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Scientific analysis would suggest this belonged to the victim! I can't think of anyone else it could belong to...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's so scientific about that!?</thought> Should we check it out?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On second thought, let's not.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What!? Why not? I mean, don't you want to know whose it is?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Probably one of the Detectives dropped it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Come on! No detective would be that dumb!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't know. One detective in particular comes to mind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right! Let's check it out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Man, what a boring strap!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's wrong with it? Everyone has different tastes, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Here, check out mine. It's a Pink Princess strap! These are hard to come by, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I see he's as popular as ever with the kids...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm. The display is still on the redial button.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Redial...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um, Mr. Wright? Most phones keep a record of all the calls you've made and received. You just press the blue button to dial the last number you called. Convenient, isn't it? I'm surprised you didn't know about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry to disappoint you, but even I know about things like "redial."</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh? Oh, I'm sorry! It's just, you never know with people from your generation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whatever... Let's check this phone out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now, I wonder who the owner of this phone called last...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Note to self: a defense attorney doesn't think first, he just pushes the button.</line>
<line speaker="Cellular">*beep*</line>
<line speaker="Cellular">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! That song! I know that!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Hey! What's going on over there?</line>
<line speaker="Cellular">*beep*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah! Oh, s-sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I see you, pardner! You pressed redial on that there phone, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, well, yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Whose phone is this, anyway? It was on the ground over there...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Whose is it? That belongs to Chief Prospector Skye.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What? It's my sister's!?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">She apparently dropped it when she was taken into custody, right after the crime. Look... the last call was made right when the murder occurred! Looks like she was fixing to call someone. Except she only spoke for a few seconds, according to this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who did she call!?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">No idea. Sorry, pardner. Now, I got a question for you, pardner. I heard a phone ring just now... one of those new- fangled ring-tunes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? That? Oh... I'm sorry, that was my phone.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">W-w-what!? Your phone!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, uh, it's kind of strange, but... Someone called me right as we picked up the other phone, a wrong number...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">... I hope you're not lying... They shoot you for that in Texas, pardner!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh, I've incited the wrath of the Lone Star patrolman...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">"A Block"... This area is reserved for prosecutors.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Defense attorneys are relegated to "B Block."</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I dream of the day when I will be able to park my car here! I'll go over to B Block to buy my hamburgers from you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not planning on giving up my job that soon...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This appears to be the car where the body was found. <thought>It looks like the lock on the trunk is busted.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lana">The crime took place in the underground parking lot at the Prosecutor's Office. The body was found in the trunk of my subordinate's car.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Quite a luxury car. It just screams "I have money to burn."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. Prosecutors get the big bucks.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This rope... is it...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yep. They laid it in the outline of the victim's body.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">... So wait...The victim must have died when the killer closed&#160;the trunk on him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>You have got to be the only person I know that would come to that conclusion.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this? Looks like a note of some sort.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Look! Something's written on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're right. Let's see... "6-7S&#160;12/2"...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's a name printed on the paper above that... "Goodman."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe it fell out of his pocket when he was killed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well? So? What does it mean, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How am I supposed to know?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Note to self: for deductive reasoning, go to Edgeworth, not Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm sure Edgeworth wouldn't know what this means either.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So the note was in here...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It must have fallen out of Detective Goodman's pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">And? And? what does it mean? Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have no idea.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Note to self: for deductive reasoning, go to Edgeworth, not Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm sure Edgeworth would be just as confused...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"B Block" is through there. That's where the visitors park.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I can see the Lunchland car over there...far in the distance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, you're right. I like the cute design on the door. <thought>I can see... a cartoon cow munching down on a juicy looking steak.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">...&#160;Doesn't that strike you as a little... creepy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just don't think too deeply about it and you'll be fine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Officer Marshall? Could you tell us more about the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">... Good men always die young. Remember that, pardner.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... could you be a little more specific?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Bruce Goodman... He was a detective, right?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Well, well, aren't you a feisty dogie there now. Detective Goodman was stabbed here at 5:15... The smiling Madonna told me the tale...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think he means the witness, Ms. Angel Starr.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">One stab to the chest. A fine piece of work. This here's the autopsy report.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Was my sister involved with the victim in any way?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Funny you should mention that, bambina. Chief Prospector Skye and Detective Goodman... had nothing in common at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Nothing in common...?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">They apparently worked together on a case a few years back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So... there's no motive!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Goodman wasn't a particularly gifted detective. That's one reason why he didn't do much work with the Chief Prospector...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But, my sister called the victim here on the day of the murder, right? Here... to this parking lot?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">So it seems. Like calling an unarmed man to a shootout at high noon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, I don't mean any offense, but... Officer Marshall, you're a patrolman, right? Not a detective.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">You callin' me out? They shoot you for that in Texas.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I was one of them fancy-shoed "Detectives" till two years ago, to tell ya the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, really? <thought>Now he tells me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">But, you're a patrolman now. So how can you be in charge of a crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Nothing gets by you, does it, bambina?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, why are you in charge?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">No reason. We're just short on hands right now. I'm keeping an eye out in the meantime.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's odd, though. Detective Gumshoe was saying he had nothing to do... nothing important, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">He's nothing but a sad ol' cowdog, that can't find his tail. Maybe it's because he runs with that Edgeworth, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth...?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">That cowdog's been kicked out of this cattle run... by order of the Chief of Police. Just, he don't realize it yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Detective Gumshoe, kicked out of the investigation!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So there's no connection between Detective Goodman and my sister!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">That's correct, but... There's a goldmine of evidence against her...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">And the prospector tomorrow is none other than Edgeworth himself... I'm afraid your sister's fate is decided, bambina. Many condolences.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Officer Marshall!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Yeah, bambina?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">H-how can you say that! You and my sister, you were...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is there something between this cop and her sister that I don't know about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">...! I apologize, bambina. Something must have gotten to me. Maybe it's that dry wind that's a-blowin' through the Prospector's Office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Dry wind or ill will, someone's up to something here... but who?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Suspicions about Mr. Edgeworth have been flying around for nearly two years now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Forged evidence... arranging testimonies, you name it.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">He was unbeatable because he did whatever it took to win. Unbeatable that is, until he met you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But rumors are just... rumors, aren't they? These are prosecutors we're talking about! Evidence is everything to them!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">If you follow the rumors about Edgeworth to their source, you find one person... But... they're off limits. Untouchable, you might say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One person? Who?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Bambina...It's your sister. Chief Prospector Lana Skye.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What!? My sister...?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Edgeworth couldn't rustle all those cattle by himself. Some people load their guns with bullets, some people load them with "deals."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What, you're saying Edgeworth was making deals to win trials?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">"Where there's gunshots, there's bound to be bullets." That's what the old-timers say. There's a big ol' secret hidden around here somewhere. Everyone knows it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is that why Detective Gumshoe was taken off the case...? Did they target him because he was closest to Edgeworth?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">I see your badge. Looks pretty... round. Our badge is a star, a lone star, shining in the nighttime sky. A beam of light, illuminating evildoers who come in the dark of night!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Note to self: evildoers are weak against starlight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey, that's a sheriff's badge!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Marshall">What's that? Some kind of police passport?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is Detective Goodman's ID card. Strangely enough... We found it a good distance away from the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Good distance, in this rat hole? If you want distance, get yourself to Texas!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Texas...</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">This is a tiny little crime scene, in a tiny little town, with tiny little evidence. What difference does a few yards make, compadre?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Note to self: if you encounter suspicious evidence, think of Texas. There's no better way to study than to hang out with the pros!</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">Ah, a toy shield! Suits the boy well. What exactly could you shield with that? A toy knight, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Officer Marshall, don't you have anything good to say about Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't like him, right? We get the point.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">You know, when I was a detective, I got one of these...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm... Let me guess... Did it have a "K" for "King of Detectives" on it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, they could use the same shield over and over.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Note to self: the Prosecutor's Office and Criminal Affairs are surprisingly cheap.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">You know it! They've gotten cheaper with every passing year, I tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">5:12 PM... The prospector's bright red steed came in at a trot, real slow like.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A... trot?</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">My Madonna tells me the crime occurred three minutes later... So it seems the Chief Prospector was lying in wait! Maybe... waiting for her prince to ride in on his bright red horse...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So what you mean is... The killer intended to use Edgeworth's car all along!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">My sister's cell phone.</line>
<line speaker="Marshall">The last time it was used was 5:18... Right after Goodman was killed. Maybe she was canceling her date for the night?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why did Lana make that call...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's no need to push this again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">What's wrong? You look like I do during finals!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Never mind. It's nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, well, how are we doing, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess we got some clues... We have an autopsy report, a note from the victim, and a cell phone...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So... you think we'll be okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, the only thing still bothering me is that Lana is confessing to the crime. She says she did it!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No problem! I can guarantee that she's not the criminal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh by the way, Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know that song your phone plays when it rings...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Cellular">...</line>
<line speaker="Cellular">*beep*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the Steel Samurai theme song, isn't it? That popular TV show... for kids?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The phone that just rang wasn't mine... it was yours. At 5:18, just after the murder took place... Your sister called you, didn't she, Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I...I'm sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you tell me what you talked about?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I... She hung up right away.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A detective is murdered, and the suspect is the top prosecutor in the district. I've got a bad feeling about this... Like... maybe I still don't know everything that went on here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
</xml>