<xml>
<title>Ryunosuke Naruhodo's Seven Days of Sin</title>
<line speaker="Judge">I hereby call to order this trial of the defendant, Ryunosuke Naruhodo. Are the counsels for the prosecution and the defence ready to proceed?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Judicial Assistant Susato Mikotoba for the defence... is ready, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">For the prosecution, I, Herlock Sholmes, naturally stand in full readiness.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And I, naturally...am not ready for this at all. I don't even know what it is that I'm supposed to have done.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, that's right. When I heard that Mr Naruhodo was in trouble, I hurried here at once. But I have no information about the charge brought against him at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I haven't done anything! The Great Ace Attorney is due to go on sale next week. I'm just trying to keep a low profile and prepare mentally for busy times ahead, that's all!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo, your brazenness knows no bounds. To call yourself a defence lawyer, having committed no less than seven crimes of the most serious nature!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait! SEVEN crimes?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What are you talking about, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Until every one of these unforgivable felonies has been fully examined in this courtroom... ...I shall not step down from this bench! THAT'S what I'm talking about, my dear fellows!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... You do realise...that's the prosecution counsel's bench, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I don't believe you should have stepped up to it in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, Counsels. Now, let us hear the charge brought by the prosecution.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As I said, there are seven charges against the accused, to be heard in seven consecutive trials this week. This evening, we examine the first of those charges - a most disturbing crime.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What crime?! Of what does Mr Naruhodo stand accused?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Of leaking information, Miss Susato... as you well know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Leaking...information...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I still remember it clearly. The words out of the accused's mouth last night at the restaurant. The topic of conversation turned to The Great Ace Attorney, to be released next week. You recall, I presume, what blurted from your lips with no regard for the public setting?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...well, I think it was something like: 'I can't believe The Great Ace Attorney goes on sale next week! I can't wait to see what curious deductions Mr Sholmes comes out with this time!'</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Precisely! There you have it! My gripe in a nutshell! This great detective's appearance in the title was supposed to be a great secret. A surreptitious surprise. I didn't want it to be common knowledge, shared with all and sundry. To speak of it so openly and indiscreetly... Upon my word, there can be no more repugnant crime!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">'Mr Sholmes', 'curious deductions'... Both undeniable spoilers!</line>
<line speaker="Susato"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think it's reasonable to say that Mr Naruhodo's words were simply 'information', not 'spoilers'. And I do believe that your appearance, Mr Sholmes, is already highly anticipated. In fact, that alone may account for many people's interest in the title.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of all the words I'd use to describe your appearance, 'surreptitious' isn't one of them.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I wonder if perhaps your real gripe is with the description of your deductions as 'curious'?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You fail to see the seriousness of the crime... my learned friend, Miss Susato!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You believe it to be a trifle. But in the world of mystery, there is nothing so important as trifles.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In summary then, the court must decide the following: In the context of a tale of mystery, in which every leaked detail could be of significance... ...is it, or is it not, a crime to utter in public that which has already been made public?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">All people have a right to knowledge, naturally. But they also have a right to ignorance.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The prosecution has called for strict penal action. We shall reconvene at five tomorrow for adjudication. The defendant, Ryunosuke Naruhodo's fate is now in the hands of you, ladies and gentlemen of the jury. Do you find him guilty or innocent? What say you, juror?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Until tomorrow evening then! Please deliberate carefully!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">HELP MEEEEEEEEEEEE!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The jury has reached a decision about the first charge brought against Ryunosuke Naruhodo. Does the defence wish to make a closing statement?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Myself and my client are very much opposed to the leaking of information, My Lord. However...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...A few minor spoilers can't really hurt, surely? I mean, just the fact that Mr Sholmes will appear is-</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">'A few minor spoilers' you say? You fail to grasp the magnitude of the situation. The appearance of this great detective...can never be described as 'minor', Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Susato"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Susato">The prosecution's last statement - and entire argument - is completely inconsistent!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I, I beg your pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">If, as you say, you wish to keep the news of your appearance a secret, Mr Sholmes... ...then standing for the prosecution in this public trial as you are... That very act is surely a 'spoiler' in itself!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... ...I couldn't deny that isn't a possibility that doesn't make some logical sense.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, state your leanings for the court!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, it would appear that the matter is settled, then.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Seven-day sinner Ryunosuke Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you very much!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I happen to know of a certain gentleman... ...who was thoroughly estranged as a result of revealing 'a few minor spoilers'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You do?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, I know your kind only too well. You're the sort of person... ...who would blithely say to someone new to the Herlock Sholmes stories: 'Sholmes, you say? Oh yes, wasn't he the man who dies in the end when he plummets from a cliff?' And suchlike. 'But then later on, it turns out that he didn't actually die at all!' And so on.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He's right, there should really have been a spoiler alert at the start of this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But I'm sure the details aren't quite right...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hereby call an end to this, the first of the defendant's trials this week.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I trust you shall all attend the next trial.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Hopefully it will go as well as today, and Mr Naruhodo will be acquitted again!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is all. Court is adjourned until the second trial tomorrow evening!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hereby call to order this trial of the defendant, Ryunosuke Naruhodo. Are the counsels for the prosecution and defence ready to proceed with this second trial?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Kazuma Asogi for the defence, My Lord. Yes, I'm ready.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Herlock Sholmes for the prosecution, My Lord. As ever, in complete and utter readiness.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And I, as ever...am in complete and utter unreadiness. What is it this time? I really have no idea what I'm supposed to have done!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The crime of which you stand accused tonight, my dear fellow...is that of dishonouring a lady!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Dishonouring...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A, a lady?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed. The accused's judicial assistant, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Judicial Assistant Mikotoba?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I still remember it clearly. The words out of the accused's mouth last night at the restaurant. As the lady in question arose from her seat to leave, he noticed she had forgotten her purse. You recall, I presume, what blurted from your lips, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...well yes, I think it was something like: 'Oh! That looks like Susato-san's purse. I, I think you're forgetting something, Sasato-san! Susas-san! I mean, Susat-tsuan..."</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The accused insulted the lady by mispronouncing her name...not once, but three times!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, certainly, to call one's own judicial assistant by the wrong name is a graceless blunder, but-</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">No buts, my learned friend! For that third attempt of 'Susat-tsuan'... ...was perilously close to 'Su's Hat Swan'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">GAAAAAAAAARGH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Just try it for yourself! Try to say that name three times in a row and see how you get on! You'll quickly find out that it's harder than your average tongue twister. The truth is...names that look prettiest on paper are a death trap for the mouth!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The accused has wrought great disgrace with an ill-fated twist of the tongue...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In summary then, the court must decide the following: Is failing to say 'Susato-san' correctly three times in rapid succession... ...a crime worthy of punishment, or merely a result of a punishing name for the tongue?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The most beautiful names have a right to be pronounced beautifully.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The prosecution has called for strict penal action. We shall reconvene at five tomorrow for adjudication. The defendant, Ryunosuke Naruhodo's fate is now in the hands of you, ladies and gentlemen of the jury. Do you find him guilty or innocent? What say you, juror?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Until tomorrow, then, when we'll see how this case ends.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">HELP MEEEEEEEEEEEE!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The jury has reached a decision about the second charge brought against Ryunosuke Naruhodo. Does the defence wish to make a closing statement?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's clear that names with too many 's' sounds next to each other are very hard to say. So if anyone is guilty here, it's whoever conceived of such a name in the first place!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm afraid that sort of chicanery won't help you here. You see, I've been a step ahead of you from the start.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">W-What do you mean 'a step ahead'?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">'Susato-san' is child's play. You Japanese have vowels between your esses. But we Englishmen stare the devil in the face with a fiendish triple ess in 'Miss Susato'!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Go ahead, try it...if you dare! A rapid-fire triple 'Miss Susato'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Miss Susus- Susato-saaaaaaaaan!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">A step ahead? That last claim of yours was a step too far!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I beg your pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Since the beginning of this trial, I've been paying careful attention to your pronunciation, Mr Sholmes. And I'd say you've been doing your utmost to avoid saying the name of the lady in question. </line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's always been 'the lady in question' or 'your judicial assistant' or some such. Why? Simple... Because you know that you're very likely to dishonour the lady by mispronouncing her name yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">.........  ...I couldn't deny that that isn't something about which I haven't been not even slightly worried.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, state your leanings for the court!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, it would appear that the matter is settled, then.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Seven-day sinner Ryunosuke Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you very much!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hereby call an end to this, the second of the defendant's trials this week.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I trust you shall all attend the next trial.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It looks as though my job here is done, partner.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thanks, Kazuma. I'll treat Susato-san to something sweet to say sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Good idea. I'm sure Judicial Assistant Mikotoba would be touched.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>You're trying to avoid saying it too, aren't you? The lady in question's name...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is all. Court is adjourned until the third trial tomorrow evening!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hereby call to order this trial of the defendant, Ryunosuke Naruhodo. Are the counsels for the prosecution and defence ready to proceed with this third trial?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Iris Wilson for the defence. I'm ready for anything, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Herlock Sholmes for the prosecution, My Lord. As ever, in complete and utter readiness.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And I, as ever...am completely unprepared. This is getting ridiculous! Night after night, my name being dragged through the mud...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And this night, you stand accused of overindulgence. You recall, I presume, the incident in question?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of course I don't recall it! I've never even heard of overindulgence as a crime!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And yet you've perfectly illustrated my point with that bellicose 'objection'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Here we go...</line>
<line speaker="Iris"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Iris">The defence demands that Hurley explains what he's talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm...perhaps before that... ...we might be able to bring the defence up to a slightly higher level?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">An excellent suggestion. Pray, where are the potato crates kept in this courtroom?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, what a good view I have from up here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, and what a charming young lawyer we had hiding in the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The accused will of course be aware of the name Hiro Shimono.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh? Oh, well, um...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh yes! The lovely Japanese voice actor who reads all Runo's lines!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Voice actor...? You're blaming me for that now?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I refer of course to the studio recording of your 'objection' line. You remember the occasion?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Tell the court, how many takes did you demand for the nebulous reason of being 'dissatisfied'?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm...I don't actually remember, but I imagine it was rather a lot?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Sixteen takes! On that one little phrase! Without sparing a single thought for Mr Shimono's vocal chords.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Good gracious indeed, My Lord. But that is not all. The following day, for reasons best known only to the accused, 'dissatisfaction' struck again! The tireless Mr Shimono had to perform a further twelve takes of the phrase. Despite the fact that only a single 'objection' soundbite is used in the game!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">GAAAAAAAAARGH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The accused, Ryunosuke Naruhodo, is charged with objectionable overindulgence of Mr Shimono's vocal chords...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In summary then, the court must decide the following: Is twenty-eight takes of 'objection' indicative of pernicketiness or perfectionism?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">No doubt the final 'objection' was an expression of Mr Shimono's true feelings on the matter.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hmmm... ...you could be on to something, Hurley. Guilty as charged, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Iris! Isn't a defence lawyer supposed to side with the defendant...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The prosecution has called for strict penal action. We shall reconvene at five tomorrow for adjudication. The defendant, Ryunosuke Naruhodo's fate is now in the hands of you, ladies and gentlemen of the jury. Do you find him guilty or innocent? What say you, juror?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I need to go and cook dinner now, so I'll see you all tomorrow! Bye!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">HELP MEEEEEEEEEEEE!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The jury has reached a decision about the third charge brought against Ryunosuke Naruhodo. Does the defence wish to make a closing statement?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well! The defence has been making some enquiries and discovered vital evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You, you have, Iris?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well well...most intriguing. Something relevant to this case?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh yes! Very relevant! It's all here in this file. As you said yesterday, Hurley, poor Mr Shimono had to perform that 'objection' twenty-eight times in total. But it turns out that the take that was actually used in the end...was the very first one!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...What a cruel taskmaster.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're right, Iris, that was new information. But did you really need to share it with the court?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It may interest you to know that the 'objection' we just heard...was take number twenty-three.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">F... F... FORGIVE MEEEEEEEEEEEE!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So, pray tell the court, ladies and gentlemen of the jury: how do you find the accused?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would appear that the jurors are unanimous in their decision.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Seven-day sinner Ryunosuke Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">UWAAAAAAAAAAAARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hereby call an end to this, the third of the defendant's trials this week.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I trust you shall all attend the next trial.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I think you got your just deserts there, Runo, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is all. Court is adjourned until the fourth trial tomorrow evening!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hereby call to order this trial of the defendant, Ryunosuke Naruhodo. Are the counsels for the prosecution and defence ready to proceed with this fourth trial?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Judicial Assistant Susato Mikotoba for the defence, My Lord. I am ready.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Herlock Sholmes for the prosecution, My Lord. In full readiness, as I'm sure you would expect.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm starting to get strangely used to spending my evenings in this dock... But I really shouldn't be here! The Great Ace Attorney's release is...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">That, my dear fellow, illustrates your crime to a tittle.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry? What does?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Could it be...that you're referring to the title of the work itself, Mr Sholmes? 'The Great Ace Attorney'.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Very astute, my dear madam. The uninspired preposing of 'Great' to the front... ...is quite frankly an affront to the original title of 'Ace Attorney'. Do you deny this crime of cheapening?</line>
<line speaker="Susato"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Susato">But...it's a rather good title, isn't it? 'The Great Ace Attorney'...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And just in case anyone cares, I'm not the one responsible for it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Besides, any enduring follower of Capcom's titles would recognise the addition of 'great'... ...as akin to the addition of 'super', which did spice up some ghouls and ghosts in the past.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You'd advocate that the next title in the series is dubbed 'ultimate' then, I suppose?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What would the prosecution's suggestion be for the title, may I ask?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm, well, I should think... 'The Great Detective Herlock Sholmes and his Sublime Sepia Deductions' or suchlike.</line>
<line speaker="Susato"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I fear that may be a little long, and...in many ways the protagonist is really Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In many ways, Miss Susato...? And Mr Sholmes... ...the trouble is your full name is so long. It's been suggested it's hard to use.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You can't casually throw an anonymous party's opinion into the mix! That's not playing by the rules! The real issue here...is that as a title 'The Great Ace Attorney'... ...makes all preceding titles seem somewhat less than great by comparison!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">AAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear...are we back on that again?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In summary then, the court must decide the following: Is 'The Great Ace Attorney' a tip-top title or a tawdry one?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It's not too late, you know. There's still time to imbue the title with a little sepia sublimeness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The prosecution has called for strict penal action. We shall reconvene at five tomorrow for adjudication. The defendant, Ryunosuke Naruhodo's fate is now in the hands of you, ladies and gentlemen of the jury. Do you find him guilty or innocent? What say you, juror?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">This is my second time defending Mr Naruhodo. But don't worry, I have something up my sleeve!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">HELP MEEEEEEEEEEEE!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The jury has reached a decision about the fourth charge brought against Ryunosuke Naruhodo. Does the defence wish to make a closing statement?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It seems there was a very particular constraint when the title was being decided. Senior Capcom staff were insistent that 'Ace Attorney' should feature in the title somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's right. Which is why the creative team came up with suggestions such as... 'Ace Attorney Renaissance' and 'Ace Attorney: Democracy'.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">There was also 'Ace Attorney: Industrial Revolution' and 'Ace Attorney in London'.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I also hear there was another candidate put forward: 'Sholmes and the Ace Attorney'. ...Why oh why was that not chosen?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Susato">That last statement of yours, Mr Sholmes, is completely inconsistent with your earlier argument!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">S-Something I said...is inconsistent?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Three days ago, on the first of these trials, you made something very clear. That your appearance in this title was to be a closely guarded secret.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That being the case, if the title you were hoping for had been chosen... ...it would have amounted to an unforgivable spoiler!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... ...I couldn't deny that those aren't words that didn't perhaps usher from my lips not so very long ago.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, state your leanings for the court!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would appear that the jurors are unanimous in their decision.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Seven-day sinner Ryunosuke Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you very much!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hereby call an end to this, the fourth of the defendant's trials this week.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I trust you shall all attend the next trial.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Just three days now until the game goes on sale. I do hope you'll attend tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is all. Court is adjourned until the fifth trial tomorrow evening!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hereby call to order this trial of the defendant, Ryunosuke Naruhodo. Are the counsels for the prosecution and defence ready to proceed with this fifth trial?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Kazuma Asogi for the defence, My Lord. I'm ready for anything!</line>
<line speaker="Holmes">Herlock Sholmes for the prosecution. I assure you, I'm quite ready.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is a waste of time! All our energy should be focused on one thing now! There are only three days left before the release date and there's still so much to do!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And there, My Lord, is a perfect example of the crime for which the accused stands trial this evening. Mr Naruhodo, you recall, I presume, your suspicious behaviour of moments ago?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">S-Suspicious behaviour? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Your eyes, my dear fellow, your eyes! Two enormous dinner plates crammed into that sudating head, with a lone raisin rolling around on each. Never before has the world seen a defence lawyer with such an untrustworthy countenance! Nor should it again!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What my learned friend fails to appreciate, is the resolve expressed by the defendant in the antechamber:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'The trials' about to get underway at last. I am hungry for this win!'</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So while those dinner-plate eyes might seem to suggest the defendant is scared... ...what they really show...is the size of his appetite for victory!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Sadly, that is not the only telltale sign of the accused's panic-stricken mind.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Though out of sight from your side of the courtroom, I assure you the dinner plates are the tip of the iceberg. For underneath the dock... ...the accused's knees are knocking louder than His Lordship's gavel!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">A clear indication... ...of how shaken he is, as evidenced by all but two of the raisins being shaken off the plates!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">AAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The accused, Ryunosuke Naruhodo, is charged with disastrously dinner-plate eyes... </line>
<line speaker="Judge">In summary then, the court must decide the following: Are wide eyes and knocking knees an unavoidable display of nerves, or an unforgivable distraction for a lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I suggest you start looking for more raisins before all we can see are the whites of your eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The prosecution has called for strict penal action. We shall reconvene at five tomorrow for adjudication. The defendant, Ryunosuke Naruhodo's fate is now in the hands of you, ladies and gentlemen of the jury. Do you find him guilty or innocent? What say you, juror?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">This is a trial that we can't afford to lose. My reputation as a lawyer is at stake.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">HELP MEEEEEEEEEEEE!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The jury has reached a decision about the fifth charge brought against Ryunosuke Naruhodo. Are there any closing statements to be made?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Woefully wide eyes and cacophonic knocking knees... You Japanese have a curious manner. It's almost as if you wish to draw attention to your foibles.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What did you say?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It really is quite the most ridiculous thing. At times I think you're two plates short of a dinner set!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...I presume that's supposed to be some witty British idiom, is it? Is that the best the world-famous great detective can do?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Time to hear the court's decision, I think, don't you? So, pray tell, ladies and gentlemen of the jury: how do you find the accused?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would appear that the jurors are unanimous in their decision.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Seven-day sinner Ryunosuke Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">UWAAAAAAAAAAAARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hereby call an end to this, the fifth of the defendant's trials this week.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Grrr...talking about us Japanese like that... It's brazen mockery!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Quite. Raisin crockery indeed! But really, there's no need for dried or sour grapes. Ah ha ha ha ha hah!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">CURSE YOU!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Mr Sholmes should really think about 'raisin' the bar a bit, I think...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is all. Court is adjourned until the sixth trial tomorrow evening!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hereby call to order this trial of the defendant, Ryunosuke Naruhodo. Are the counsels for the prosecution and defence ready to proceed with this sixth trial?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Iris Wilson, My Lord, humbly representing the defence. I am ready, thank you, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Herlock Sholmes for the prosecution. Ready and eager to proceed, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The dock is starting to feel like my home port now. But how many times do I have to experience this sinking feeling before you're satisfied?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed! That very question brings us neatly to the crime of the day!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">What have you got, Hurley?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">How many times must the accused - or rather the accused and his defence-lawyering dynasty... ...stand accused in the dock before they are satisfied?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My defence-lawyering dynasty? What...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You recall, I presume, your future relation by the name of Phoenix Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I can't say the name rings a bell, no.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">He, like you, is - or will be - a defence lawyer destined for the dock twice! No doubt his fate was predetermined by yours...which has seen you charged with seven crimes already. Between the pair of you, therefore, that's a total of nine court appearances as the accused!</line>
<line speaker="Iris"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Iris">One of those seven times isn't even part of the game, Hurley. It's in an escape room event.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">An event? Pray, what do you mean, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Haven't you heard of it? 'Murder at the Old Bailey'. It's been hugely popular up and down the country!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, I'm delighted the public enjoys seeing Mr Naruhodo sweat as much as I.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And five of the seven appearances are the five trials I've had to endure this week! None of these have anything to do with the game at all!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm, nevertheless... ...it's a poor protagonist who's so closely acquainted with the dock even before his adventures go on sale.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Uuugh...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">If this trend continues, one can only presume... ...that great tribulations as well as trials await in the game itself!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">AAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The accused, Ryunosuke Naruhodo, is charged with excessive appearances of his dynasty in the dock... </line>
<line speaker="Judge">In summary then, the court must decide the following: For members of the Naruhodo clan, whose role as protagonists in these tales is to uphold justice... ...is a total of nine appearances in the dock unsurprising or unforgivable?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I have little doubt that the number will continue to increase. As early as tomorrow evening, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'll look forward to that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The prosecution has called for strict penal action. We shall reconvene at five tomorrow for adjudication. The defendant, Ryunosuke Naruhodo's fate is now in the hands of you, ladies and gentlemen of the jury. Do you find him guilty or innocent? What say you, juror?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It is exciting, though, isn't it? Wondering if Runo will be convicted or not!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">HELP MEEEEEEEEEEEE!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The jury has reached a decision about the sixth charge brought against Ryunosuke Naruhodo. Are there any closing statements?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The prosecution acknowledges the recent rise in prominence of the so-called 'dark hero'. The modern age has ushered the demise of protagonists of my kind: the guileless genius and champion of justice.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh Hurley, that was a masterstroke. You didn't even bat an eyelid.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...H-However! A hero so dark, his suit is as black as pitch and the dock is his permanent abode? That, I posit to the court, is a shade too far! Over-egging the black pudding!</line>
<line speaker="Iris"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Iris">I think you've overlooked something here, Hurley.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Nearly all the main characters that have appeared in Ace Attorney over the years... ...have been defendants of some description or another. And mostly hopeless cases at that.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">W-What are you saying?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I'm saying... ...that being in the dock is a sure sign of a venerable Ace Attorney hero!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">AAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, state your leanings for the court!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would appear that the jurors are unanimous in their decision.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Seven-day sinner Ryunosuke Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you very much!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hereby call an end to this, the sixth of the defendant's trials this week.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The next trial is to be the last. I trust you shall all be in attendance.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's right! Tomorrow's the day at last! The release date!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is all. Court is adjourned until the final trial tomorrow evening!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hereby call to order this trial of the defendant, Ryunosuke Naruhodo. Are the counsels for the prosecution and defence ready to proceed with this final trial?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Herlock Sholmes for the prosecution, My Lord. Quite ready, I assure you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke Naruhodo for the defence. I'm more ready than I've ever been!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well well, so you're vacating the dock in favour of the defence's bench at last, my dear fellow.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...For the past six days, I've watched my friends working tirelessly to advocate for me. But tonight I'm defending myself! I'll soon show you who's the fool from this side of the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's...a somewhat ambiguous turn of phrase, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Let's hope it's not you, Ryunosuke!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Oh...yes...that was a bit unclear...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Laudable determination, Mr Naruhodo. And most timely. For this evening's proceedings call for redoubled efforts on my part, too. You see, the week's earlier accusations pale before the great crime of which you now stand accused!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...! Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Orrrdaaar!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes...to what are you referring? What is this alleged 'great crime'?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Very well, Ryunosuke Naruhodo. I hereby formally charge you... ...of the most serious and most heinous crime. The crime of-</line>
<line speaker="???">???:</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I...am Lord Barok van Zieks.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! It's, it's the legendary prosecutor known throughout London as the Reaper of the Bailey!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The, the Reaper?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Seven-day sinner Ryunosuke Naruhodo... the charge is murder!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke/Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Don't be ridiculous! The defence dismisses the charge outright!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I didn't do it! I would never... I would never kill anyone!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The quintessential look...of a sacrificial lamb. You will be tried in your own land in the Far East, the Empire of Japan. Court will convene tomorrow, the 9th July! Rest assured, you haven't seen the last of me... my Nipponese friend.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The time has finally come, Mr Naruhodo! It's the 9th tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well then...it's time to get going!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Prosecutor Barok van Zieks... Ladies and gentlemen of the international jury... I swear I'll prove my innocence! I will win...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We must solve this case, Naruhodo-san! By ourselves if we have to!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So then...let us unravel this mystery...and discover what events led to this curious murder.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I will become a lawyer. I have to!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I know you can do it, Mr Naruhodo! I have complete faith in you!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And I shall be observing keenly from the wings.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...some help would be appreciated actually, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The Great Ace Attorney: Adventures</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Oh? You don't mean to say...this is the end? But what of the great crime I had prepared for Mr Naruhodo? He'll be bereft without it!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Never mind, Hurley. We'll just have to wait for Runo and the others at Baker Street. At least we can play The Great Ace Attorney to pass the time!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, you're quite right. We shall be waiting faithfully in London. So...until we meet again! I remain your humble savant...Herlock Sholmes.</line>
</xml>