<xml>
<title>Secrets of the Underground Ruins</title>
<line speaker="Maya">Who would've thought something like this would exist underground? This place is totally different from Labyrinthia. It kinda looks like... something straight out of a history book.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A long-forgotten remnant of the past. It does stir up a desire to explore.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">C'mon, Professor! Let's go explore this place!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm afraid that finding the Great Witch is our utmost priority, Miss Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay! In that case, let's hurry up and catch her so we can do some serious exploration of these ruins!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ha ha. Indeed. Archaic ruins are my speciality, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh yeah... I almost forgot you're an archaeologist, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Now then, shall we begin our search?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">My, these pillars appear to be most elaborately constructed. Those that built these ruins were quite skilled.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">WHOA. How high does the ceiling go?! I can't even see it from here!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It appears these ruins are quite large. Simply fascinating.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Who could have built such a waterway? The archaeological finds in these ruins are simply fascinating.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Crazy to see this kind of waterway in a bunch of old ruins like this. ...I wouldn't swim in it, though.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm. This door won't budge. It looks like it needs a key to open. I betcha the Great Witch is on the other side of this door!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, that is a possibility, however... there is still another room nearby that we have yet to explore.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, Professor! We should go check out that other room first, then.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder what this room is? There are stone statues everywhere. Say, Professor... Is it me, or do these statues all look really sad?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I agree. There is a certain air of sadness to them. They almost seem to be in pain.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Brrr...they're giving me the chills.</line>
<line speaker="???">...Heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh c'mon, Professor! I know being creeped out by statues seems kinda silly, but you don't have to laugh at me!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...No, Miss Fey. That was not me.</line>
<line speaker="The Great Witch">So glad you could finally make it, Professor Hershel Layton.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">As I thought. It was you that led us here. Tell us... what secret lies within these ruins?</line>
<line speaker="The Great Witch">Now, now... I think you're capable of journeying to "the Beginning" and finding out the truth all on your own.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">"The Beginning"?</line>
<line speaker="The Great Witch">Have you ever wondered why the Storyteller started writing the Story in the first place...? More importantly... why does he continue to write it...? The answers to those questions are located within these very ruins.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If that is true, then might I ask why you are sharing this information with us?</line>
<line speaker="The Great Witch">...Simple. I want you to get closer to the truth. I'm afraid you'll have to work out the rest for yourselves, but I'm sure that's child's play for a gentleman of your calibre.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What exactly are you plotting?</line>
<line speaker="The Great Witch">When the light of truth shines upon the hidden darkness of the First Story, the legendary figure will rise... The Great Witch Bezella!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Huh? B-but... you're Bezella...aren't you?!</line>
<line speaker="The Great Witch">Heh heh... Me? Bezella? I hate to disappoint you, but you've got the wrong person.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, but! The Shades were calling you the "Great Witch"...</line>
<line speaker="The Great Witch">Ah yes...they did indeed call me by such a name. However... that was for an entirely different reason.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...I'm afraid she is correct, Miss Fey. This person is not Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The real Bezella would never expose herself so freely. It would place her in far too much danger. It would be tantamount to turning herself in. Also...there was something very strange about those Shades in the forest.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Strange...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">One must wonder...why they would consider her the Great Witch when there is no magic present here...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah... Th-that's true... So much has happened so far...but none of it was related to any magic...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">When we met in the Eldwitch Woods, and even now... you had something you wanted us to find. If you were truly Bezella, there would be no reason for you to lead us along in such a manner.</line>
<line speaker="The Great Witch">That is correct. I am not Bezella... Rather, I actually wish to meet with Bezella. And that moment will soon come to pass...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="The Great Witch">The truth lies with your cute new friend... Until we meet again...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...! Please, wait! We're not finished yet...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............ ...I can't hear her voice any more. I think she's gone...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...It would appear so.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That witch...wasn't Bezella after all, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would seem our "Great Witch" has been demoted to a mere "witch".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aw, man...and here I thought we finally managed to catch Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Remember what she said, Miss Fey. When we find the truth, we will find Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Say, Professor... When we do find the real Bezella... do you think this will finally be over? I mean, everything... The witch trials, that fake fire pit... Do you think it'll all finally come to an end?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, I do. Bezella is at the root of all disaster in Labyrinthia. If we catch her, then everything should come to an end.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Then we know what we've gotta do. Let's go, Professor! Maybe there's a clue or two around in these ruins somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Of course. We cannot afford to stop just yet. Let us move on, Miss Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? I wonder what that sparkly thing was just now....</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Oh, something seems to have fallen. Hmm...it appears to be a key.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You think the witch dropped it?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Judging by the patterns on this key, it would appear to have some sort of connection to these ruins.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! It definitely does! Remember that HUGE door back near the entrance? I bet it's related to that door... My spirit medium's instinct is never wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">S-spirit medium's instinct, you say? Well then, let us head back and check.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! But, y'know...that witch must be pretty absent-minded to just drop her key like that. That's something Nick would do!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm not sure that's entirely the case. Perhaps...she intended to drop it here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? But why would she do that?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">So we can continue to move deeper inside the ruins, naturally.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh. You mean...she's trying to lead us to "the Beginning"?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, precisely.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Boy, she really wants us to find this "truth", huh...whatever that may be.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We could not have asked for a better clue... Even if there is an ulterior motive behind it. If it is the truth she would like us to find, then we must be prepared to face it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All right! Hold on to your hat, Professor! Because "The Order of the English Gentleman and Feisty Spirit Medium" is coming through!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ha ha. A most...ambitious title if there ever was one... Let us head to the entrance, Miss Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Wright... Mr Wright... We made it outside. The coast looks clear!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ow... Sheesh, my back is killing me.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I think that elderly woman has left for a break now. To be honest, I was a little nervous there for a second.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">By the way, where are we? Espella, do you know?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">No... I've never seen this place before. There isn't a forest like this anywhere in Labyrinthia...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We must have travelled quite a distance...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Um, did you guys see that just now?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">My...I wonder who that is. That's quite an odd outfit they have on.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right then! How about I go over and ask where we are?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait...are you serious? But...they're wearing such weird outfits...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Now, Mr Wright. You mustn't judge a book by its cover!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, you're right. What was I thinking...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">This must be where the wagon's horses rest after coming through the tunnel.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The horses' food and water looks like it was recently filled. I bet they must use these horses all the time.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Brrr... Is it me, or did the temperature drop when we walked into this fog?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A creepy mansion covered in creepy fog in an equally creepy forest... G-great...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Get a load of that flowerbed. They are- ACHOO! ...*sniff*...pretty.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">What an absolutely lovely scent! There's something very familiar about it.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um, excuse me! Could you perhaps tell us where we are?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">This is...Eldwitch Woods... An outside world that exists away from "the Story". An empty world... A world with no official existence... A world unwritten in the annals of history...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An "outside world"...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Eldwitch Woods...?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">All who dwell in these woods live as Shades, each bound to their tasks.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wh-what do you mean by their "tasks"?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">............ Could it be? Are you... Are you new recruits? Why haven't you attended the Great Witch's orientation ritual?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-the Great Witch...?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">......</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I can't help but feel he's giving us the most disapproving looks right now!</line>
<line speaker="Shade">You...you must see her right away! We exist...to carry out our tasks... Nothing more...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">H-hey! Wait... ...He's gone. Well that was strange...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Could that have been...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...? Do you know what that was about, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">There is a fairy tale that is often told to the children in Labyrinthia...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What kind of fairy tale?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's a story about a secret forest where the souls of witches sentenced to burn in the flames wander around.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A secret...forest...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Those souls cannot be seen by the living, and they say anyone who is able to see them...is possessed by the evil spirit.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A forest of wandering souls...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Maybe this is the forest mentioned in that story...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-but, I mean... it's just a kid's fairy tale, right?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">If that story is true... does that mean the person we just spoke to was a witch's spirit?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no way... Wait, hold on... Remember how we got here? We came through that cage in the fire pit, all the way down here. Which means... I think there's a very good chance that witches are connected to this forest. <thought>And...if I'm right, that means a certain someone must be here somewhere... We're coming for you, Maya!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">We should go check out the forest, then. Mr Wright! Espella! I hope you're ready!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mmm, yes. Maybe we'll find clues as to Maya's whereabouts.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, guys. Let's get going already. Our first stop... is that creepy-looking "haunted house" up ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Be careful, Mr Wright! We could be one bad step away from getting lost in this forest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Relax, Luke. We can find our way thanks to the position of the sun! ...Uhh, now which way is west?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">This place is quite eerie, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder if Maya passed through here too...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These mushrooms are huge! I've never seen any this big before.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">If these mushrooms were edible, I could make a loaf of mushroom bread big enough for all of us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who needs a roof when you've got branches? The sunlight coming in is really pretty, to boot.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright, I've read about trees growing together like this. It's a process called inosculation!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Look at the size of those trees! I-I've never seen anything like it!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">If the professor were here, I bet he'd find these trees very fascinating.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">My, how interesting... Look at how elaborate those little vases and figurines are.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what the heck could those tools possibly be used for?! ...You know what? I don't even want to know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of their houses. Yikes...this makes Labyrinthia look like the 21st century by comparison.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">These Shades must live in these dwellings...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">This well is full to the brim with water.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yeah, but...they don't seem to be using it at all.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Look, Mr Wright! It's a tree house! Ahem, I-I mean, err...that tree house is quite fascinating, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Knowing my luck, I bet that thing will come crashing down the second I set foot inside...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That path leads back to the lake we just came from.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If we're done looking around, we should probably head back and check out that creepy mansion.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What's that? It looks like some sort of altar, or something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'm getting goosebumps just looking at it. AH! What was that?! W-we should go...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet Maya would've loved to sleep the afternoon away under a tree like this...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow... It looks like someone must have fixed the bridge recently.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoever fixed this must be pretty handy. I couldn't even build a birdhouse out of sticks if I tried...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">These are the same flowers that were around the mansion. Just look at how many of them there are!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh my. Not even Kira sold flowers that looked or smelled like these... Amazing!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey, look! There's the mansion where the wagon left us.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Once we're done here, let's get back to the mansion and start our search.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup. We're definitely right outside of Labyrinthia...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">To think that all Labyrinthians have spent their entire lives within the confines of this wall...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These puzzles show up in the weirdest places sometimes...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Um... Would it be all right if I were to try solving this puzzle? I've been watching you all solving puzzles, and it really looks like fun...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, Espella. We don't mind sitting this one out, do we, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Of course not! I'll be here cheering for you! Show us what you can do, Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Thank you both! Okay then, here goes nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">50</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That hole we fell through is clearly connected to the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Maya must've fallen down here, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This means all of the people found "guilty" were transported through here...right under our noses.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what is this place...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It looks like a workshop of some sort. I wonder what's being mixed inside those cauldrons...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, maybe it's a witch's potion...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">*sniff* Hey...do you smell that? Do you think it's coming from the liquid inside? I feel...like I've smelled this scent before.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Umm, Luke? I don't think it's a good idea to breathe in too much of this scent. That's probably why all those people are wearing masks.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wha...?! Do you think...they could be wearing gas masks...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh... So...this room could possibly be a little more than hazardous to our health, huh? I think we'd better move on for now... I think my sinuses are stuffy...*sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright, look! There's another door on the other side of the room! And it looks like there's no toxic gas there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I don't know if I'd call it "toxic" just yet. Anyway, we need to proceed with our search, so let's go.</line>
<line speaker="Shade">...Oh, woe is me... What should I do...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Is something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">The Great Witch has gone missing... But I can't help search for her, because I have my tasks to complete... But...surely the well-being of the mistress takes precedence over my task... No, no, no...I shouldn't abandon my post here...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She's going around in circles. What should we do?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">...I'm so conflicted. What should I do...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um, excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">but [sic] is this "Great Witch" you mentioned called Bezella, by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="Shade">The Great Witch is the Great Witch! She is our mistress... Oh Great Witch...if only I could bring you back to us... But if only I did not have to leave my post...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It looks like something big must have happened here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you think this has something to do with the Great Witch? Not sure if I want to know, to be honest...</line>
<line speaker="Shade">The disappearance of the mistress fills me with worry, yet... I must see to my task... But...but...surely my duty to my mistress comes before my duty to my task... But...but...BUT...if I were to leave my post, I won't complete my task...</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Red flower... Mix in... Stir... Red flower... Mix in... Stir... No matter what happens... The recipe never changes... Red flower... Mix in... Stir...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's really focusing on stirring whatever's in that pot. Sorta reminds me of Maya whenever she tries to cook soup...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Maybe we shouldn't disturb him.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I wonder why he's so focused on stirring...</line>
<line speaker="Shade">Red flower... Mix in... Stir... Red flower... Mix in... Stir...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup. He's still stirring that stuff with a vengeance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Woah. They've really got the fire going on this one... Wonder what they're making?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I don't even want to think about how they went about making this stuff, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Judging by the colour, this must be made using the flowers.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ow, ow ow! Cor, that's scorching HOT!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Look at all these flowers, Mr Wright. I bet you could make a really nice flower necklace out of these.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They must've picked these flowers from right outside the mansion. ACHOO! ...Urgh. *sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Ahhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-is that...BLOOD?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The room is covered with it. What could have happened here?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... No, wait. This doesn't seem to be blood...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There... *sniff* You smell that? It smells like that liquid they're making in the room back there.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You know, now that you've mentioned it... I think this is that liquid.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, thank goodness. So that probably means no one was hurt here, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess not. Still...something clearly happened here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh...? Mr Wright, Espella... Look over there... Is that...a secret passage behind the chandelier?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, good eye, Luke! I wonder where it leads...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It...looks pitch black in there... So, um...should we go inside?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Of course. We're on an investigation, aren't we?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">R-right...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this? Luke, are you scared?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You've got it all wrong! I'm perfectly fine in the dark! No problems at all! Right then. I-I'll be right behind you, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yup. He's scared.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">U-um... I'm right behind you as well, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...You're scared too, huh, Espella? Thanks, guys... Who do I get to walk behind, then?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a huge rip down the middle of this curtain. I sure hope no one was hiding behind this thing.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I don't think this curtain would make the best hiding spot, Mr Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Blimey! Look at the chandelier! It's completely destroyed.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">There is quite a bit of damage around the entire room. Something quite big must have happened here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like this chandelier fell recently. It doesn't look like anyone was underneath it when it fell.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's still wet... This must've happened not too long ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If this stuff was actually blood... Brr! Gives me the chills just thinking about it.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Umm...Mr Wright? I don't feel so good...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-wow... Who'd have thought there'd be some ancient underground ruins here...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Wow... This place is amazing, isn't it? Look at those large pillars and that stream of water... Everything here looks so old. I've never seen anything quite like it. And you say this kind of place is called a "roo-in", is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, yeah... I guess you don't really have any ancient ruins like this within Labyrinthia, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ancient ruins...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Something wrong, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's just... This reminds me of the professor... If he were here, he could tell us anything we wanted to know about these ruins.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, that's right...the professor was an archaeologist.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yeah... Sometimes I can almost hear the professor's kind words calling out... Even now...I can almost hear his voice... *sniff*... Professor...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me too... I can almost hear the professor's voice... And Maya's, too...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I-I think I hear them as well...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um...come to think of it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It really is like...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">We can actually...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hear them...</line>
<line speaker="???">Now then...let's...check over on that side...</line>
<line speaker="???">...Professor...over here...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...! Th-those voices just now! It has to be...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... Th-there's no mistaking it...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor! PROFESSOR!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Luke! What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">P-Professor! It...it's really you! I-I...I thought...you'd never come back... Even though deep down I believed the spell could be broken somehow...there were times I just wasn't sure it was possible. *sob* Professor...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...I'm so sorry, my boy. I've caused you quite a bit of worry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Professor! You're all right! Um...Professor, what about Maya...? I...uhh...thought I heard her voice, too...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah, yes. Not to worry, Mr Wright. Rest assured Miss Fey is just-</line>
<line speaker="Maya">YOOOOOOOOO, NIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIICK!  Hey, Nick! Niiiiiiick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maya! Am I dreaming? Is it really you?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup, yup! The professor and I are as real as real can be!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You have no idea how relieved I am. Really. I've never been so happy to see you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I, uh...I'm really sorry, Nick. You must've been worried sick. It's just... Well, I wanted to do something to help Espella, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no! It's not your fault, Maya. It's mine. If only I'd helped you sooner... then none of this would've happened... And you wouldn't... have been dropped into that pit of fire!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I...*sniff* I thought I'd never see you again, Nick. I...I'm really sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Come now. Everyone here did the best that they could. That is what enabled us to power through the hardship and reunite. That is what I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, you're right, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Good old Professor Layton logic! Logic so good...it'll leave you good as gold, right, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ha ha. Indeed, Miss Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm so glad you're all okay. Um...Maya! Are you hurt?! Are you suffering from any burns? And Professor! Has your arm been properly reattached to your body?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We're quite all right, Espella, I assure you. You may rest easy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! Look! We're perfectly fine.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, thank goodness...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Phew. Espella looks super relieved...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">We're entirely unharmed, Espella. Please, dry your tears.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look what you started, Nick! Everyone got all sappy and now you made Espella cry!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright! A gentleman must never, ever make a lady cry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-why is it MY fault...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Hee hee... Thank you, everyone.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright. You kept those two safe and out of harm's way. For that, you have my utmost gratitude.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no problem, Professor! I honestly couldn't have done it on my own. Luke and Espella really helped me when I needed it the most. Likewise, I should be thanking you for keeping Maya safe. Thank you so much.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Not at all, Mr Wright. After all, it is a gentleman's duty to help a lady in need.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, you should really learn to be a proper gentleman, like the professor here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?! W-well... I'm not too sure I'd be able to pull off the whole top hat look, for one...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright, it is an honour to once again team up with you. No matter what challenges may lie in our way, with your help I am certain we can overcome them. Let us go forth and solve the mystery that is Labyrinthia, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Absolutely. We'll fight for Espella until the very end. Professor, I'm looking forward to working with you and putting an end to this mystery once and for all!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It will be my pleasure, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm, I see. So that is what happened to Miss Kira...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. That's why I think there's more to the witch trials than meets the eye.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah ha! So you figured out there was something fishy with that fire pit. The patented "Nick Investigation Method"! Dive head-first into a pit and figure out it's not really a pit after all. Proven and tested!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Boy, thanks. Anyway, that was how we ended up here. So...what about that "Great Witch" you said you ran into?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We still do not know much about her. However, it seems she was the one responsible for leading us here. She also told us of a place containing many secrets regarding the Storyteller's Story. A place she refers to as "the Beginning".</line>
<line speaker="Espella">"The Beginning"... You're saying...my father's secrets are hidden there?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">As I suspected. You have never heard of this place, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That's right. This is also the first time I've ever seen these ruins. ...I think everything will be made clear when we get there. Labyrinthia... Even the Great Witch...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is as the Great Witch said it would be.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ It's a bit scary, to be honest.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I feel as if... getting to the bottom of all this and exposing Labyrinthia's secrets...will change everything. Knowing my father's secrets...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I think the old me would be absolutely terrified right now. She probably couldn't even go on. But...I must stay strong. I must know the truth. I've been so blind to the truth this entire time. Because of you all... I'm finally able to see the world for what it really is! That's why I want to go along with you!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We're all in this together!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Woo! Get ready, Espella! This is going to be an adventure you'll never forget!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Okay, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I believe that large door on the other side of the room should lead us further inside.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... In that case...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We should investigate immediately, right, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, that's right. I must say, I have not seen you so excited in quite a while, my boy.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">R-really? Heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's because he's just itching to get to solving some puzzles with you, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ha ha. Then we should not delay. Let's investigate that large gate ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Amazing... Look at these pillars. They must be really old and yet they're still standing.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">My, these pillars appear to be most elaborately constructed. Those that built these ruins were quite skilled.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I wonder if ancient Labyrinthians were the ones that built this place?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Perhaps the painting in the Great Archive was found here in these very ruins.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">WHOA. How high does the ceiling go?! I can't even see it from here!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It appears these ruins are quite large. Simply fascinating.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't believe something this huge can exist underground...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey, Professor, why do you think someone would build something like this, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Who could have built such a waterway? The archaeological finds in these ruins are simply fascinating.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Crazy to see this kind of waterway in a bunch of old ruins like this. ...I wouldn't swim in it, though.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">So much water... I wonder where it all goes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess the water that flows through Labyrinthia is the same water that goes through these ruins.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? That's weird. There's no handle. It doesn't look like we'll be able to pull or push the door open.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh! Look. It looks like there's a keyhole.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But...we don't have a key.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Heh heh heh. Nick, what would you do without me? Zvarri! The professor and I found this back in the side-room over there!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It appears this key belongs to this door.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now, watch as "Maya the Magnificent" works her magic and opens the door! Please, hold your applause... ...<cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>> ............Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What seems to be the matter, Miss Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What gives?! This key won't work. Maybe it's a fake...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I like how your first instinct is to think the key is fake, instead of just belonging to another door.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Let us not hastily jump to any conclusions. Look closely here. It appears this key...is part of a puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-right... A puzzle, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would seem our progression will not be as easy as we thought.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, then. If it's a puzzle that needs solving, that's your cue, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Not quite, Mr Wright. This puzzle requires your particular expertise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, m-me?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Your unique way of thinking may be crucial to finding the solution. Do not worry, you will do fine. Remember, you have seen many different kinds of puzzles during our time here in Labyrinthia. I believe you are now well prepared for tackling any number of puzzles that may come your way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not exactly sure that's true, but... if there are any contradictions in this puzzle, I'll do my very best to point them out!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">50</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect submission during the multiple choice segment</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">After inserting key blade through both sides of lock</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hmm... This key just won't turn! It gets stuck halfway through!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's like Maya said. There must be some special way of unlocking it...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Heh heh heh... You just need to flip your way of thinking, that's all. It could be that we just need to flip the key, too!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That's it, Maya! The "key" is in how you hold the key. Let's give it another shot!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? It's still not working? But we've tried everything... It just won't open.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">There must be some other way the key fits into the keyhole.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm. Perhaps it would be wise to re-evaluate our way of thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Boy... This is like the puzzle to end all puzzles...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">C'mon, Nick! Quit your whining! Where's that ace attorney spirit?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who's whining?! Anyways... Maybe we should try a little courtroom thinking on this one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...So, the problem is that we haven't been able to figure out what we have to do past this point.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm? Have you spotted something, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, yeah... You could say that. I think we've been thinking about this all wrong... That's why we haven't been able to see the "true nature" of this puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Excellent, Mr Wright. Let us clear our heads and give it another go, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"The 'key' to proceeding is in the key"... This must have something to do with the true nature of the key itself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This wouldn't be much of a door if the keyhole didn't work. It can't be that, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh boy... These two are really serious about puzzles...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This wouldn't be much of a door if the keyhole didn't work. It can't be that, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh boy... These two are really serious about puzzles...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The true nature of this puzzle... lies in the very key itself! Take a closer look at the key. Notice the small gaps all around? We just have to move this and... There! The "key" to the key! So what do we do now? Professor, are you thinking what I'm thinking?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. These pieces appear to fit into something. It's a puzzle within a puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A puzzle within a... Hey! Mr Wright! That must mean the area around the keyhole is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. The pieces are the key and the space around the "keyhole" is the real keyhole!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa! That was awesome, Nick! Who'd have thought the key would have a completely different form?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Now that's what I call thinking outside the box, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Now we'll be able to continue through the ruins, and it's all thanks to you, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, ha ha... I don't really think I did all that much, though.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You have my thanks as well, Mr Wright. Such a...unique skill as yours is no small feat, I assure you. With our combined efforts, I am confident we can get to the bottom of the mysteries clouding Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Absolutely, Professor. ...You know, it's been a good while since we were last able to team up.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. Unfortunately, I've been a little less animate than usual of late.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But hey! It all worked out in the end. And it's all thank to the professor's golden arm!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, but still... the only reason we even got his arm back was because that pawnbroker returned it. We got really lucky, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Did you say my arm was returned by a pawnbroker, Mr Wright? If I may ask...what is the particular story behind that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-don't worry about it, Professor! It's probably best if we just keep on moving.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Y-yes! Good idea, Mr Wright! Let's go, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what? There's...fire in those statues...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm. It would appear we've stumbled upon yet another very elaborate mechanism here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Luke! Espella! Check this out! Those plants are glowing!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um, Maya, that's actually luminous moss! Even though the moss looks like it's glowing in the dark... it's actually reflecting the light from its surroundings. Its unique cells are responsible for the mysterious green colour.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">So, it's actually reflecting light? I must say, that was an incredibly detailed explanation, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Of course! I am the professor's apprentice, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Luke, check this out. If you poke the moss, it totally makes your finger glow! I say we try a little experiment. Stay still. I'm gonna put a whole bunch of moss all over you... that way you'll be as "bright" as the professor!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">N-no! That's not funny! Please put down that clump of moss, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Hee hee.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like the tension level just took a big drop, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I think it is about time we saw some smiling faces, wouldn't you agree, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, definitely. Having the whole gang together again is reason enough to smile, all right.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright, let's give them some space and explore on ahead ourselves for the time being.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, look! There's a puzzle hidden here!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And quite an ancient one at that, my boy... I do wonder what sort of puzzle this could be. Most fascinating.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'll solve it straight away, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">20</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The water's just shooting outta there, huh? Kinda like a river of SOULS! Spoooooooky!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The water's coming out of that cave pretty fast. It's almost like it's coming out of a pipe somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One wrong step and it's into the rushing stream. ...I wonder where you'd end up?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Water sources like this were often the cradle of ancient civilisations.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I can't see anything up ahead through all of this darkness...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I am certain "the Beginning" lies just up ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We can't stop now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Professor, it looks like there are letters of some sort etched into this stone slate.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This...would appear to be some kind of ancient script.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh... A real shame we can't read it.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright, surely you remember my occupation, do you not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... O-oh, yeah! You said you're...an archaeologist, right? Then that means you can actually read it?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I cannot say for certain, but I will do my best to see what I can decode. Give me one moment.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the professor is an archaeologist trying to uncover the secrets of magic... Sounds like something out of a movie...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick...what are you and the professor doing over there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We found some ancient writing on this stone slate. The professor is attempting to decipher it right now, so keep your voice down.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's so cool. In a really sciency, geeky kinda way!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Hey, where are Espella and Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, them? They're over by the water trying to wash all the moss off Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm gonna go out on a limb here and say you must have had something to do with that, Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">My apologies for the wait... I have managed to decipher the script.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Amazing, Professor! So? So? Don't keep us waiting! What's it say? Is it a clue about witches and magic? Or maybe it's Bezella's secret evil plans for taking over Labyrinthia?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...I am afraid not, Miss Fey. This slate... appears to be a warning.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A...warning, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes. Allow me to read it aloud:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">C-"calamity"...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Haunted with memories most terrifying...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you think it means...Bezella? If we continue on to "the Beginning", will we end up finding the real Bezella?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Going strictly by what we've read so far, I would say that is the most likely scenario.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">But Bezella is the one responsible for the appearance of witches and all the other misfortunes we've seen so far... Yet, what's written on this slate seems to say the opposite. It's almost like Bezella was actually sealed away.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And long ago, someone must have been able to break that seal and release her. That would explain why Bezella is on the loose again.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">G-guys, what should we do?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">......</line>
<line speaker="Layton">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...I say we go on.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Didn't we all agree that we would seek out the truth no matter what? If that's the case, then we cannot just turn back now.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Right you are, Espella. We cannot abandon our duty and turn back. Although the road ahead may be fraught with danger... it is unlikely that we will have another opportunity like this to find out the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. We only have until the start of the parade. That doesn't give us much time. We have to find some decisive clues here!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Like finding out who released Bezella from her prison.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All right then, it's settled. C'mon, guys, let's saddle up!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Too right! Let's get going.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">First is the Seal of Leviathan... I believe it may be referring to this very river. Perhaps we can find a clue somewhere nearby.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey...there's something under the water. It looks like a stone path.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You're right, Maya. But it doesn't look safe to cross with that current.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You don't think we could somehow raise those platforms up and use them to get across, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ ...Well done, my boy. It would seem we have discovered another puzzle. I believe these "seals" mentioned in the text are actually puzzles.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Um... Professor, would it be all right if I gave this puzzle a try?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">No need to worry, Espella. The professor will get us across in no time!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">B-but... I want to do my part and help out, too! Please let me help out! I MUST REPAY YOUR KINDNESS!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, I-I'm sorry. I didn't mean to shout just now.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">No need to apologise. You've made your feelings quite clear, Espella. And for that, you have my thanks. Now then, we shall leave this puzzle to you. I know you will be successful.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">O-okay! Thank you so much! I won't let you down, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Amazing, Espella! You raised the platforms!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I really did it, didn't I?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That was quite remarkable, Espella. Extremely well done.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I knew you could do it, Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The civilization that once existed here must have been quite advanced considering the mechanisms used on these platforms. I cannot help but wonder what became of them...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I bet there will be a clue to that somewhere up ahead, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this must be...the Seal of Despair.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Y'know, it's probably best we DON'T look down that bottomless pit. Not unless you want a one-way trip into darkness.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...As I thought. This, too, is a puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Leave it to me, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh-uh! This bad boy is all mine!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, now, it seems you've both gained some of Espella's spirit. In that case, how about you both tackle this puzzle together? I'm sure you two will solve it marvellously.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">All right!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Just leave it to us!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Quitting the puzzle immediately leads back into the puzzle</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We did it! We fixed the bridge! Now we can go on to the last seal!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, time to focus! Just keep staring straight ahead, and whatever you do, DON'T LOOK DOWN!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">J-just make sure you don't go jumping around on that thing... I don't think my heart could take it.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But, Mr Wright. It's really nice and sturdy. Look!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AAAAAAHHHHH! C-cut that out, Luke! Seriously, you're gonna give me a heart attack!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Hee hee. They're so full of energy, aren't they, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That they are, Espella. Keeping our spirits up will bode well for our investigation. Come, the last seal is just up ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This is the final one, right?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. The gates of destruction will open once the Seal of Sages is broken... It seems our turn has come, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?! Oh, y-yes. I've been really looking forward to this, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...That "HUH?!" didn't exactly scream "I can't wait to do this puzzle", Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you hush up?!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Hey, take a look at those two square recesses in that pedestal. It looks like they're here for some purpose. I wonder what it could be?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This is a puzzle that cannot be solved by one person alone. I believe we must combine our strength if we are to have any hope of opening that door. How fitting that the final seal should present us with such a formidable challenge. Mr Wright, I have no doubt that together we can solve this puzzle. Shall we begin?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm ready when you are, Professor! <thought>The professor is a puzzle-solving expert. I just hope I don't slip up too much...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Picarats">60</line>
<line speaker="Notes">No penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...! Did you hear that just now? The door's opening!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Woo! Way to go! I knew you guys could do it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whew... Glad we got past that one. I wonder what's on the other side of this door...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, it certainly is intriguing, Mr Wright. We do not know what might await us on the other side of that door.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's all right. I'm not scared. We've come so far and we must continue. We must find out what's behind all of this. Let's do it. Let's move forward!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This room...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like...a shrine of some sort.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It certainly is very beautiful. That light is almost unearthly... It seems quite unfitting that this place should be associated with destruction, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's not like the rest of the ruins at all... It's actually really well preserved.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm... I wonder if someone else came here before us.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...C'mon, guys. I think we can relax a bit. Especially after that puzzle that almost made Nick pass out. Y'know, I honestly thought Bezella would come charging at us the second we opened the door and turn us all into frogs.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Maya... You're starting to give me the creeps...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So it, uhh...looks like Bezella's a no-show, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...I suggest we scour the room for any potential clues.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It seems the ceiling and pillars in this room are crumbling into the water. Let us hurry.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There are flower petals floating on the water. They look like the flowers growing near the mansion outside.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now that I think about it, this water is probably flowing in from the lake up on the surface.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">The water is glowing so brightly, there's no need for torches here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Are those things serpents? Maybe dragons? Oh, I know! They must be dragon serpents!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Those vines have become quite overgrown. They're covering this altar from top to bottom.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... There are traces of an object having been placed here. What could it have been?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Those two creatures on the wall are probably there to watch over whatever was on the altar.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">These stairs just suddenly end... I've got it! They must be stairs to nowhere!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I-I don't think that's it, Maya... It must have led to something, but what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It must've been something pretty important for them to build a room around it...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Quite true, Mr Wright. There is little doubt that whatever once stood here was of the utmost importance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's up with this pedestal? It looks a bit strange. It looks like something is missing...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would appear something quite large once stood here. Perhaps an object of worship.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Something large...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah...look up there! Above the shrine...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">What's that? It looks like there are marks all over the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... Whatever was on this pedestal must have been even larger than I originally thought.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seems whatever it was has been taken away for some reason. I wonder why...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The inscription on this stone plaque could perhaps offer us a clue. Although... I'm afraid the words in this inscription are somewhat ancient.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So...you can't read it what it says?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would be quite a different story if I were able to take this relic back to London for analysis. As it stands now, however...I may only be able to decipher a portion of it.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Really, Professor?! What does it say?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ It seems as if the previous inhabitants of these ruins were responsible for this inscription... While the inscription itself would appear to provide yet another mystery to be solved. ...Allow me to read it aloud.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...The former inhabitants of these ruins created a bell out of pure silver as a tribute to the gods they worshipped here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So they made a giant silver bell... <thought>That's actually pretty impressive.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">However, when the bell was rung, it did not summon a god, but instead, an evil demon. This evil demon...brought up on this world a great catastrophe, causing considerable damage to the land.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Did you say..."a great catastrophe"? Wh-what could have happened?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Those that survived the incident dubbed it the "Bell of Ruin" and sealed it within this very room. They then fled in fear of the curse placed upon this land by the demon. The inscription contains one final warning.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...That is as much as I can gather. I believe the object that was removed from this shrine...was the very Bell of Ruin mentioned in the inscription.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, could this have anything to do with Bezella?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...I cannot say for sure, Luke. After all, demons and witches are two very different concepts. However, perhaps there is a chance that the two are connected in origin, through this legend.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Origin", Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Think back to what was written. What followed the great catastrophe?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...You must mean the "curse placed upon this land" part, right?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I imagine that when the bell was rung, it must have summoned "something".</line>
<line speaker="Espella">What sort of curse could that have been? And...what was this "great catastrophe" brought upon by the demon? W-wait... Could it be...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...The fire that destroyed the entire town?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Espella, what's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Ah... No, no. Nothing's wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Are you sure? You don't have to put on a brave face for us. Tell us if you're not feeling good, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Y-yes, of course...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But this still has me wondering... What exactly was the "catastrophe" that happened a long time ago?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I can only think of one thing in Labyrinthia that could be called a "catastrophe"... the Legendary Fire.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Of course... Both the Bell of Ruin and the legend of Bezella must be...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Espella, are you absolutely sure you're feeling okay? Your face has gone really pale...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...The Legendary...Fire...</line>
<line speaker="???">...Do you remember now, Espella...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Wh-who are you...?</line>
<line speaker="???">...Allow me to remind you... ...of who and what you truly are... ...and what you did so many years ago...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">What I...did... ...I...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Espella, are you all right?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">No, I...I... No, I'm...I am...that's right... I am Bezella... The Great Witch Bezella...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">E-Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">And so it has begun.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It was like Espella wasn't herself any more. Almost as if she was possessed. She kept murmuring "I'm the Great Witch Bezella" over and over and over again. She took off running when we tried to calm her down. We tried going after her, but she lost us... We searched everywhere for her. The ruins, the forest... But... there was no sign of her, no matter where we looked. We thought she might have returned to town. And if she did... the knights would be sure to catch her and drag her back to that terrifying courtroom... Needless to say, we went back to town straight away to search for her. And then, without warning... Labyrinthia was hit by a heavy rainstorm. There was an ominous silence over the entire town square... The only thing I could hear was the rain. We didn't know it at the time... but that rain, it was a sign... of the terrible things that were to come...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That pillar has definitely seen better days... Um... Do you think it's safe to be in this room?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It seems these pillars have started to crumble away. The damage appears minimal, so we should be safe here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I don't think we should stick around here longer than we have to, Professor...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh just look at the water cascading from the ceiling... It's so shiny and pretty.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Check out all those statues! These sorta remind me of the statue of Ami Fey in the Hazakura Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">These statues appear to be worshipping something, don't they?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A few of these statues have their ears covered... I wonder why?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Such excellent craftsmanship. Techniques like this have long since been lost to the annals of time.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What could have been the purpose of these? Hmm... It would be better that we didn't touch them.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y'know, Professor, I bet you the people that built this place must've really, REALLY loved music!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That certainly looks...important. Whoa. What's with the sudden chill?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">This is certainly very old... I can't even begin to guess how long it's been here.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Much of this area looks the same. It would be easy to get lost, so stay close, Miss Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Wait... I recognise that tree. Weren't we just here? Or was it that tree? ...Stupid identical trees!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Be careful, Mr Wright! We could be one bad step away from getting lost in this forest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Relax, Luke. We can find our way thanks to the position of the sun! ...Uhh, now which way is west?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Fun fact: Professor, did you know not all mushrooms are edible? Mystic Maya's Fun Fact of the Day!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ha, ha. Right you are, Miss Fey. The colour of these mushrooms does not seem...safe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These mushrooms are huge! I've never seen any this big before.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">If these mushrooms were edible, I could make a loaf of mushroom bread big enough for all of us!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Check out the branches on that tree. It kinda reminds me of a stadium dome! ...Minus the stadium.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. And it would appear this arrangement of branches is natural. Simply remarkable.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who needs a roof when you've got branches? The sunlight coming in is really pretty, to boot.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright, I've read about trees growing together like this. It's a process called inosculation!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Look at the size of those trees! I-I've never seen anything like it!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">In reality, this tree is really two trees grown together. Its twisted structure is simply fascinating.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's the trunk... No, no wait! That's a branch...? Hmm...a root?! This tree's a jerk, let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Could these pots have been used in some sort of ceremony? There's no mistake, these are certainly very old.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I bet you're just dying to check out these relics, huh, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">My, how interesting... Look at how elaborate those little vases and figurines are.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what the heck could those tools possibly be used for?! ...You know what? I don't even want to know.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Compared to the houses found in Labyrinthia, the Shades' dwellings appear much more primitive.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Primitive? It doesn't look like they have indoor plumbing, Professor. That's WORSE than primitive!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of their houses. Yikes...this makes Labyrinthia look like the 21st century by comparison.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">These Shades must live in these dwellings...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Professor, I'm happy to report that the Shades have mastered well-making technology!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. This well reminds me of the features of Labyrinthia. Perhaps they share the same source.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">This well is full to the brim with water.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yeah, but...they don't seem to be using it at all.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">They've built a house up on a tree. How inventive. They must use a series of ladders to reach the top.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I knew you were smart, Professor! You do NOT want to hear Nick's thoughts on ladders, trust me.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Look, Mr Wright! It's a tree house! Ahem, I-I mean, err...that tree house is quite fascinating, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Knowing my luck, I bet that thing will come crashing down the second I set foot inside...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This small path looks as if it leads away from the Shades' village.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup. It's a path. For walking.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That path leads back to the lake we just came from.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Fascinating. I would like nothing more than to examine that shrine, but I'm afraid we must hurry on.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wonder who built that thing? Y'think it was the Shades' great-great-great-great-GREAT-grandparents?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What's that? It looks like some sort of altar, or something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'm getting goosebumps just looking at it. AH! What was that?! W-we should go...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder if Wordsmith is still in the market for a new napping spot...? This tree is totally napping material!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Under better circumstances, this tree would be most ideal for enjoying a nice cup of tea under its shade.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet Maya would've loved to sleep the afternoon away under a tree like this...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Say, I think we're entitled to a few flowers, don't you think? We ARE the Great Witch's guests, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">These flowers certainly have a most unique scent. ...Miss Fey, please refrain from picking the flowers.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">These are the same flowers that were around the mansion. Just look at how many of them there are!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh my. Not even Kira sold flowers that looked or smelled like these... Amazing!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-is that a mansion over there on the other side? Do you think that's the Great Witch's evil secret lair?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm, could that be...? Let us find a way across and examine that side ourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey, look! There's the mansion where the wagon left us.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Once we're done here, let's get back to the mansion and start our search.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The horses have plenty of food and water... I must say, they seem quite content.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Horses! Okay, okay... What do I have to do to get Nick on one of these? Money is no object!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">This must be where the wagon's horses rest after coming through the tunnel.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The horses' food and water looks like it was recently filled. I bet they must use these horses all the time.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The fog is very dense here. It gives this area a most unearthly feel...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's really hard to see around here... Who needs a security system when you've got fog, right, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Brrr... Is it me, or did the temperature drop when we walked into this fog?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A creepy mansion covered in creepy fog in an equally creepy forest... G-great...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">These are sure [sic] some pretty flowers. And they're everywhere! Quick! Put some under your hat, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Now, Miss Fey... It is not a gentleman's place to take what does not belong to him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Get a load of that flowerbed. They are- ACHOO! ...*sniff*...pretty.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">What an absolutely lovely scent! There's something very familiar about it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They really cranked up the heat on this pot. Look at that blue liquid bubble!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Such a myriad of instruments. Creating these liquids must need the most precise measurements.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Woah. They've really got the fire going on this one... Wonder what they're making?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I don't even want to think about how they went about making this stuff, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder which liquid has the most bubbles when it boils? Red or blue?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That is quite the sizeable pot. It must take quite a bit of time to bring that amount to a boil.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Judging by the colour, this must be made using the flowers.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ow, ow ow! Cor, that's scorching HOT!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... These appear to be the flowers that grow in the vicinity of the mansion.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">More flowers! I bet Espella would love these. Seriously, Professor, put some under your hat!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Look at all these flowers, Mr Wright. I bet you could make a really nice flower necklace out of these.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They must've picked these flowers from right outside the mansion. ACHOO! ...Urgh. *sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The curtain hanging from this wall appears to have suffered a single tear down the middle.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait, Professor! Let me just check... All right, it's clear! No one's hiding behind the curtain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a huge rip down the middle of this curtain. I sure hope no one was hiding behind this thing.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I don't think this curtain would make the best hiding spot, Mr Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This place definitely screams "something serious just went down", doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It certainly seems so, Miss Fey. Unfortunately, the culprit seems to have disappeared...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Blimey! Look at the chandelier! It's completely destroyed.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">There is quite a bit of damage around the entire room. Something quite big must have happened here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like this chandelier fell recently. It doesn't look like anyone was underneath it when it fell.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This red liquid managed to get sprayed throughout quite a bit of the room.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">From the looks of this place, the Great Witch definitely had her hands full...but what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's still wet... This must've happened not too long ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If this stuff was actually blood... Brr! Gives me the chills just thinking about it.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Umm...Mr Wright? I don't feel so good...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Ever since I started watching you all solve puzzles, I've realised it's really not so easy...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Don't worry, Espella! You'll solve it for sure next time!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Thank you, Luke. I'll do my best!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Well, I didn't quite solve it that time. Still, it was fun trying! I'm ready to give this puzzle another try!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Professor! I, uhh...think I've met my match. You think maybe you could finish the rest?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm afraid I cannot do that, Mr Wright. This is a puzzle only you can solve.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean only I can solve it?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I speak, of course, of your particular method of thinking... Mr Wright, your ability to think outside of the box is the key to solving this puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Think outside of the box", huh?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Give it time. The answer will come to you.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright, you are the only person capable of solving this puzzle. I believe you already know why. Indeed. I refer, of course, to your unique way of thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I-I guess that's not quite right...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... It is as they said. Puzzles as ancient as these cannot always be solved by ordinary methods, I'm afraid. How about we give it another go later?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A puzzle hidden away from the annals of time... Simply fascinating.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'll do my very best to solve it, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm sorry! I guess it's a little more difficult than I thought it would be!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Espella, there is no shame in pacing yourself when necessary. Use that time to come up with a plan.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">R-right, Professor! I promise I won't give up! I'll just take a little break to clear my head and then get right back to it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow... Espella is super determined.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">I have to work out this Seal of Leviathan... and get those platforms up, so we can all continue on!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We just need to solve this in order to make a path across...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All right! Let's roll up our sleeves and get to the bottom of this puzzle... LITERALLY!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Umm...Maya? I, err...don't think "literally" means what you think it means.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Hee hee. You're so funny. You're really becoming fast friends, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I see why it's called the Seal of Despair... Look how pitch-black it is down there!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'll take your word for it. See, I have a very strict "don't look into any bottomless pits" policy. Safety first!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-this is way harder than I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes. Quite the formidable puzzle, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Maybe you're both a little stressed, given all that's happened. How about you try taking a deep breath?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Yeah, that might just work. Okay, you first, Professor. Then you, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...*pant*...*gasp*...*pant*... *gasp*...*pant*...*gasp*...*pant*...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Wow, Mr Wright. This puzzle must really have you stressed out.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Boy, Nick, you sound like you just ran a marathon...underwater...in concrete shoes.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright! Do not let the puzzle get to you!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yes, Mr Wright! Think of something less stressful...like all those court cases you've won in the past!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...*pant*...*gasp*...*pant*... *gasp*...*pant*...*gasp*...*pant*...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Solving the Seal of Sages should allow us to continue on to the final room of these ruins. However, this puzzle cannot be solved by a single person alone. This is the final seal and also the final puzzle. With teamwork, we can solve this. Are you ready, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-of course! We'll give this another try!</line>
</xml>