<xml>
<title>Shady Types</title>
<line speaker="Layton">Did you say, "suspicious characters"?</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">That's wight! Suspicious chawacters! I saw them, I did! In Nulwitch Woods... A pair of mystewious men!</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Yea, I saw them too. No matter how you look at it, they were a couple of weirdos, all right.</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">Mmm...! Ngaaaa...! Ngaaaa...! They're desperados, I tell you! Yes, that's what they are, desperados!</line>
<line speaker="Allan">They're an embarrassment, is what they are. And right on the day of the fire festival, too!</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">O-okay! I'll take them on! I'm not afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Petal">Whaddya mean, you'll take 'em on? You're nothin' but a crybaby.</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">Gyah ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is all this...? Seems like everyone and his brother has [sic] come here to make complaints at us!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Perhaps it's just that they all want to see you again...and think you can help.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Whatever the reason, we can't very well ignore the fact that there seem to be a pair of villains on the loose...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! I...I just had a thought of who they might be!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Me too! There were those two weird-looking rogues, right? I think they were called...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Robbs and Muggs...you mean? <thought>That's the pair that waylaid Espella in the woods that one time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Espella, you wouldn't happen to know what became of those two, would you?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Actually, yes, I do... They were rehabilitated and are both currently working in the library.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But apart from them...we don't have any other suspects, do we?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, in that case, I suggest we all set out to the woods and take a look around for ourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Good thinking, Professor! Sounds like another exciting case to crack!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! Come on, Nick! We're up for this too, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">According to the witnesses, this is where they were sighted... Two clearly suspicious characters... supposedly basking in the sun somewhere around here.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">They certainly sound like a couple of laid-back villains, if they were "basking in the sun"...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whooooooa! Th-there they are...over there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yep... I see them too. Definitely suspicious...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm not sure I've ever seen a more suspicious-looking pair of characters!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, Luke... I must admit, they somewhat resemble the kind of image one often sees on "most wanted" posters...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">After my many years as a judge, I have recently found myself wondering... What exactly do we mean by "crime"? How exactly can we define it...?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">........................ We are no more than bubbles, being carried by a great river. Drifting this way and that, until we disappear... The tiny sound of the bubbles bursting goes unheard by anyone. And yet...they undoubtedly do make their sound... BLAM!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed... That is a unique way of looking at things. I, meanwhile, believe... that the world is not as simple as: "those who use witchcraft are criminals".</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">........................ Even so, the warm wind blows over the grassy plains, quietly causing the red flowers to sway...before moving on. No one sees the wind as it moves... It is only felt by the flowers, as they are touched.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They seem to be having some kind of complicated, high-level conversation...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, Luke. It would appear they're involved in deep philosophical discussion.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That's just like Mr Wordsmith... He always sounds so poetic and deep.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You can say that again. I think it's a bit too deep for me... I'm lost!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Honestly, I'm not sure whether what I'm hearing is sublime or ridiculous...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I feel...that after a year since I stepped down as a judge, I still cannot say with utter confidence... what path my life should take, or what on earth I should aim for now.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">........................ There were days when even I wished to simply become the wind... But if I were to become the wind... I would never again be able to slurp upon spaghetti.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed... To be honest with you, I had never even considered that. It would seem that I should continue on my current path, at least for the time being...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">........................ Whatever the case, I cannot even consider a world in which one is not free to slurp upon one's spaghetti... Where is that kindly neighbour who will free me from my fate this evening...and from that despicable monster we call money?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Somehow...listening to them talking... is making me feel all profound.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Me too...I suddenly have a profound feeling that I'd like to eat some spaghetti right about now!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's just like Mr Wordsmith... Always the most tasteful choice of words.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Personally, I get the feeling he's trying to persuade the judge to buy him dinner tonight, in a roundabout sort of way.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Oh? Well, I never... This is a most distinguished turnout we have here!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">Fortuitous meetings are no more than inevitable vicissitudes within the natural ebb and flow of our lives...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">May I ask what it is that brings you all to an out-of-the-way place like this?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah...well... Actually...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We came here to check on reports of two suspicious characters said to have been basking in the sun!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Tactful as always, Maya...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Two suspicious characters, you say? And you took the trouble to come all the way out here just to warn us? Well, don't worry, we'll keep our eyes open!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Missing the point as always, Your Honour...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">By the way, what brings you to this neck of the woods?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well...it's a little embarrassing really... I was just seeking advice from my wise companion here. I've been wondering how to proceed in life, now that I've stepped down from my post.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And did you find the answer to your question from Wordsmith?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well...to be honest... I have no idea what he was talking about...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that so...? <thought>Why am I not surprised to hear that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I was getting into a bit of a nervous sweat just about the time you arrived.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">I am merely floating on a warm breeze, shedding warm tears, like flower petals dancing in the wind.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So! You decided to become a fortune teller, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Yes. When I met you all about a year ago, I came to realise... My beliefs were being changed by the Story. The belief that "witches must be guilty" was just an illusion. This world is incomprehensible, like a dark and puzzling labyrinth.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">In a sense, puzzles are a microcosm of that labyrinth, or so I like to believe.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...And that's why you decided to become a fortune teller?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's right. I felt that as a fortune teller, I could help those who came to consult me find their way forward to a brighter future. But to tell you the truth... I felt my appearance might be well suited to the role, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Personally I think your appearance fits the role of "suspicious character" better...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">But when it comes to giving people advice, I came to realise it's not that easy...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">Really...? I believe...all is well within one's grasp! The answer to the ultimate puzzle of life...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh...? Please don't say it's 42...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mr Wordsmith!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">When faced with a perplexing puzzle, the way forward is to broaden one's outlook... Then, while holding that broadened view... look back upon that same puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Certainly...when I have a problem, I'm often unable to see anything else.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So we should broaden our outlook, then... That sounds like good advice!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">And then you should make use of your hands, eyes and all of your senses to feel out a solution. If you look around you...at those bushes... or that tree over there...there's always a hint waiting to be found. Of this, you can be certain... Hint 1, Hint 2, Hint 3...and naturally, the Super Hint are waiting there for you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Check this out! I found some hint coins in that tree and bushes over there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>Are you kidding me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, when it comes to solving puzzles, "each to his own" is what I say. A puzzle is a labyrinth born of the human intellect. However, occasionally... there are puzzles that can prove most refreshing when unravelled at the drop of a hat. A metaphorical hat, that is. Take the following puzzle, for example...</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Boy, I just LOVE this kind of puzzle! Two choices means you only have to try it twice!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Did you really just say that, Maya...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So here's my amazing strategy: step one, try UP just to see what happens. Step two: VICTORY POSE! Turns out that UP was totally the right answer!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Well, I'm not sure what to make of that strategy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know, I've just realised what a mysterious object the hint coin really is.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">How do you mean, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I always set out to get all the coins and leave no stone unturned... But then, when I get stuck in a puzzle, I never end up using them... Not a one. Sort of feels like I'm wasting a coin, like I hate seeing the hint coin counter go down, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah... I know exactly what you mean!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That just goes to show what a cheapskate you are, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm not sure that's entirely true, Miss Fey.</line>
<line speaker="???">Nonsense...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">I've seen and done a lot of things during this long life of mine... On the great ocean of puzzles, the traveller who carries a wealth of coins runs the risk of being pulled under by their weight.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa... That sounds like it belongs in a fortune cookie!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">Which is why... whenever I tackle any puzzle... I always look at the Super Hint before I start!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">........................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">........................</line>
<line speaker="Luke">........................</line>
<line speaker="Maya">........................</line>
<line speaker="Espella">........................</line>
<line speaker="Judge">While it may be true that the world is full of things that are difficult to fathom... By your own words, Wordsmith... I find you quite clearly, in a word, guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">........................ I am merely floating on a warm breeze, shedding warm tears, like flower petals basking in the twilight of a very long day...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, as I've said already... When it comes to solving puzzles, "each to his own" is what I always say.</line>
</xml>