<xml>
<title>Special Trial 2017</title>
<line speaker="Judge">I hereby call this court to order for this retrospective of fifteen years of Ace Attorney. Are the defence and prosecution ready to proceed?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Erm... ...I'd be more ready...if I had a clue where I was.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is the Supreme Court of Judicature in the Empire of Japan...in the Meiji era.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAAAAAAAAAT?! That's like...a looong time ago, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh, maybe we'll get to meet some of our ancestors!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Maya, seriously, could you be any less surprised?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would seem that some sort of time warp has taken place...but no matter. So how about the prosecution? Are you ready to proceed?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um... Well, the thing is, I'm actually, um... a defence lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Be that as it may, circumstances dictate that for today, you shall stand for the prosecution.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Circumstances dictate it? I think perhaps he means the powers that be dictate it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I hope you don't think I'm being rude, Mr Prosecutor, but... ...who exactly are you? You seem...strangely familiar.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Interesting... I was just thinking the same thing. It's hard to explain. It's almost as if I know you as well as I know myself...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I think the fastest way to resolve this is to have you both introduce yourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix/Ryunosuke">Of course. I'm Defence Attorney... Phoenix Wright / Ryunosuke Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...I thought you might share a surname or something.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But you could be brothers, couldn't you? I mean, you both have that same...spikiness!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think I might remember if I had a long-lost brother, Miss Susato.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......... I remember. Yeah, being told there was an attorney named Ryunosuke Naruhodo somewhere in my family tree.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, you did share a surname once? And gramps over there is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...One of my ancestors!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">WHAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I think she just called you a grandfather, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I suddenly feel very old...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">AAAAAAAAAH! Then...then...that must mean... ...you, standing beside him... You must be one of MY ancestors!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're both dignified and ladylike and...well... basically my ideal ancestor! I'm your great, great, grand-something Maya Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, well...I'm Judicial Assistant Susato Mikotoba, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In other words, a total stranger.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uuugh...I just can't catch a break. I mean, wow, that is BITTER disappointment...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I hope you can forgive me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh! I know! I can fix this! You could become an honorary ancestor of the Fey family!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">'Susato Fey'...? Well it, it does have a certain ring to it, I'm sure, but...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think we might have just heard the most illogical request in history.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uuugh, but it really does have such an awesome ring to it. Susato Fey...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This trial will discuss the fifteenth anniversary of Ace Attorney that's being celebrated this year.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Fifteenth anniversary?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You'd better believe it! The very first Ace Attorney was released back in 2001. And to celebrate that fact, we've been doing a whole bunch of stuff this year.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's right! Like in January, we put on a huge event. The '15th Anniversary Special Trial'! It was sooo much fun!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was. It really drove home the impressiveness of our fifteen-year-long history.</line>
<line speaker="Susato"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Susato">If I might be permitted...to make a small observation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh! Sure...what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">If driving home the impressiveness of a long history was the intention... ...then you should have been celebrating the more than one hundred years since Mr Naruhodo's birth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">More...more than one hundred years?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...All this impressiveness just makes me feel impressively old.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wonderful, wonderful! The court bows down before your ancient wisdom!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think...they've started to worship you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Let's try not to mention the Meiji era again.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't forget that last year we took to the stage and finally appeared in a TV anime series, too! A new story every week! I mean, that was really ace, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Tee-vee...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">A-ni-me...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What on earth are you talking about? Stop half-explaining things!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A hundred years is a terrifying chasm to bridge...it really is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, and there was another interesting development this year, wasn't there? An orchestral concert. The first in nine years, if I'm not mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're not mistaken! With nine years of pent-up emotion inside, I cried so hard!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Or-kes-tral...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Kon-sert...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! A western instrumental group performance! Even we ancestors know about those!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Beethoven...Mozart...Bahha... Oh, how delightful!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I've never heard of that last one, but sure, you get the idea.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I think it's Bach. Things can get a bit bent out of shape when you mould Western names into Japanese.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right? Didn't they used to call Shakespeare 'Sao' or something?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You could have that cool 'o' on the end of your name, Nicko!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Like 'o' for 'old man'? No thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And a matter of days ago, on August 3rd... ...to great anticipation across the Empire of Japan, The Great Ace Attorney 2 went on sale!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Um...thank you very much, Your Excellency!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, we really enjoyed that one. What a story!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It was so moving! I was blown away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet you were. After all... ...there were a LOT of loose ends that needed tying up!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are, are you okay?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You just...touched a nerve, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Your ancestor went through rather a lot, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It all started with our great forefathers, after all. We are truly blessed to be in your presence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-What?! Explain yourself, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's been bothering me right since the start of this trial, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The way Mr Naruhodo moves. It's very smooth. A little...too smooth, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, is it? I, I didn't notice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly! Just like that!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're right, Nick... Like, when you thump the bench, it's really jerky. There's only two frames.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Out of interest, what does your 'objection' look like?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That's not actually humanly possible, surely.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The point is this! The jerkiness on this side of the courtroom... ...proves that we're your predecessors! In other words...WE are the ancestors here!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...What can I say to that?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps you're both predecessors and ancestors of each other. If this is some sort of warping of time, that should be entirely possible, I think!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I think we've covered everything now. It's time for this court to adjourn.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, in that case... ...how are we supposed to get back home? You know, to the twenty-first century?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well...you could go and explore Meiji Tokyo and pass the time that way!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The great imperial capital is full of wonders. I'm sure a hundred years will pass just like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......... Hm... ...I think this is a perfect opportunity to use that timeless phrase of mine, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh! A joint predecessor-ancestor performance! What a treat!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Altogether now, then...for the continued success of Ace Attorney! One, two...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix/Maya/Ryunosuke/Susato"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya! Put the brakes on!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You know what they say: what goes around comes around.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Goodbye for now, everybody. See you again soon!</line>
</xml>