<xml>
<title>Tavern Tale</title>
<line speaker="Barnham">One puzzle means...one more step on the path to puzzle mastery...</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Well, I hope you have some comfy shoes ready...because at this rate, you're gonna be walking that path forever.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Hmph...the fiercer the adversary, the better, I assure you. That is why... no matter how foolishly difficult this infernal "More Chalices!" may be, it WILL be solved by the hand of Barnham!</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">You sure about that? It looks to me like the hand of Barnham could use a hand of its own right about now, Zacky-boy!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Tell me, Rouge, how many chalices have I broken since starting this puzzle three nights ago?</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Heh. Let's just say, if you take any longer... I'll be having to serve my customers juice out of their own hats.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Well, I should make my way back. It seems the storm outside has subsided.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">............ A stormy night like this...really brings back memories, doesn't it, Zack? Like the time you first set foot into this very tavern... It was a dark and stormy night just like this one.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...... Indeed, it was.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Heh. I remember you walked through that door soggier than a rat in a river...</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Well, well...what aid could THE captain of the knights need from a lowly tavern owner like me? If you think for a second I'm going to sell out whatever bandit you're after, then you've got another thing coming.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Please...they are after us. I ask for but a moment's shelter.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">"After you"...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ Surely you have heard word of the recent witch sighting at the farm on the outskirts of town, have you not?</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Who hasn't? Word is that witch did quite a number on the farm's chickens and crops. I heard you guys tried to put up a fence to keep 'em out. A lot of good that did, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">There were no traces of footprints at the scene. 'Twas surely a witch's handiwork.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">So? Shouldn't you be out there hunting down this supposed witch?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That is correct... And so, tonight I finally managed to capture the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">You caught the culprit...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Yes. This fiend right here...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I give you...our "witch"... The beast cannot be more than a year old.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">My, my...he's certainly the tiniest "criminal" I've ever seen.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Quite. Every day, this beast has been getting itself into trouble. Honestly... No one would've ever suspected this pup could be the one behind those missing chickens.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">...By the way, I've gotta ask: what's up with that helmet?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...I put it on him a short while ago. 'Tis a toy helmet I just happened to have lying around.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Let me see if I'm barking up the right tree... This little guy here would hide in the bushes and attack any passing dogs or kids?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">...Okay, but there were a LOT of chickens and crops that went missing from that farm. Why on earth would this little guy go and take so many? If he was planning on eating them, you'd think one chicken would be more than enough for 'im.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Yes... The beast is still a mere whelp. Every battle is, for him, a terrifying battle of life or death. Until now, the source of the disappearing chickens was a mystery. However, tonight our little friend here made a grave error.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">What kind of error?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">There was a group of townspeople patrolling the crime scene during the storm tonight. They were under the assumption that the culprit was a witch. Something tells me the pup's little trick didn't go as planned. Yet...he went through with his trick and ended up biting off more than he could chew...so to speak. The townspeople were hungry for a culprit to capture and chased after the mutt. He was thus forced to escape into the forest. He managed to lose them in the forest. ...With the exception of one.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">And let me guess...that "one" was one Zacharias Barnham, right?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">He truly put forth a valiant effort... Quite clever for the beast that he is.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">The little guy must have been scared stiff, what with all that armour clattering around after him.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I chased him through the forest, before finally... he grew tired and stopped to rest in a clearing deep within the forest. ...'Twas the beast's home.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">So you ended up smack dab in the middle of "enemy territory". Sounds like an impasse if I ever saw one. So, what then? The chase was over. Why didn't you just hand the pup over to the townsfolk?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ That was not an option.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">And why's that?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It was because...of what I saw there deep within the recesses of that forest.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I saw...the chickens the beast had taken. His prey was left in a large pile. And yet...there was no hint that he had actually eaten any of them.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Wh-what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Curled up among this mountain of chickens, lay a much larger dog... It was readily apparent that the beast was already dead.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">This little one here nestled itself against the larger beast, yet there was no response. I could but gaze upon this whelp in silent admiration for his efforts...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I distinctly remember the larger one's appearance... It had a scar above its left eye, a tail that looked as if it were singed by the Legendary Fire itself, and black and white coloured fur.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">You did...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">We had met once before...in town, not a few days prior. ...I was at the head of the Storyteller's parade. That's when... suddenly a large dog jumped in front of me. It had been chasing the chickens at the farm nearby when it shot forth from the alley. ...I was caught completely off guard. My horse instantly reeled back in panic, but sadly I was unable to calm it... I failed to keep hold of the reins... There was naught I could do and so I was thrust from my horse.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">...Oh, I get it now. That must've been the famous Barnham's Wild Ride incident everyone loves talking about. Heard you were dragged all over town. Don't seem any worse for wear, though. You're definitely now the stuff of legends.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Unfortunately, the dog that ran into the parade was much more "worse for wear".</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">In the chaos that followed, the beast was caught under my horse, trampled and kicked aside. Somehow it managed to drag itself upright... It then limped its way back to the alley and disappeared.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">...Unbelievable. So you mean...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Indeed. The dead dog in the forest was the very same dog from the parade. There is no mistake... The beast was mortally wounded at that parade.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">A-all right, so... What about the pup?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">'Tis only an assumption, but... perhaps this little one is the beast's offspring.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...If only I had not fallen from my horse. ...If only I had been able to take control...</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I think...this little one was there to witness what I did to his mother. He must be quite aware of my actions that day.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">...What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">While he may still be young, and his stature small...this dog is a true knight of the highest calibre. He protects that which needs protecting. And...will ready his fangs at but a moment's notice for many a just cause. ...That is why I could not simply hand this most valiant knight over to the townsfolk.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">As we speak, they are braving the storm in search of him. However, they will likely give up before too long. I ask you, please keep this little one safe here... I beg of you.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">............ What exactly do you plan on doing with the pup?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ This brave little knight stood valiantly in the face of insurmountable odds, all for the sake of protecting one close to him. As such, I will first assign him a most noble name befitting one of such valour. Then...I will personally see to it that he is welcomed into the Knights of the Inquisition.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">...Hmph. From where I'm standing, it really doesn't look like this little guy is all too thrilled with you and your plans.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I-it would appear so, but...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">No doubt about it... He doesn't like you one bit. ...That's what little guys like this do. They bite.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">U-urgh... 'Twas my error!</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Oh, c'mon now. You're not even bleeding, you big baby. The big bad knight captain...bitten by a cute little pup, like some kind of chew toy. Not the most "manly" of stories.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Nonsense! It was an honour to be chewed on by such an admirable creature.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Heh. Ever the fast-talker, eh, Mr Knight Captain? Look, gimme a minute and I'll get you patched up in no time. Until then... how about you keep yourself entertained with this little puzzle I came up with... Mouse Mayhem 2 should be child's play for a knight like you, Mr Knight Captain!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I see. My, how fascinating... No doubt this puzzle was originally created quite a while ago, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">S-Sir Top Hat?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. And a good evening to you,  Mr Barnham.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">W-were you here this whole time...?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Not at all. I just arrived right now to get a cup of water. ...Hmm, but it does seem I've managed to arrive just in time to hear an old story.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Heh... Anyway, where's the rest of your motley crew gone?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah, yes. Mr Wright and the others appear to be sound asleep upstairs. They were all enjoying being together again after so long, they must have tired themselves out quite a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">Ah, all right. Well, glad to hear they're doin' fine.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...By the way, Mr Barnham.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wh-what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps you could tell me how you obtained that scar I see above your left eyebrow...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...... I received this quite some time ago. A most formidable knight gave me this old wound. 'Twas not by his sword, but rather his small fangs that he gave me this injury.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">...Say, Mr Fancy Hat.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, Miss Rouge?</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">That little...story you just heard. Do me a favour and keep it under that hat of yours, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Why, of course, Miss Rouge. However...there is but one condition.</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">...And that is?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If you would do me the honour... of allowing me to take on the puzzle that left Mr Barnham stumped for three days... I speak of More Chalices!</line>
<line speaker="Rouge">............ Well, well, well...looks like we've got ourselves another challenger.</line>
</xml>