<xml>
<title>The Memoirs of the Clouded Kokoro</title>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>Mmm, what a delicious smell wafting up the stairs... It must be nearly time for breakfast. I'd better go down to Mr Sholmes's suite... ...and say good morning to the great detective and his flatmate.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! So you have scale balances in Japan too, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well yes, but nothing like the Old Bailey's huge example.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">The thing about those scales is, they're only ever in balance right at the start of a trial, aren't they? Otherwise they always seem to be hanging one way or another...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'd noticed that exact same thing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ooh, is this Japanese kanji script embroidered here?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right. The name of the armband's owner.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah! So that's how you write 'Naruhodo' is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Actually, no. It's my best friend's name, not mine. It's pronounced 'Kazuma Asogi'. I actually believe this armband in some way embodies his spirit, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hm... So you have to write all those lines just for one person's name? Kanji is funny, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's right. Never mind my feelings about my best friend. It's lines I really want to talk about...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah, Runo, good! I was just about to call up to you. The bacon's ready.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Good morning, Iris. It smells delicious as usual. Before we eat, though, I have some news. I had a surprise this morning-</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Shh! Not another word, Mr Naruhodo! This could be just the abstruse thing for my pre-breakfast stagnation-repelling mental stimulation, my dear fellow.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Morning' to you too, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah...yes...I see... So that's it... The truth is as clear to me as day. My faculties of observation have revealed it again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wh-What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You, Mr Naruhodo. You have, this very morning, met with a surprise! ...Well? Is that not the case?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Really, my dear fellow, it barely warrants explanation. Firstly, your hair is particularly unkempt. Somewhat reminiscent of a bird's nest. Secondly, you have neglected to fasten the third button of your jacket. Clearly, when considered together, these two facts point to you having been flustered this morning.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Can I talk now?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But of course, of course! Though I don't look for admiration, you understand.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My hair always looks like this. It's been this way since I first met you.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Oh. It has?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And the button...was ripped off last night, if you remember? ...By you.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hurley pulled your button off?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Ah yes, I recall the incident now. It was after supper, was it not? As the evening advanced, I picked up my violin and began to play the wailing notes of a haunting tune. But then, to my utter dismay, the third string snapped! Why did it have to happen? WHY?! Little wonder then, that in my vexation, I grabbed the first button I saw and ripped it from its proper place!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Well, I'd like it back now, please. It's troubling me that I can't fasten my jacket.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And it's troubling me that you expect me to know where it is! Somewhere thereabouts on the floor, one presumes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Helpful.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What matters at the present time, my dear fellow, is simply whether or not my deduction was unerring.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But Hurley, Runo said it when he came in, didn't he? 'I had a surprise this morning.'</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Ah ha ha ha ha hah! Well, that really is a surprise!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, this man is the pride of the British Empire. The famous consulting detective, Mr Herlock Sholmes. There can't be a single person in the world who doesn't know his name.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Alright then, enough of this silly conversation. Come and eat this bacon before it goes cold. And I have a new herbal tea for you to try, too! My latest special blend!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And here we have Iris Wilson, Mr Sholmes's lodger and companion. A truly exceptional young girl, who's the author of a highly successful serialisation here in London. Yes, 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes' as published in Randst Magazine.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So, Mr Naruhodo, won't you put us out of our misery? What surprised you this fine morning?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, well, I received a letter...from Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! From Susie, you mean?! Was it? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right. And she had some rather startling news, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah... intriguing indeed. You must tell us all about it over breakfast!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh yes! What fun!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That machine really is imposing, isn't it? But I can never remember its name.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hurley calls it his 'Great Analytiscope'. It can analyse anything at all!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That doesn't really help me. What does 'analysing' something even mean?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, an extremely astute question, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, as Iris said, my machine here spits out analysis results of anything with which you care to present it. But how to interpret those results, that's the key! And I confess I have no idea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Clearly, I'm going to have to construct a Great Analytiscope-Analytiscope to solve the problem.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That...might not help.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Books, papers, scientific implements... These shelves are stuffed to the gunnels. Miss Susato wouldn't be able to help herself if she were here. She can't stand mess.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Susie might not be able to stand mess, but she wouldn't dare touch those shelves.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh? Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Everything's in intricate balance. Hurley spends ages on it. If you were to touch even one thing, the whole lot would come tumbling down.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Susie noticed it was a very delicate arrangement right from the outset.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You make it sound like a meeting of great minds. But the truth is, Mr Sholmes just needs to tidy up.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah yes, Mr Sholmes's faithful musical companion. Wasn't this violin made by somebody famous?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, it's a Stradivarius. Though I'm afraid you'd have to save up for a hundred years before you could afford one, Runo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But didn't you buy it for a song, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I found it a pawnbrokery among the forfeited articles. It clearly said 'Stradivarius' on the label.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The ignorant broker had no idea of its true value, you see. So I paid a mere fifty-five shillings for it. Yes, I have something of a turn for shopping. Herlock Sholmes...bargain hunter!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... But...is it really a Stradivarius, then?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But of course, my dear fellow! It said so on the label.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I think perhaps the 'ignorant' broker had something of a turn for selling...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When it gets to this time of year, Londoners seem to leave their hearths alight all day long. And I love it. There's something very relaxing about watching the flames flit and dance about.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But a fireplace in days of summertime is a waste of space. Really, no use at all.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Rather like a great detective in days of no crimes and no criminals, hm, Hurley?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But consider this: instead of a fireplace, a frostplace! That's my latest idea. An extraordinary hearth from which emanates a cool breeze in the hot summer months. What do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I think if you invented such a thing, your name would go down in history!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The principle is extremely simple. One must of course light a cold fire in the hearth.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, of course! Brilliant!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The trouble is...none of the fires I build ever burn cold. How it taunts me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So as you British say...it's a bit of a damp squib?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah yes, the huge metal chest with the lace cloth laid on it, being used as a table for tea and coffee. It's very sturdy, that's for sure. And firmly locked shut.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That chest contains my father's detailed records of Hurley's many cases!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, so I've been led to believe. Though personally, I've never actually seen inside.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And that's the way it will stay! Those papers are a secret between Daddy and me. If you go opening it uninvited, you might find yourself being bitten!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What, is there a beast inside there, or something?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">These are different pieces of evidence from cases you've solved, aren't they, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Not quite, Mr Naruhodo, not quite. These trinkets are a selection from cases I've solved with particular aplomb. They are souvenirs of my success. Memories, Mr Naruhodo, memories.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really... So, tell me about the case in which the bust of Napoleon featured.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm...I forget.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Memories, he says... Wonderful, Mr Sholmes, wonderful.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I look forward to finding out what aroma your tea will have, Iris. Every single day.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah, well, I infuse a different concoction of herbs from the garden every time, so it's never the same twice.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When you call it a 'concoction' it sounds more like a science experiment than something for teatime.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh yes! That's because different blends can have very different properties! Some calm you down, some make you feel jolly, some give you energy... Today's particular blend is something quite special, so you're really in for a treat!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That sounds...ominous...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah yes, this is where you note down ideas, isn't it, Iris? What's in the melting pot today? Hm, 'The Blue Carbuncle'...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, it's from a case of theft that Hurley solved ages ago. The theft of a precious stone. A carbuncle is another name for a garnet, you see. Especially if it's cut with a rounded top.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, really? And this garnet was blue, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, that's the thing... They're usually red. No blue garnets have ever been discovered.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">So who knows what the stolen gemstone actually was. That's the real mystery of the case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...A proper Herlock Sholmes conundrum, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>There are so many different bottles up there on that charming little set of white shelves.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! Do be careful, Runo! You mustn't try the contents of any of those bottles, even if you're hungry!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I wouldn't do something stupid like that! I'm not a child, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, I wish I could say the same for Hurley. The other day, he polished off a full bottle of one of my alkaloids.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He what?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">He said he was hungry.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'll...be extra careful.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I can type with my eyes shut, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can believe it. When a deadline's approaching, you sound like a Gatling gun!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That reminds me of a dream I had the other day. It was such a funny one! It woke me, actually. I was typing for a whole hour in the pitch-black, but I didn't make a single mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's incredible!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But then, when it got light...I found that there wasn't any paper in the machine. Now I wonder if I'd actually been typing at all...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I think you might just have fallen asleep on the job.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is the letter that arrived from Japan this morning. By international post.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, how lovely! Look at Susie's beautiful writing! I wish I could read it!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And how is your judicial assistant faring, may I ask?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">She's very well, thank you. In fact, according to what she's written... ...she actually appeared as a lawyer at the Japanese Supreme Court and won a case!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah! Really?! Oh, isn't she wonderful!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">A cut above your good self, my dear fellow.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I've won cases, too, you know.</thought> Apparently, Mr Natsume appeared in the trial as a witness.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Natsume... Natsume... No, I don't recall that name.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of course you do! We helped the man...twice! You know, in those two cases that took place on Briar Road six months ago.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah! The moustached, twitchy man with the somewhat feline eyes and the moustache?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">He didn't have two moustaches, Hurley.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, who could forget those two cases? They made a very deep impression on me. ...Although I must confess, the details are a little hazy now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>A very deep impression they made on you. Clearly.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So...what was this 'startling news' penned by Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Do you remember the case of the haunted lodgings, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, yes...it's very interesting, you know. I don't feel entirely uncertain that a case of that nature did not...NOT occur.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He's totally forgotten, then.</thought> Anyway, in her letter... ...Miss Susato asked that we read over her case notes again and investigate further.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Though it took place half a year ago? For what purpose?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Because of something that Mr Natsume said to her, apparently. He suggested that the real reason why she was called back to Japan so suddenly... ...might have something to do with that case of the haunted lodgings.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">On Mr Natsume's return to Japan, Miss Susato's father questioned him about the case, she says. And something Mr Natsume said appeared to trouble Professor Mikotoba, prompting him to send that telegram.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! THAT case, yes! It was very strange, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And I had compiled the whole story into a nice, neat manuscript ready for publication, too. But then Hurley here was all funny about it, remember? He was very mean. 'That story must not be published!' you said. Very mysteriously as well...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Really? I said that? Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Do you perhaps know something about it as well, Mr Sholmes? About why Miss Susato was suddenly told four mouths [sic] ago that she had to return to Japan?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It's been four months now since we waved Susie off at Dover. It was such a shock, wasn't it? The way she just suddenly announced that she had to go back to Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed it was. Due to a telegram she received from her homeland, I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right. Telling her to return urgently.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, because her father had passed away.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no no! It just said he was suffering from a high fever, the cause of which was unknown. He's not dead! But according to this letter... ...that news about her father's fever was just a ruse.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">A ruse! So Susie's daddy lied to her so that she'd make the voyage back home? Why would he do that?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I have to admit, I have absolutely no idea. But she believes it's almost certainly related to the case of the haunted lodgings.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, um, Mr Sholmes, about this...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Shh! Not another word! ...Ah, yes, I see... This would be a collar...for a breed of miniature canine with a particularly long neck. And for winter use!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Actually...it's the armband I always wear that symbolises my role as a defence lawyer...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Precisely! Which leads us to but one conclusion: Your arm is in fact the particularly long neck of a miniature canine!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'm starting to wish I'd never shown him this now. The man's barking mad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hmmm... Hurley, do you know what it's all about?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Hm? Ah, well, who can say?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? But, but you said...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Please, I have engagements, my dear fellow! My calendar is quite surprisingly full today. And a stringent analysis of the matter would be excessive, I feel. Even if I were quite at leisure. So! Man the fort in my absence, won't you, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I will, Hurley, don't worry. See you later!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He scuttled off rather quickly there... I think perhaps Professor Mikotoba isn't the only person hiding something here. Soseki-san was involved in two cases, but only one of them was forbidden from being published. By, of all people...Mr Sholmes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah-ha! I've found them at last!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Iris! Are, are they...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">The notes about the case? That's right. Susie and I compiled them together. 'The Case of the Haunted Lodgings'... Do you want to read them, Runo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Absolutely. Thank you, Iris. I have no idea what secrets could still be hiding in the shadows of this case... ...but perhaps if I read over the notes again, something might come to light.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's the spirit!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Joyful, Joyous, Jubilant Jubilation!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Was the man's reaction after the trial. But his jubilant jubilation was short lived. We received a telegram from Mr Sholmes the following morning. 'The victim of the Briar Road stabbing has regained consciousness. Hurry to Barts at once!' So Susato-san and I summoned a hansom and headed immediately to the hospital.</line>
<line speaker="Before clearing all Converse options in Sholmes's Suite">30th August</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The office spade... Now that Susato-san's gone, the shovellers aren't represented to correct me. ......... Maybe I'll have to do it myself. 'That's not a spade, Naruhodo-san; it's a shovel!'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Susato-san's tea set that she left here with me. I still think green tea is just too bitter, though. Thank goodness for sugar and milk! Mr Sholmes certainly wasn't expecting the acrid taste that one time. I've never heard anyone let out a scream like that before. Or seen anyone fall down the stairs quite like that either. ...It always bring a smile to my lips when I'm feeling a little down.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The kettle's gently simmering away there on top of the stove as usual. It was kind of Susato-san to send that Japanese tea. Iris really likes it. But for me, it's the sound of the stove and burbling kettle I like the most. On biting winter mornings.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Now at first glance, my desk here might look as though it's in a mess. However... ...it's not in a mess at all. Everything is exactly where I want it to be. But whenever Susato-san looked at it, she'd put her hands on her hips and say, 'Oh dear.' Her way of saying that I should make it a more orderly and neat mess. ...I miss that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah yes, the daruma doll I brought with me from Japan. I always intended to colour in the other eye once I'd become a fully-fledged lawyer. But it's still winking at me. Like it's trying to say, 'I can wait. Take as long as you need.' ...Or maybe not. I'll just have to keep on doing the best I can, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The photograph of us all together that day... It makes me a little sad to look at it now, which is why I'd taken to lying it flat. But Mr Sholmes righted it every single time. And I've grown accustomed to it. ...I hope we'll all be together again like that one day soon.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I never did see what Susato-san's room looks like. I could go in now, of course. But I don't dare. They say a young maiden's private chamber is a place of bitter-sweet secrets. Although from the laughter I used to hear when Iris would visit, I imagine it's mainly sweet.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at the prawns and the anemones gently swaying around in the tank. Regular cleaning, some food and fresh seawater is all they need. And some conversation, of course. It seemed like a lot of effort at first, but it was worth it. I'm starting to be able to tell what they're thinking. Funny to think that so many people in London had aquariums like this once. When they were in vogue. You'd never expect to find sea anemones in the middle of the capital! I think I'll have to name them soon...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm right in thinking that these scales are a symbol of the defence in law, aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">They're supposed to symbolise treating everything equally...and fairly. That's why they're always in the middle, balanced. Equal measures on both sides.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Recently though, whenever I see a set of scales, I can only think of the enormous Scales of Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's entirely understandable. They are such a powerful symbol in the courtroom, aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And the thing about the Scales of Justice is... ...they're always leaning one way or the other. They're only ever in balance right at the start.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...It must be something peculiar to the British... I'm afraid I can't shed any light on it, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's very fine embroidery here that shows the name of the armband's owner. In this case...Kazuma Asogi. So I'm always carrying my best friend's hopes and dreams with me on my right arm just here. All the time. To be honest, it's something that weighs very heavily on me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Oh, I didn't realise it was such a burden, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I think it's why my right shoulder aches so much.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Are you sure that's not to do with you reading in bed or the like?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">There you are at last!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Good morning, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I think not.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You're late! What on earth took you so long!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Your telegram only arrived at five o'clock, Mr Sholmes. And it's a twenty-minute ride to the hospital.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right, and it's half past five now. I think we made very good time.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The time is utterly irrelevant! The fact is, I have been waiting for what has felt like an eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In point of fact, I myself was awoken at four this morning by a telegram boy. And feeling it was somewhat unjust that I alone had been roused at such an hour, I sent one to you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well thanks for that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Anyway, you're here now, so... The victim is over there. She's only just regained consciousness. You should introduce yourselves. And I shall observe from here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So that's the lady who was found on the snow-covered pavement with the knife in her back...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Her name is... Ah yes, here we are. Miss Green.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...good morning.</line>
<line speaker="???">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hello. Um...I'm, erm, Ryunosuke Naruhodo. From the Empire of Japan.</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh no! Was, was it your knife that...? Are you the man who...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no no! I'm a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And I'm Susato Mikotoba. Pleased to meet you.</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh no! Was, was it your knife then? Are you the one?!</line>
<line speaker="???">Best wishes...for me? Um...thank you. I'm Olive. Olive Green. I'm an artist.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Well... No, that's not right, is it? What I mean is, I'm trying to be an artist. Well, what I really mean is, I desperately want to be an artist. But the truth is...I don't have any talent. I know I don't. It's no wonder I was stabbed in the back.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I...don't think that's related, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gosh, this young woman seems to bend over backwards to put herself down.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Seeing as we're here, we should ask her about what happened from her perspective, I suppose.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">To suddenly be struck in the back by a blade as you were walking along the pavement... What a terrible experience you had, Miss Green.</line>
<line speaker="Green">......... It was so cold that day. And the fog was so thick. I couldn't see a thing. That was four days ago now, I think. Is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's right. I'm afraid you've been comatose all that time.</line>
<line speaker="Green">But the case has been solved, hasn't it? While I've been here in hospital, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed it has, my dear madam! Spectacularly, by none other than I, Herlock Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes! As you well know, it was Mr Naruhodo's hard work in court that solved the case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Are you...yet to hear what happened, Miss Green?</line>
<line speaker="Green">Yes, I'm afraid so. A gentleman from the police force is supposed to be coming to fill me in shortly.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Me coming round seems to have made everyone frantically busy. I'm so sorry. I should never have regained consciousness. It was selfish of me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no! We're all so relieved that you're on the mend, Miss Green, really we are!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>With that kind of attitude, maybe her surname should be 'Blue' not Green...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you're an artist, are you, Miss Green?</line>
<line speaker="Green">Oh no! Oh, I couldn't possibly claim that! I'm a fledgling artist at best. I mean, I'm a student of art, really. At the Thorndyke Academy of Fine Arts.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my... An academy of fine arts! Great Britain is such a wonderful country!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Tell me, Miss Green do you live hereabouts?</line>
<line speaker="Green">Oh, no, actually... I don't deserve it, but I have a little flat on Brixton Road.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I see. How very interesting.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Oh no! ...Is it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Brixton is some ten stops away on the Underground from here. And Thorndyke Academy is a mere three-minute walk from Brixton town centre.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Does that matter, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Perhaps not. But Briar Road is a far less salubrious part of town by comparison. Dwelt in by those of inferior means. Including the maleficent Mr Moustache.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Inferior means? I suppose Soseki-san does fit the bill...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It struck me as somewhat out of the ordinary for a young fine arts student to be walking in such a district. That's all.</line>
<line speaker="Green">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What's this? She's suddenly clammed up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes! You should be ashamed of yourself, prying into a young maiden's private affairs!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah ha ha ha ha hah! Oh, dear me! Do forgive me!</line>
<line speaker="Green">Um, if you don't mind... ...I'm being discharged shortly, so I need to pack up my things.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes, of course. We won't keep you. Thank you so much, Miss Green.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look, there's a photograph in this frame here.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes. It's a picture of a young gentleman.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He looks to be about the same age as Miss Green, I would say.</thought> Perhaps the young woman's 'special someone', do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">My my, Mr Naruhodo, I didn't know you had a sense for matters of the heart.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Not in the least. I sincerely said the first thing I thought of.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This rounded wooden figure isn't the most charming, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, I don't think that's a decoration, Mr Naruhodo. It's an artist's mannequin, I believe. Used when practising sketching the human form in different poses.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? It's not exactly what you'd call a typical figure for that purpose though, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, I suppose not. I confess I've never seen one quite so 'full-figured' before.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, if you want to draw a full-figured person, it's the right tool for the job.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, this looks like the patient's treatment notes. Let's see... 'Do not feed.' ...What is this place, a zoo?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You know, I seem to remember seeing an almost identical sign in our local park.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">For the pigeons, yes. This is a person. <thought>Poor woman, I hope she hasn't read this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There are lots of bottles in that cabinet, aren't there? Do you think it's safe to keep them like that?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Hee hee! If you were a patient here, I feel sure you'd take some medicine by mistake when you were half asleep!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That is a worry. But at least the cabinet has a lock, even if it's only a flimsy-looking one.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, I've no doubt you'd manage to unlock that somehow while you were half asleep as well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...There are limits even to what I can do when I'm half asleep, you know, Miss Susato.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That must be a bag of Miss Green's personal belongings.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">She would have been brought directly here after she was found stabbed on the pavement, though.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I expect a friend or family member probably brought some things for her.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright then, let's see what's inside. A change of clothes, no doubt, and...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, Mr Naruhodo! You must never scrutinise a young maiden's personal belongings.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>But the young maiden might have chocolates, or biscuits, or caramel...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Eek! A mouse, Mr Naruhodo! An enormous mouse!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm... Vermin in a hospital? That doesn't seem the best.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But it looks like a very healthy specimen, doesn't it? It's very plump.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'm not sure we can say that's down to the 'excellence' of this facility, if that's what you were thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, this looks like the treatment notes for whoever's occupying this bed. Let's see... 'Do not permit to run around the hospital.'</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The patient doesn't seem to be here at the moment, so...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He or she is probably running around the hospital, then.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear...how worrying.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's worrying is why they haven't discharged the patient yet.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There are all sorts of medicines in this cabinet, look. I'm not sure if it's safe leaving them in reach of everyone like this.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, you're right. I can imagine if you were peckish, you might try a whole bottle or two.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Well, at least there seems to be a little lock to secure the cabinet doors.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I don't imagine that would stop you if you were hungry. I worry that you'd break the lock.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Hunger doesn't turn me into a criminal, you know, Miss Susato.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>'Narrowfodder' now...?</thought> Well, um, if you're looking for Naruhodo, the lawyer, that's me, but...</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah! Mr Narrowfodder, good. This is for you. It's a message from a Mr Saucy Nutsmeg.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Natsume?! Sent a message...to me?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But why would a policeman be delivering a message from Mr Natsume?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Exactly... <thought>What's going on? What's a Scotland Yard constable doing playing delivery boy at this time in the morning?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Argh, what are you waiting for?! Let me see that!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Well...this is most unexpected...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is something wrong, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">'Is something wrong, Mr Sholmes?' he says! Have you not seen this note?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, how could I have?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It would seem that London's criminals have no intention of letting the great detective rest. A new case calls. A case of murder, no less. ...We must depart at once!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Murder?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Call a cab! Time is of the essence!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...the trouble is... ...we've yet to read Mr Natsume's note. I was thinking we ought to pay him a visit in his lodgings once we did.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">That will be entirely convenient.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Convenient? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It's all here in the note, my dear fellows. The murder we must investigate...took place at Mr Moustache's lodgings!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait...WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'll hail a fiacre at once!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This enormous machine takes up the entire desk, doesn't it? It's really very imposing.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah, Hurley's Great Analytiscope, yes. It can analyse anything at all, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But I've never seen anyone actually using it.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well it's his invention, so I don't know how to operate it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why don't you get it to analyse its own operation then?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ooh, Runo! You're razor-sharp today, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's all sorts on these shelves: chemistry apparatus, books, papers and...lots of things I've never seen before. It's all heaped up so high, I can't help feeling that the whole lot is going to topple at any moment.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It looks as though it might topple, and yet it doesn't. The epitome of Mr Sholmes's brilliance!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I don't get it. As it happens, I'm quite well practised when it comes to stacking shelves myself. Just the other day, the shelf in my office finally gave way under the strain, though.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It looks as though it might topple, and it does. Yes, the epitome of your disarray!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I really don't get it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is Mr Sholmes's famous violin. The one he found being sold for a song at a pawnbrokery. What's it called again? A 'Shodi-something'...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes, this wonderful instrument features in 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes'. It's a world-famous Stradivarius!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Stradi...what?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Stradivarius, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Stragi... Stragivor...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Are you even trying now?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We'll come back to this another time, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I do like this fireplace. It's one of the best things I've seen since we arrived in the country, in fact. Although...I do yearn for a Japanese kotatsu. Putting your legs under a warm, blanketed table is so comforting.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Do be careful, Mr Naruhodo. Don't mistakenly put your feet into the fire, will you? You'd suffer terrible burns, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>I worry sometimes about how Susato-san sees me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's curious how this enormous metal chest is being used as a coffee table. And even more curious to think that Iris's father's notes about Mr Sholmes's cases are inside it.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You mustn't look in there, Runo! Those notes are a secret between Daddy and me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And Mr Sholmes isn't somehow in on the secret?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hurley tends to forget, you see. As soon as he's solved a case, in fact. Once when he read one of my manuscripts, we had a terrible argument about it. 'Never have I solved such a case!' he said. He was absolutely adamant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sometimes I wonder if he's from another planet, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at all these mementoes of Mr Sholmes's past cases. You know, Miss Susato's eyes still sparkle every time she lays eyes on them.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But yours don't, do they, Runo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I have read 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes' now. By order of Miss Susato. But, the trouble is... ...having seen the 'real thing' in action, somehow the stories don't quite ring true for me.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, he does solve the cases...in the end.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I suppose so. Perhaps there's more to the great detective than meets the eye...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It always strikes me how pretty and neatly arranged this tea set is.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It's my favourite one. In fact, I think it's high time for afternoon tea! Wait there, I'll fetch the special blend that I've prepared for today!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Oh Iris, you do love your tea, don't you? She looks so happy at the prospect!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">And after you've drunk it, I'll collect some experimental data, if that's alright.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Just what is she about to make me drink?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah yes, this is where you note down ideas, isn't it, Iris? So, what's on the blackboard today...? 'Buck up, Runo'. ...What is this?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, I'm just playing around with ideas for the title of next month's instalment. Another idea I had was 'The Beryl Coronet'. I'm really torn about which one to use. What do you think, Runo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Anything but 'Buck up, Runo', obviously!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hm, I suppose you're right... I tell you what, I'll surprise you with it. You'll have to wait until next month and see!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh...so many sleepless nights...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's a charming little white shelf. And full of charming little bottles, too.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh yes. But don't touch any of those. They might explode.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ah. A charming shelf full of charming bottles full of charring ingredients...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">You know, Hurley mistakenly drank from one of them the other day.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! <thought>And HOW?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">I think he was lucky, though. He hasn't exploded yet. Chemistry can be a very hazardous occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It's living with Mr Sholmes that's the hazardous occupation, if you ask me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Um, Iris...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's incredible concentration, that is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I find it quite remarkable how she can focus on so many different things at once.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Perhaps I should try drinking more herbal tea.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...The blend third from the right would be good for you, Runo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Um, Iris...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This girl is destined for great things, I'm sure.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If I've remembered correctly, this large and imposing lump of iron is called a 'typewriter'.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">To think that every single one of 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes' blossomed from this very machine! Ah...it's such a dreamy thought...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I actually had a go on it the other day. The metal bars that move when you hit the keys got all tangled up somehow and that made Iris angry.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo... ...you're ruining my dreamy thoughts. Please don't do that again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh...now I've made Susato-san angry as well...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What on earth...?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! The gentleman is deceased, without question! He's dead!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">L-L-L-Locum Student Mr Naruhodo Esquire!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Natsume!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh...why...? Why is this happening? Why to me? I'VE ONLY JUST GOT OUT OF COURT! YESTERDAY! I WAS FINALLY HOME AFTER TWO DAYS OF MISERY! AND THEN I WAKE UP THE NEXT DAY TO THIS! NO EARLY BIRD SHOULD CATCH A WORM LIKE THIS!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I see you're in high spirits again this morning, Mr Moustache.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAARGH!!! Not the horrible HERR LOCK SHOLMES! SHOO! SHOVE OFF! SHOW YOURSELF THE DOOR! I NEVER INVITED YOU!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes came here with us. I'm quite sure he'll be able to help you, Mr Natsume!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I am entirely at your disposal, Mr Moustache. What can I do for you?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">GRRRRRRRRRRRRRRR!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Tsk, here they are...already. The busybodies.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, Inspector Gregson. What a pleasant surprise.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Pleasant, is it? Gives me heartburn every time I see your face at a crime scene, Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hah! I deduce, Inspector...that your heartburn is a result of your excessive consumption of fried food.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...good morning, Inspector.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">.........This is a crime scene! Don't you go touchin' anythin'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Or 'Good morning to you too, sunshine...'</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What a terrible thing to have happened...</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">It's only been three days since I was arrested for the incident on the pavement outside. And then, having finally regained my freedom, it starts happening all over again...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So, the victim lived here on the ground floor, and your room is just one storey up, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Yes, that's right. In a way, we were neighbours, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So did you know the victim? Were you friends?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What's the matter with Soseki-san now? It was an innocent enough question, wasn't it? Why does he seem so shaken by it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">W-W-W-Well... I s-suppose he, he wasn't a complete str-str-stranger... B-B-B-But, did he ever invite me to his r-r-room? N-N-N-NEVER! On my honour! I swear it!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...What an extreme reaction. You're probably wishing you'd never asked now, aren't you, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">When we found him here, I felt wretched. Which is why I sent word asking you to come... ...THROUGH THAT INSPECTOR OVER THERE!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So, Inspector, what was the victim's name? Who was he?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Mr William Shamspeare. He was a lodger here. As you can probably tell, he was an actor. A bit of a dead loss, as it happens. Or...just dead.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Shamspeare...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">It was the landlord, old Mr Garrideb and the other ledger, Mr Natsume, who found him. The fella didn't rise at his usual hour, so Garrideb got worried and kicked the door down.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...doesn't Mr Garrideb have a bad leg?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Ah, yeah, you're right there. It was that jittery Japanese hunchback over there who actually did the kickin'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Really? Soseki-san?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">The victim was pretty hard up, it seems. Even done some time inside for petty crimes. He had no money, no place to go and no friends. His only acquaintances were the people in this house. ...Miserable life and a miserable end to it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...what exactly is Mr Natsume still doing here? He's not involved in the investigation, so shouldn't you have sent him away from the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Well...I'm not sayin' it's because the fella looks odd or anythin'... Or that he acts suspicious... ...but I thought it would be prudent to take a statement from the culpri- I mean, cohabiter.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You nearly said 'culprit' there, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear...Mr Natsume appears to be under suspicion again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It certainly seems that way. He does just come across as such an...odd fellow, doesn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Poor man... How unfortunate.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Anyway, I can't say much until the coroner gets here... ...but I don't think the fella's been a goner that long. The body's still warm.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Even if the inspector would allow it, I don't think I could bring myself to touch a dead body.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Oi! I said hands off! You're gonna mess up my crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, um... No, I just wanted to look, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">No chance! I know your kind! You'll mess it up just by lookin' at it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh...someone's in a bad mood.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">There's certainly some bad air in here, isn't there? Ah ha ha ha ha hah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Alright, it sounds like I'd better talk to the inspector first and try to curry some favour...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Mr Sholmes, what are you doing?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hah! You need only observe to know it, my dear fellow. Investigating, naturally!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...There's nothing natural about that pose.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes! Have you made some miraculous discovery?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Patience, my dear madam, patience. We've not been here in this room five minutes. So far, all I've managed to deduce is what actually happened.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">My goodness! But...isn't that everything we need to know, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm... Now that you propose the idea, I believe one could, indeed, see it that way. At the present time, I have managed to draw two incontrovertible conclusions. The first, that there was a physical struggle here last night in which the victim fought for his life.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">AAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Natsume, what's wrong? Is something that Mr Sholmes said significant somehow?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">N-No... Don't mind me! Forget I was here!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And my second conclusion... ...is that there was a poison lingering in the air here last night that passed the victim's lips.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">N-N-N-NONSENSE!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright, Mr Natsume. Why are you reacting so extremely to Mr Sholmes's deductions?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">N-N-N-No... Please! Pretend I'm not here!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Impossible to ignore.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You must tell us everything, Mr Sholmes! Spare no detail!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... But of course. Let the theatrical tragedy before us be unravelled by my great deductions, presented for your pleasure in two acts!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>We've heard some truly astounding great deductions from Mr Sholmes in the past... No doubt this will be no exception. What miracles will unfold before our eyes this time?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So, my dear fellows, for your delight and wonder, let the curtain rise... ...for Herlock Sholmes's 'Logic and Reasoning Spectacular', Act One!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Careful observation of the victim reveals to us the events that transpired in this disconsolate room last night. Foam at the mouth of the deceased clearly indicates the use of poison. Next to the victim, we notice a large dining plate, which contains, you will observe... ...one half of a sizeable bar of soap. Meaningful? Indubitably. Why is this soap set so purposefully upon the dish? Like the victim's last supper, in fact. Yes... Could it be that the man was about to eat it? Of course, the fork reveals the answer. It appears that the young man's appetite was his undoing. Taking up arms in the form of his cutlery, the victim engaged in a deadly battle for his life. Yet the struggle against his hunger was in vain, for in the end, he couldn't resist devouring the slippery feast! But London's foul soap is besmirched by foul poison. Yes, the victim's life was claimed by poison that tainted the contents of the plate! The soap...and the lather about the young man's mouth are too perfectly matched to ignore. The cause of death was clearly intoxication due to excessive ingestion of foul soap! ...Though personally, I have a greater interest in the taste of foul candlewax, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The cause of death identified, we proceed to Act Two, where we ponder the next question: Was this suicide or murder? The audience will recall that death occurred during the victim's 'last supper'. Did the man dine and die alone? This single teacup suggests the answer. To draw a conclusion on such meagre evidence would be foolish however, certainly. The careful criminal could have absconded with his own cup to cover his tracks. Well, allow me to lift the veil of doubt, my dear fellow. Indeed. What reveals the answer, of course, is the broken lock! Though forced open now, at the time of the incident, this door was locked. And the sole key was in the victim's pocket. In other words, when the victim consumed the poison, he must have been alone. Alone with his inferior soap, from whence wafted an inferior scent. And with that acrid aroma lingering in the air, the victim met his end...in tragic solitude. We can take comfort only in the fact that his soul was well cleansed on its way to the hereafter.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Thus concludes the final act of Herlock Sholmes's great deduction!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">......... </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...There's just one thing, Mr Sholmes...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You are disposed to identifying 'just one thing', aren't you, Mr Naruhodo? Pray, what concerns you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...no matter how hungry he was, do you really think the man would have eaten soap?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It is quite apparent that this man had barely a penny to his name. It is a curious thing, but to one so destitute, soap can suddenly appear quite irresistibly appetising.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">How extraordinary!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In truth, I have tried a little soap myself in the past.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You've eaten it, you mean?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow, it was some time ago now. My postulation was that it would cleanse my gut.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And did it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As I writhed in agony on the floor and spilt the contents of my stomach...yes, I believe it did. The experience taught me a valuable lesson: soap is quite poisonous. It has an unpleasant taste and leads to great discomfort. In summary, I cannot recommend it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Believe me, I wouldn't eat it even if you did.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">There's something that troubles me as well, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's Mr Natsume.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I couldn't help noticing him shuddering and quivering out of the corner of my eye. Almost as if Mr Sholmes's deductions touched a nerve somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">N-N-N-N-N-Nonsense...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well, that clenched teeth episode didn't last...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think...judging by Mr Natsume's reaction... ...the great detective's deductions may need some gentle corrections in order to reach the actual truth.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, Mr Sholmes's observations and deductions are sometimes a little too sharp... He has a tendency to hit the nail on the side of the head and drive it in at an obtuse angle. When he does that, it falls to us to straighten things out.</thought> Alright then, let's see what we can do.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, we must pick out the key words in Mr Sholmes's quite brilliant deductions... ...and discreetly exchange them for something that makes a little more sense. If we can do that... ...I'm sure we'll arrive at what Mr Sholmes meant to say in the first place!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In that case...are you ready for the second performance of the day? Once again, my dear fellows, for your continued delight and wonder, let the curtain rise... ...for Herlock Sholmes's 'Logic and Reasoning Spectacular', Act One!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Careful observation of the victim reveals to us the events that transpired in this disconsolate room last night. Foam at the mouth of the deceased clearly indicates the use of poison. Next to the victim, we notice a large dining plate, which contains, you will observe... ...one half of a sizeable bar of soap. Meaningful? Indubitably. Why is this soap set so purposefully upon the dish? Like the victim's last supper, in fact. Yes... Could it be that the man was about to eat it? Of course, the fork reveals the answer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, you can't deny that a fork implies the man was eating something, or about to eat something.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's true. If I were to decide to eat some soap, I should prefer to use a fork than to attempt it with chopsticks.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And of course, only half of the bar of soap is left on the plate.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But might there not be some other explanation? Something material that proves whether or not the man really ate some soap...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I suppose you'd eat soap with a fork, would you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I don't think it's a question of which implement you'd use. You shouldn't eat soap full stop!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But then why?! Why does the man have a fork in his hand?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... I understand your frustration, Mr Naruhodo, but please don't take it out on me. The point is... ...if we decide the man used this fork to eat the soap, we wouldn't be changing Mr Sholmes's deduction. So we really ought to consider some other clues.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you think he was drinking tea with his soap?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The cup's empty, so there's no way of knowing.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! How about this for an idea? Perhaps the cup was full of water... ...and he was dissolving soap in it so he could gulp as much down as possible?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Please remember that he may not actually have been the soap-lover that he's been made out to be.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look! There's more soap on the floor here! Mr Shamspeare must really have loved the stuff!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Let's not jump to conclusions, Mr Naruhodo. Look closely at this soap... Do you see that it would fit together perfectly with the half bar on the table?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What the...?! How can that be?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think... ...that they are two halves of the same bar that broke apart!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo, with that answer you haven't righted my reasoning in any way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As a logician, you will never surpass me. The science of deduction and analysis requires long and patient study. I'm several steps ahead of you. And your attempts to correct me serve only to highlight your deficiencies.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...this is what you get for agreeing with someone? <thought>I need to reconsider my answer, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow, possibilities are endless. The question we are currently pondering is whether or not this vivacious-looking victim ate the soap.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Until we have established that, I suggest you keep your 'possibilities' to yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh! <thought>It looks like I was getting ahead of myself.</thought> ...'Vivacious' might not be the most appropriate term to describe a dead man, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Some soup on a plate, and a fork in hand... Even so, surely you wouldn't try to eat soap, no matter how hungry you were.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's what we must determine: was the victim eating soap when he died or not? Until we can establish that with some certainty, we shan't make any progress.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Talk about a slippery problem...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Could it be that the man was about to eat it? Of course, the other piece of soap reveals the answer.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It being the other half of the soap on the table. In short, the victim was not eating soap at all. But it's obvious, really. For no depths of hunger could drive any man to attempt to eat soap. Even I, with my unquenchable thirst for practical knowledge, took only a single bite!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But that begs the question of how the man was poisoned. Because there's no sign of any food on the table.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">An excellent observation, Mr Naruhodo. And one that furnishes us with the answer we seek. For London's foul soap is besmirched by foul poison. Yes, the victim's life was claimed by poison that tainted the contents of the plate!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes is still pushing the soap argument, then.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps he's suggesting the man licked the soap rather than ate it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If soap in London is that poisonous, I don't think I want to be washing my hands with it. <thought>But there are no signs of any food in this room at all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Of course, food isn't the only thing that passes people's lips, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'The contents of the plate' is just...the soap again, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, you know there's a saying in Japanese, don't you? 'If your food is poisoned, you might as well eat it plate and all.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, there's an image... All I can picture now is the victim first taking a bite of the soap and then the plate. The soap like some tofu, and the plate like a giant rice cracker...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... That sounds like a very bland combination.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...a Western vessel for the serving of infusions of dried tea leaves.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's a teacup, Mr Naruhodo, as you well know. Stop putting on airs. And it's empty...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, so we've already established that the victim wasn't eating soap when he died. However... ...there's significant evidence to suggest that he was drinking tea.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">My thoughts exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If the victim didn't eat the soap, then what did he eat?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes... It's a real mystery, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! I've got it! He wasn't interested in eating the soap at all! It was this fork he wanted to satisfy his hunger with!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Mr Naruhodo. I really don't think it's helpful to continue with this line of reasoning that the gentleman had peculiar tastes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Susato-san has such a gentle way with words. But I know when I've been told off...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...It may interest you to know, Mr Naruhodo, that there is no such saying in English.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And what flawed logic in any case! Why, if one ate poison, would one have to eat a plate as well?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Don't blame me for my country's crazy sayings...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">A theory that can be refuted in short order, I'm afraid, my dear fellow. Look at the victim's face. He wears the make-up commonly employed by those of his profession, including rouge for the lips. Yet there is no hint of rouge on the fork. Hence we can be assured that the fork never touched the man's mouth!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes... ...that was actually brilliant. <thought>I think I need to look around some more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If the cause of death was poison, how did it get into the victim's body?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think it might be difficult to establish the answer conclusively at this point. But at the very least, the idea of poisoned soap should be discounted, I think. I'm sure there's a far more likely explanation before our eyes here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Something obvious that could explain how poison passed the victim's lips...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, the victim's life was claimed by poison that tainted the teacup!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed! Cups have been the vessel of choice for practising poisoners over the centuries. And it would appear that this victim drank every last drop.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's no sign of food anywhere in the room.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Which leads us to the immutable conclusion: The cause of death was clearly intoxication due to the ingestion of poison contained in this teacup!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The cause of death identified, we proceed to Act Two, where we ponder the next question: Was this suicide or murder? The audience will recall that death occurred during the victim's 'last supper'. Did the man dine and die alone? This single teacup suggests the answer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, the 'Western vessel for infused hot drinks' again. It's already featured heavily in our deductions so far.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, we can imagine that shortly before his death, Mr Shamspeare was having a drink of tea. There would be nothing remarkable about that. But what troubles me...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Is Mr Natsume's reaction when he heard Mr Sholmes suggest it. <thought>There's more to this deduction than it seems...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">We must closely examine the scene of the crime again for some more clues!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's empty, and it's the only cup on the table...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It would appear so, yes. And when you consider those facts, Mr Sholmes's reasoning seems highly logical.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>But it's always the same in these deductions... The real truth is always buried a little deeper than the great detective suggests.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo...you seem very dubious of Mr Sholmes all of a sudden...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The fork again?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The victim just seems to be holding it so pointedly. It makes it impossible to let go of the idea that it must be involved somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Well, let's hope it turns out to be a useful clue in the end.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's, it's another Western vessel for infused-</line>
<line speaker="Susato">IT'S A TEACUP! ...And it too is empty.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Given that he's actually holding this one in his hand...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...We can assume that this is the cup from which Mr Shamspeare was actually drinking.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... ...But, if that's the case... <thought>This changes everything! Everything we've deduced up to now is turned on its head!</thought> I have a bad feeling about this. I almost don't want to say it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes...I know exactly how you feel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo, with that answer you haven't righted my reasoning in any way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As a logician, you will never surpass me. The science of deduction and analysis requires long and patient study. I'm several steps ahead of you. And your attempts to correct me serve only to highlight your deficiencies.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...this is what you get for agreeing with someone? <thought>I need to reconsider my answer, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Which leads you to conclude there were no other persons present at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Precisely, Mr Sholmes, precisely!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">If that is your train of thought, my dear fellow... ...all you have succeeded in doing is substituting my 'single teacup' for a 'single fork'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes...you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm afraid I can't permit such plagiarism!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How exactly do you plagiarise a train of thought? I even showed all my working...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's crucial that we determine whether or not there was somebody else present at the time of death. It will tell us if this was a murder or suicide.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, and while the argument that the presence of a single teacup shows he was alone is a good one... <thought>...we need to make sure we look at this from all angles...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Did the man dine and die alone? This other teacup suggests the answer. Yes! There were two teacups in this room all along!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In other words, this is a strong indication that at the victim's 'last supper'... ...there was a guest present!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...At the very least, we can say now with certainty... ...that somebody else was here in this room last night, taking tea with the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Wh-Wh-What are you TALKING ABOUT?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">To draw a conclusion on such meagre evidence would be foolish however, certainly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In which case, what more can we deduce about this possible 'guest' at the table?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, allow me to lift the veil of doubt, my dear fellow.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you mean to say, you know who exactly was in this room at the time of the victim's death?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed. What reveals the answer, of course, is the broken lock!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'm not sure I like where this deduction is going now.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm afraid it's too late to go back to the halcyon days of eating too much soap.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But the identity of the 'guest' who was in here last night when the victim passed away is... Is something I have a very bad feeling about.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, you can try to ignore your feelings, but we cannot ignore the truth, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>No, I suppose not. Time to look around again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear, the latch is most definitely broken, isn't it? The door was kicked in by Mr Natsume, according to what Mr Garrideb told the inspector.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Who knew his short, thin little legs had so much strength in them?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I'm not sure the length of his legs is in any way significant here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Perhaps this says more about the poor state of the door than about Mr Natsume's strength, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Careful. If he overheard that remark, he'd almost certainly have a 'lively' response.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I don't know... Can this broken lock really tell us anything about who was here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">...It's empty.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Empty of liquid...but full of air! That makes you think, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It makes me think that you're full of hot air. We should be thinking about who else was in the room at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Bother. Susato-san's quip in response was cleverer than my original riddle...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">At first glance, it seems that the only things in this room are the makeshift stage and the costumes. I overlooked these three books initially.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I wonder what they are. Let's see, the titles read... 'The Picture of Monsieur Lecoq', 'Canterbury Yearnings' and... ...'A Meal for Gaboriau'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Wait... I'm sure I've heard those titles before...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It could just be an incredible coincidence, but... ...they're the exact same three books that Mr Natsume purchased the other day!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? <thought>Yes, on the day of the unfortunate incident when Miss Green was stabbed... ...Soseki-san had just been to a bookshop and bought them, that's right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">And now those three titles are here in the room of the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yet Mr Natsume claims never to have been here before. ......... What, what does this mean, do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I, I really don't know what to make of it...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">At first glance, it seems that the only things in this room are the makeshift stage and the costumes. I overlooked these three books initially.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I wonder what they are. Let's see, the titles read... 'The Picture of Monsieur Lecoq', 'Canterbury Yearnings' and... ...'A Meal for Gaboriau'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Wait... I'm sure I've heard those titles before...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It could just be an incredible coincidence, but... ...they're the exact same three books that Mr Natsume purchased the other day!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? <thought>Yes, on the day of the unfortunate incident when Miss Green was stabbed... ...Soseki-san had just been to a bookshop and bought them, that's right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">And now those three titles are here in the room of the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yet Mr Natsume claims never to have been here before. ......... What, what does this mean, do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I, I really don't know what to make of it...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Even Mr Shamspeare didn't eat candles, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We've already established that he didn't eat soap, either!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, do you think perhaps... ...the 'guest' brought this candle here last night?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Even if he or she did, does it reveal anything about the guest's identity?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Good point. There goes my idea. Snuffed out like that candle will be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">If you sigh so deeply, Mr Naruhodo, you're in danger of blowing out the flame.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo, with that answer you haven't righted my reasoning in any way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As a logician, you will never surpass me. The science of deduction and analysis requires long and patient study. I'm several steps ahead of you. And your attempts to correct me serve only to highlight your deficiencies.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...this is what you get for agreeing with someone? <thought>I need to reconsider my answer, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...That may possibly be rather too much conjecture, do you not think, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">To make a great deduction, you must step beyond the realms of conjecture, and into the arena of facts! I would conjecture that you may possibly never make the leap, however.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I must warn you, Mr Naruhodo... ...that a sprinkling of phrases such as 'yet clearly' and 'in other words' will not fool anyone!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...but I always hear you using turns of phrase like that in your deductions, Mr Sholmes-</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Then more fool you! If you will attempt to emulate the ways of a great detective, you must first identify the greatness!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Quite the glowing answer, Mr Naruhodo. However...you appear to have overlooked the possibility that a police officer lit the candle. You will need to burn brighter than that to make a great detective, my dear fellow!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...The whole point of this exercise is to fix YOUR mistakes, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Was there somebody else in here last night, or not... Clearly that's a fundamental question that will reveal the truth about this man's passing.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Exactly. So we must make sure we have solid grounds for our conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I must have another look around and make sure there's not more here than meets the eye...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Indeed. What reveals the answer, of course, is the pile of familiar books!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Quite so! It's no mere coincidence that these three titles are here in this room. It's the link to the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Natsume, you purchased these books four days ago at a secondhand bookshop.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Th-That's just...a c-c-c-coincidence!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In that case, you will be able to bring the same three titles from your own room, will you not? This very moment!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you can't bring your own copies here, it proves that these three books are in fact yours.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Hnnnnnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Having purchased the books four days ago and returned to your lodgings, you were arrested the very next day. So you could conceivably have brought the books here on that evening, but you never mentioned that.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In other words, you could only have brought these three books here to the victim's room... ...last night, having returned to your lodgings after the trial concluded at the Old Bailey.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Ah...um...aaah...aaaaaah...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In short...there is only one possible conclusion: The victim died here in his room last night as a result of poisoning.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And that same night, the victim had a visitor.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And that visitor...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Was you, Mr Soseki Natsume!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Thus concludes the final act of Herlock Sholmes's great deduction!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Huuurgh...uuurgh... Not again... Not again... Not again... NOT AGAAAAAAAAAAAAIN!!!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Well then, Mr Natsume... ...it would appear you're gonna have to accompany me down to the Yard...again.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">But, but, but... But wait! HOLD YOUR HORSES!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Door! Key! Locked! Entry! Exit! Entirely! Impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He's so flustered he's being even stranger than normal...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">What, you think that's an alibi? You could have just made a copy.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">You live in the same buildin', after all. You'd have had plenty of opportunity, I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">B-B-B-B-But... MISERY MEEEEEEEEE!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Sorry, sir, you'll get your chance to give your side of the story later.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The facts speak for themselves, Mr Moustache.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Aaargh...you...you... You horrible Herr Lock Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He really has found himself an arch-rival now, hasn't he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Come on now, no dilly-dallyin'. Outside! There's a carriage waitin'.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Locum Student Mr Naruhodo Esquire! I, I never imagined I'd be in this position again, but... YOU HAVE TO HELP ME! Please! Please! I'm innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Alright, I understand. We'll come to your cell later and talk about it.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">And one more thing!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">My, my poor little kitty-cat... Please give him his breakfast for me!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow, that honour belongs to you!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, at least that means Inspector Gregson is no longer here. We can examine the crime scene in more detail now.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's right. Ah, and of course...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Have you forgotten what the inspector mentioned before? It was the landlord, Mr Garrideb, who discovered Mr Shamspeare.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, Mr John Garrideb, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I expect we could find him in his sitting room on the top floor as usual.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right. We must remember to go and talk to him later, then.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">This is some sort of makeshift stage, I think, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Where does the audience sit, though? For the nightly Shakespeare performances.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Actors aspiring to the great stage must practise their art, Mr Naruhodo, with or without an audience. In fact, on a related note, perhaps you should set up a mock bench for the defence in your office.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Then you could practise your art every single day!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I'll think about it...if you promise to don a beard and play the role of the judge.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Well, if...if that would help you achieve your goal!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This I have to see...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is a gas wall light, isn't it? It must be connected to a gas pipe in the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gas lights, a gas stove... London really is a city of gas.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But now that I think about it...Mr and Mrs Garrideb had an open fire on the top floor, didn't they?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes, you're right. I don't recall seeing a gas stove up there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I much prefer a real fire anyway. It's so much cosier.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And here we have...another disproportionately large machine. This looks like a meter of some kind.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah...this is a gas meter, I think. It seems that in this district, residents pay for gas as they use it with coins.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, I see. Yes, now you've pointed it out... ...I can see that there's a slot just here that looks like it would take a coin. So you mean, if you put a coin in here...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's right. That would buy you about two hours of gas for lights and heating.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...if you were a poor person with no money, you'd have to sleep in the freezing cold?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes...or if you were a scatterbrain with no change because you forgot to exchange your money at the bank.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Thank goodness there's no meter in our office.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, the poor man... So young to die. Do you suppose it was a very painful death, being poisoned as he was?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't know. All we can do now is hope that he'll be reborn to a better life...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I suppose you're right. I wonder... Do you think that putting our hands together in a Japanese prayer will help a British soul?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I made sure I had a reference at the ready for just such an occasion as this, actually. This book is entitled, 'The Beginner's Guide to Praying for the Departed - The British Way'! I'll just reread it now. One moment...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's...quite a spine on that book, isn't there?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah...one of the teacups that Mr Shamspeare and his guest drank from last night. But don't go drinking from them, Mr Naruhodo! There's bitter poison inside!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm not planning on drinking any, don't worry. Anyway, the cups are both empty.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's true. So, one was Mr Shamspeare's... ...and the other must be the cup that Mr Natsume was drinking from.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>But Soseki-san wasn't poisoned, of course...</thought> Perhaps we should take these so we can examine them in more detail later.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah...one of the teacups that Mr Shamspeare and his guest drank from last night. But don't go drinking from them, Mr Naruhodo! There's bitter poison inside!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm not planning on drinking any, don't worry. Anyway, the cups are both empty.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's true. So, one was Mr Shamspeare's... ...and the other must be the cup that Mr Natsume was drinking from.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>But Soseki-san wasn't poisoned, of course...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">As we've seen from the outside, the window is completely bricked up. A vestige of the former window tax that Britons had to pay.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What strange things they used to tax in Great Britain! I mean, making people pay for the number of windows they had in a property... It's extraordinary.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's heartbreaking to think of the poor having to block up their windows just to avoid an unaffordable tax. ...Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What is it, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">If you look closely...a number of the bricks are loose!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes... It looks as though an amateur has broken out a few of them just here... <thought>Was it Mr Shamspeare who did it, I wonder? Being the lodger renting this room.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, look at this, Mr Naruhodo... On the outside, there's a little ledge. And there's something on it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What, outside?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Brrr...it's so cold outside. You can feel it through this gap.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It did snow all last night. It would be cold. But more importantly... ...what is it on the ledge out there? What are those snow-covered lumps?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's...more bars of soap!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Soap? What are bars of soap doing lined up on a ledge outside the window?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I, I have no idea... But the pair of them look rather charming like that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Still, that's very strange, isn't it? Bars of soap lined up outside the window.</thought> I think perhaps we should take one. There are two, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... I, I suppose we could... ...Oh, what's this? Look here at this soap...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Do you see? In the middle there? There's a patch that's a different colour. It's, it's sort of transparent, but...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Some sort of fancy design, I suppose. Only in Great Britain!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It looks like the Hinomaru flag of Japan, doesn't it? How wonderful! It's probably a very expensive brand.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Expensive? Then what's it doing in this ramshackle old room...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Brrr...it's so cold outside. You can feel it through this gap.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It did snow all last night. It would be cold. But more importantly... ...what is it on the ledge out there? What are those snow-covered lumps?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's...more bars of soap!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Soap? What are bars of soap doing lined up on a ledge outside the window?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I, I have no idea...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at these extravagant, bright costumes! Somehow they look out of place in this room, with its grim, shady goings-on.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">This one looks like a king's attire.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A king? ...I've always dreamt of being a king.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, I think you'd be more suited to a feudal lord. A daimyo or suchlike.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">With a chonmage topknot? Every Japanese man wishes he had a chonmage.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, you'd look wonderful with one! And you already have the sword.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Can you imagine what would happen if I walked around the streets of London with a chonmage and a sword?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What's this...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It looks like part of an envelope, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I think you may be right. Perhaps it was torn off when the letter was opened.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is that significant?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, it's a little out of place, perhaps. When you look around the room... ...there's no sign of a letter, or the rest of the envelope in fact, is there?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah... <thought>She's right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">And yet here we have the torn-off end of an envelope... It just strikes me as unusual.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I agree. <thought>We'd better take this, just in case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">What's this...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It looks like part of an envelope, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I think you may be right. Perhaps it was torn off when the letter was opened.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is that significant?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, it's a little out of place, perhaps. When you look around the room... ...there's no sign of a letter, or the rest of the envelope in fact, is there?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah... <thought>She's right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">And yet here we have the torn-off end of an envelope... It just strikes me as unusual.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">There's not much on these shelves, is there? Just this wine glass and bottle. And both of them are cracked.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...not much use, are they?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, I was just reminded of the Reaper, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Prosecutor Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes. He's so reckless with his wine glasses. I was thinking it's a waste and that he should donate some to the needy.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You can suggest it next time we meet.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">This is the teacup from which Mr Natsume was drinking.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes... Unlike the other one, the inside of the cup is completely clean.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I suppose he must have drunk the contents before the tea had a chance to leave a mark.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I always gulp it down, too.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Sorry, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, if you just sip it little by little, it goes cold.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Clearly, I shall have to instruct you in the proper way to take tea.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">This is the teacup from which Mr Natsume was drinking.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes... Unlike the other one, the inside of the cup is completely clean.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I suppose he must have drunk the contents before the tea had a chance to leave a mark.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I always gulp it down, too.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Sorry, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, if you just sip it little by little, it goes cold.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Clearly, I shall have to instruct you in the proper way to take tea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This must be the cup that Mr Shamspeare was drinking from then. It's stained on the inside.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Tea does that, I'm afraid. Even green tea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh really? I've never noticed before.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You've never noticed?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I never leave it in the cup long enough to leave a mark. I like to gulp it down. 'Drink tea while it's hot!' That's the Japanese way, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... So many people seem to have the wrong idea about our culture...and most of them are Japanese!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">This part is a different colour. It's an exquisite design, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Trust the British to turn a boring bar of soap into something special...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I quite like it! It reminds me of the Hinomaru design of the Japanese flag. I expect this is rather expensive soap.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That doesn't seem likely, given who it belongs to.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Whoever opened this envelope didn't bother with a letter opener or scissors, did they?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Yes, whoever opened it...was clearly someone with an unrefined temperament. And judging from the angle of the rip here...the person in question must have been right-handed!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Susato! I think perhaps...someone's been reading too much of 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes'!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You can never read too much of it, Mr Naruhodo! Never!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Inspector Gregson! B-Back so soon?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">After I threw that little Japanese fella in the clink, I went and reported this to the investigation division. In five minutes' time, this place will be cordoned off by the Yard.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, I see. Well, we'd better be leaving then.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Poor Mr Natsume must be feeling very low, being back in a cell again so soon...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm sure. We should probably go...and.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What's wrong, Mr Naruhodo? KYAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'Out, out, brief candle! Life's but a walking shadow, a poor player... That struts and frets his hour upon the stage, And then is heard no more...' ......... ...Now, how soundeth the next part?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">'It is a tale. Told by an idiot, full of sound and fury, Signifying nothing.'</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Indeed! Oh, happy day!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wa-Wa-Wa-Wa-Wa... ...WALKING DEEEEEEEEEAD!!!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">The, the fella isn't dead at all?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What was that nonsense he was saying, though?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think... Yes, it was from William Shakespeare's 'Macbeth'. A soliloquy from Act Five, Scene Five.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Shakespeare...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Whatever do you think will happen now?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Good question. What a strange situation for Mr Natsume. Arrested for murder, but then the victim comes back to life!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think perhaps the victim was never dead in the first place. It seems very likely that Mr Shamspeare did consume poison, as we deduced... ...but was it an accident, attempted suicide...or attempted murder? Until the truth can be established, I imagine the police will keep Mr Natsume in custody.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I suppose so... Let's hope it doesn't come to anything more than a night in the cells... <thought>Oh...what's this? What's that man doing over there? He looks like he's trying to see into Soseki-san's lodgings...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Is something wrong, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, excuse me! Could we have a word?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He just ran off...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I feel sure that I've seen that man somewhere before. Where was it...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm... <thought>I do too, but I don't remember...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, we've done as much investigating here as we can, I think. Perhaps we ought to go to the prison and speak with Mr Natsume again.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">A good idea!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The Garrideb household - and Mr Natsume's lodgings - are in a prominent position there on the corner. Sometimes when I look at the building, I can't help feeling that it's at a bit of a slant...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It does rather look as though it would collapse in even the smallest earthquake, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And isn't it supposed to be haunted as well? <thought>I think I might have a hunch as to why Soseki-san has such a hunched back...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">With the exception of the top floor, where Mr and Mrs Garrideb live, all the windows are bricked up.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's because of an old window tax that was charged on the number of windows a property had. In order to pay less tax, the poorer members of society filled in many of their windows.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But the tax has since been abolished, hasn't it? So the windows could all be opened up again, surely.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Unfortunately, it would appear that the residents of this district can't afford to pay to have the work done.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...that is a sad state of affairs.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Especially for people like poor Mr Natsume, who have to live all cooped up in a windowless room.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I suppose that's the price you pay for living in very cheap accommodation.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...It all seems rather pointless when you put it like that.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">There always seems to be a bicycle outside the Garrideb residence. I read that bicycles are extremely popular all over Great Britain at the moment, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That one seems very...warped though. Especially the front wheel. Is that to make it more of a challenge to ride, do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, I'm afraid that may be a result of the rider's incompetence. For the front wheel to be so badly warped, I'm afraid the rider may have been similarly afflicted.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Then...there's a good chance Mr Natsume has been practising on this bicycle, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... I fear you may be right...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">London's blanketed in fog again today, and the sky is covered in cloud. But if you look carefully in the distance, you can just make out the Crystal Tower being built.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, the Crystal Tower, yes. The centrepiece of the Great Exhibition that's to open in six months' time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Everyone's talking about the Great Exhibition of London at the moment, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, it's to be the largest event of its kind anywhere in the world, with technology and scientists from all over. I can't wait for it myself!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Do you think visiting students from the Far East like us will be granted entry?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The last Great Exhibition that was held in London had more than six million visitors, it seems. And this time, the British are determined to make it an even bigger success to outdo the Paris Exposition!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I see... That's an incredible number of people! And with so many people expected to attend, we should easily be able to slip in unnoticed.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">There's always the honest approach of buying tickets at the main entrance, Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why has somebody built this snowman on some sort of pedestal, do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's not a pedestal, Mr Naruhodo. That's part of the snowman's body.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? But it already has a perfectly good body.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, it's true that British snowmen are usually made with two balls of snow. Perhaps this is a foreigner.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And now we're looking at him as if he's strange. Poor man. I know how he feels.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">If anything, it's Japanese and British two-ball snowmen that are the strange ones, isn't it? After all, real people do have three sections: head, torso and legs.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Do you ever think that perhaps you think about things too much?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Perhaps we should put this spade away somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's not a spade, Naruhodo-san; it's a shovel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, shovels are for digging. That's for scooping up loose material. It's a spade.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, spades are for digging. That's for scooping up loose material. It's a shovel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Well, it doesn't really matter, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You're so right, Naruhodo-san. We mustn't quarrel over such trifles.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">On reflection then, I think I'll leave this spade where it is.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I think that's for the best. We may need a shovel when we're working in the garden.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I heard that there's another room behind that door.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, it's my bedroom, Naruhodo-san, as you well know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Shall I help you unpack your things?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...That's very kind, but no thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your luggage looked very heavy. Are you sure I can't help you move it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...That's very kind, but really, no thank you. A young maiden's private chamber is a place of bitter-sweet secrets, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The only secret I have is the five yen banknote hidden on the back side of my daruma doll...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">These tanks are for keeping sea creatures. They're called aquariums and they were all the rage in London at one time, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, the English are so clever, coming up with the idea of having ocean life on display in the home!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And it means you always have an emergency midnight feast on hand, too.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I'm not sure that's really the idea.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Soseki-san is...so terribly unlucky, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You can say that again. Suspected of two different murders in two days... I've never known anybody to be so badly in the wrong place at the wrong time so many times!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... I have. And I'm looking at him right now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... You know, I hadn't really considered it much before, but I think you might be right... I have been quite unlucky in that respect, haven't I? Am, am I cursed...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no, Naruhodo-san! I'm sure you're overthinking it!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You've been wearing that ever since we arrived in Great Britain, haven't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...it's what shows that I'm a lawyer, so...it seems appropriate.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm not sure that it really means much in this country though, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I wouldn't say that. It might not be official, but it looks official. Often when the police stop me, I just show them this and they leave me alone.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...You're stopped by the police? Often?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, you know...I'm a 'suspicious' foreigner, dressed all in black with a sword at my side.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I do think it's probably the sword that's the main reason. Still, it makes me happy to see you wearing it. And the armband.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I made up my mind that I'll carry them always. This symbol of who I am, and the sword 'Karuma'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Susato-san, what do you make of this?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah yes. The soap that we found on the ledge outside Mr Shamspeare's blocked-up window.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Since we discovered him poisoned, I've been scared to wash my hands. I keep thinking the 'foul soap' is going to be the end of me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, the soap's bad name was cleared in the end, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm...I suppose so... But I'm still worried about it. I think it would be safer just never to wash my hands again.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think you haven't thought that through. You will wash your hands, Naruhodo-san. You will.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Susato-san, what do you make of this?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... What indeed? Let me see... .........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you don't know, really, it's fine to say so. I won't hold it against you!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Here we are again. The eccentric landlord's eccentric top floor abode...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">We're here because Mr Garrideb's the one who discovered the incident this morning, don't forget.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Ah...you chaps, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, good morning, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Thank you for your...cooperation in court yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It was quite a trial... As much for Mr Garrideb as anyone, really.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Came straight back here after all that business at the Bailey yesterday. Didn't expect to wake up to more bally nonsense this morning!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I wonder...if you wouldn't mind telling us exactly what happened, Mr Garrideb?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Yes...I suppose you'd like to know all about that dead loss of an actor chap in the ground floor room.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Those were exactly Inspector Gregson's words, weren't they?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's a single apron drying on that enormous cannon-shaped clothes horse, look.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No no, Mr Naruhodo. That's a real cannon.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I knew that. I was just testing you.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Piece of history, that is. Seen plenty of action on the battlefield, I can tell you. Now the old girl and I are just enjoying the peace and quiet of retirement together. And of course, she'd come in handy if the enemy decided to launch an attack again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Is there a war going on that I don't know about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! A copy of Randst Magazine! 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes' is being read all over London. Isn't it wonderful?!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Naturally, one asks oneself if such a singular detective could really exist. But having met the chap, it's undeniable. He is most certainly singular. Singularly dangerous.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's genuine public opinion for you, Miss Susato. Perhaps it should be reflected in the stories?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Make no mistake, Mr Naruhodo, I intend to snuff out the sort of public opinion we just heard, personally.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'm starting to see where Mr Sholmes's untainted reputation comes from now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's your military uniform, isn't it, Mr Garrideb?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Well, ceremonial garb, yes. Been hanging on the wall ever since my retirement bash. Not in active service now, you know. Doesn't mean much to me any more. You could have the old thing if you wanted it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well...it might suit Lord van Zieks, perhaps. An overly ostentatious outfit like this could be just what he needs!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Very tactful, Miss Susato. Very tactful indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah yes, those enormous mortar shells. It's quite something, seeing them up close, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Didn't...you say something about firing them into the barracks, Mr Garrideb?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Ah, you remember, do you? Just a little 'mishap' that occurred during training one day. 'What are you doing firing on your own men?!' the captain bellowed at me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm not surprised. 'A little mishap' doesn't really do it justice, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Well...one has these little incidents when one's a hot-headed young private.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Perhaps I should put some evidence that resulted from one of MY little mishaps on display...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, does the great lawyer, like the great detective, want to exhibit some trophies of his finest moments?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Good to see Mr Garrideb's medal of honour still proudly displayed on the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The inscription reads: 'For Distinguished Participation', if you remember.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I remember. Because I remember thinking even I might stand a chance of picking up honours like that.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Wouldn't know it to look at me now perhaps, but I had my devil-may-care days, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Devil-may-care? What did you get up to?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">......... Well, all in the past now, of course. And best left there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Best not! I want to know now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You look very dashing in your uniform there, Mr Garrideb.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Ah, that old portrait, eh? Drawn by an art student who used to rent the room downstairs.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, you look so wonderfully young and courageous and strong!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Yes, well... The chap presented it to me one day and asked if I'd let him off the month's rent in return.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, I see. So...you did, presumably?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">I bally well did not.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">A portrait is a portrait. But rent is rent. ...Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And yet it's still there proudly on the wall...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We know what that screen is hiding now. The aftermath of the fiery altercation the other day.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Hmph. Don't suppose I'll be able to clear that mess up for some time now.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear...this must be a very difficult situation for you.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">I'll say. People talk about twists of fate and whatnot... ...but this is a twist and a half! A rotten show all round!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He's clearly struggling with everything that's happened...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's a good view over the wintry East End from up here. It's an oppressively grey scene. There's really nothing comparable in Japan. And down below...Briar Road, partly blanketed in snow.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And the pavement where poor Miss Green was struck in the back by that knife...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thinking about it, this is the only room in this building that actually has a window to the outside world. Sometimes...Great Britain really does seem like a strange land, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I suppose all foreign cultures seem strange at first. Imagine how an Englishman would feel on arriving in Japan and seeing people with a chonmage topknot.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...that's a good point.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's an impressive collection of cakes on that fancy silver cake stand there.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I feel sure that it was full of cakes when we first investigated in here as well.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Yes, quite right. Haven't touched it since. Haven't done much at all really, since it all happened. Time's rather stood still for me, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Time has stood still'? Now that's an interesting phrase... <thought>I might be able to use that excuse when I'm next supposed to be tidying the office.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">...You could just tidy up, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">These shelves look like they've been completely torn apart by a wild beast!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Hmph. Reminds me of the Battle of Maiwand, don't you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ah, the experiences of a seasoned veteran...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Enemy had us surrounded on all sides. We really thought we were done for, the whole bally company. We were taking a real pounding from their cannons, so all we could do was run for our lives.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Oh. I thought that story was going in a different direction, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Well, the whole experience taught me one thing, I can tell you... When you're done for, you're really done for.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... That's not what a lawyer who often finds himself under fire wants to hear...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It must have been a real shock for you this morning. I hear that you discovered what had happened.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Ah, well, that hopeless actor chap rises at five o'clock sharp every morning without fail. But at five thirty this morning, he still hadn't lit the gas. So I went down and knocked on his door, but no bally answer.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And that's when you broke into his room by kicking down the door?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Well, I called on that rum-looking Japanese chap to do the grunt work, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wasn't it a little...premature to kick the door down? The man could have just overslept by half an hour.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's very true, Mr Naruhodo. If thirty minutes' oversleeping warranted such behaviour... ...I'd have to kick your door down every morning!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Well, um, you know... Better to be safe than sorry and all that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Is it just me, or is he avoiding our gaze now all of a sudden?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Except that it was a sorry situation indeed that you found on the far side of the door...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The victim's name is Mr Shamspeare, I believe. Is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Yes, William Shamspeare. Took the ground floor room three months ago now.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And...how would you describe him?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">In a word...destitute.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Destitute?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Well, let's face it, the only redeeming feature of that room is the cheap rent. Anyone wanting to live in a place like that is either broke or has a bally screw loose.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So hard to choose which category Soseki-san would fall into...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Mr Naruhodo. That's a little rude.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">He was doing research, as well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Research? Into what?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Shakespeare, of course! Shakespeare! Read a few plays of the old bard myself, you know. 'Romeo and Hamlet' and all that.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes... William Shakespeare is England's most highly regarded classical playwright and author. He's known as 'Sao' in Japanese, as you know, and many of his works have already been translated.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It seems incredible that 'Shakespeare' was shortened to 'Sao', though. Someone was too heavy-handed there... <thought>There were a lot of costumes in the victim's room actually, weren't there?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Of course, Mr Natsume is a scholar of English literature as well. I imagine he and Mr Shamspeare would have had much in common.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>'Shakespeare Interpretation Disagreement Leads to Shocking Murder!' ...Let's hope it's not that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! Really, how rude!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">After Mr Natsume's trial yesterday, you came straight back here, I believe, didn't you? Did you notice anything strange between then and this morning?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Well now...must have been about six in the evening by the time I got home. Snow was coming down rather heavily as I remember, and it was completely dark already. That failed actor chap was out at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Mr Garrideb noticed there was no light from his room or something, I suppose...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Couldn't summon the energy for anything much, so I just sat in front of the fire up here. It was after eight before Shamspeare got back. And the chap was up until past one in the morning, I'll have you know! Suppose he met his end some time after that. I was asleep by then, so I'm rather in the dark there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, thank you. That was very illuminating.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is everything alright, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well...I was just thinking it's a little strange, that's all. Mr Garrideb...you were up here in your room all evening, if I've understood correctly?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Not a big fan of stairs. Not with this blasted leg.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Then...how is it that you seem to know? The precise movements of your tenant on the ground floor, I mean?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's a very good point. I can't imagine that you could hear noises from the ground floor all the way up here. <thought>Does this old man like to spy on his tenants, is that it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">I say! I know what you're thinking, and it's a bally outrage! I'm ex-military, don't you know? I don't go around spying on my tenants! Why would I?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Then how did you know, Mr Garrideb?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">It's the gas, woman! The gas tells me everything!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The, the gas?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">After Mr Natsume's trial yesterday, you came straight back here, I believe, didn't you? Did you notice anything strange between then and this morning?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Well now...must have been about six in the evening by the time I got home. Snow was coming down rather heavily as I remember, and it was completely dark already. That failed actor chap was out at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Mr Garrideb noticed there was no light from his room or something, I suppose...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Couldn't summon the energy for anything much, so I just sat in front of the fire up here. It was after eight before Shamspeare got back. And the chap was up until past one in the morning, I'll have you know! Suppose he met his end some time after that. I was asleep by then, so I'm rather in the dark there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, thank you. That was very illuminating.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What on earth do you mean, sir? How can the gas tell you anything, let alone everything?!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Well, as you're probably aware, the gas is supplied to the building by pipes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I'd more or less worked that out.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Every room in the building is connected by a single pipe to the gas main outside. And the gas company supplies gas to properties via the main.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...I understand that, too.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Let me see if I can explain. Let's say I was to light the gas lamps up here... What do you suppose would happen?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...obviously the room would get brighter.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Exactly! But at the same time... ...the lights in all the other rooms of the house would dim for a moment.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? They'd dim? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps it's because...when you light a gas lamp, it briefly uses more gas than usual... ...and that reduces the amount of gas in the pipe for the other lamps that are connected to it? That might explain why the other lamps dim momentarily, mightn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, of course! Because everything's connected to a single supply pipe!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Is that supposed to happen, though? It sounds rather undesirable.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Jolly good point. Fact is, the gas company's pipes in these parts are pretty hopeless. Long worn out. And barely got any gas in them to start with! Opposite's also true, of course. Extinguish the lamps up here and they glow brighter in the rest of the house.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Right, I see. So by watching the flickering of the lamps in one room, you can determine what's happening elsewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">...You've got it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, of course, because when people come back home in the evening, and before they go to sleep at night... ...what they're guaranteed to do is either light or put out their lamps and fires!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Clever...</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">In point of fact, the room on the ground floor and the one above it use slightly different amounts of gas. By watching the lights in here closely, I can work out almost exactly what's going on in the whole house.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gosh! ...That's fascinating, Mr Garrideb! Absolutely fascinating!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Oh well, nothing to it, really.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And I can't really see that it's going to help us with the case, either. <thought>What I'd like to know... ...is why Mr Garrideb is so interested in what his tenants are up to in the first place. I feel like there's more to it than idle curiosity...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Garrideb, could I show you this?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Been quite a couple of days, as you can imagine. I'm afraid I'm rather tired. Haven't really got the energy in the old eyeballs, to be honest with you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Some other time, then.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">A good idea!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Look, Mr Naruhodo. Mr Natsume...have the police finished questioning you now?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Locum Student Mr Naruhodo Esquire!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">What is he? Tell me! Is he a ghost? Is he here to haunt me?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Let me guess... You're talking about Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">He actually calls himself a great detective, Mr Natsume. Not a ghost.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">But, but his diabolic deductions... They're not of this world... They've...they've...they've left me... AAAH! Cursed! I'm cursed, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well, that sort of hurts...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Credit where credit is due, Mr Naruhodo. You were heavily involved in the deduction, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, um...moving on... We have some wonderful news!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The victim that we all thought was dead...has come back to life again!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Now, in the absolutely worst case, you could only be tried for attempted murder! That's...great, isn't it? Mr Natsume?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">IT'S TERRIBLE!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I'm stuck! In this cell! Suffering! For some silly! Wrong end of the stick! 'You did it, didn't you?' 'Confess!' 'You're a killer!' 'Why the moustache?' CONSTANT QUESTIONS!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm sorry to hear that...</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">ARGH, THAT SELFISH SHYSTER! Make up your mind! Are you dead or alive? If you were going to come back to life, why bother dying?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...it seems likely that Mr Shamspeare was never actually dead in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Ah, yes, that might make sense... And I'm pleased that he's alive, of course. Our lively debate last night was much fun. I'd be sad to think it was our last.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oops.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Mr Natsume...does this mean... ...that you did see the victim last night? You met with Mr Shamspeare, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... I'm not saying another word! I demand to have a lawyer present!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Who do you think I am? Please, Mr Natsume, we need to hear your side of the story!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Ugh... Why am I cursed like this...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Can you tell us exactly what happened last night then, Mr Natsume?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">There's nothing to tell! But...Mr Naruhodo Esquire...I'm eternally grateful to you for helping me with that accursed case yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The case that saw poor Miss Green hospitalised after she ended up with a knife in her back...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's hard to believe that was only yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">After the trial was over, I trudged my weary way back to my lowly lodgings. And that evening, at...past nine, it must have been, I visited Mr Shamspeare.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you did go to the victim's room, then?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">As we feared...</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING WRONG! I'D NEVER BEEN TO HIS ROOM BEFORE! IT WAS THE FIRST TIME!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Then...what made you decide to go?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I bumped into him when I arrived back at the house. We got chatting, and it developed into a discussion. But he had to go out, so I bade him farewell.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That ties in with what Mr Garrideb said. That the victim went out and came back after eight.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">We met again later that evening, at around nine or just after, when I took him some nice tea I'd brewed as a gift.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So it was you who brought the tea that had clearly been drunk at the scene then?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And...I suppose you were discussing the works of Shakespeare, were you?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Yes, that's right. That's exactly right. Romeo! And Juliet! Who was the stronger? ...It was a delightful debate!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm sure...</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Such a Stimulating Subject, Shakespeare!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And...the debate became very heated, so you slipped poison into Mr Shamspeare's tea?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">NO! NEVER! NOT AT ALL! TEAM JULIET WON! THAT WAS ME! AND WHEN I LEFT HIS ROOM... ...THE FLAMBOYANT FELLOW WAS FIGHTING FIT! I SWEAR IT! CATEGORICALLY!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Natsume, you often say the same thing about yourself, I've noticed... That you have a 'cursed existence'.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I'm sure I've mentioned this to you before, but... ...I've been here in Great Britain for a year now, and in that time, I've learnt that it's no place for me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It can be very trying to live in a foreign land, and adapt to the ways of another culture...</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">There are foreigners everywhere I look. And they all stare at me. They all laugh. That's the impression I get whenever I go out. It makes me scared to leave my room. Which is why I've become a recluse. But even in my room, I find no respite from my fears. I've moved more times than I can remember. And then, one week ago, I moved into Briar Road.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But why? I mean, why did you choose that place? It doesn't seem very...comfortable.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Because the rent is cheap. I have so little money, it spoke to me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The rent...?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Obviously, there's a reason why it's cheap. Because the room is cursed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Cursed? Cursed how?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">The previous occupant - the man who lived there before I took the room - died there.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">He was only a young man, but one morning he was found dead and no one could explain why.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Surely no one would want to live in a room with a history like that...</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I didn't. When the letting agent recommended the place, I wavered. BUT I WANT BOOKS! AND BOOKS COST MONEY! A HORRIBLE HISTORY IS A SMALL PRICE TO PAY! When I realised it would mean I could buy more books, I signed the lease like lightning.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Brave? ...Or blinkered?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">But after I moved in, I soon came to realise what I'd done. I r-realised how horrible that room's h-h-history r-r-really was!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gosh...was it really so awful?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">How did the room's horrible history affect you, Mr Natsume? What happened?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">...At, at first, it was just a feeling. The feeling of beady eyes boring into my back... Watching me...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you think that might just have been your mind playing tricks on you?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">No no no. My mind doesn't know any tricks! It was someone else. It's been one l-long nightmare ever since I was g-g-given the keys to the place!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A nightmare? You've been having bad dreams, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">All, all the souls who've d-died in that room l-l-lean over me in my sleep...AND TRY TO STRANGLE ME!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That really is horrible.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">And...now I come to think of it, it happened again last night, too. The very same night that Mr Shamspeare was writhing in agony from the poison in his body... ...I was on the verge of being suffocated silently by those miserable spirits in my room!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You simply must move out of that room as soon as possible!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Yes, you're right. I know it! And that's why... ...I'm already searching! For the next room with a history to call home!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think perhaps you should try to avoid accommodation with any kind of history at all. Otherwise...I'm scared that you yourself may become history.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Whew. Susato-san knows how to make the man listen...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Have I shown you this before, Mr Natsume?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh! Yes! The sweet, sweet aroma of our beloved homeland!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It shows that the wearer is a defence lawyer. It means nothing in Great Britain, of course, but I still wear it.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh, I know exactly how you feel, Locum Student Mr Naruhodo Esquire! MY HARAMAKI BELLYBAND! I DON'T FEEL RIGHT WITHOUT IT!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your...haramaki bellyband?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">It's perfect for the cold English winters. Just the thing to keep my tummy warm!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes...I see the link... Almost...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Natsume, about this receipt...</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">It, it occurs to me now... ...that it was those confounded books that saw me arrested the first time, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes...I suppose that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">After I spent my precious pennies on them, that's the thanks I get... Now I don't know when I'll read them. No, not when... ...IF! I MAY VERY WELL HATE THEM TOO MUCH TO EVEN OPEN THEIR COVERS!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I don't know that we can blame the books for everything that's happened, Mr Natsume...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Natsume, what do you know about this?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Ah...THERE it is! That lathery lowlife that took my neighbour's life and sent me sliding to the depths of despair!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You've really gone off soap, haven't you?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Absolutely! And I've made up my mind... The next time someone gives me soap as a present, it's...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I don't know that we can blame soap for everything that's happened, Mr Natsume...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm, Mr Natsume... It's nothing much, but-</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Ah! It's been too long since I've been offered a present with that delightfully humble etiquette of our homeland!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">You're too kind. I accept it gladly!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry, but...I wasn't trying to give it to you, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean Mr Garrideb?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Yes. He knows that if people keep dying there, he'll never be able to rent it out again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, that's true. I, for one, wouldn't go near the place.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah... Perhaps... ...that may explain why the landlord pays so much attention to the gas lamps and his tenants' movements.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean...because he's worried about their well-being? <thought>He does seem to have an unusually keen interest in the amount of gas in the pipes... There must be a reason why he keeps such close tabs on the occupants of his let rooms.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">What do you mean, 'he pays so much attention to the gas lamps'?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear! No! It's nothing to do with you, Mr Natsume! Please, forget I said anything!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh, now you're talking about me behind my back as well...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's important is that Mr Shamspeare isn't in fact dead at all. Once he's come round and he's able to tell us what happened, we'll be able to get you released.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Yes, please! Oh, I do hope you're right!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ahem! Excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Inspector Gregson!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I couldn't help overhearin' what you just said. And on that note... ...I have some good news and some bad news.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Which d'you want first?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Always! Every time! The bad news comes first! 'When hope is all you have, hold onto it!' That's my guiding principle!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Right, well, in that case...the good news it is!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Sorry, but it's just a lot easier to explain everythin' that way.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">...Then why did you ask me my preference?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">As you might have heard, the victim, Mr Shamspeare, was just unconscious. He's come round now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...we saw it happen in all its terrifying glory.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">He's still bein' treated by the doctors, but we've managed to get a written statement from him already.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, isn't that wonderful, Mr Natsume?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh, thank goodness... It's all over, then. I can leave this sombre cell...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Sorry, no. That's not on the cards.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">What?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Why ever not, Inspector?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Mr Shamspeare has implicated someone as bein' responsible for what happened last night.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Implicated someone?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">You, you don't mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I'm sorry to say I do, yes. He's pointed the finger at you, Mr Natsume.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">ARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">'By sweet poison did he seeketh to end my life. That wicked'st caitiff...Soseki Natsume!'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">So I'm afraid you'll be appearin' in court as planned. You'll be wantin' to make the necessary preparations.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Nnnnnn... NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOH!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And so...once again, Soseki-san found himself having to take the dock in the Old Bailey. Whether his room was haunted or whether he was just terribly unlucky, I knew I had no choice... The following day I would represent him in court, and do my utmost to break the curse that blighted him!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't find anything out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Nothing particular of note...</thought></line>
</xml>