<xml>
<title>The Foreign Turnabout <thought>demo</thought></title>
<line speaker="???">This blight on my soul... I'll have the child take the blame...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>My name is Phoenix Wright, and I run a small law office. Well, that's what I do back home, anyway. Right now, I'm just a traveler; a stranger in a strange land. This is the Kingdom of Khura'in -- a land of spirit mediums and mystery. I was going to take it easy, maybe take in a few sights, until... my cheery guide, Ahlbi Ur'gaid... was suddenly arrested for murder. I couldn't just leave him to his fate... so I took up his defense. Little did I know just how foreign this country's court system would be. Talk about culture shock...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">O foreign lawyer... Let me make this crystal clear to you. We have no need for defense attorneys here in the Kingdom of Khura'in. All of our verdicts are guided by our royal priestess, Her Benevolence, Princess Rayfa. Her Divination Séances determine all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But I can't just let a verdict be handed down with nobody standing in Ahlbi's corner!</thought> If Ahlbi doesn't have a defense attorney, then I'll do it -- I'll be his attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. It is a little unorthodox, but I will allow it. Though I hope you are prepared for the consequences as well.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. Mr. Phoenix Wright. To think you would dare go against Her Benevolence and me, Gaspen Payne -- I see you are as foolhardy as ever. Hee hee hee hee hee. No matter. You will learn the hard way what it means to defend someone in this country.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh... Have we met before...? Or are you confusing me with someone else? ...Not that now's the time for that. I gotta say, it sounds like one tough crowd out there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Just you watch! That defense attorney will try and twist the truth! You can bet on it! Get him, Prosecutor Payne! Crush that defense devil!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why in the world do they hate lawyers so much here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, if you would please give your opening argument once again, Mr. Payne.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Certainly, Your Magistry. The accused is charged with two crimes: larceny... and murder. Yesterday, the national treasure known as the Founder's Orb... was stolen from the treasure room of Tehm'pul Temple. But that's not all. Along with the empty treasure box... was the dead body of Mr. Paht Rohl, a temple security guard. We believe he was murdered by the thief who stole the treasure. Please allow me to submit as evidence the victim's autopsy report and crime photo.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should be able to check out the evidence by looking in the Court Record (R</thought>. I'd better take a good look at it all later.) And what was the weapon used in this heinous act, Mr. Payne?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The victim was bludgeoned to death with the treasure box itself. As you can see here, it's covered in blood. Since you seem to be shamelessly uninformed, allow me to share this newspaper article.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! That's the article containing the only public photos of the box in existence.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Indeed. It's forbidden for anyone outside of the royal family to view the treasure itself. Which is what makes these photos so special.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess there are national treasures that are off-limits to the public back home, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Magistry, the prosecution would like to call the accused as our first witness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Accused, you will take the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Accused, state your name and occupation again, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Ahlbi Ur'gaid, sir.. I'm in training to be a monk... and I'm a tour guide, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry, Ahlbi. I'm here to defend you.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Mr. Wright... I didn't know you were a lawyer... You... You tricked me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">If I knew you were a lawyer, I wouldn't have given you that tour!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Ahlbi, what's gotten into you?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Don't talk to me! You... You disgust me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now even Ahlbi's against me? What's going on here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. This must be a new experience for you, Mr. Wright, being loathed by a client. Now, then, accused, please give this court your testimony. I want you to tell us what you were doing at the time of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I didn't kill Mr. Rohl, and I didn't steal the treasure.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The incident occurred after the Dance of Devotion rite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Dance of Devotion"?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You mean you don't know?! The Dance of Devotion that is performed by Her Benevolence to the Song of Ceremony... It's only the must-see of any Khura'inese tour!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"<thought>That sour-faced girl from earlier? ...I can't see her dancing to ANYTHING, to be honest.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You disappoint me, defense. I expect you to study and memorize this lyrics sheet posthaste!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, your cross-examination, please.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"<thought>Finally, something familiar in this foreign court. Hmm, should I refresh my memory on how cross-examinations work...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay, so the text in green represents Ahlbi's testimony. And I can progress through it by touching the right arrow. If I want to go back to a previous statement, I can do it by touching the left arrow. And if I find a suspicious-looking statement... I should touch "Present" (R</thought> to open the Court Record. The Court Record contains all of the evidence and data pertinent to this case. So all I have to do is find something that contradicts Ahlbi's testimony... and Present <thought>x</thought> it to the court. But if nothing really sticks out... I can always Press <thought>L</thought> him for a little more info. All right, Phoenix. Time to take a good listen to Ahlbi's testimony!)</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nah, I'll just treat this like any trial back home.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I didn't kill Mr. Rohl, and I didn't steal the treasure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">............ You do? But you're a lawyer. Of course you'd say that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, now. There's no need for that.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">But he's right. Lawyers always claim their client is innocent, even if they have to lie. Just like you're doing right now, accused.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">D-Don't lump me in with that lawyer! I'm NOT lying! I didn't steal anything and I didn't kill anybody!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I'm not allowed to go anywhere near the treasure room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">It's a rule of the temple. They keep a lot of important things in that room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, like the Founder's Orb, in particular. Only the royal family may lay eyes on it. They say that anyone without spiritual power would instantly go blind.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I heard you wouldn't be blinded if you just looked at the outer treasure box. But I've never been anywhere near the treasure room. I'm too scared. You've gotta believe me...!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I've never even seen that treasure box with the green Khura'inese butterfly on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Yeah. You can see it in that newspaper article. Look! See? There's a relief of the Khura'inese butterfly on the treasure box.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, this design here carved on the back of the box. I see it now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">It's a sacred butterfly, said to carry the soul, or "mitamah," of the departed. Its wings form a loop that cradles the mitamah and carries it to the Twilight Realm.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As you can see, there's even one depicted here behind me at the judge's bench.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, what do you know? There it is. ...Though it kinda looks like he's about to be carried off to the Twilight Realm himself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I certainly don't think Ahlbi committed murder. However...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Don't talk to me. You... You disgust me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...That outburst earlier makes me wonder if he'd willingly tell me the truth. I'd better compare his statements and the Court Record carefully. If I find an inconsistency, I can Present some evidence and maybe get him to open up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, Ahlbi... Why would you lie to me...?</thought> So, you say you've never laid eyes on the treasure box. Is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">That's right. It's forbidden, so I'd never do that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In that case... how did you know there was a green butterfly on it?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Oof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait, did that bag just move on its own...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I-I... I saw the picture of it... in that newspaper article.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nope. Take another look. These photos are in black and white. You couldn't possibly tell what color the butterfly is from these pictures!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Nngh... Ooh... Aaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-What the--?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">P-P-Pohlkunka! What is going on here?!</line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">Rrr... Ruff, ruff! Ruff, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I-I'm sorry about this. This is my dog, Shah'do.</line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">Ruff, ruff, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's what was making his bag move...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">O Holy Mother. I thought my heart was about to stop for a second there. Oh, and for our foreign lawyer, "pohlkunka" is what we say when we're surprised.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I see... <thought>Well, that was rather surprising. I can't believe he explained that word to me. Is His Magistry secretly a language nerd...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Still, if what you've discovered through your cross-examination is correct... then the accused has seen the murder weapon in person before. Which just makes him more suspicious than ever!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Which just makes things worse than ever...</thought> Ahlbi. Please give only true statements. I can't help you if you don't tell the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">............</line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">Ruff! Ruff! Ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Darn. I just can't seem to get him to open up to me. What in the world happened in this country... to make even a kid like Ahlbi hate lawyers so much?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">As I suspected, this "cross-examination" session has served no purpose whatsoever. But armed as we are with Her Benevolence's Insight... there's no reason to doubt his guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait just one moment, Your Magistry! I haven't seen this Divination Séance for myself yet. As the defense, I have the right to check it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......Hmm... Very well. We will ask to have Her Benevolence perform the Divination Séance again. But, then, right after your tearful begs for mercy, I really do have to be going.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The only "tearful begs" are going to come from the prosecution when we're through!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There she is: "Her Benevolence"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">......Barb-headed attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I am told you question the veracity of the sacred Divination Séance. Rest assured, you will soon see the error of your foolish ways!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Your Benevolence. The Divination Séance, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Certainly. Nayna, my robe... O Holy Mother! We hold this Divination Séance in your name! Let the eyes of everyone here be clear, and our ears be unstopped! O Dance of Devotion! Guide the victim's soul to me! So that we may receive their final memories in the Pool of Souls!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What just happened?! An image appeared in the pool!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">A final message from the victim's soul, the last communication of his mitamah... The Divination Séance has revealed this to us.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Her Benevolence can use her power of Spirit Communion... to project a victim's memories of the last few moments before their demise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So what we saw in the pool is what Mr. Rohl actually experienced?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">In the victim's memories, we see the accused raising a weapon up over his head. This is consistent with the findings of the police investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This looks bad for Ahlbi... Really, really bad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You'll have plenty of time to regret your folly in the Twilight Realm. The souls of the departed speak only the truth, and I but give their messages a voice. If you think my Insights contain falsehood, I challenge you to prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The accused swung whatever he was holding down on the victim's head!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">These are the victim's experiences just before his death.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>As the victim's final memories, we can assume they aren't lies. So how do I break this down?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Allow me to relieve you of your ignorance, defense. Did you notice the words that appeared in the Séance vision?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come to think of it, I did see words... like "Song of Ceremony" and "Incense."</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The victim's final memories are not limited to sight alone. Sight, smell, taste, sound, touch -- all is laid bare in the Pool of Souls.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what Mr. Rohl experienced with his five senses appears in the vision as words, right?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Precisely. And by examining these sensations... we can perceive the victim's final moments with unparalleled clarity.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay, so this vision shows what the victim was experiencing with his five senses... Wait a minute. Just before... Her Benevolence said "after the morning Dance of Devotion," didn't she? Isn't there something off about that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll use these arrows (D-Pad or Circle Pad</thought> to select the Insight I think is off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yes, this is the Insight that sounded funny. Now I'll just carefully compare this Insight with the Séance vision. If I notice a sensation that seems contradictory, I'll tap "Select" (X</thought>!)</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... This part of the vision doesn't seem to really contradict the Insight. I'd better tap "Select" (X</thought> at some other point in the vision!)</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is it -- this is the part of the vision that contradicts the Insight. Now I just select the sensation I think is inconsistent and then "Present" (X</thought> it!)</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait... No, that's not it. This sensation isn't really inconsistent with the Insight. I'd better find the sensation that IS, and "Present" (X</thought> that!)</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait just a moment!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes? What is it, Barbed Head?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're saying the incident occurred AFTER the morning Dance of Devotion, right?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That is right. What of it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then isn't it strange that Mr. Rohl could still hear the Song of Ceremony?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! You're absolutely right!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That's enough!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. Is that all that troubles you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What the victim heard was just a practice run of the Song of Ceremony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Practice run? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Mr. Payne, if you would?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Certainly! The incident occurred in the interval between the morning performance... during which time, the song's singers were practicing in the performance hall.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Precisely! I was there as well, so I can corroborate this statement.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. So what the victim hears was that practice session.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh. There goes my contradiction...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">A most exquisite rebuttal, Your Benevolence. Now, if you wouldn't mind, could you please revise your Insight for us?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I'm getting the hang of this. If I point out an inconsistency, she'll update her Insights accordingly. So if I keep pointing things out, maybe I can knock all of her Insights out after all! I'd better find another inconsistency, no matter how small!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... It's a bit hard to focus on the Insights with the Séance vision going. I'll try using the "Pause" button (L</thought> to temporarily stop the vision. There! I paused the vision! I think I can touch the flashing panels <thought>Y/A</thought> to jump to different parts of the vision. I'll try moving the mitamah mark to the flashing red panel there. Okay, now that I know how to get around in Séance visions... it's time to find inconsistencies between the Insight and the vision!)</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're saying the victim's field of vision went dark right after he was struck, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Of course, as anyone with eyes can see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, pardon me, but... I must disagree.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Benevolence, please take another look at the exact moment the victim felt pain.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hm...? ......Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Everything goes black and then -- only after that -- the victim feels pain.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I-Inconceivable!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This places the order of events at odds with what you say happened!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">P-P-P... Pohlkunka!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your Benevolence! What is the meaning of this?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I c-cannot be wrong! My Insights are beyond fallacy!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If what the defense says is true, this is a very grave matter indeed! I'm afraid this contradiction... is something we simply can't ignore!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All right! I crushed that Insight! Even if I have to fight every person in this country... I swear I'll get Ahlbi acquitted of this crime... in the main game!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No... The only thing "odd" I find here... is your objection. I hope this will help you change your ways.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That didn't go very well... Actually... I guess I wasn't even remotely close on that one... I'd better take another good look at Ahlbi's statements and the evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're laying your life on the line on THAT...? And what exactly about the testimony is inconsistent with that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... <thought>Urk. Suddenly, I'm not so sure...</thought> I apologize, Your Magistry. May I try again?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">By all means... But know this: You just drove a nail into your own coffin!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gaaaaagh... But I just KNOW something's off about this statement. Guess I should search the Court Record again for something that contradicts it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! Guess that's not it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">More of your defense attorney shenanigans, is it? Well, I won't stand for it. In the name of the Holy Mother, I give you a penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Urk! <thought>I'm SURE this is the piece of evidence I need, though. I guess I'd better take another look at Ahlbi's statements...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">An inconsistency, you say? And where exactly do you see this supposed "inconsistency"?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, defense, please be specific.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I don't know how specific I can be, exactly, but... I just get the vague feeling that something doesn't quite add up... you know?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, I don't know. But I DO know you're skating on thin ice, defense. By your leave, You're Benevolence...?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Do it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh... <thought>And here I thought I was skating so gracefully on that ice, too... I get the feeling I was way off the mark with that one... I'd better take another good look at the Insights and the sensations... I doubt there are any mistakes in the victim's last memories... So that must mean one of Her Benevolence's Insights is off! I'll use these buttons (D-Pad or Circle Pad</thought> to cycle through the Insights and check each one carefully. And then I'll compare the Insights with the sensations and look for an inconsistency!)</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">An inconsistency, you say? And where exactly do you see this supposed "inconsistency"?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, defense, please be specific.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I don't know how specific I can be, exactly, but... I just get the vague feeling that something doesn't quite add up... you know?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, I don't know. But I DO know you're skating on thin ice, defense. By your leave, You're Benevolence...?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Do it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh... <thought>And here I thought I was skating so gracefully on that ice, too... I'm feeling pretty confident I got the right sensation. I guess I'd better take another look at which Insight to present... I'll use (D-Pad or Circle Pad</thought> to cycle through the Insights... and try to find the Insight that's inconsistent with this sensation!)</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">An inconsistency, you say? And where exactly do you see this supposed "inconsistency"?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, defense, please be specific.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I don't know how specific I can be, exactly, but... I just get the vague feeling that something doesn't quite add up... you know?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, I don't know. But I DO know you're skating on thin ice, defense. By your leave, You're Benevolence...?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Do it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh... <thought>And here I thought I was skating so gracefully on that ice, too... I'm pretty sure this is the Insight that's off. I guess I'd better take another look at which sensation to point out... I'd better check the victim's last memories carefully from beginning to end... and look for a sensation that's inconsistent with this Insight!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! I could really use a partner to consult with right about now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh. You seem to be having a hard time. Can't do anything without your little friends? It's so sad when the mind starts to go...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Can't do anything without--"?! I'll show you who's got the sharper mind yet! Get your head back in it, Phoenix! You can do this! If I think back on everything I've heard... Yes, that one statement is definitely fishy!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! I can't seem to find any inconsistencies... But something's been nagging at me. I think it has something to do with the sensation of pain... Although, I shouldn't overlook the moment the victim was struck either. I think I'll take another look at the Insights with those things in mind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The defense's case is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims. This court finds the accused, Ahlbi Ur'gaid...</line>
</xml>