
<xml>
<title>The Rite of Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wasn't able to find any conclusive evidence yesterday. But if I can figure out Lady Kee'ra's motive for threatening the high priest, then maybe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Nick,  um... today, I... well...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't look so down, Maya. I'm going to defend you with everything I've got!</line>
<line speaker="???">You would do well to cease this insanity while you still can.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...As I said yesterday, I'm going to defend my client in court.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Well, know this... You shall not witness a miracle of the sort that occurred last time. The moment she is found guilty, you, too, will be found guilty of abetting the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I never claimed to be a miracle maker. But I AM good at discovering the truth. And unlike miracles, the truth is always waiting to be found.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The truth, you say? Hmph. Then it seems you have chosen your fate. This shall be... your very last trial.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Right! I may be a defendant this time... ...but I'll be by your side like always, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Maya. This place is tough on lawyers. I'll need all the help I can get. Plus, it's always good to have you on the team! Well, it's time. Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let the trial of Maya Fey begin.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is ready, Your Magistry.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">........................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">........................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Quiet! Can't you see Prosecutor Sahdmadhi is absorbed in silent prayer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great. The trial's barely started and the judge is already mad at me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's very devout for a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm? Why is the accused standing over there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, umm... Well... Your Magistry. In addition to being the accused, she is also my assistant.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accused is your assistant, you say? ...Very well, then. A criminal does indeed make a fitting partner to a lawyer with a defiled soul.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That ...wasn't very nice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, well, bad-mouthing lawyers seems to be a custom of sorts here in Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I must say, I am surprised to see you still here in Khura'in, Mr. Wright. And even more so to find you in the Hall of Justice once more. I cannot fathom why you would willingly risk your life in yet another trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The answer is simple, Your Magistry: I am a lawyer, and this is what lawyers do. <thought>Although to be frank, I'd rather be anywhere but here right now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">........................... Such foolishness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi! Are you ready to begin now?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Yes, Your Magistry. The prosecution is ready. Let us begin without further delay. But first, I promise you both this: I will cast your wicked souls into the fires of hell. Thus shall the soul of the victim attain salvation.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ha ha ha ha ha! Splendid! I would expect nothing less of you, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi.</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Please save the victim's soul, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi!Punish the wicked lawyer who dares to stop these last rites!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think I'll pass on that whole fire and brimstone deal. But I'm not surprised by your words or stance, considering what Apollo's told me about you.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">So, it was you who instilled that putrid lawyerly guile within him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Putrid... what?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">He, too, must soon face the fires, lest his soul be lost to redemption. But I shall send you on ahead, so that he will not be lonely when he arrives</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but I'm afraid it won't be that easy. People say I never know when to give up! Nervous, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A little...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Feels like it's been ages since we stood side by side like this in court.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Too bad I'm the defendant...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry. We haven't lost a case together yet!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're right! Let's give this everything we've got, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Now then, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi, would you please explain the case at hand?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Of course, Your Magistry. Let us begin the last rites of the victim. Maya Fey has been charged with the crime of murder. The victim of her heinous crime was high priest Tahrust Inmee. He was conducting the Purification Rite when he was brutally slain.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And the cause of death?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Let us review the victim's autopsy report and the crime scene photo, shall we? The cause of death was blood loss from a stab wound delivered to the abdomen. The murder weapon was likely the Warbaa'd </line>
<line speaker="Judge">A sacred relic used as a tool of murder? The Holy Mother's wrath shall be most severe.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The murder itself took place at the height of the Purification Rite. The accused had donned Lady Kee'ra's sacred robes. And the victim was there to offer prayers as a high priest of Khura'inism. During the rite, the victim and accused were the only two at the Inner Sanctum. Therefore, the only person who could have slain the victim is Maya Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I must say, that does cast a great deal of suspicion upon the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Indeed. Now then, allow me to submit this diagram of the crime scene as evidence in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">In Khura'inism, slaying a priest is a sin most grave and dreadful. As such, Maya Fey's soul shall be plunged into the lowest level of hell -- the Hell of Tickling. There, she shall be tickled without end for 500 million years.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is a terrible fate indeed. Would the defense care to respond? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And here I thought the lowest level of hell was the Hell of Back Pain!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't remember killing anyone, and I don't have that dagger or anything like it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As my client stated, she has no memory of the event as described by the prosecution. But more importantly, she had no motive to kill the high priest in the first place!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So it is, and so it shall be. The Divination Séance reveals the truth for all to see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Here we go again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Please show in the royal priestess!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">It's Princess Rayfa! Oh, how beautiful Her Benevolence looks again today!Glory to the Holy Mother for this blessed day!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>As popular as ever, I see.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Rest assured, good people of Khura'in. I will defeat this murderer and her abettor. They shall not escape on their Freedom Express</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What a joy it is to have the royal priestess back in the Hall of Justice! May the Holy Mother grant us her divine favor! Ur dihara Khura'in!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Ur dihara Khura'in!Ur dihara Khura'in!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She sure looks pleased with herself... Especially for someone who didn't know what a "Freedom Express" was until yesterday.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hm? Is there something stuck to my face, Barbed Head?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, nothing, Your Benevolence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Your Benevolence, the Divination Séance if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Very well... Nayna, my robe... O Holy Mother! We hold this Divination Séance in your name! Let the eyes of everyone here be clear, and our ears be unstopped! O Dance of Devotion! Guide the victim's soul to me! So that we may receive their final memories in the Pool of Souls!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The victim's mitamah has spoken... The Divination Séance is complete.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great... Another clearly incriminating Séance vision.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It could not be any clearer, O foul defense. The accused donned the sacred robes of Lady Kee'ra, and then attacked the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, how very terrible it must have been. The figure of Lady Kee'ra lit against the dim lantern light... The scent of incense growing ever more potent as she drew near... One can almost sense the horror Abbot Inmee must have felt!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The facts as presented by Her Benevolence are indisputable.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...B-B-But! Th-That wasn't me! Do something, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm working on it! <thought>That couldn't have been any clearer. Looks like I'm in for another uphill battle.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The accused committed this vile act during our ancient tradition, Purification Rite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come to think of it, the Rites Guide explains the multipart Purification Rite in detail.</thought> The Transformation Rite... The high priest reads scripture, while a priestess dons the robes of Lady Kee'ra. The Rite of Water... Lady Kee'ra enters the spring, and the high priest purifies her, along with her dagger. The Rite of Fire... The priestess circles the sacred flames to purify her soul.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Indeed... It would seem that the murder occurred during the Transformation Rite. The rite dictates that the high priest stand in front of the spring. Therefore, the accused must have attacked him from the direction of the broken lantern. Well, Barbed Head? Would you care to object?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course. Because I know my client is innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Heh heh, so you say. You truly do not know when you are beaten, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I managed to pull it off last time with Ahlbi. I'll just have to do it again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...You intend to find fault with Her Benevolence's insights yet again? It would seem lawyers are pohlkunan creatures indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Look at that pohlkunan! Pohlkunan! Pohlkunan!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Wh-What exactly is a "pohlkunan"?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Someone who's a real piece of work, so to speak.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>They can call me anything they want. The only thing I care about is uncovering the truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">So, Barbed Head. Are you foolish enough to risk your life for your so-called truth? Because my insights ARE the truth! To deny them is to willingly dig your own grave!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The victim commenced the Purification Rite by bowing to the lanterns and reading a sutra.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...That is everything the victim experienced in his final moments.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Dressed in the sacred robes of Lady Kee'ra, the accused rushed the victim head-on. The brutal stabbing she perpetrated could not have been any clearer.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, it is plain for all to see.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-No, it wasn't me! A sudden drowsiness came over me during the Transformation Rite. I didn't even get a chance to put on Lady Kee'ra's robes!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You waste our time with such meaningless statements, accused. You cannot explain away the truths revealed by the royal priestess's divine insight.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooooh... ...How did you end up finding contradictions last time?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The deceased's final memories include all five senses.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, you mean those words that appeared in the Pool of Souls? It looked to me like the bigger the word, the stronger the sensation was to the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, that's how it looked to me, too. The sensations themselves are never wrong -- only their interpretations. That's why I tried to point out mistakes in Rayfa's Insights the last time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, there could be contradictions between what Abbot Inmee felt and her Insights, huh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You got it. And I'm going to find them this time, too. <thought>Should I check how to point out contradictions in Rayfa's Insights?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nah, I remember how it works. Still... The sensations this time seem to fluctuate more than the ones from Ahlbi's trial. In which case, I'd better keep an eye on changes in their intensity, too. Okay! Time to point out the sensations that contradict the Insights!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The victim commenced the Purification Rite by bowing to the lanterns and reading a sutra.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim supposedly heard the accused's approaching footsteps. But did he really?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What nonsense is this?! Is it not abundantly clear?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, it's not. Because there is something strange about those footsteps.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">S-Strange? Explain yourself, Barbed Head.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The footsteps are strange because...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The timing doesn't make any sense! There shouldn't be any footsteps!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">There should not be footsteps as the accused was approaching the victim? Really? Then do you suggest that the accused was actually floating through the air?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">.........I suggest you hold your tongue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Suggestion noted. <thought>If that's not it, then...</thought> But there's definitely something strange about those footsteps. They're strange because...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They're not getting any louder!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And why exactly does that matter?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please focus your attention on the incense the victim smelled. The scent grows stronger as the accused approaches. If the accused really had approached the victim... ...the sound of her footsteps would've grown louder as the scent of incense grew stronger!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Ahhh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Why, that makes perfect sense! How can this be explained, Your Benevolence?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Um, w-well... There must be a reason...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What does that even mean...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's not exactly singing your praises, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Still, we cannot discount this information solely on account of its lawyerly source. Your Benevolence... Perhaps you must listen more carefully to the abbot's mitamah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Listen more carefully? What's he talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmm... Yes, it would appear so. I shall try to refine the sensation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Refine the sensation?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I can more accurately gauge sensations by deepening my communication with a mitamah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I didn't know you could do that. <thought>Why have we never done this before?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">By refining a sensation, a clearer picture of the truth can be discovered.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">O blessed mitamah, I beseech you! Hear me now and respond to my call!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Footsteps" changed into "bells"? What could this mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Bells? But the only bells at the scene of the crime were...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! That jingling must've come from Abbot Inmee's bells!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean those big things he had on his ankles?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Well, there you have it. The sound of bells was from the high priest's own footsteps.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Th-Then that means...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If the footsteps belonged to the victim himself... It means it was the victim who was moving -- not the accused! The victim was the one who went running toward the broken lantern from the spring! A far cry from what Her Benevolence's Insight would have us believe!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Nngh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But why would the victim have approached the accused?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe he was trying to defend himself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please explain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He could've felt threatened by Lady Kee'ra standing there with a dagger. If so, he might have thought to overpower her before she attacked.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Still your voices! This is nothing but a theory, and a poor one at that! B-Be not led astray by this lawyer's obvious postulation!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Is there something you would care to say, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Even if it was Abbot Inmee who moved, it does not negate the accused's crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The accused was likely waiting for the high priest to approach.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And as he neared, she plunged the dagger into him. It is as simple as that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, right... It really doesn't change much, does it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes! It is as the prosecutor has said! In fact, it is as I meant to say all along as well!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Riiight... And that's why you were so shocked when you first heard it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Understand now, lawyer? That contradiction you conjured up has come to naught. Once I hone my Insights, it will vanish like the dying rays of the sun!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">See? The fact that it was Abbot Inmee who moved... changes nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arngh! <thought>C'mon Phoenix. You gotta keep your cool. That contradiction I pointed out must mean something. That one sensation changed after Princess Rayfa refined her vision. It stands to reason that something else might have changed too because of the refinement. I should focus on any sensations that have changed... ...while searching for more contradictions between them and her Insights!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The victim commenced the Purification Rite by bowing to the lanterns and reading a sutra.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> How do we know the Purification Rite was performed exactly as it was supposed to be?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. That's easy. The customs governing the rite are very clear, and Abbot Inmee would've adhered to them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, that's strange.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Would you care to explain just what is so strange?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. I would ask you to consider the sound of the victim's footsteps. The sound of bells changes to the sound of water at one point.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's simple. The victim must have stepped in some water.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. And the only source of water in the Inner Sanctum... is the spring. ...And therein lies the contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Wh-What contradiction?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe the rite started out as it should have. The victim stood with his back to the spring, and the accused stood right in front of him. But, we now know that the victim then moved into the spring.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">P-Pohlkunka! That is absurd!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This means the accused's location differs from what Her Benevolence's Insight indicates!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Aaaungh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-Then, where do you propose the accused stood once she donned Lady Kee'ra's robes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Based on the sound of the victim's footsteps, I believe Maya was standing here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Not when you say it that way, Your Magistry...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Keep making sloppy statements like that, Mr. Wright, and I'll have your tongue!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please... A-Anything but the chop-chop...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then let's have an actual answer out of you. Where do you believe the accused was actually standing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Until this moment, we've all just assumed... ...that Abbot Inmee and Ms. Fey were standing where they were supposed to be... ...as shown in this rites guide. In short... The victim should've been standing with his back to the spring, and the accused in front. However, if that is how they were really standing... ...he couldn't have stepped into the spring as he approached her. The problem is, the victim DID step into the spring. This can only mean that Ms. Fey had actually been standing in the water!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But if this is true... then their positions would've been completely reversed!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What is going on here, Ms. Fey! Were you really standing in the spring?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...I-I'm sorry, but... I barely remember anything about the rite.</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">The high priest would never make such an obvious blunder during a rite!What on earth...? Is that even possible?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That's enough!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Be that as it may, this does not overturn my Insights!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It doesn't?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Let us say the accused was standing in the spring. ...So what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">..."So what"? This completely reverses their positions is what!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That their positions differed from what is customary is rather curious. However, what does that change? It certainly does not erase the accused's brutal crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">..................I guess you have a point there.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You lawyers are an absurd breed. Never thinking ahead, you cling to the first insignificant contradiction you can muster.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sounds like Princess Rayfa has a pretty good grasp on what lawyers are all about.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Oh, Maya. Where would I be without your brutally frank commentary right now. <thought>Is this contradiction really meaningless? But something really doesn't feel right. Did I take a wrong turn somewhere?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. I will now amend my Insight to account for this new truth.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Now the contradiction is no more. But the truth of the matter still stands, no matter how stubbornly you deny it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you have to say for yourself now, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nnngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Your Magistry, this lawyer may have raised a trivial objection... ...but Her Benevolence's Insights have no further inadequacies of any kind.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes... So it would seem.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a second! But there IS another contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Still you flounder about? Wretched beast... Though you rack that putrid brain of yours, nothing worthwhile will come of it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maya, please tell me you remember something that might help us out here...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sorry... I really don't remember a thing. But now that the place I was standing in has changed, who knows? That alone may cause a new discrepancy with Princess Rayfa's Insights.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's right. We now know that Maya was standing in the spring. A major change like that could very well produce a contradiction. I should take another look at the Inner Sanctum diagram in the Court Record... ...and confirm where Maya and Abbot Inmee were standing. And then focus on finding any discrepancies between their positions and the Insights.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The victim commenced the Purification Rite by bowing to the lanterns and reading a sutra.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Benevolence... I've found a new contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You... You did? Hmph. No doubt it is but another of your vile attempts to slander my Insights.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nope. Take a good look at what the victim saw. It just might change your mind. The lantern flame behind the accused was flickering.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">There is nothing unusual about that. Especially as the wind had stirred.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, that's where you're wrong. If the accused had been standing in the spring... ...then what you see here should be one of the lanterns flanking the statue.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I fail to see your point.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My point is, something is wrong here. The two lanterns flanking the statue were both outfitted with glass wind guards. So neither lantern's flame should have been flickering in the wind in the first place!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">........................Heh.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She seems pretty tickled, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't remember saying anything funny.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I fail to see what you wish to prove here, but... very well. I shall refine the vision and reveal the truth for all to see. O blessed mitamah, I beseech you! Fix your sight upon the lantern there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Huh? That lantern doesn't have a wind guard on it.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">And rightly so. For the wind guard was removed to reveal the sacred flame within for the Rite of Fire. Therefore, there is nothing odd about the flame flickering.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Say whaaat?! B-But when we searched the crime scene, those lanterns had their wind guards on!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">That's because the police put them back on. The sacred flames have burned uninterrupted for hundreds of years, defense. We could not risk them being extinguished, even during an investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That would never fly back home...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Well, Barbed Head? Are you done quibbling? If so, then it is time to bow down before this testimony of the mitamah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.........Arnghk!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Don't worry, Maya! I'm just getting started! <thought>All right, let's go over everything we know so far. Maya was wearing Lady Kee'ra's robes and standing in the spring. The high priest is thought to have been moving toward her. So I should look for sensations that stand in contradiction to this arrangement. I won't give up! I'm going to find a contradiction that will undermine the accusation against Maya!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The victim commenced the Purification Rite by bowing to the lanterns and reading a sutra.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-What could this possibly mean? That lantern clearly contradicts the Insight... But this contradiction... ...will overturn the entire case I've been building.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you all right, Mr. Wright? One minute you shout out, and in the next, you fall silent.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Perhaps it is like the bellow of one who is barreling down a hill with no way of stopping. Is that not right, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">..................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Don't get cold feet now, Phoenix. Even if this overturns the entire case you've built so far... ...the only way is to keep moving forward -- because that's where we'll find the truth!</thought> ...Sorry, but I'm not barreling down a hill. In fact, I'm in full control of everything with the indisputable contradiction I found!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Is that so?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The lantern behind the accused clearly-- No, BLATANTLY contradicts your Insight!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Does it now...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One of the lanterns on the entrance side of the Inner Sanctum was broken. And if you watch what Abbot Inmee saw in his final moments... ...you will notice that the lantern behind the praying form of Ms. Fey is broken. The lantern behind Lady Kee'ra, however, is still intact. In short, we are seeing two different lanterns in this Séance vision!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">H-How could this be?! And even if it were so, how would that contradict my Insights?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.................. Let me start by saying, the claim I'm about to raise... ...will overturn the case I've built thus far.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Will the defense please explain himself?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Based on the broken lantern, we can tell...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The correct position of the lanterns!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">But did you not just explain that yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, did I?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense will own up to its own statements!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better stop filling His Magistry's anger meter...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The fact that there was a broken lantern does not change anything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I beg to differ, Your Magistry! There is one thing it makes clear. And that is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Where the accused and the victim were standing!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But did you not just finish asserting that the accused was standing somewhere else?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I did. And I built my argument on that faulty premise. But thankfully, it has led us here... ...to the actual spot where Maya Fey was standing!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I must say, if the defense keeps changing its assertions in such a capricious manner... ...its credibility may come into question.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm willing to take that risk, Your Magistry, because I believe this will be the last time. I'd like to start by pointing out the actual spot where the accused was standing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well... Show us where you now believe the accused was actually standing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Based on the location of the broken lantern, where was Maya really standing?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... And you are sure it was there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, uh, my hand slipped. Sorry, can we just say that one didn't count?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counting such baffling gaffes is my job, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it was worth a try... <thought>I need to think about the location of the broken lantern. That should make the spot where Maya was standing more than apparent!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">O Holy Mother of Khura'in, Mr. Wright! You remind us yet again why lawyers are reviled. This time, see that you point out where the accused was really standing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wasn't thinking straight before, but now it's all falling into place. We know the victim had stepped into the spring. That means Maya Fey had to have been standing in the water as he approached. However, his memory, which has only now become clear, reveals that... ...Ms. Fey was standing by the side of the broken lantern. In other words... ...she was standing where she was supposed to be according to custom.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Rayfa:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, this is where things take a different turn -- and I mean that literally. The victim had to have been moving toward the spring. That means that while he was moving, he had his back turned toward the accused!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What's this?! Do you mean to say the victim turned around during the rite?! But such an image appears nowhere in the Séance vision!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, it does appear. It's just that no one noticed until now.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">N-No one noticed?! How could no one have noticed something so big?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was a moment when the scripture the victim was holding was all we could see. Thanks to that, none of us could tell that he was, in fact, turning around in that moment.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Nngh!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...S-Such insolence!	</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A huge error, you say? Do explain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The huge error is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The order in which the smaller rites were performed is all wrong! But there's only one way to tell. So let's ask for confirmation from someone who was actually there. Well, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sorry, Nick... I was out cold, so I don't remember a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...It seems there is no way to know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nngh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">But what I'm wondering is... ...what does the order of the rites have to do with this case in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............Truth be told, I hadn't considered that yet.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Consider the meaning behind this penalty, then!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Consider it done, Your Magistry... Your Magistry! Please give me another chance!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. But do not test my patience any further. Now, tell me. What is the huge error in Her Benevolence's Insights?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The scene of the crime is wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">But the vision clearly shows that Abbot Inmee was murdered at the Inner Sanctum!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could there be another place that looks just like it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...No, there can't.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Agh. If that's not it, then...</thought> Your Magistry! Please give me another chance!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. But do not test my patience any further. Now, tell me. What is the huge error in Her Benevolence's Insights?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe this is what happened at the scene of the crime: The victim was reading a sutra when suddenly, he sensed someone behind him. He immediately looked back to see someone dressed as Lady Kee'ra standing there. Wishing to see who it was, he approached the robed figure. That's when he was stabbed!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">This cannot be!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, but it can. And it is! The Insight stating the accused stabbed the victim is wrong! And that is the real truth lying behind this testimony of the dead!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Po...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Po...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Po...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Pohlkunkaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A- Are you suggesting... ...that there was someone else at the scene of the crime?! </line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hnnnnnngh! Have I misunderstood... the voice of the mitamah... yet again? ...Th-This--! This cannot be!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whew... That was a close one. But I managed to divine the true meaning behind the Séance vision somehow. I should add these new facts to the Court Record.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Your Benevolence, please allow me to take it from here. I will overturn the brash accusations of this faithless, putrid-minded lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Y-Yes... I shall place my trust in you.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you sure about this, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">My work as an international prosecutor has taken me to courtrooms around the world. And in that time, I have learned to perform last rites for souls in trials lacking a Séance.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, of course. Forgive my ludicrous inquiry.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Moreover, I have with me a forensic investigator from overseas. I will show you all the most magnificent last rites ever seen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess he really does think highly of Ema and her forensic expertise. I'm impressed that he's come to understand their value. Then again... ...he IS an international prosecutor who's solved tough cases around the world. Time to hunker down, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, let us continue with today's proceedings. Could the defense please tell us who the third party dressed as Lady Kee'ra was? Your new claim has negated the Insights of the royal priestess... ...so I trust you have some evidence to support it, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, of course. (This third party must have really wanted to </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, we're waiting, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The evidence that can reveal the identity of the third party... is this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Ah, yes. I suppose this evidence does clearly demonstrate one thing: The fact that you are lowlier than the lowliest of worms, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Even a lawyer like you cannot not worm your way out of this one, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh, talk about opening up a can of worms... Your Magistry, I'd like to present another piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, it seems the worm is not without a spine. Very well. What other evidence do you have for us today?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Three days before the Purification Rite... ...the victim received a warning letter from an unidentified individual!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He did?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoever sent it clearly meant to threaten the high priest. The letter said, "Do not perform the rite." But the rite went on as scheduled. I believe that is why the high priest was murdered.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who do you suppose sent that letter?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A person with something to hide -- the rebel hunter disguised as Lady Kee'ra herself!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Peace! I-I... I don't understand. I had heard the Lady Kee'ra that has been in the news of late only hunted rebels. If so, why would she have killed the high priest?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excellent question. Maybe it would help to think of it this way: What if the high priest... had secretly been a rebel?!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">The high priest?! He couldn't possibly have been a rebel!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The high priest -- a devout follower of Khura'inism... a rebel?! Do you even comprehend the blasphemy of which you speak? Well? DO YOU?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, too, found it hard to believe at first. But as I continued my investigation, it started to become more and more plausible.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gallery">That shameless pohlkunan lawyer...He's making a mockery of our religion!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...As a faithful Khura'inist, I take issue with these claims. And I am loath to admit them into today's proceedings.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't like where this is going.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The defense's claims are but vile blasphemy tantamount to spitting on the Holy Mother.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-Is it really that big of a deal, Maya...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Abbot Inmee was a distinguished monk, and very well-respected, too, so... yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... Please don't let this turn into an international incident...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">But fear not, good people of Khura'in. The rantings of this putrid-brained lawyer who seeks to sully the soul of the deceased... ...shall come to no avail once I conclude these last rites. The prosecution's assertion that the accused killed the victim remains unchanged.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But...the victim was stabbed in his abdomen! How is that possible when he had his back turned toward Ms. Fey?! Someone else must have killed him!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How can he be so confident?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Heh heh heh... Something has occurred to me, you see. And your allegations of a third party are but a deluded fantasy. And I shall prove that by calling a new witness to the stand. ...An eyewitness who will deliver a definitive answer that will dispel the defense's doubts.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-An eyewitness...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Let us call this eyewitness to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's him again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, now... He has to be the shaggiest witness I have ever laid eyes upon. Please state your name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, um... I'm, ya know, that so-and-so, whatchamacallit! A'nohn Ihmus TBD! 'Least that's what they've been calling me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"TBD"? As in "to be determined"? Can't you just tell us your real name?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The witness has suffered a blow to the head, rendering him amnesiac. Therefore... ...I named him "A'nohn Ihmus <thought>TBD</thought>" in my report, but he thinks "TBD" is part of his name.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Have no fear. I have already questioned him at length. While it is true he has utterly forgotten his name and past... ...his memory of what he witnessed is still very much intact.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Considering the dearth of information, any new knowledge may be of help. Therefore, I will permit his testimony. Now, Mr. Ihmus, please tell us what you saw.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">..................</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">That night, I was up at the top of Mt. Poniponi, the mountain next to the Inner Sanctum.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no way you saw Ms. Fey stab the victim with a dagger!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-I swear I don't know what he's talking about! ...Or don't remember, at any rate!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mt. Poniponi... the beautiful mountain that is also known as the Little Sanctum.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>They must be talking about that smaller mountain from the poster...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Ihmus, I was wondering...</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">What can I do ya for?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The Inner Sanctum lies at a high elevation where clouds and fog can obscure the view. Are you sure you were able to see what happened from the mountaintop next to it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Good point!</thought> H-His Magistry raises an excellent question! Well, Mr. Ihmus?!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">On the day of the rite, there wasn't a cloud in the sky! I had a perfect view! If ya don't believe me, check the weather forecast in the paper that day!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Don't we have the newspaper for that day?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, let's take a look. Hmm... It does say calm, clear skies, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">See? Told ya so!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, it would appear the witness has offered testimony worth hearing.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Mr. Ihmus. I, too, have a question for you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Didn't he already question the witness?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Well, that's what I'm here for, right? Shoot!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">How was the accused holding the dagger? Was she holding it underhanded, its blade protruding from the bottom of her hand?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Yep, I believe she was! It's called a reverse grip!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Ah... I thought as much.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Cease your interruptions, you putrid-headed lawyer. Do you not see the significance in how the blade was held?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why don't you enlighten me, O enlightened one?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Feh. I knew you were a fool. I can already picture you in your next life.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-Next life...?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Yes... After your soul writhes for centuries in the pits of hell... ...you shall be reborn as a witless sea urchin, with barbs limited to your posterior. You shall live a short, inconsequential life, only to be brutally devoured by a sea otter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That was a bit excessive. I simply asked what the dagger grip had to do with the case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Now, pay attention.  How the accused held the dagger is of vital importance. With such information, we can infer exactly what actions she took. You were saying that the victim was killed while he had his back to the accused. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">As such, the accused's dagger grip tells us something very important: The accused approached the victim from behind, swung her arms around him... ...and plunged the dagger deep into his abdomen, using a reverse grip!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Thus, Mr. Ihmus's testimony clears up any doubts that might remain.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ha ha ha! And it coincides with Her Benevolence's Insights as well!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is a disaster! I thought I'd blown those Insights out of the water, but now they're back to haunt me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, the defense may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">That night, I was up at the top of Mt. Poniponi, the mountain next to the Inner Sanctum.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Oh, I'm sure of it! It was a really poniponi-ish mountain!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What does that even mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Ya know, now that I think about it, it was a mighty fine view!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">I hate crowds, so I climbed up there to pray in peace</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Wrong, bucko! This is a once-a-year, epic event! I wanted to pray as close to the actual thing as possible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you're so gung-ho about it, why didn't you go pray at the Plaza of Devotion?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Like I said, I hate crowds. I wanted to pray in peace!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>O Holy Mother, why do I only get the annoying ones...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">And my burning faith demanded that I climb up the mountain closest to the Inner Sanctum! Also...</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">I know it's a no-no, but since there was no one around...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Hee-HO! Y-You're exactly right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In that case, Mr. Ihmus, let me ask you this: Was there a reason you didn't want to be seen?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Uh... About that... If ya get caught climbing the surrounding mountains on the day o' the rite... ...ya can get in big, big trouble!  Har har har har har!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Th-That's it?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Yeah, it's totally embarrassing getting yelled at when you're a grown-up! Har har har har har!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, you're a real "grown-up," all right...</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">And since nobody was around, I lost all inhibition and...</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">...I used my binoculars to spy on the rite at the Inner Sanctum.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">A-Actually, I just happened to have 'em for bird watching.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Bird watching, huh...? I see.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're not going to keep pressing him on this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's sketchy as heck, but I don't really have anything I can really sink my teeth into yet.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh... okay then.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Haaar har har har har! I love the great outdoors! That's just the kinda guy I am! A guy called... A'nohn Ihmus TBD!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">..................</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-He's... really starting to get on my nerves.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">As I looked through my binoculars, I couldn't believe what was unfolding before me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">That's when I saw the accused... stab the high priest with a dagger!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Are ya saying I'm lying about this?! Well, I'm not! It's etched permanently in this old noggin!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-But, I didn't do what you say I did... I didn't even get a chance to touch the dagger on the day of the rite!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Whadda I know o' that? All I know is what I saw! I've never even seen ya before in my life. What possible reason could I have to lie?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urrrrrrgh...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I didn't expect there to be any witnesses way up there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-But, I... I don't remember doing that at all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know. I have a feeling the witness is lying. There has to be an inconsistency somewhere in his testimony. <thought>I should take another look at the Court Record.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Magistry! I had my doubts about this bushy-bearded witness, but now I KNOW we can't trust him.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">What?!  You ain't just judging me solely on my bodacious beard, are ya?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not at all, Mr. Ihmus. It's much more than your sketchy appearance. It's your sketchy testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">H-His testimony, you say?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. Recall how the Inner Sanctum was that day. Specifically, that it was completely enclosed by the ritual curtain.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why yes! I believe you're right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The curtain would have completely blocked the witness's view from Mt. Poniponi. Therefore, he couldn't possibly have seen the murder happen!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Hoo-hah...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Ihmus, have you been knowingly making false statements to this court?!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Err... Umm... Well, uhhh... AAIEEEEEE! YA GOT MEEEEEEEEEE!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness will lower his voice!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">I didn't actually see the accused herself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He "didn't actually see the accused herself"? What's that supposed to mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Lemme set the record straight! I beg ya!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">I saw their shadowy silhouettes, projected against the ritual curtain!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sh-Shadows...? That's what you saw?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">That's right. I could see what was going on by the shadows projected onto the ritual curtain.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In the future, Mr. Ihmus, I would rather you offer up accurate testimony from the start.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Forgive me, my main man Mr. Magistry. Chalk it up to my fuzzy memory!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Though he saw but shadows, it is still valuable testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You have to be kidding me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-What are we going to do now, Nick?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... All I can think of is... ...to look for inconsistencies between the actual rite and what Mr. Ihmus says he saw.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, the defense may cross-examine the witness once more.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">I saw their shadowy silhouettes, projected against the ritual curtain!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">...That's right. Those shadow figures on that bright white curtain... They showed through plain as day. I could see everything that happened!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But Ms. Fey and Abbot Inmee were at the top of a mountain, late at night. The only light up there was coming from four small lanterns. How could the shadows have been projected that clearly onto the curtain?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">No wonder people harp on you lawyers! You're always so dang skeptical! The lanterns weren't the only sources of light, ya know!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">The figures were created by the light of the full moon on that clear and still night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">'Course I did! The bright moonlight projected them onto that curtain, clear as day. It was like watching a scene out o' a horror movie from my front row seat on Mt. Poniponi!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I guess the moon does shine a bit brighter when you're way up there...</thought> Maya, do you recall how bright the moon was that night?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... I remember there weren't any clouds, and that the moon was definitely out. But I don't remember if it could cast any shadows.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, thanks. <thought>We can't deny that the moon was really bright. Which means it's possible that it was bright enough to cause shadows to appear.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Har har har har har! I remember it just like it happened!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">She was just a shadow, but I could tell it was the accused, reverse-gripping that dagger!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">It was that little bun on toppa her head! Didn't need to see her face. That distinctive bob's a dead giveaway! Never underestimate my keen sense o' observation! Har har har har har! Now that's one funny haircut!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's not nice to make fun of a girl's hairstyle! I like my hair this way! Besides! You're one to talk, you sasquatch!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">You're not into this wild, manly look I'm sporting? Shows what you know, little girl! Haaar har har har har!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick...!  Isn't there some kind of a crime you can charge him with?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm afraid it doesn't work that way...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now he claims he only saw shadows? His testimony has sketchy written all over it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then there must be an inconsistency in there somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yep. <thought>Was he really watching everything from Mt. Poniponi? If so, then I should see how his testimony lines up with the conditions of the rite.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You saw silhouettes projected by the moonlight? Sorry,  but that's just not possible.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Wh-Whaddaya mean?! How's it not possible that it was totally possible?! That's impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I'm going to need a "logicalese" translation on that...</thought> Let's take a look at this rites guide, shall we, Mr. Ihmus? The rite is held "when the moon is directly over the summit of Mt. Poniponi."</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Doot doot doooooot...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So if the moon was shining from the west, shadows would've been cast eastward. But Mr. Ihmus was standing to the west of the Inner Sanctum on Mt. Poniponi.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O Holy Mother!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. Our witness here couldn't have seen any shadowy figures on that curtain!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">N-N-No... NO WAAAAAAAAAAAAAAY-HEE-HEE-HEEEE!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Perhaps it was the sacred flames of the lanterns that cast the shadows he saw?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm afraid not. I inspected them during my investigation, but... ...the flames were too small to cast the crisp, distinct figures Mr. Ihmus claims to have seen.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">But...! I did see those silhouettes! Really!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But how could he, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe he was someplace where they WERE visible...? <thought>Wait... Don't tell me...!</thought> Your Magistry! If Mr. Ihmus really did see those shadows, it brings a brand-new fact to light!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And that would be...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The brand-new fact that comes to light if Mr. Ihmus really did see those shadows is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He didn't see the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">But I just told ya I DID see the silhouettes on the curtain! If you think I didn't see the murder, then prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't actually prove it, but my lawyer's intuition tells me you didn't see it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, you shall have to do better than that. Unless you want more of these, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's saying he saw the shadows from Mt. Poniponi, which I've shown is impossible. In that case...</thought> Your Magistry.  If Mr. Ihmus really did see the shadows, there can be only one explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He wasn't where he claimed to be at the time of the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">D-Doot doot dooooot...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh? Then where do you propose the witness was?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Someplace where he could have seen the shadow figures, naturally!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait! You mean... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">None of the mountains east of the Inner Sanctum are close enough for a good view. That leaves only one place he could've clearly seen the shadows from.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...And where might that be?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is where Mr. Ihmus was at the time of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He was at the Plaza of Devotion!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Do you truly believe Mr. Ihmus could see the Inner Sanctum from there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He must have really good eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Ooh, I do pride myself on my excellent vision! But still, you think I could've seen the Inner Sanctum with a big ol' mountain in the way?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's not a matter of good eyesight, defense. I must punish you for not seeing that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh... Should've seen that coming... <thought>All righty, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You lawyers are a desperate lot, aren't you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry, Your Magistry. I'll get it right this time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He was at the high priest's home!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And just how do you propose he saw those curtain shadows from there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm, the witness must be clairvoyant.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Clairvoyant?! Is this true, Mr. Ihmus?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Do I look like a psychic nutjob to you?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Not a psychic one, at any rate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, at least the insult wasn't directed at me this time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You lawyers are a desperate lot, aren't you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry, Your Magistry. I'll get it right this time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Ihmus was at the Inner Sanctum -- just outside the curtain on the east side! That's the only place from which he could've seen the shadowy figures!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Hoo-haaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.........Ngh!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really?! Wow, I didn't even think of that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But wasn't the Inner Sanctum off-limits to all but the victim and the accused?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the third party who was there, you mean. I get the feeling that's a subject Prosecutor Sahdmadhi would rather not touch right now.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.....................</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, you mean...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. This witness was at the scene of the crime. Which means he is the mysterious third party we saw during the Divination Séance. He could be the one who dressed as Lady Kee'ra and killed the high priest!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Goo-geeeeeeh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Wh- Whaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, umm... He must've, uhhh...  <thought>I haven't thought THAT far ahead...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The sanctum has sheer cliffs on three sides and a steep, towering rock face on the other. No one could have made it there by climbing the faces of those cliffs.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">His Magistry speaks true. To say Mr. Ihmus was at such an inaccessible location is but a bid to tarnish his credibility. Is that not right?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Right! I wasn't at the Inner Sanctum! No sir, no how! At least I'm pretty sure I wasn't!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">I'm starting to think I've been imagining things! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! Th... This is insane!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">I knew we couldn't trust that lawyer. He's trying to frame the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Peace! Peace, I say!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is impossible! Unless I can show how he got to the Inner Sanctum... ...it just looks like I'm trying to slander Mr. Ihmus.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I believe in you, Nick! Rah, rah, siss boom bah! Fight, fight, Phoenix Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Just look at the accused. Has she no shame?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's your problem, lady?! Phoenix Wright is very trustworthy, I'll have you know!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">She's got some nerve for a criminal! I bet that lawyer poisoned her mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Please, Maya, you're only making it worse. I appreciate the vote of confidence, but it's probably best to keep it to yourself for now...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I would advise the defense to think carefully before making any more sudden outbursts.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Magistry... <thought>If I wasn't the bad guy before, I definitely am now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Now, Mr. Ihmus. I would like you to think back carefully... ...before you testify next about where you were that night.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">I was never at the Inner Sanctum, I tell ya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess it might've been impossible for him to get to the Inner Sanctum like he claims, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Now will you desist in trying to frame this innocent witness?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Is it not time to end these cross-examinations?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">"A moment of desperation leads to 100 million years of torment." It means that for each moment a sinner spends struggling to deny their sins... ...100 million years of torment are added to their time in hell.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Khura'inism is the strictest religion ever!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And just so you know, you've already accrued 200 million extra years.</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Plus the 500 million years they started with... that's 700 million years of torment!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sure, what's another 200 million, give or take.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, it's a big deal to me! I can't keep saying that the witness was there at the Inner Sanctum... ...if I can't prove it. The problem is, how am I going to do that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">I was never at the Inner Sanctum, I tell ya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">All I'm sure of is that you're deeply skeptical! Hey, Mr. Prosecutor, are all lawyers always like this?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Most certainly. They always try to pin crimes on innocent witnesses, without any proof whatsoever. They are no better than bacteria or viruses.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Yikes! You mean he's contagious?! He's gonna give me... lawyer-itis!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay, this is getting ridiculous.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Whew, that was a close one. He almost put me there at the scene of the crime when I wasn't even there!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">That much I'm sure of, even with the fuzzy memory.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">I sure did. What's the big deal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll tell you what! Your testimony isn't very credible if your memory of the events is fuzzy!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Oh, no worries there. My memory may be fuzzy, but I'm very clear on one thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Here we go again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">If you asked me whether or not I remember what I did that night, I'd say I do!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In short, you are confident that your testimony is true. ...Is that correct, Mr. Ihmus?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Har har har har har! Exactly! Guess ya don't get to be a judge for nothing! So, in closing, I can clearly say that I was totally not there!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Besides, it woulda been impossible to get there in the first place!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">If you have something to say, just say it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Couldn't there have been another way to get there? A way that wouldn't attract attention?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">No, there isn't!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Which means, there is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps the defense would share its theory with us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't even have a wild guess, let alone a theory, though. Time to reach into my bag of bluffs!</thought> To reach the Inner Sanctum without attracting any attention...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No one would've noticed if he had scaled up the side of the mountain. He could've snuck into the Inner Sanctum that way!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Har har har har har! The cliff face is all loose and crumbly 'round there. Even a pro mountain climber couldn't have made it up that way!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Everyone here in Khura'in knows that. But let us forgive the defense's ignorance -- he is a foreigner, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Why doesn't anyone ever tell me these things?!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Tough luck, lawyer! I couldn't have gotten up to the Inner Sanctum by scaling the cliff!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arrrgh! ...Please add that to your testimony, Mr. Ihmus.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"No one could climb up those cliffs. The rocks are all loose and crumbly!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe you snuck up to the Inner Sanctum via the stairs in the Plaza of Devotion?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Har har har har har! With all those people at the plaza?! I don't think so!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But they were all completely absorbed in prayer. With a little stealth, you could've slipped by without drawing any attention!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I am afraid that would have been impossible. During the rite... ...the gate to the stairs was locked tight from the Inner Sanctum side.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What?!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Yeah! If I'd tried to force the lock open... ...someone there woulda noticed, even if they were deep in prayer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh! ...P-Please add that to your testimony, Mr. Ihmus.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"The plaza gate is locked from the side facing the Inner Sanctum."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe you fell from the sky?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Har har har har har! The lawyer thinks he's a comedian now!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I was wondering what crazy theory you would propose next. Well, defense, let's hear it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Ihmus could've... um... parachuted down! We already know the weather was clear, and there was no wind to speak of. Perfect weather for skydiving, I'd say!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Now that you have been backed into a corner, your delusions grow ever more delusional. The Inner Sanctum is on a tiny ledge upon a sheer cliff over 2,000 meters tall. One misstep, and a skydiver would soon find themself in the Twilight Realm.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Yeah! I don't care how still the wind was. Even I couldn't have made that jump!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait! What's this building on top of the sacred mountain...?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">That is Royal Penitentiary No. 4.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, right. Princess Rayfa mentioned there was a prison up there.</thought> How do you get your prisoners up there anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">By helicopter. But only with authorization from the minister of justice. He is the only one who can approve flights that pass over the Inner Sanctum.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Might I also add, defense... ...that no parachute or any other equipment necessary for skydiving have been found.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Are ya saying I flew down there by flapping my arms? I may be an incredible dude, but even I'm not capable of that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arngh... Well, please add that statement to your testimony, Mr. Ihmus.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"It's not like I can fly through the air, either!"</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">No one could climb up those cliffs. The rocks are all loose and crumbly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">As I said before, the rock's all loose and crumbly! And there's no route up there where the rock's more solid. Moreover, I've never rock climbed a day in my life!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Any attempt to climb that mountain would be as good as throwing your life away.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aw, come on, Your Magistry...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You continue to claim that the witness was at the Inner Sanctum. Yet said claim shall remain but a claim without any supporting evidence, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, I realize that, Your Magistry. <thought>If I can't find any inconsistencies, guess I can always try to elicit some more testimony.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">The plaza gate is locked from the side facing the Inner Sanctum.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The high priest himself was seen locking it before the rite began. And we have many believers from the plaza who can corroborate this.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Guess you struck out again, Mr. Lawyer Man!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What if there was a spare key to the gate? But I'm in no position to prove that, so... what now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You continue to claim that the witness was at the Inner Sanctum. Yet said claim shall remain but a claim without any supporting evidence, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, I realize that, Your Magistry. <thought>If I can't find any inconsistencies, guess I can always try to elicit some more testimony.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">It's not like I can fly through the air, either!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">As I have already stated... ...nothing of the sort was found in or around the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Har har har har har! I'd sure like to see some o' that so-called gear you're talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I know, I know... But was there really nothing like that at the Inner Sanctum? What if there was something that could've been used as a parachute? I should give the evidence another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You continue to claim that the witness was at the Inner Sanctum. Yet said claim shall remain but a claim without any supporting evidence, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, I realize that, Your Magistry. <thought>If I can't find any inconsistencies, guess I can always try to elicit some more testimony.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Boy, you lawyers sure are scary!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now hold on. Lawyers aren't scary!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">But you're saying I was at the Inner Sanctum when I wasn't! Anyone who'd try to frame an innocent man like that is scary in my book!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">LAWYERS ARE SCARY! LAWYERS ARE SCARY!IT'S A SETUP! IT'S DEFINITELY A SETUP!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not trying to set anyone up! I-I'm going to provide evidence and explain exactly how it was done.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The gallery speaks true. They know the depth of a lawyer's sin, and the poverty of his virtue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There may be some bad apples, but we're not all like that, you know!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't worry, Nick! I'll still root for you, no matter how morally bankrupt you become!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Thanks a bunch, Maya...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Har har har har har!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mr. Ihmus wasn't at the Inner Sanctum? Or more precisely, couldn't get there?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... I don't see a way out of this. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, these kinds of debates only get worse if you argue them the wrong way. I'll have to pry some conclusive testimony out of him, and then present some evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Like when you're trying to catch frogs from a pond! Once you've got a grip on one, you'd better hold on tight!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Right... Something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Mr. Ihmus is right. He couldn't have skydived down there without any gear.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Well now, finally come around, have ya? Now you see that I couldn't have possibly been there at the Inner Sanctum!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. ...If you didn't have any gear, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Wh-Wh-Whaaat on eaaaarth are you talking about?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That overreaction is a dead giveaway that I'm on the right track!</thought> Take a look at this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Those are prayer flags, are they not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, but they have been sewn together... ...to create one big banner. A banner that could also function like a parachute!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Pohlkunka...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The people of Khura'in are so used to seeing prayer flags... ...that the police didn't even think twice about these flags during their investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">N-No, this cannot be!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness landed at the Inner Sanctum by using these prayer flags as a parachute! Is that not right, Mr. Ihmus?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">There's no way out. I'm surrounded!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Mr. Ihmus?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">All this talk's jogged my memory. I-I-I guess... I guess I WAS there at the Inner Sanctum after all!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Grrrrrr...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As I suspected, there WERE three people there that night!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You did it, Nick! You weren't wrong, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, thanks? Mr. Ihmus. You were the one disguised as Lady Kee'ra that night, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Whaaa...?! N-No way, no how! Uhh... It's like this... Umm... Oh, yeah! I was only there at the Inner Sanctum by accident!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By accident?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Exactly! And that thing's not a parachute. It's a homemade paraglider!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A paraglider? Are you telling me you could fly using that patchwork mess of material?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">It may not look like much, but it's as sturdy as can be! I rode the wind like an eagle, going higher and higher from my earthly launching point! But then something happened that forced me to land at the Inner Sanctum!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you just happened to land there? You expect me to believe that?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, now. Please calm yourself, Mr. Wright. However, the fact that the witness was at the Inner Sanctum is crucial testimony indeed. And it certainly warrants further explication. Therefore, let's continue with more testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">That evening, I was enjoying a trek through the night sky with my homemade paraglider.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Mr. Ihmus, you failed to mention any of this during your pre-trial questioning.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Can't be helped! I mean, I'm just remembering it now!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Continue such slipshod testimony and you will be cast into the Hell of Hangnails... ...where you shall have hangnails grown and ripped out for 800 million years.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">HOO-HAAAAAAH! ...I think I'll pass on that! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like that caught Prosecutor Sahdmadhi off-guard. This is my chance to rip his case to shreds!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">That evening, I was enjoying a trek through the night sky with my homemade paraglider.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">A devout Khura'inist like me can pray anywhere -- even while flying through the sky! But I wouldn't recommend you try it. You're bound to end up dead! Har har har har har!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A paraglider? I didn't see anything like that!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">That's 'cause o' the ritual curtain! It blocked your view! You shoulda seen me, majestically soaring between the mountains!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">R-Really? ...What do you think, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Don't ask me.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Har har har! I was really enjoying that flight! At first, anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">But just as Mt. Poniponi was drawing near, something terrible happened!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Exactly! And when I say terrible, I mean TERRIBLE!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? Was there something unexpected near Mt. Poniponi?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Err... What was it again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Wait, you don't remember?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Uhh... Let's just say it was terrible!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">An accident forced me to make an emergency landing at the Inner Sanctum!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Good question. Now what was it again...? ...Wind? Oh yeah, it was the wind! And not just any wind, but a sudden gale force wind. Made me lose control.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The wind was strong enough to make you lose control?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Ya got that right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, then. Please add that to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"Gale force winds came out of nowhere, so I made an emergency landing at the sanctum!"</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Gale force winds came out of nowhere, so I made an emergency landing at the sanctum!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Yep! Just the right amount o' wind for paragliding! So that sudden gale force wind was a real shocker!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see. So a decent wind had been blowing until then.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Right! A paraglider's not much use without a decent wind!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">As I landed, I banged my head, causing me to lose my memory!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">That's easy! Where the paraglider ended up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess that makes sense. So, outside the ritual curtain, on the side where the moonlight shadows were cast.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">But right as I landed, I hit my head on a rock! I lost both my consciousness and my memory! Haaar har har har har!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something's seriously wrong with this guy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">So you see, I ended up at the Inner Sanctum purely by accident!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Yeah, I'm just a lucky kinda guy! It's times like these that separate the men from the boys!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow, I'd say you were incredibly lucky... Almost miraculously so.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">If ya got something to say, just say it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...All right, Mr. Ihmus. It wasn't an accident, was it? You landed at the Inner Sanctum on purpose.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Wh-What the--?! No, it was an accident, I'm telling ya! You don't even have any proof! So stop making things up about me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>His testimony's like a moving target!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, Nick! Time for some evidence. You know, really grab him by the scruff of his neck!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-One thing at a time, Maya. First, I have to find an inconsistency. <thought>But where there is constantly changing testimony... ...there are bound to be discrepancies and other issues!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We have a saying in my country, Mr. Ihmus: "One lie begets another."</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Huh? What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It means someone caught lying will lie again in an attempt to conceal their first lie. In other words, this current testimony is just a blatant lie you're telling to cover your tracks!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">What did you just say?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You claimed gale force winds caused you to lose control... ...but this newspaper has the weather report for the day of the murder. It says, "The area around the Inner Sanctum will enjoy calm, clear skies today."</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">P-P-P-Pohlkunkaaaaaaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, I do believe it does say that!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">One lie begets another... That makes sense, but... Is it really a saying back home? I've never heard of it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I kind of made that one up.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">For real?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Magistry! The witness's testimony contains another flaw -- one that's even more fatal to his cause.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">More fatal, you say? The defense will explain himself at once!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Ihmus claims he was flying up around the Inner Sanctum with his paraglider. But it would've been impossible to get all the way up there without any wind!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, yes! I believe you're right! But we know the witness was at the Inner Sanctum, so... Mr. Ihmus! How did you get there?! And from where?</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">...........................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Without any wind, he couldn't have flown up there from the bottom of the mountain. By process of elimination... ...the only starting point that makes ANY sense is...!</thought> Your Magistry, I believe I have the answer to your question. To reach the Inner Sanctum, Mr. Ihmus must have launched himself from here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Do you truly believe he arrived at the Inner Sanctum from there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes! Positive!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I fail to see how he could have reached the Inner Sanctum from there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Of course. What was I thinking?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You are a fool. Such an answer is no better than what a monkey might offer.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now now, let us not be cruel. Even a monkey could point out a more probable location.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great. Now the judge thinks I'm lower than a monkey.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">So, the lawyer was monkeying around when he claimed Mr. Ihmus flew down from above.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi. The witness DID fly down from above. With that in mind... To get to the Inner Sanctum, Mr. Ihmus must have launched himself from here!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Hoo-hah! ...Are you insane?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That's where he came from?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If he couldn't have come from below, the only other option is from above. So you see, A'nohn Ihmus came down from Royal Penitentiary No. 4! From there, he could have easily reached the Inner Sanctum by parachute! And that means he might have also killed the high priest!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Ihmus! Were you the third party at the Inner Sanctum?! And the one behind the warning to halt the rite that the victim received?! Was it you we saw in his final memory?! Are you the rebel hunter Lady Kee'ra?!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">HOOOOOOOOO-HAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH! Hey, Mr. Prosecutor, sir! Help me out here!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">..................</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You did it! You finally left him speechless!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Aw, c'mon, Mr. Prosecutor Man!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Quiet, you fool. You should use this time to prepare yourself for what is to come. For a fate far worse than Hangnail Hell awaits you now.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">.........</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Well done, defense. I must concede this point to you. The witness did, in fact, descend to the Inner Sanctum from Royal Penitentiary No. 4.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? He didn't even put up a fight this time. That's awfully... generous of him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">But if you are as perceptive as you seem, then surely you've already figured out the riddle. ...The riddle of A'nohn Ihmus's true identity.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, umm... <thought>His true identity? Not sure I know quite yet, but I guess I'll have to answer with something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...It would seem I am the only one still in the dark here. Would the defense care to enlighten me? Who is this man we've been calling A'nohn Ihmus?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness's true identity is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">That's because it doesn't. This piece of evidence has nothing to do with the witness's identity.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was just testing Prosecutor Sahdmadhi, to see if he really knew!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...It seems you are the clueless one here, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Couldn't bluff my way out of that one... Hmm... If he was at Royal Penitentiary No. 4 before he landed at the Inner Sanctum... ...then he must be...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Unless you wish to be removed from this Hall of Justice, I suggest you think carefully. What is A'nohn Ihmus's true identity?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is this really him?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Hmph. Only now do you realize the truth. Well? Please do share with us your belated insight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's wrong, Nick? Just say it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because this isn't going to be very helpful to our case...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really?! Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Unfortunately, I've got no other choice.</thought> That scruffy beard and shaggy mane completely threw me off. But it's all becoming clear now. The nighttime B.A.S.E. jump from the mountaintop prison... The precision landing at the Inner Sanctum using only a homemade parachute...</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">.....................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Only a paratrooper, or more precisely, a former paratrooper, could've pulled that off. This witness is Datz Are'bal -- prison escapee and key member of Dhurke's rebel group!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">GAAAH-HAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness is an escaped prisoner?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Precisely. The police have been scouring every corner of the city to no avail. Meanwhile, here he was under our noses the entire time.</line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Hoo-haaaaaaaaaaaah! Didn't think anyone would see through my clever disguise!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Heh heh heh. But the witness's charade is not all that has been shattered. ...Is it, defense?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Boy, do I hate this guy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Please recall the defense's own words...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoever sent it clearly meant to threaten the high priest. The letter said, "Do not perform the rite." But the rite went on as scheduled. I believe that is why the high priest was murdered.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who do you suppose sent that letter?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A person with something to hide -- the rebel hunter disguised as Lady Kee'ra herself!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">He claimed that the real killer was "the rebel hunter disguised as Lady Kee'ra."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, and what's your point?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">What of the witness's true identity?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Only a paratrooper, or more precisely, a former paratrooper, could've pulled that off. This witness is Datz Are'bal -- prison escapee and key member of Dhurke's rebel group!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">*gasp* Oh no!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">He is a rebel and an escaped prisoner. He could not possibly have been Lady Kee'ra, mortal enemy of the rebels!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Now, perhaps the witness will enlighten us to the truth. After all, he has yet to refute any of this. </line>
<line speaker="Ihmus">Hoo-haaah! Ya got me! I'm the razor-sharp fangs of the Defiant Dragons!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">...Datz Are'bal!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">When did you get your memory back?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Oh, around the time you guys were talking about there being no wind. But ya gotta gimme credit for making up all that testimony off the top o' my head!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you prepared to tell us the truth now?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Well, it's true I parachuted down to the Inner Sanctum...  ...but I banged my head on impact, and ended up unconscious outside the ritual curtain! In short, all my eyewitness testimony was a big fat lie.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A big fat LIIIIIIEE?!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Oh, and by the way! Long time no see... Yuty!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.........</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait... They know each other?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Your Magistry. This filthy rebel belongs in a jail cell.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, yes! Of course! Bailiff, seize him at once!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Seems ya really have forgotten the will of the dragon, huh, Yuty. But I haven't. And no dogs of the Ga'ran regime are gonna lay a finger on me! ...Alley-oop!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Deploy all available resources! I want all units placed on high alert!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The escaped prisoner... escaped again.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The police force has been placed on high alert. He will be caught before long.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">An escaped prisoner who's escaped the law again after giving a ton of false testimony... Talk about a troublemaker.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He really pulled a number on all of us. <thought>What was the point of all that, anyway?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I can't help but feel that entire episode was an enormous waste of time.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Your Magistry. Perhaps it was not as great of a waste as you might believe.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What makes you say that, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Datz Are'bal dropped something as he made his escape from these halls.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hm? That scrap of paper looks awfully familiar.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">These appear to be direct orders from Dhurke.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">From Dhurke?! The rebel leader?! Oh, but we only have a small corner of it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait, I remember now...!</thought> Your Magistry, I've seen that scrap of paper before!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You have?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The scrap of paper Datz Are'bal dropped is a part of this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Really? Because I fail to see the connection.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I suspected as much. Okay, on to the next piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">One moment, Mr. Wright! We move on when I say it's time to move on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arngh, can't you let it slide once in a while? <thought>I better carefully compare the scrap of paper Mr. Are'bal dropped to the evidence I have.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I will ask the defense once more. Where have you seen this scrap of paper before?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And this is...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I found it at the scene of the crime. It appears to be a copy of the order that Mr. Are'bal dropped. If we put the two together, we should be able to read what the order says!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! And just what does it say, Mr. Wright?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">..................... I can't read Khura'inese.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah... Prosecutor Sahdmadhi, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The ignorant lawyer has not bothered to learn our language? Very well, then... .............................. ...I do not understand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well? Wh-What does it say?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Using the lamplights as a landmark, he was to parachute down to the Inner Sanctum. Upon the rite's completion, he was to don Lady Kee'ra's robes and make his escape.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?! That is how he was to escape from prison?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So, if I were to assume that Mr. Are'bal was the one who killed the high priest... ...then maybe it was because Abbot Inmee tried to thwart his escape plan...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">O foul lawyer... I'm afraid that is simply ludicrous.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? B-But I didn't say anything. <thought>D-Did he just read my mind?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I know how your putrid mind works. Unfortunately for you, however, now that the rebel's escape plan has been revealed... ...it is clear that Datz Are'bal is not the high priest's killer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-How can you be so sure?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">If only you would use that putrid brain of yours every once in a while. Datz Are'bal's plan could not have worked without the help of a certain individual.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I am speaking of Abbot Inmee, of course. Had Datz Are'bal simply donned Lady Kee'ra's robes and made his escape alone... ...he would have been far too conspicuous. But were he by the high priest's side... ...the faithful citizens praying in the plaza would have had no cause to suspect anything. It is, therefore, unthinkable that Datz Are'bal was the high priest's killer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AUGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-So then, you're saying...! The high priest was a...?! Oh, I cannot bear to say it!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I am afraid it is so. He numbered among the rebels who threaten our kingdom.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How could this be?!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">...The high priest... a rebel?Th-There must be some kind of mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Let it go, and move on. Accept the truth. It is the only way. And that goes double for you, defense. Cease your futile battle now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And why should I?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Because I will now put the final nail in the coffin of the accused. Now that we have eliminated Datz Are'bal from our list of suspects... ...there is only one person that still remains: the accused, Maya Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Something... important? Please do explain, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We can't end this trial without looking into...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about the arrow that was fired into the high priest's house?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It was simply a means to deliver the warning letter to the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm...That's more or less the same conclusion we came to yesterday...</thought> You know... I guess you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh? Then THIS should be just about right as well! It seems there is no need to continue this trial any longer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Your Magistry. There is still something important that must be brought to light!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about the murder weapon?! We haven't found it yet!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">What does it matter if it has been found or not? The fact remains that the victim was killed with it by the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I also fail to see how that would be important, Mr. Wright. This, however, is. It seems there is no need to continue this trial any longer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Your Magistry. There is still something important that must be brought to light!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm talking about the true identity of the Lady Kee'ra we saw in the Séance vision! If that wasn't Datz Are'bal, then who was it?! </line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It has? <thought>What's he talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It is as I have maintained from the start. There was no third party in the Séance vision.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-What the--?! I... I can't do my finger point!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">YAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...It is time to let it go, and move on. Your fate has already been sealed, much like your arm.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Th-This hardly seems fair.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It is quite simple once you consider where the victim and the accused were at the time. If the victim was near the spring with his back to the accused, what would he see ahead?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Besides the water itself... there is nothing but the warbaa'd statue.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Precisely. The Lady Kee'ra we saw in the Séance is the warbaa'd statue draped in her sacred robes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-NOOO WAAAAAAAAAAAY!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The accused wanted the false Lady Kee'ra to appear in the Séance vision... ...before she came from behind and stabbed the victim with the dagger in a reverse grip.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But why would the accused want to do something like create a false Lady Kee'ra?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">To show it to the victim as he was being slain.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what reason would the accused have to fool the victim she was about to kill?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It was not the victim she was trying to fool. ...It was this very court itself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Come again?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Suspicion would not fall on the accused if it looked as if another Lady Kee'ra was there. And the defense was foolish enough to fall for it and claim it was a third party in disguise.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are... Are you saying...?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I am. It was all a cleverly wicked scheme, perpetrated by the accused. A scheme in which she sought to use the Séance vision to mislead us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This can't be happening!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">What a face you are making, defense. I am surprised you are taking this so hard. After all, did I not clearly state a while back... ...that you were chasing after naught but a deluded fantasy?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Heh heh heh...Something has occurred to me, you see. And your allegations of a third party are but a </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You're telling me he knew this is how it would turn out all the way back then...? And that he was just waiting for the most effective moment to spring it on me?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Heh heh heh. Do you understand now? I have had you dancing in the palm of my hand this entire time. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It... It can't be--!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is an outrage! You took our royal priestess's sacred Divination Séance... ...and used it to commit this most foul and despicable murder?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-No! I did nothing of the sort!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! It's not true! I... I didn't...!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. It seems this trial is over. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... The accused is... uhh... is not the killer! And uh... here's why... <thought>Now what do I do!? I've got nothing!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would appear that the defense has run out of arguments to make.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I thought for sure that that rebel was the killer! The only person with a possible motive -- the one dressed as Lady Kee'ra -- has vanished. And I've got nothing to use against Prosecutor Sahdmadhi's argument! Damn it! I can't lose now! Not like this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well then, I shall now render my verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait! Please, wait! I'm begging you!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It is time to let it go, and move on.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This trial need not be drawn out any longer. The defense has failed to counter the charge filed by the prosecution. In accordance with the law, I invoke the Defense Culpability Act against the defense. Now, then. This court finds the accused, Maya Fey... ...and the defense, Phoenix Wright... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is the meaning of this?!</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">A body has been found in the Plaza of Devotion, Your Magistry!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A body? What happened now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">And we found this sticking out of the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Why that's... Warbaa'd Dagger!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Lady Kee'ra! She has returned from the Twilight Realm once more!She has come to defeat the rebels!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Peace!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Well, it would seem the dagger that was once lost has now been found.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">I have one more thing to report, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">This dagger... It bears the fingerprints of Maya Fey on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHA-HAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why would Maya's prints be on it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.............................. I cannot believe it, yet it must be true...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is something the matter, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">This trial has run its course, and the accused's guilt has been firmly established. However... ...it would seem the defense was right about one thing. You claimed that the murder at the Inner Sanctum... ...had been carried out by the rebel hunter masquerading as Lady Kee'ra.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I did say something to that effect, but what of it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor Sahdmadhi! A-Are you suggesting what I think you are?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I believe the true identity of the rebel hunter who has been masquerading as Lady Kee'ra... ...is none other than the accused, Ms. Maya Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-Wh-Whaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Meeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I realize how shocking this must seem. Looking back, however, I now realize there was much that pointed to this fact. The rebel-hunting Lady Kee'ra was first sighted about two years ago. And the accused first came to our kingdom two years ago as well.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Why, the timing matches perfectly!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">But there is more... That warning letter was found in the high priest's bedroom three days before the rite. Despite his house being locked up tight that night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Abbot Inmee was an important figure with a ton of duties, including training acolytes. He was really kind, even to a foreigner like me. He even invited me over to his house whenever I was between training sessions.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The accused could have easily left the house unlocked for herself without anyone noticing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">If we assume that the accused was Lady Kee'ra... ...that more than establishes her motive for killing the high priest.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, the victim was secretly an insurgent, bent on helping Datz Are'bal escape, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Precisely. That made him a target of Lady Kee'ra's wrath. And after killing the high priest, she then unleashed her divine justice on another rebel. So, it seems the scope of this case has expanded. We now have... two murders perpetrated by Ms. Maya Fey, masquerading as Lady Kee'ra.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.................. If Ms. Fey is indeed a serial killer, it would affect the severity of her punishment. In light of this, I believe this second murder must be investigated before we can proceed.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">As you wish, Your Magistry. Maya Fey, I hereby charge you with this second murder. May your defiled soul feel the weight of your sins.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A new murder charge on top of a guilty verdict?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems the defense will live to see one more day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Talk about "hanging on by a thread"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Heh heh heh. Come tomorrow, a far more terrible punishment awaits you.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hereby suspend these proceedings so that the second murder may be investigated. Until the conclusion of this new investigation, this court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Let it go, and move on. Abandon this folly. You know very well your evidence proves nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nice try, but you can't make me give up. I'm going to prove I'm right!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You can point your finger as much as you want, but you're simply wasting your time. It is a pitiful sight to see a lawyer who doesn't know when he is beat.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm? Did the defense have something he would like to say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That fell on deaf ears.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry. That scream just sort of slipped out.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't know about trials in your country, but we refrain from such rash outbursts here. Perhaps this will deter any future urges you might have.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not helping my case in the judge's eyes, both literally and figuratively.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Inconsistent...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly! That's where the inconsistency lies!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, I believe it is in the defense's thought process that the inconsistency lies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh. Guess there wasn't an inconsistency there after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm... still trying to figure this whole Insight thing out. When the words change size... ...that means the intensity of those sensations is changing, too, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what it looks like to me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So then... that's probably something we should keep an eye on, too. In short, we should be on the lookout for... ...changes that shouldn't take place, but they do anyway... ...and changes that don't occur when they should.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How very perceptive of you. <thought>I guess all that training's sharpened Maya's mind along with her powers.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's compare the vision to the Insights, while looking for changes in sensory intensity!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sounds like a plan!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Inconsistent...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly! That's where the inconsistency lies!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, I believe it is in the defense's thought process that the inconsistency lies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh. Guess there wasn't an inconsistency there after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Looks like you can't count on your bluffing skills to save your butt this time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... This is a tough one.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, to me, there's something about this one statement that seems off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, it does sound a little strange, doesn't it? Thanks, Maya. I'll take another look at the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You can always count on me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're looking a little pale there, Nick. Are you all right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This trial is really putting me through the wringer.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe it's just a matter of getting the information you need.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right... Thanks, Maya. <thought>Guess I'd better keep pressing, then!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Once you get more info, you can use it to make one of your famous bluffs!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She makes it sound like bluffing is my default move.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's wrong, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, I'm having a tough time spotting a contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, there was one sensation that caught my eye. You know that footsteps sensation? Didn't something about it seem strange to you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now that you mention it... Thanks. I'll focus on that as I review the Insights.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're making that "I-can't-find-a-contradiction" face of yours again, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, well... I'm kinda clutching at straws here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And I think we should focus on the sound of bells that were just uncovered.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're right. Let's focus on that sensation and take another look at Rayfa's Insights.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You look like you're having a tough time, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, because I can't find any contradictions. I mean, the sensations in the vision all seem perfectly fine to me...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">In that case, why don't you read the Insights while focusing on what the victim saw?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Of course! His sense of sight! Time to go over those Insights again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya... I can't find any contradictions.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, Nick. A bit early to throw in the towel, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I didn't notice anything wrong with the sensations that appeared as words just now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well then, maybe the contradiction is in what Abbot Inmee saw. I think there's something fishy about the things that we can more clearly see now. Also... We should focus on not only the sensations, but the updated Insights, as well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. Thanks, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This trial need not be drawn out any longer. The defense has failed to counter the charge filed by the prosecution. In accordance with the law, I invoke the Defense Culpability Act against the defense. Now, then. This court finds the accused, Maya Fey... ...and the defense, Phoenix Wright... </line>
</xml>