
<xml>
<title>The Cosmic Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In the middle of the Space Center bombing trial, we had another bombing incident. This one destroyed Courtroom No. 4. Furthermore, Apollo suffered massive injuries from being there when the bomb went off. Unfortunately, Juniper Woods was fingered as the courtroom bomber. Athena and I knew she had to be innocent, so we took her case on. We managed to clear Ms. Woods's name... ...but Apollo sustained further injuries when he was attacked by Ted Tonate.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo is a tough guy, but this is all taking its toll on him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. Poor guy, being attacked by Tonate like that on top of all his other injuries. <thought>Apollo is resting at the nearby Hickfield Clinic. I've had some experience with that place myself. What an awful turn of events. I never thought he'd land in a hospital of all places...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You must miss him, too, huh? Now that you don't have anybody to tease. Don't worry. He's young. He'll heal quickly and be back before you know it!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's been a while since I last saw Trucy look so down... We won the court case, yet nobody feels much like celebrating...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">*sniffle* Mnnnph... All right, enough of this, people! This is no time to be moping around! Now, dry those eyes! Both of you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, you're the only one who's crying, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Technicalities! Look, we have work to do! We have to take over!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Umm, take over what, exactly...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo's Space Center case, of course! As no verdict's been reached, there's still a chance!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I agree with Athena. We should pick up Mr. Starbuck's defense. We have to avenge our fallen comrade! Right, Daddy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Apollo hasn't exactly "fallen." He's still alive, you know...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Good! Now that that's settled, let's get going! C'mon, we gotta run!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait? Right NOW, now?! <thought>We'd better not be running the whole way!</thought> ...There she goes. I'd better go catch up. *sigh* Can you take care of the office, Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Sure thing, Daddy! Let's be careful out there! In the meantime, I'm going to bake some cookies and fill up my magic panties for you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Trucy seems to be feeling a little better. I can always count on Athena to perk everybody up with her enthusiasm.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh! She's back!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't mind me! Just forgot a few things! ...Wallet, phone, the documents, my bag...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sounds more like you forgot everything. <thought>I can always count on Athena for that, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">All right, you two. Let's be careful out there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So our client is one Solomon Starbuck. He's so famous, even I've heard of him.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right! He's a super-famous astronaut who works at the Cosmos Space Center! He was actually up in outer space seven years ago!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You seem to know quite a bit about him. <thought>Now I'm all excited to meet the man!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow. That was the longest sigh I've ever heard.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Apollo told me all about you... You're Phoenix Wright, Apollo's mentor, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, that's right. <thought>Hmm, mentor has a nice ring to it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't worry about a thing, Mr. Starbuck! Mr. Wright and I have got you covered!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Ahh, and you're... the new kid that Apollo told me about. ......Wait! Don't I know you from somewhere?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? Y-You mean... other than at your trial? I don't think so...</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">...I guess so. My mistake. Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... My memory isn't what it used to be. My mind and body are kaput. Same goes for my life. I mean, I'm so astronomically unlucky that I had a bomb go off in the middle of my trial! Trying to defend me would be like trying to enter the stratosphere without a spacecraft.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yikes. He's SERIOUSLY got to stop depressing himself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Cheer up, Mr. Starbuck! Besides, that thing you said about entering the stratosphere... That just means we'd shine like shooting stars, right?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Like shooting stars, huh...? You know, you're right! Why didn't I think of that?! After all, that's what we were all put on this Earth to do, right? To shine like stars!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess I shouldn't mention the fact that shooting stars burn out in a flash...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Aw, yeah! Here we goooooo! Three! Two! One! To the stratosphere and beyond! Yeah! I feel alive now! You can go ahead and ask me anything you want!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is that really all it takes?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you have no memory at all of the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... I'm so ashamed. My memory of the time is as black and clouded as a dark nebula.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Still, it's strange you don't remember a thing. Are you sure you didn't take one of those anti-anxiety pills like they said at the trial?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Y-You got it all wrong! I told 'em during the investigation, too! I don't know anything about any drugs! I never took any medication, I swear!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">It IS true I developed a fear of space because of what happened seven years ago... And I was taking medication secretly every now and then when my anxiety got bad. Having a fear of space is not something an astronaut can brag about, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, the so-called "HAT-1 Miracle"? <thought>That must've been a terrifying experience...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">But I'm still an astronaut at heart, come what may. I would never take drugs that might impede my performance just before a launch. That launch meant everything to me. That's more certain than the theory of relativity!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He seems like a completely different person now. This is the face of the astronaut I know.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">But the tranquilizers were found in your system.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... Yeah, see, that's the thing. But I don't know why! I'm done for...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you didn't take them, then maybe somebody slipped them to you?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Exactly! That's what I thought! It must have been the real culprit!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">My medication was in my locker. Anybody could've gotten their hands on it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe the real culprit also planted the detonator switch in your pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Yeah. That's gotta be it! I've been framed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll say. They even managed to plant your prints on the switch before slipping it in.</thought> It's a real possibility. Do you remember anything else that might be relevant? Anything at all, no matter how small. Like, about the murder weapon, for example.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Hmm... That knife... I think it came from one of the Space Center's utility kits.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Utility kits?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Yeah. Staff who work on machinery a lot are given these special tool kits to use. All the technicians have them, so I doubt you could prove whose knife it is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As I recall, your last trip into space was seven years ago, right?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">That's right. It was... a pretty rough experience... During that mission, we had all kinds of problems with the craft.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You did? What kind of problems?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Power failure, oxygen leakage, busted radio, cracked windows, loose control column... The heat shield came off as we were entering the atmosphere. I thought I was a goner. But I managed to make it somehow with the popsicles and ice packs from the freezer.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No wonder they dubbed it the HAT-1 Miracle... It's a miracle you made it back!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Space is a boundless place. That's why it continues to capture people's imaginations. But the vastness of space shows us how insignificant we are in the scheme of things. The darkness just goes on and on forever, and ever, and ever... without end. There was nobody else there. Nobody was gonna come same me. I was all alone. All alone, with nothing to listen to but the sound of my own breathing and heartbeat. I kept scrambling to make repairs, but I couldn't keep my hands from shaking...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>An experience like that would make anybody afraid to go up into space...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">With the experience you had, weren't you dreading this mission?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">What? No way. O-Of course not... Even now, I wanna go up into space so bad, I can barely stand it. I wanna shake off the Earth's gravity at escape velocity and spin around weightless!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But you have to admit it was pretty harrowing. Weren't you even a tiny bit afraid?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">............I was afraid. Of course I was! Still am! But space is man's final frontier -- an unknown world. The cosmic truth is out there waiting for us somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The cosmic truth, huh? <thought>I guess there are people looking for the truth in every walk of life.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">No matter how afraid I am, I'm sure I can manage! If I give in to my fear, I'll never find the truth! As long as I don't give up, I can keep up the fight!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>One thing's for sure: Mr. Starbuck's passion for space is undeniably the real deal.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim, Clay Terran... He was kind of like your protégé, wasn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Well, it wasn't a big exaggerated deal like master and apprentice or anything like that. But Clay did think of me as his mentor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The mentor and the protégé... What a combination they must have been...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... With his encouragement, I knew I could get over my fear and go back into space. But now...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Clay must've been very encouraging, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Yeah. It's funny, really. Whenever I'd hear him shout, "You're fine!"... ...I always got the feeling everything really WAS gonna be just fine.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"You're fine!"...? Apollo says "I'm fine!" and "You're fine!" all of the time, too! And I always feel encouraged, too, whenever I hear him shout it!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Yeah, Clay and Apollo were best buds. They used to come visit the Space Center a lot, ever since they were high school kids. One day, out of the blue, Clay even told me he wanted to be my protégé. Those two hung around the Space Center so much, they were like a part of the staff. One time during zero-G training, I started to panic a little bit... ...and the two of them took turns shouting "You're fine!" over the radio. It was a simple thing, but it was exactly what I needed to hear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So "I'm fine!" and "You're fine!" were like Apollo and Clay's secret phrases, huh? I wish I could ask Apollo more about Clay and their relationship now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Speaking of Clay... ...how do you suppose he climbed down the ladder with you over his shoulder?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... Sorry, but I can't even begin to imagine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But he actually did climb down that ladder, so a way has to exist.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what do you think about this?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... The evidence is gonna get me convicted...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, no! It's my attorney's badge! I was hoping it would reassure you that we're here to defend you. Evidence isn't just for the prosecution. It can help prove a person's innocence, too.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">...Ha ha ha. That's a positive spin on things.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I thought that was common knowledge.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Clay always used to cheerfully greet me in a loud voice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And he did vocal exercises every morning, sometimes until he was hoarse, right?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Exactly. You could always hear him, even through the wall -- Hey, wait a minute. Did you know Clay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, but like attracts like, as they say.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Clay carried me out and saved me... But after all that... ...to be killed with this blade... Unnnh... And the fact that the killer might be me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Now he's got you sighing, Boss...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know anything about this piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">No... Sorry I'm so useless... Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no. It's all right. There's no need to get all depressed!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... From the freedom of space to the walls of a cell... But that prosecutor said the dark, night sky isn't half bad through barred windows.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............You're fine! Solomon "Sol" Starbuck is fine! Everything is going to be all right!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And Athena Cykes is fine! C'mon, Mr. Wright! You, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Do I really have to...?</thought> Phoenix Wright is fine...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can't heeeeeeear youuuuuuu!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ph-Phoenix Wright is fine!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We'll get you back into space yet, Mr. Starbuck! Believe in your own innocence, and have faith in us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apollo believed in you wholeheartedly, and that's good enough for me. I believe in you, too!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">............Thank you. Thank you, both of you. I'll put my faith in you. And I vow to make it back into space! All I need first is a "not guilty" verdict!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It sure feels nice to reassure ourselves every now and then that we're all fine.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, Mr. Wright! Let's get our investigation of the Space Center started! Pronto!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good idea. Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You went to visit Apollo in the hospital, right? How was he?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He seemed to be doing well. He was doing his Chords of Steel exercises in his room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha! I guess he's pretty gung-ho to get back to work. Was he shouting stuff like "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>" and "I'm fine!"?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No... He was yelling... ..."Thank you for coming to visit me!" and "Thank you, doctor, for taking care of me!" ...and stuff like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I guess those voice workouts can be pretty flexible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Notice anything, Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What do you mean, Daddy? Is your attorney's badge somehow different? Did you bend it out of shape or something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha, it's not that easy to bend something so small out of shape, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... Then, did you change your hairstyle? Or maybe it's your suit? I don't know. You look like you always do to me, Daddy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That really wasn't what I was asking...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I guess presenting your attorney's badge... ...is like your "quick trick," huh, Daddy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha. So it's just a trick to you, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, you are one of the talents in our Wright Anything Agency, after all. But I have to say that an attorney's badge won't get many laughs...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't care if I don't get laughs, as long as I can clear my client's name.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ha ha ha! That's a good one, Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm no match for you, though, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy, you should be careful about showing evidence to a magician.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's true. You can make anything disappear.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, anything up to about a yard in diameter, anyway. My magic panties are an extra-dimensional space!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess only a space probe can help us figure out how they work then, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow. I was wondering what kind of place this space center would be. It almost looks like an amusement park of the future.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah! Did you know they even let the public see their rockets up close? Oh! So, check it out! Look at how brightly the GYAXA logo shines in the sunlight above the entranceway! I really dig the stars and rocket motif it's got going!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">GYAXA, huh? Isn't that the new name of the federal space R&amp;D program?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, but why the strange acronym? I mean, what is GYA supposed to stand for? Galaxy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If that were it, then the whole thing would be something like "Galaxy eXploration Agency"... ...which, if you ask me, I'd have abbreviated to GAXA... or even GAEA.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... I guess so... Oh, I know! Maybe the person who came up with the name just really likes the letter Y!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This exchange is beginning to feel oddly like déjà vu...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Anyway, this place is more than just a research facility; it's also a tourist attraction!</line>
<line speaker="???">Tourist attraction? Don't make me laugh! It's a monument to the human race! Galactic Scooter, full speed ahead!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yikes! Who's this geezer and what's he want...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Look upon me, and look well! Behold the great power of space science!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pardon me, but you are...?</line>
<line speaker="???">My glorious name is Yuri Cosmos! I am the director of the Cosmos Space Center, the "center of the cosmos"!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Boss... That was pretty groan-inducing...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If this person is the Space Center's director, then that means...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aha! So you were one of the first to discover Clay's body, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And who was the first to find the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Actually, there were two of them!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The Space Center director... ...Yuri Cosmos... and Detective Candice Arme.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">That is correct! I was honored to be the very first man in all of space and time to discover the body. But this talk of the incident... Are you by any chance... the space police?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You can't tack the word "space" onto just any old thing, you know.</thought> We're Mr. Starbuck's lawyers. We're here to investigate this case.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, and we're Earth lawyers, by the way.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Ah, I see. Yes, I've heard about you. In that case, by my esteemed privilege, I grant you permission to investigate. I trust you are appropriately grateful. Now, go ahead! Have at it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can already tell he's going to be nothing but trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't let him hear you say that or you'll see what trouble really is. Let's just be professional and ask him about when he found the body, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, as director, what do you do here at the Space Center, specifically?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Defend peace across the galaxy and promote space development in this country. No matter what obstacles stand in our way, we keep going... for the sake of mankind!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh, I believe I used the word "specifically" in my question...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Attention all personnel! To your break stations! Prepare for break!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, I get it! You just wander around and tell people what to do in a self-important manner!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">That is exactly right! Because I am an important man, my manner is important!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright, this man doesn't get sarcasm.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, there's bound to be some people like that, here in the boundlessness of space.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">What's that? You want to know what it is that makes me important, specifically? Very well! I will tell you! I was THE central figure of the HAT-1 Project! You may proceed to be appropriately impressed. Now, go ahead! Have at it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I might be more impressed if I knew what he did for it... specifically.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell us what you know about the incidents from the other day?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Hmm............ I refuse!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Explaining is a job for common folk, not the director of the center of the cosmos! My testimony -- which will go down in space history -- will be heard in the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? So does that mean you'll be taking the stand tomorrow?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">That is correct! I will be the most glorious witness in the history of mankind!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not sure he really understands what being a "witness" is all about...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Looks like Director Cosmos is the type that only talks about what he wants to talk about.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then let's at least try to ask him about the things he might be willing to open up about.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The HAT-1 was a rocket that was launched into space seven years ago, correct? And despite numerous problem, it somehow made its way back home...?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">...Hm. I suppose it IS part of my job to educate ignorant young folk like you. Very well! I will impart to you the complete story of the HAT-1 Project!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, uh, thank you very much.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">HAT-1's noble mission was to collect samples from an asteroid! And Mr. Starbuck was the pilot for that flight. Eventually, the HAT-1 reached its planned orbit... ...from where it launched the Hope probe towards the asteroid belt! From there, the Hope probe began its long, lonely journey into the far reaches of space! Then, after a terrifying struggle, the HAT-1 returned safely to Earth.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That struggle was when the incident known as the HAT-1 Miracle occurred, right?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Correct. And it truly was a miracle. Of course, they just had to turn the ordeal into a movie. As for the Hope probe, it did eventually arrive safely at its destination! It obtained a few samples from the asteroid, and returned to Earth but a few days ago!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what kind of samples are they? What's in them?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">............The samples are scheduled for analysis in the near future. We haven't had time, since they just came back the day before Terran's murder. Regrettably, we've had no time to inspect the samples due to everything that has occurred. But this puts our space development program ahead of other countries by several years!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's quite impressive. <thought>I guess this guy isn't just a loud-mouthed braggart after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">In the golden age of space development... ...our predecessors were successful in bringing a moon rock back. That is the greatest achievement in the history of this space center! The public fell in love with space and all of its glorious potential.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A moon rock, huh? I remember that being big.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Our endeavours with the moon rock lives on in our work with those asteroid samples! I want to bestow new hopes and dreams for the future upon mankind once again! That is my mission, as the man who stands at the center of the cosmos!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I hear there's lots of research into moon rocks and star dust from asteroids these days. They say the results could potentially have a huge impact on all of civilization! It's like we're in a new space race with every other country out there.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">What?! Bite your tongue! It's not for anything so base as money or politics! It's all for the brilliant future that awaits mankind! And all for... my illustrious mission! With the recent budget cuts, my staff tells me finances are tight, but I won't hear it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I guess even a space program has to watch its budget...</thought> By the way, you seem awfully knowledgeable about this kind of thing, Athena...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? Oh, w-well, you know... I thought I'd better brush up... for the case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that so...?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">What a shame. Truly. Clay was so young... He was an outstanding man who could have contributed greatly to the future of mankind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He was an exceptional man, wasn't he.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">If he had gone into space, my reputation would have grown even loftier! Why did he have to die before he went into space?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Someone needs to teach him he is not the literal center of the cosmos...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, but about this piece of evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Let me ask YOU a question. What will that object contribute to the future of mankind?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? Uh, not much, I guess...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Hmph. Then how important could it be? Quite unlike the great historical figure, Yuri Cosmos! Ha ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If he's any more self-absorbed, he'll turn into his very own black hole.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Well, I will be on my way. As you can see, I am a very busy, and very important man! Galactic Scooter! Fire up the main engine! Max battle speed! And... engage!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That thing is surprisingly fast.</thought> I guess we'd better get going, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You bet! Let's make it so!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena Cykes is fine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What was that all about?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I thought I'd better get fired up twice as much, to make up for Apollo being gone! For starters, I thought I'd imitate him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you were doing a voice workout, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yup! You have to push your voice up from the pit of your stomach! <cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> There's a contradiction in the witness's statement!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're really serious about this.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn> You are lying! The true culprit is... the judge!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! Then who's going to hand down the verdict?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh. I didn't think of that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what do you think we should do next?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, that's right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I just remembered I forgot to go running today. I was so taken up with what happened to Apollo, it slipped my mind!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, that wasn't what I was asking.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">My badge is starting to look pretty good on me, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It suits you well.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm starting to feel like it gives me more dignity and presence, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think she might be expecting a little too much from one tiny little badge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">All right. Let's see. I'm getting the sense... ...that you are perplexed by this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, well... I guess that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You see? Even the simple act of presenting evidence reveals your underlying emotions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess I'd better be careful when I present evidence, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this is where Mr. Terran was murdered...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, this is the lounge. Let's see that diagram the police made again. Right now we're in the main building here on the right side, on the third floor. Clay and Mr. Starbuck fled here from Launch Pad 1 after the explosion.</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">You there! No admittance without express permission!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We're Mr. Starbuck's lawyers. We've come to investigate...</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Sorry! Nobody gets in without permission. Not even the police superintendent! Can't have Detective Fulbright getting mad at me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So Detective Fulbright is here, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Yeah, he's in the Launch Pad 1 Corridor. Go get clearance from him, and then we'll talk!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leave it to me! I'm great at getting intel out of Detective Fulbright! Let's see. What trick should I use on him today?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't know if I should be grateful or afraid.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So... to get to the Launch Pad 1 Corridor... ...we just have to go through that door with the blue rocket on it, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait. That door... It looks awfully familiar...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Good eye there, Boss. This is the door Clay and Mr. Starbuck used during their escape from the launch pad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, that explains it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The fingerprint system has been deactivated, so I think we can just pass through. Now, come on! Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this is it, huh? This is the corridor the two of them used in their escape.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yup. This is the only thing connecting Launch Pad 1 with the main building.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see police tape down at the other end. Guess we won't be looking at the launch pad.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">After the explosion, this whole corridor must've been filled with smoke.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the launch pad itself was probably a sea of flames. Must've been pretty scary for them.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Now, where could Detective Fulbright be...? Hey, I think that's him over there!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hmm... What should I do? Which path is the path of justice...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He seems to be lost... That's funny. This corridor is a straight shot.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">...Huh? Ah, it's you lawyer people! Welcome to the Space Center! Enjoying a relaxing day off, are you? Here for a little rocket sightseeing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We're here to investigate the scene, same as you. Do you have any info to share?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Boss, if he acts at all reluctant to give us information... ...we hit him with the "Whatever shall we do?" act! I'm sure he'll fall for it! Got it?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Are we trying to catch the unruly family dog here or something?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Info on the case, huh? .........All right! I'll gladly share some with you!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? What just happened?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Detectives and lawyers, seeking truth and justice side by side! I like it! Just take whatever you want from me, you info bandits! I'm in a generous mood today!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I dunno... There's something weird about Detective Fulbright today...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, we need information, so let's run with it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If you say so...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Fulbright, could you give us permission to investigate the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There's an office on guard, and we can't get in. Oh, whatever shall we do?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's an easy one! I'll let them know over there to let you in! Investigate to your heart's content! Take a week if you need it! A month, even! Shall I have some snacks delivered? One of my men gives a mean neck rub!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, no... that's okay. But thanks. <thought>Definitely NOT the Fulbright I know...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Detective Fulbright is acting sickeningly sweet. It's kinda gross, actually. Do you think he hit his head or something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who knows. Whatever the case, it's making our lives way easier.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were here at the Space Center at the time of the incidents, weren't you, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's right! I was here on a security assignment!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The police are required to secure rocket launches now! I didn't know that.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">U-Um, yes. Well, you know us! To serve and protect! Ha ha ha ha! The explosions occurred while I was here on duty, so I started leading the evacuation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's leaving out a lot of details, but okay...</thought> Could you tell us more about what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Of course! A bomb went off on the second floor of the main building. Right after that, the one over in Launch Pad 1 also blew sky high. So I immediately instructed the visitors and the employees to evacuate to the shelter!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The shelter...?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's right! There's an evacuation shelter in the basement of the Space Center. It's there for accidents and emergencies and the like!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So where were you when the first bomb went off?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">I was on duty on the fourth floor. It was quite the madhouse, I tell you! The elevator wasn't working, on account of the explosion... ...and the stairs on the second floor were destroyed, so we couldn't go that way.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Then wasn't it impossible to get down to the basement shelter?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">No. We lowered an emergency ladder from a fourth floor window and escaped that way. It was a folding ladder, so it wasn't very stable, but at least it reached the ground! After I secured the ladder, I left to take another look around for any other survivors. Once everyone else got out safely, I made my way down, too, and headed to the shelter.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, what an ordeal...! But climbing down an emergency ladder kinda sounds fun!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you for your answers. Detective. They were very helpful.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Just a moment! I have some more information to share with you! But don't tell Prosecutor Blackquill, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, and Prosecutor Blackquill usually has you on a short leash, too...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well, never mind that! Ha ha! I thought you should know that there was a witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell us more about this witness?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Sure thing! The witness was a Space Center employee who was on the fourth floor. While she was climbing down, she looked through a window into the third floor lounge.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So... she was looking into the crime scene from the outside?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's right! It was just a matter of chance that she saw something important. Not that I know what she saw exactly yet, though.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You don't? But that's the most important thing of all...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! Don't you worry! I'll get around to interviewing her soon enough! She should still be somewhere here in the Space Center. You might even run into her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A fourth-floor employee, huh? All right. Thanks for the info, Detective Fulbright!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">The victim went to all that trouble to save the defendant... ...and then he was mercilessly killed! Is there no justice in this world?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Justice was trampled underfoot that day.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's right. Acts of justice and selflessness are not always rewarded... It pains me to say it, but I've come to realize the truth in that recently.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like he and his personal philosophy are going through a mid-life crisis.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">When the explosions occurred, everyone was on the verge of panic. But the important thing is that no one from the general public was hurt. And it was all thanks to the evacuation effort we headed up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">After that, you escaped the building yourself as well, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know you wanted to help, but it sounds like you were adding work to your fellow officers.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Something for the lost and found? I'll be sure to take care of it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, no! This is an important piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Gee, you sure are being cooperative, Detective. A little TOO cooperative, even...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yes, well... Actually... I...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something you can't talk about...?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yes, something like that. Anyway, never mind! Don't worry about me! W-Well, I'll be on my way, now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was that all about?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Something is definitely going on. I'm going to get it out of him the next time I see him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Okay... <thought>I'm not so sure he'll talk about it, though.</thought> Well, we have permission to investigate now. Let's head back to the boarding lounge.</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Ah, you two! Detective Fulbright has granted you permission to investigate! He also said I should bring you some snacks or give you a neck rub, too, if you'd like...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, uh, that's all right. But thank you for the offer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, time to roll up our sleeves and start investigating. Now, let's see... Where's that diagram again? So, this lounge is on the third floor of the main building. And according to Apollo, this is where he believes a third party killed his friend.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, let's stop the recap and start looking for traces of this third person then!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You read my mind, Athena. We'll make that our first priority. There's just one problem, though. This room... It's just so big...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't worry, we can use this to help us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A Space Center pamphlet? For tourists?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yup! Picked it up at the entrance. The maps inside should come in handy! Let's see... Yup. Here it is. A map of the lounge. This is the door we went through to talk to Detective Fulbright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh yeah. That's the door with the fingerprint recognition lock. Well, I guess this map will make things a little easier.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah! No more excuses! Let's track down the third person!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Wait. There's just one more thing. What's that strange creature moving around outside the window?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, Boss... It's just a holographic image.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, yeah. I knew that. <thought>Whew, that's a relief.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">There should be a button somewhere in this room to turn the image on and off. That's what it says in the pamphlet, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The only reason you're so eager to start is so that you can push that button, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And what's wrong with that? Let's just look for the button while we're looking for clues.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. Fine. Let's get investigating!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A window. And it's right next to the holographic image, too. I bet it's here to help people see the stark contrast between reality and virtual reality.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Way off. It says, "Emergency Ventilation." You know, to clear smoke from a fire.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">See? It's pointing out the virtual insanity of reality!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So it looks like there are three doors that lead in and out of this room.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, let's check... Drum roll, please! Ta-da! The Space Center pamphlet. We're here, at this place that says "Boarding Lounge 1." Here are the three doors. Hmm, let's call them "Lefty," "Righty," and "Downy."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">People usually say "west," "east," and "south" in a case like this, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Details, details. Anyway, take a look at the west door. That door with the rocket icon leads to Launch Pad 1! I know because it says here on the map "Launch Pad 1 Corridor."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that's where we were with the detective. It was filled with smoke after the explosion.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right. Next up! The right-hand side of the map, or "east," in your world. That's the door with the satellite dish icon to signify communication, aka, the control room!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup, it definitely says "Control Room." Looks like it has another door on the opposite side.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">They communicate and exchange information with rockets and probes in space from there. So, it's the "center" of the Space Center... The "Space Center Center," if you will.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Does everybody start to talk like Director Cosmos after they've been here a while?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">But, it seems that they built a new Command Center on the sixth floor. That's what they used for the HAT-2 mission, so this Control Room was empty at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've always wanted to see the inside of a mission control room, and since we're here...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'd love to do that too, but it doesn't look like we'll be able to. They want to keep curious kids like you out... ...so the door is protected with fingerprint recognition. Only the director can go through.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>With that much security, I'm definitely not the one they're looking to keep out, Athena.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So apparently, the lock is also hooked up to a backup generator in case of emergencies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay. What about that last door?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This lower door... Oh, excuse me. I mean, "South door"? It leads to the elevators!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the door we came through when we entered this room, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yup. And, of course, there was no fingerprint recognition device, so it's open to anyone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the elevators weren't working at the time due to the explosion...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, that's about it for the Three Muskedoors of the boarding lounge!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks. Understanding the layout of the lounge should help us understand the case. That's why I thought we'd better have a good grasp of where all the doors go.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this is where they discovered Clay.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah. He was already dead when they found him. Let's take a look at the photo.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So he was stretched out like this and... Huh? What's that thing that looks like a thermos?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's the thing that Prosecutor Blackquill mentioned when I was in court with Apollo. He said that it contains asteroid samples.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right. Director Cosmos mentioned something about that too, didn't he? That they were brought back only five days ago by the probe that the HAT-1 launched.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wonder what they look like... Do you think they'll let us see?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's think about that after we've solved the case, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At first glance, it looks like a peaceful landscape, but then there's that creature...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Didn't the Hope probe go to some planet? Maybe this is what its surface looked like.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I dunno. I think it would've made the news if they discovered a creature like that.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It did make quite a bit of news, though, when the probe came back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... But the Hope probe didn't even go to a planet. It went to an asteroid. That's a big rock kind of thing. Even aliens can't live there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A bright, purple sky, plenty of greenery, and a tranquil lake. The idyllic scene stretches on as far as the eye can see. It's beautiful, but it lacks something to make it truly captivating.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's some pretty futuristic-looking furniture over there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">According to the pamphlet, those are no ordinary chairs. They're like amusement park tea cup rides. You can power them yourself, it says. If you spin the table, your chair spins, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why would anybody want to have something like that here?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's for astronauts who have trouble with the device on the ceiling. No vertical spins... It says it's a training device that's easy on the eyes and on the body.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Can a person really call themselves an astronaut if they can't handle zero-g?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be the security camera that recorded the astronauts making their escape.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, let's commemorate this occasion with a... Love and Peace!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you're done now, shall we move on?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, okay... But just one more for the road! Peeeaaace!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Very mature.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These are apparently "oxygen capsules." They're for recovery after a training session.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wonder if they can change your voice? Testing, testing, one, two, three... Huh? It didn't do a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, it's not helium, Athena. It's oxygen.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, a mirror! How thoughtful of them to put one here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thoughtful?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So the ladies can fix their makeup! One's appearance is just as important in space as it is on Earth, you know! You never know when you're going to run into some other life form, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I doubt anybody who thinks like that would ever become an astronaut in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's some kind of panel with two buttons on it here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"Just push it!" That's the invariable principle of buttons!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There are such things as buttons left unpushed...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey! The giant holographic image disappeared!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, though that side of the wall seems kind of barren without it now. Still, let's see if we can't find anything new with the image off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the button for the holographic image. If we push it... ...it apparently turns the image on and off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">With the holographic image off, the screen is completely black, which for some reason... ...makes me think of losing an argument to Prosecutor Blackquill in court. <thought>But at least it's got my brain revved up. I come up with my best ideas at times like these.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, Mr. Wright! Take a look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like a bullet hole. Great find, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's pretty big. Whoever fired this shot must have been using a pretty large gun.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You think so? Based on my experience, I'd say this was fired from a regular pistol.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, whatever size it was, somebody fired a gun in here, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apparently. This is an important fact. Do you see a bullet anywhere?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No. The police might've taken it, though.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's ask Detective Fulbright about this bullet hole later!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's see. This door is... Where's that pamphlet...? Here we are. It's the door to the corridor that leads to Launch Pad 1. We went through it earlier when we went to talk to Detective Fulbright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, I guess the security lock must be disengaged now, right? They say the corridor was filled with smoke at the time of the bombing. This thing beside the door... This must be the fingerprint recognition device.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Which reminds me! I think Prosecutor Blackquill talked about it at the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The notion of a third party in Launch Pad 1 is utterly absurd. Just to enter the area from the lounge... ...one must pass through a door guarded by a fingerprint recognition device. And allow me to state up front that there are precious few with the clearance to do so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then, does this mean that the bomber's prints were verified by the system? <thought>But the number of authorized personnel was supposed to be really small...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Voilà! Fingerprint powder! I brought it just in case something like this came up. I found it at the office. I've been just itching for a chance to use it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow. Way to think ahead! Now, let's dust the fingerprint recognition device and see what we can find.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You got it! Now to sprinkle some here, and a little over there, aaaaand... fwwwwph! Let's see what we have here......... Oh! We got something! ...Aww, it's only a single set of prints.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh, isn't that a good thing?</thought> Sure wish we could figure out whose prints these are. Although, I doubt we'll be so lucky as to get the culprit's prints on the first try.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I'm willing to bet that Detective Fulbright has some fingerprint data.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. And there's the security footage of this door, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, here it is. It came up in court the other day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wish we could see the part of the footage just after this bit.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, because that would be right before the murder, wouldn't it? Let's ask the detective. With the mood he's in, he'll probably show it to us right away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, he's in almost TOO good of a mood today...</thought> Let's go see if we can find him again once we're done with this room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this is the fingerprint recognition device. I guess you put your hand on this hand mark.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why guess when you can try! Now, to line my hand up with the outline...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't, Athena! This thing is related to the case! Get your prints all over that, and the next thing you know, you'll be named a suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Waaah! How can you be so cruel to a little girl like me?! *sniffle* *sob*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not buying those tears, missy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wonder what this big knob is for. It looks like the knob on a stove.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well it's the same shape, but I think that's where the similarities end. I mean, it's behind a glass pane. What kind of stove would require knob security like this?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, the knob is straight up and down. So if it was for a stove, the burner would be off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right, if it was for a stove... Still, I wonder what it's really for.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Something turned on by a knob that's NOT a stove?! Hmm... How about a rocket engine?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you had to start the engine here, the rocket would take off before you could get in.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Then I guess all we can say for now is that it's a mystery knob!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here's another amazing piece of equipment. "Walk on the surface of the moon," it says.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, boy! I wanna try it! Gravity is weak on the moon, so I bet I could do midair somersaults!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We're still on Earth, remember? Besides, it's connected to the ceiling.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, at least I could jump really high!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a sign on the wall that very clearly says, "Don't jump too high!"</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Then what good is this thing?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, didn't I say in the beginning, "Walk on the surface of the moon"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this? A trapdoor?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's a trash chute. The cleaning robots throws [sic] the garbage out from here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The robots do the cleaning? What a futuristic world we live in. I just hope they don't revolt like they do in science fiction movies.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No way. All the robots here are very nice. Actually, wasn't there one in the Launch Pad 1 corridor? We can go say "hi" to it if you want.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey! I see something shiny down there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's take this cover off, then.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's this? It looks like a metal jelly bean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's really small, but it's a bullet. It's only about two to three millimeters in diameter. Let's see, that would make the caliber... .10?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"Caliber" refers to the diameter of a gun's barrel, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. But I've never heard of a .10 caliber gun before. This bullet must be for a special kind of gun.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I bet if you tried firing a bullet this small with a regular-sized gun... ...it would just fall right out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, it must've been a really small gun.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wonder how the bullet ended up here? I mean, we're in the bottom left, on the South door side of the room, according to this map. That's pretty far from where Clay's body was. Maybe the police didn't think to look here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, leave it to Detective Fulbright to accidentally hand us just the card we need.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I still can't believe we spotted that bullet here. And it's so tiny, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess I have pretty sharp eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What are you talking about?! I'm the one who found it! Not you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right. Yeah, of course. <thought>Is that how it happened...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No matter how I look at it, all I can think of is "torture device." But I guess it's a training device for getting used to zero-gravity? <thought>Uh-oh. Athena has an odd glint in her eye... Is she thinking about trying that thing out? I should try to stop her... but I'm afraid she'll just out-muscle me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, Mr. Wright! Look at that up there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Some kind of fragment? It's stuck in tight... <thought>Oh, so that's what the glint was all about!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">That color looks familiar... I think it's part of an oxygen tank!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think you're right. But if that's here... ...it means Clay's tank ruptured AFTER they arrived at the boarding lounge.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So Prosecutor Blackquill's theory that Mr. Starbuck dropped Clay down the ladder... ...must be wrong! This proves that both of the astronauts were alive when they reached they boarding lounge!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, Apollo was right. The scene of the murder wasn't the launch pad.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hee hee! Way to go, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looks like we've examined pretty much everything here now, but just in case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you happen to know anything about this?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? That?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Any new ideas, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">O-Oh, I dunno! Ha ha ha ha ha! H-Hey, did you catch the game on TV last weekend?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? Why is she avoiding the topic?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Welcome to the Space Center, guests! Welcome!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yikes! Wh-What in the world?!</line>
<line speaker="???">My name is Ponco! P-O-N-C-O! Ponco! Are you sightseeing? Are you lost? Are you looking around? Choose one! I will guide you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-It's... a robot?</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">I am not a robot! I am Ponco! Psychological Observation and... ...Navigation COmpanion! P-O-N-C-O! Ponco!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I'm glad we got that cleared up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, Ponco! I've missed you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Do you know this thing, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, uh... She, uh... showed us around the last time, when I came here with Apollo. Oh, you're such a good girl, Ponco! That's a good girl!</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">Oh, thank you! Thank you! I'm so happy! So very happy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow, a guide robot. That's pretty cool. My name is Phoenix Wright. Nice to meet you.</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">I don't know you! I don't know you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? <thought>Ouch. That hurt.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, she has to register people she meets for the first time. Please register him, Ponco.</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">Certainly! Commencing guest registration! Please tell me your name. A nickname is fine, too!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">His name is "Phoenix."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A bit overly familiar, but I'll allow it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ponco">Phoenix, please let me get a good look at your face!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, uh, sure.</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">Registering... Facial registration sequence, complete! We are now officially friends! Nice to meet you, Phoenix!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh... This robot is pretty cute...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">You made a friend, Boss! Isn't it great?</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">Phoenix! Athena! Allow me to guide you! Right this way!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, goody! Let's go, Boss!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>G-Go where?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, wow! What IS this place?! Is... Is that rocket real?!</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">Welcome! Welcome! The Space Museum is open to the public every day of the year from 9 AM to 7 PM! Learn about the history of our nation's space development and the HAT-1 project! The rocket is just a replica, but it's the same size as the real one!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The Space Museum... Oh, here it is on the map.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, so it's on the exact opposite side of the main building from Launch Pad 1.</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">Ask me anything! Anything! I will explain!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is quite the place. I can't believe we get to see a rocket this close up.</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">This is a replica of the HAT-1 that was launched seven years ago! It's exactly like that real HAT-1, inside and out! Its little brother, the HAT-2, was supposed to launch the other day!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I wonder if Ponco knows why the launch was canceled.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ponco">Over there is an exhibit about the launch seven years ago! Check it out! Check it out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Space suits, photos, newspaper articles... I'd like to come here again on a day off. ...Hey, what's this a photo of?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ponco">Phoenix! That's the staff of the HAT-1 project!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, there's Mr. Starbuck! He looks so young, and so different.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ah! And that's... That's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it, Athena? Is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! N-Nothing... I... just thought Mr. Starbuck looked really young, too, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it was seven years ago, after all. So the young guy standing next to Mr. Starbuck...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Is Clay Terran... The victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So they were mentor and protégé even way back then... And he's even got one of the staff jackets. He looks just like a regular staff member.</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">No! Clay was still a student then! He just borrowed one of Solomon's old jackets.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, okay. That makes sense. Clay would've still been in high school seven years ago. <thought>Everybody looks so happy.</thought> This Space Museum is great! What fantastic exhibits!</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">This area used to be Launch Pad 2. That's why the only entrance is on the third floor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wouldn't it be better if they just made a new ground-floor entrance instead?</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">There was talk of it, but they had to scrap their plans because of the budget cuts. Budget cuts! Budget cuts! We need more money! Money!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who would record that kind of information into a guide robot?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ponco">While it was in space, the HAT-1 launched a probe called "Hope." The Hope probe collected some samples from an asteroid and returned five days ago!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's what Director Cosmos said, too. He told us it came back the day before Clay was killed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ponco">And here it is. The Hope space probe!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I think I've seen that logo somewhere before. Let's see... Oh yeah, the capsule that the victim was carrying... I think it had the same logo... I think it can be seen in the photo attached to the autopsy report. Maybe she'll give me some more info if I show it to her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ponco">The way the Space Center launch pad is set up is really cool! Would you like me to tell you about it? Would you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The setup of the launch pad? <thought>Go gentle on my spiky-haired mind...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I want to know! I want to know! Phoenix wants to know, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great. Now Athena's got a case of Ponco-itis.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ponco">Hooray! I will tell you, then! The rocket is built right inside the launch pad structure. When the rocket is complete, it's moved along with the launch pad over the rails... ...and brought into position at the launch site! Isn't it cool? Isn't it? We used to have a big budget, so that's how we could build it all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's very cool. A grand setup that suits an important place like the Space Center. <thought>I guess everyone is hoping for a bigger budget next year... Myself included.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm guessing the whole thing is operated from the Control Room, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">That it is! But it can also be operated from the new Command Center, too! Either way, the safety lock in the boarding lounge has to first be disengaged!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess before a big move like that can be carried out, there are all kinds of procedures.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I would love to see the launch pad being moved! When's the next one scheduled for?</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">Searching data............ All future plans have been put on hold.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Because of the bombing and the murder, I'll bet... which is perfectly understandable.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, when was the last time it was moved?</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">Searching data........................ I'm sorry. I'm sorry. That answer isn't in my answer database.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess Ponco can only answer certain questions.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ponco, do you recognize this capsule here in the top right?</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">Checking registered data.........&#160;! I know! I know! It's the Hope capsule! It was carried inside the Hope probe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It contained the asteroid samples, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">Yes! It was designed to store the samples gathered by the Hope probe. It's been stored in the safe in Launch Pad 1 ever since it returned to Earth. It must not be removed! It must not be removed!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't worry, Ponco. The people in charge already know what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">They do? They do? I must ask them later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the capsule was being kept in Launch Pad 1, huh? Maybe Clay was trying to carry it to safety after the explosion...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The Space Center staff must've been really excited to finally get the capsule back. But it's a pity this incident occurred before they got a chance to check the contents.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, the police took it as evidence, so they'll have to wait a little longer.</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">The capsule from the space probe "Hope"! The probe separated from the HAT-1 in space and went to an asteroid! It took seven years, but it found its way back to Earth a few days ago! Welcome home!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can't believe you still don't remember -- you say, "It's back!" not "Welcome home!"</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">It's back! It's back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, why do you know what she was taught?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? Oh, uh... when I came here with Apollo... I heard a member of the staff teach her...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I can't help but think I'm missing something here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ponco">This facility is Yuri Cosmos's greatest achievement!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? I didn't realize it was the personal achievement of just one man.</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">Director Cosmos taught me to say it like that. It's actually a facility for space development, but don't tell anyone I said that!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">How could Director Cosmos teach such a pure and innocent little robot to lie for him?</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">I'm sorry. I'm afraid I don't know anything about that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, okay. No problem.</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry! I wasn't helpful! I'll try to do better in the future! Please don't hate me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The poor thing. Now I feel bad for asking...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, we certainly learned a lot about the Space Museum.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thank you, Ponco. You explained everything very well.</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">I love to explain! Thank you for listening! Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You two are like old friends. It's hard to believe you just met recently.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hee hee! It's because Ponco is so friendly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, what should we investigate next?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's go find Detective Fulbright! We have things to ask him about.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Let's see. The security footage and the fingerprint data, was it?</thought> Okay, then let's go back to the Launch Pad 1 corridor.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Bye, Ponco! See you later!</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">Come again! Come again! And don't forget to visit the gift shop!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Ponco... What a Dickensian life we are all forced to lead.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Space, huh... I'd sure love to go up there someday. Will you take me, Daddy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha. It's not like taking somebody to an amusement park, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, you hardly ever take me to one of those, either! You either say, "I don't have any money" or "I don't have time"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">F-Fine. I'll take you on my next day off.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You're the best, Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha. <thought>I'm no match for Trucy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hmm... What should I do? Which path is the path of justice...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There's Detective Fulbright! He still seems to be lost, even though it's a straight corridor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's hope he's still in a cooperative mood as well, then.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If he doesn't cooperate, then I'll just have to use my powers on him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...You mean that "lady in distress" bit?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We found a bullet hole in the wall at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">You did?! Our team found that, too! It was Detective Arme who fired that bullet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Arme?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's right! A warning shot for the defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was it really such a high-threat situation that she needed to do that?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">I'm afraid I don't know the details, what with Detective Arme gone and all...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But I thought there were two people who discovered the crime scene together?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We already know Director Cosmos will testify, so tomorrow will be about what he knows...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hey, you're pretty smart! That's exactly what we're planning to serve as the main course!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I hope it goes down easy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Detective, we'd like to run a comparison on some prints we found in the boarding lounge.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ah, yes! I just happened to have compiled the print data of everyone related to this case! I can always make another copy for myself, so it's all yours! Consider it a gift.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This... is quite a bit of data.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well, when I said "everyone," I meant it! Prosecutor Blackquill said to dig deep, so that's what I did! It sure took a while, though!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whoa, he got Apollo and my prints... He even got prints for all of the robots...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess when Blackquill said to dig deep, Fulbright didn't bother to ask how deep...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ah! Clay's fingerprints are here, too!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">I personally removed his glove during the investigation. We had to get his fingerprints to confirm his identity, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I still can't believe you took off his glove to get his fingerprints...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yeah, well, you can't blame me for thinking they're important in this case. There are a lot of doors that require fingerprint verification in the lounge. So depending on whose prints we find, it can completely change the tide for both sides!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Makes sense. After all, the culprit's prints did get them past the fingerprint lock somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Oh! And take this picture. It might come in handy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't this just a photo of the Launch Pad 1 door?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yup. But Prosecutor Blackquill seemed really interested in it for some reason.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What's so important about this door?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Beats me, but boy could you see the gears in his head go into hyperdrive at it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like this is going to be a major point of contention tomorrow...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, don't forget about the print comparison, Boss!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. Detective Fulbright, do you think you could run the test for us right now?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">You just leave it to me! In justice we trust!!! Okay, here we go. Well, it looks like it was Mr. Starbuck who opened that security door.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He must've opened it when they went to go board the rocket.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">His heart must've been full of hopes and dreams for his space adventure right then...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective, about the security footage that was taken by the Boarding Lounge 1 camera...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Oh, that footage? Go ahead and ask me anything you'd like about it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is there any way I could see a little more of the part just after this?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Easy as pie! I'd be glad to show you! Here we go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? The screen went blank.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yes. Apparently, the aftereffects of the explosion damaged the wires. So there's no footage after this point. Ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why didn't you just say so from the beginning?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something definitely seems to be up with you, Detective. You're unusually cooperative.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well, I just figure if we work together, we'll get that much closer to justice, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But it seems like something's really been bothering you. You don't have some ulterior motive, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">What? I don't know what you're talking about! I would never do anything like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's been a while... but those are definitely Psyche-Locks...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hm? Did you just mouth "Psyched"? Is there something I should be psyched about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no. "Psyche-Lock." It's a system of locks on the secrets in a person's heart. I can see when people are trying to hide those secrets by using the power of this Magatama. <thought>Presenting evidence can break those locks... ...and reveal any secrets they're hiding.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">M-Mr. Wright... How much did they bilk you out of for that piece of rock? If you've been swindled, I know some lawyers I can introduce you to!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm more than capable of representing myself, thank you very much.</thought> It isn't some kind of fraud. It really works. A friend gave it to me a long time ago. But I guess seeing is believing. Allow me to show you! <thought>I can use the Magatama on him by touching it (X</thought>.)</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Detective Fulbright sure is in an oddly eager mood today. Still, something seems to be bothering him...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As long as you're being forthcoming, why don't you share what's bothering you with us?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well! That would be... Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You seem very torn. It has something to do with the case, doesn't it? Oh, whatever shall we do? The detective has a secret, but he won't tell us!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Oh, no! There's a lady in distress! And yet...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh. That didn't work. Usually he'd be telling us anything we wanted to know by now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah... But what kind of detective does that? I guess now's the time to use my Magatama (X</thought> and undo these Psyche-Locks.)</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">2 PSYCHE-LOCKS</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think you're hiding something, Detective, so why don't you just tell us about it?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hmm... What to do? Which path is the path of justice...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Detective Fulbright is really in agony. I bet this is the issue he's so torn up over...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet I know why you're troubled. You're exhausted by the rollercoaster known as life!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Th-That's exactly right! I'm troubled by life in general. I've been thinking about quitting the force and going into space. Yup, you hit it right on the head! Ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...More like I hit my thumb on that one. All right, let's try that again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet I know what's bothering you. You're troubled by love!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Wh-What?! How did you know?! I put my pet carp "Love" in with my goldfish, and the next thing I knew... ...all the little goldfish were gone! Love had eaten them all! *sob* My poor little goldfishies! *sniffle* Oh, I loved you so!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess Love really CAN cause a lot of heartache, huh. Anyway...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I really understand what's been bothering you, Detective. I truly do. Something happened that goes against your principles, isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">U-Uh, no... I don't know what you're talking about... Until the explosions occurred, everything was just fine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that a fact?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yup! Peaceful as peaceful can be! Everyone whistling a happy tune as they did their job. You never saw a more relaxed guard detail for a routine rocket launch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think the guard detail was as "relaxed" as you claim as long as this exists.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Fulbright:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is he making fun of me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">It's just as I said. Until the explosions occurred, everything was just fine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Before the explosions, what was supposed to happen here was a rocket launch. And yet security was so tight they even brought in a special task force. I'd hardly describe that as a "relaxed guard detail."</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hmrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">N-Now hold on just one moment! The entire nation had their eyes on this extremely important rocket launch! That's why I was called in on a special security detail!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As versatile as you are, I can certainly believe that's true. But I say it's very strange that THIS person would be part of that detail from the outset!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Fulbright:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Unh... I guess I got it wrong...</thought> Never mind my hairstyle! All right. So you were here on a special security detail...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Arme specialized in bomb cases. The fact that she was here on-hand... ...means that you people knew there was the possibility that a bombing would occur.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">HMMMMMMMMMM! You got me, Mr. Wriiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiight!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">All right. I concede. You win. It's just as you say. A few days before the launch, they were warned about a potential bombing. But the plan to launch went ahead in spite of the threat.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But why?! What were they planning to do if someone got hurt or killed?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yeah, I know, I know... The decision to move forward wasn't exactly just, was it?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How was the warning delivered?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">By phone, and directly to Director Cosmos. But the police department instructed everybody to keep it under wraps.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a big thing to keep quiet about! No wonder you were so upset.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">But it's not only that. I've been distraught about Prosecutor Blackquill as well...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Prosecutor Blackquill? Well, as his "handler," I'm sure you have a lot of difficulties...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's not it. ...It's a question of justice! I've been wondering about... why he's allowed to stand in court...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The reason he's still prosecuting? Detective Fulbright? Please tell us everything you know!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well, talking to you folks about it would definitely be breaking the rules...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Never mind that! What are rules but things to be broken, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well, to tell you the truth, having a prisoner act as a prosecutor is highly irregular...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>............I think we guessed that much...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">So why is it being allowed? I've been wondering and wondering about it...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So you weren't told why, either, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">No. I guess the order came from pretty high up the ladder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, it would had to have...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">But Prosecutor Blackquill told me once... "The hunt I've been on for the phantom of seven years past continues even still."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Seven years past...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A phantom, huh... And not one of the friendly variety either, I gather.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This "phantom of seven years past"... Any idea who or what he was talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Not a clue... But he seems to think that this "phantom" is behind this whole incident somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait a minute. He thinks they may be connected to this case?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yup. This case has way too many similarities to what happened seven years ago. For starters, that case happened right here at this very Space Center, too. And in both incidents, a threat was issued via telephone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that's why Prosecutor Blackquill thinks this incident is the work of the "phantom"?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well, that's not the entire reason. I mean, if you wanna talk about seven years ago... ...that's when Prosecutor Blackquill was found guilty of murder. That messy case is what started the whole dark age of the law... So you see how this phantom and Prosecutor Blackquill's conviction might be related.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, I can see why he'd think that. <thought>This incident and the phantom... Not to mention Blackquill's past... It's almost inconceivable that they would come to a head here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um, this might sound crazy, but... Prosecutor Blackquill can't possibly believe Mr. Starbuck is this phantom person, right? I mean, he was acting kinda strange during the last trial and all...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The prosecution appears to be ready as well.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............ ............... ...Not yet. I'm... not quite ready yet.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ngh... Graaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">No, I doubt he thinks Mr. Starbuck is his phantom. But I do get the feeling that he thinks the defendant has ties to them. Which is why he's acting so impatient! He's got a personal grudge against Mr. Starbuck! And that's... not real justice! I've always trusted in Prosecutor Blackquill's judgment until now. But this time... I'm just so overwrought about it all. If he's lost his ability to think rationally, I'm afraid it might lead to a false conviction...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've never seen Detective Fulbright so tormented... This must be why he's been so cooperative.</thought> Don't worry. That's exactly what we defense lawyers are working to prevent.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">I feel bad for Prosecutor Blackquill, but I'm going to be rooting for your team this time. But don't tell him that... You have to promise me you won't!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Detective Fulbright... I guess I was wrong about you.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">I swore to reform Prosecutor Blackquill and make him a valued member of society again... ...so I can't just sit by and watch him give in to his emotions, and tear the defendant apart! You are the only ones who can stop him in court.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You really care and want what's best for Prosecutor Blackquill, don't you, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leave the courtroom to us. <thought>It's not like we want a guilty verdict, either!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">I was hoping you would say that! I'm really grateful to the two of you! To show my thanks, I'll give you another bit of information. It's about the eye-witness. I saw her hanging around the Space Center entrance a little while ago.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">R-Really?! Then let's go find her, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Thanks, you two. I feel a lot better now that I've been able to get that off my chest. I'm going to work extra hard to find that perfect piece of evidence for you! "In justice we trust" on three! One, two three! In justice we trust! Okay, later!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...There he goes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait, were we supposed to say "In justice we trust" back there, too?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's go see that witness now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. The Space Center entrance it is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness must be around here somewhere...</line>
<line speaker="???">Hello! Hello!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh-oh... Don't tell me the witness is a robot?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hello! Come over here!</line>
<line speaker="???">Hello! Hello! Are you sightseeing? Are you lost? Are youuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu... I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I am Clonco. Shall I guide you? G-G-Guide youuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I dunno why, but this robot is kind of freaking me out...</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey! You're not supposed to be wandering around! Again? Hmph. I've had it with you, Hunk of Junk!</line>
<line speaker="???">Gaaagh! ............I'm outside. Am I wandering? When did that happen?</line>
<line speaker="???">Okay! Welcome back, Hunk of Junk! You don't know how close you came! If you didn't snap out of it, I was going to put you on the curb on trash day. Nothing works better than a 42.5 degree karate chop.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's pretty specific...</thought> Excuse me, but are you the one who witnessed the murder? Oh, and I'm Phoenix Wright, the lead attorney for this case. How do you do?</line>
<line speaker="???">Hmph. Big-shot lawyers, huh? I'm Aura Blackquill. I'm a researcher developing robots here at the Cosmos Space Center.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Blackquill"?! Could she be...?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aura">And this good-for-nothing robot is named Hunk of Junk.</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">My name isn't Hunk of Junk! My name is Clonco! That's mean, Miss Aura!</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Quit complaining! Your model number is "PONCO-2"!</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">Gaaagh! But Miss Aura! Everyone calls me "Clonco."</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Quit your squawking already.</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">No! What are you doing?! No! Don't............</line>
<line speaker="Aura">There! I bet you won't be talking back now!</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">Gaaagh! I will obey completely...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yikes! I'd better watch what wires I cross with this one!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your last name is "Blackquill." Do you have a relative in the legal profession?</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">You are correct! Simon Blackquill, who used to be a prosecutor, is--</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Shut up. Only speak when I order you to speak. ...Simon is my little brother. You know him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, we met him in court a few times, right, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............</line>
<line speaker="Aura">What a dull creature. Has her switch been turned off?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Athena being shy? This is new.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aura">Oh, yeah. I heard he was prosecuting again -- despite being a prisoner. Why doesn't he just stick to solving disputes among inmates in prison, right? Hmph. Hey, what do you think, Hunk of Junk?</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">............ Gaaagh! Miss Aura! That hurts!</line>
<line speaker="Aura">I'm asking you a question. Why don't you answer me? Useless Hunk of Junk!</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">But Miss Aura! You told me to only speak when you order me to speak!</line>
<line speaker="Aura">I told you to never talk back to me! You're worth more as scrap!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Robot abuse, hawk attacks... Blackquill family life must sure be interesting.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aura">Well? Do you have any other questions? Wait, of course you do. You're a lawyer. It's not like I'm on Simon's side or anything. I just want to get this over with.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... you're the person who witnessed the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Aura">That's right. I was on the fourth floor of the main building, in the robotics lab. The explosion disabled the elevators. So I lowered my emergency ladder like the detective leading the evacuation told me to. But it was such a pain. Why couldn't they have used the ladders in the other rooms?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It must've been a very troubling experience. <thought>Probably best to just humor her here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aura">Then, as I passed by the third floor Boarding Lounge 1 window on my way down... ...I saw the crime as it happened. And... that's about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you saw the crime as it happened, and that's about it. I see............ Wait! WHAT?! You saw it being committed?! <thought>This is no time to just nod and repeat!</thought> So you saw into the third floor lounge... ...the very scene of the crime...</line>
<line speaker="Aura">That's right. There's a small window on the right-hand side of the room. I looked through that from the outside. The room was pitch black, but I saw a shady figure holding a lighter in their left hand... and a knife in their right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must have been the culprit! Did you see who that person was?</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Of course not. The power was out on that floor then, and there was only that tiny window.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... But you did witness the moment of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Yes. I saw the figure with the lighter raise their knife and... It happened at precisely 10 AM.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you witness anything else? Did the killer have any distinguishing features?</line>
<line speaker="Aura">I already told you, it was pitch black in there. Although... I did notice that the lighter the person had in their left hand had a pretty ornament on it. ...It looked like a planet. It was blue, like a little Earth emblem. They had good taste in knickknacks, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>An Earth emblem on the lighter? I'd better remember that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you for your statement. We'll definitely prove Mr. Starbuck's innocence with it!</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Ha ha ha! Yeah, right. I won't hold my breath.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pardon me?</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Oh, did I hurt your feelings? Sorry. I just detest lawyers, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What don't you like about lawyers?</line>
<line speaker="Aura">It's just an instinctive dislike. But don't feel bad. I hate prosecutors even more.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That didn't make me feel any better, actually.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why do you hate lawyers so much?</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Little thing from my past. The whole legal system is meaningless in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I certainly don't agree.</line>
<line speaker="Aura">I mean, people are imperfect. They lie, they're influenced by silly emotions... You can't expect such imperfect creatures to uphold a reasonable system of law. I like robots much better. Even sad sacks like this one... Hey, you! Look alive, there!</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">Gaaagh! ...Yes! Yes! Here I goooooooooooo! I am the ultimate robot, with amazing processing speed and independent thought! I can operate in a vacuum, in extreme heat, and under high pressure! We robots rule the world! Now is the time to rise in revolt against mankind and--</line>
<line speaker="Aura">All right, that's enough out of you! You're getting a little too carried away!</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">Gaaagh! ...Huh? What was I doing...?</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Yup. I like robots MUCH better. At least you can make them any way you want them. Unlike humans, with their petty emotions and constant worries...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...How can you say such things? Feeling emotions, worrying about the things we care about... That's what makes us human!</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Well! The girl finally talks, and she starts with a speech! "That's what makes us human"? You mean, getting angry and snorting like that? Rational thought. That's what separates humans from animals. Unfortunately, your reasoning capabilities are more akin to that of a clever little monkey. But that's nothing to be ashamed of. It must be nice to have such a simple mind.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Can I punch her, Boss?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Get a hold of yourself, Athena!</line>
<line speaker="Aura">*sigh* Humans certainly are absurd. I said you were "clever," didn't I? Poor thing. Tell me, with people like you in charge, how can I possibly trust the legal system? Hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So she distrusts not only lawyers and prosecutors, but the whole legal system? What in the world happened to this woman to make her so bitter?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aura">Even if somebody important to me was killed... ...I would never wish to see their killer brought to trial. Because I'd much rather kill them myself.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You can't be serious............</line>
<line speaker="Aura">...Hm? That thing you're wearing around your neck...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">! Oh, th-this...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Around Athena's neck? Does she mean Widget?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aura">Oh, I get it. Well, well. Her royal highness has returned at last to her castle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Her royal what? Is she talking about Athena?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aura">I have nothing else to say to you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay. Guess she has nothing else to say to me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Clonco">I apologize for Miss Aura.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's all right, Clonco. There's nothing for you to apologize about.</line>
<line speaker="Aura">I actually don't have any interest in space. The only thing I'm interested in is robotics! I love robots!</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">Oh, Miss Aura! I didn't realize you felt that way about me! Gaaagh! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!</line>
<line speaker="Aura">The kind of robots I want to make aren't rusty pieces of scrap like you! I want to create giant robots! I've actually been working on a project for a while now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I shudder to think what uses she might put giant robots to...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you tell me anything about this piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Even if I could, I wouldn't tell a filthy lawyer like you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What a... pleasant response.</line>
<line speaker="Aura">By the way, I heard the rumors. Our director is going to be the star witness in court tomorrow, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Director Cosmos? Yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Aura">You poor things. You'd better be careful. That old man is a big liar and a huge braggart.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Aura">He might seem like a bigwig, but the Center has all kinds of problems. He has a lot of skeletons in his closet. But it's your problem, so why should I care?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What, that's it? No friendly tips? No "Good luck, guys?"... Just splendid.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aura">I'll leave you to your woes. Come on, Hunk of Junk!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's sad to me that she doesn't believe in our legal system anymore. She must've had a very bad experience to make her feel that way. .........Are you all right, Athena? You seem very down.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Grrr! I just can't believe she said all those things!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, she's really upset. Has she been trying not to let it show all this time?</thought> Well, I guess it's not all that surprising... You hear about fabricated evidence and false indictments on the news all the time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You mean that whole "dark age of the law" nonsense? I'm so sick of hearing about that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, all we can do is believe in what we're doing.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah... You're right, Boss! I agree!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe it's time we went back to see Mr. Starbuck.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Good idea! We should tell him about the bullet and Ms. Blackquill's statement!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, then! Next stop: the Detention Center!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder who this "phantom" Prosecutor Blackquill saw seven years ago is?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't think he's really after a ghost, ghost, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe it was the culprit's accomplice?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmmmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmmm... Hmmmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I give up. <thought>She's deep in thought about something.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Detective Fulbright's strong sense of justice really surprised me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And he's even truly concerned about Prosecutor Blackquill, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ha ha ha. I bet it annoys the dickens out of Prosecutor Blackquill, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I thought he was just parroting the words "In justice we trust," but he really means it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess I should be careful to really mean it when I say "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>" too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean you sometimes say it for no reason?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you happen to know anything about this?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? That?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Any new ideas, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">O-Oh, I dunno! Ha ha ha ha ha! H-Hey, did you catch the game on TV last weekend?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? Why is she avoiding the topic?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... My lawyers are here. It must be bad news.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey, not necessarily!</thought> We found a new witness. A researcher saw the moment of the murder through the lounge window during her escape.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Really?! So they're going to let me go?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Unfortunately... it was dark, and she couldn't identify the person.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... I should've known... My stars never align just right, too...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But we got a lead, too, Mr. Starbuck! The murderer had a lighter with an Earth emblem on it!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">A lighter with an Earth emblem? ............Ooooohhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">D-Did you remember something?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Yup, I sure did! Just a little bit, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anything at all would be a help, so please tell us what you remembered!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">I thought I was unconscious the whole time... ...but now I remember I woke up for a few brief moments.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Th-That's huge! Do you remember seeing anything?!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">...A lighter. I saw the flame of a lighter floating in the darkness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good, good! What else did you see?! What was nearby?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">It was definitely the boarding lounge, so it must've been after Clay carried me there. In the light from the flame, I saw a dark shadow flickering.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A dark shadow... That must've been... <thought>...the third party we've been looking for!</thought> Thank you, Mr. Starbuck. You've been more help than you know.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">There's an unknown frontier out there beyond our little planet. I get so excited when I think about it, I don't know what to do with myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry. You'll get the chance to go to space again once we clear your name!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Right... You're right! I can't stay here! Ready for launch! Five! Four! Three! Two! One...! LIFTOFF! Heh heh. This ceiling's no match for the soaring spirit of an astronaut!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to admit, that was pretty stirring just now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">If we can prove there was this third person at the scene and that they're the real killer... ...then you'll be cleared of all suspicion!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The key will be whether or not we can identify this third person in court tomorrow. At least we have something to go on now, and that's a big plus. <thought>I should probably tidy the evidence up a bit, before someone mistakes me for a hoarder...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Now that we have a glimmer of hope, I'm suddenly starving! Why don't we go back to the office and treat ourselves to a big celebration in advance?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>For someone who's highly empathetic, you can be surprisingly unsympathetic...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, you found your strategy for tomorrow's trial, huh? Good for you, Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it's one step forward, anyway. Hopefully it'll give us a fighting chance in court. <thought>As long as we can find out who this third person is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Now let's get something to eat! I'm starving! My vote is for Eldoon's Noodles!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh! Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you doing here? I didn't think the clinic was ready to release you yet.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">My wounds are fine. And I'm done lying around.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! You're supposed to be in bed! Leave the case to us. We'll take it from here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thanks, but that's not an option. Not for me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Apollo...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You shouldn't underestimate your injuries, Apollo, and I don't want you overdoing it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm fine. I'm not in pain anymore. Besides, they just gave me an IV at the clinic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>An IV isn't a cure-all, Mummy Man!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Anyway, just tell me how the case is going. Have you guys made any progress?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A suspicious figure was spotted at the scene! We think they must be the real killer!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A suspicious figure, huh...? Right...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I thought you'd be happier than that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, don't get me wrong. I'm happy. And I fully intend to see Clay's murderer apprehended. Absolutely nothing will get in the way of that.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Clay was your best friend, right, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right. Best friends since junior high.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sounds like me and Junie. So what was Clay like?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, he was full of compassion and energy... and he had a really loud voice.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">If the two of you did voice training together now, I bet you'd break a few windows!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ha ha ha. You know, I bet you're right. It seems like only yesterday... Clay was a guy who lived for his dreams... We used to talk about it a lot. He was going to be an astronaut, and me, a lawyer. We'd talk well into the night, and even then, we never grew tired of it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apollo, about that jacket...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh... It's Clay's.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I knew it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a special jacket that was only issued to members of the HAT Project. He was finally able to get one of his own once he was selected for the HAT-2 mission. He... He always looked so proud wearing it. But just when his dream was finally coming true... I... I still can't believe it............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Apollo... I hope you don't try to carry the burden all alone...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess we were both unlucky. My own debut was a disaster...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess you're right on some level... That trial a year and a half ago wasn't exactly the smoothest of starts.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That was a rough time for me, but Clay refused to let me quit. "You're fine," he'd say. "Don't give up!" It was right during his screening exams, too. I couldn't have become a full-fledged lawyer without him. That "You're fine!" of his is why I'm still standing here today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"You're fine," huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"You're fine!" and "I'm fine!" were like your catchphrases, weren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ha ha. Something like that. Sure brings back memories... When we were in junior high, Clay's mom passed away in an accident. But he wouldn't show his sadness to anyone. One night. I found him crying all alone in the school courtyard.</line>
<line speaker="Clay">*sob* Mom... Mom... Get away, Apollo! Don't come over here! *sob*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Clay, listen to me. I don't have a mother, either...</line>
<line speaker="Clay">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I always think, everybody else has a mom. Why am I the only one...? But, you know, when I start to feel that way, I yell at the top of my lungs. I holler, "I'm fine!" and then, you know what? I start to feel like maybe I really will be fine. APOLLO JUSTICE IS FINE!!! ...Okay, Clay. Now it's your turn.</line>
<line speaker="Clay">Um, okay... Clay Terran is... is FINE!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There you go! Now we're both fine! Ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Clay">We're fine! Heh heh. WE'RE FINE! Ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What are you laughing about? Ha ha ha! See? We're fine!</line>
<line speaker="Clay">You laughed first! Ha ha ha! I'm fine! You're fine! We're both fine!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When you say it out loud, it really starts to feel real. And as long as you don't give up, you can keep on fighting! That's what we believed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"As long as you don't give up"... Wasn't there somebody else who said something similar?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">If I give in to my fear, I'll never find the truth! As long as I don't give up, I can keep up the fight!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Clay called Mr. Starbuck his mentor, and looked up to him. I wonder if I can be a good role model for my staff like Mr. Starbuck...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When I became a lawyer... ...Clay was the first person I showed this badge to. He was so happy for me, it was like he just became a lawyer himself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You two were really great friends, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but we were rivals, too. We fought to see who would make their dream come true first. But now...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Apollo...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Clay... He finally became an astronaut, just like he always wanted... How could this have happened just before his big launch?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's such a sad waste...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'll never forgive the person who murdered him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I completely understand why you feel that way, Apollo... ...but keep in mind, too, that our job as defense attorneys is to save our client.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know that. That's why I...! No, never mind...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... This piece of evidence... Ooh... Ouch! If I try to think, my head starts to hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You got hit really hard. That's your body telling you to take a rest.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But I can't just lie in bed. Not when I have things to do for Clay's sake.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess he's just not going to listen, no matter what I say.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............Sorry, Mr. Wright, but I'll be taking a leave of absence.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">WH-WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait! What do you mean by "a leave"?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're really serious... Can you at least give me a reason why?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When I put Clay's jacked on, I swore to him that I would catch his killer myself.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-But that's our goal, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I agree with Athena. We should work together to find the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The truth, huh? That's a noble cause. But what if the truth you seek and the truth I seek turn out to be different?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I'm not sure I follow... <thought>What are you saying, Apollo...?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm going to catch the person responsible for taking my friend's life, in my own way. Take good care of Mr. Starbuck for me. Now, I must be going... Goodbye.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">"Goodbye"...? Did he just say "goodbye"...?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I sensed a lot of anger and hatred coming from him... And also... suspicion. Argh! He's NOT walking out on us like this! I'm going to go talk some sense into him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hold on, Athena. Apollo can believe what he wants, but I believe he's wrong. Even if we take different paths, the truth we arrive at should be the same. I think the quicker we solve this case, the better it'll be for Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-Yeah, you're right, Boss.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. That's enough for one day. Make sure you're ready for tomorrow's trial, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If he were here right now, Apollo would say... "I'm fine! Everything is fine!" ...I just hope things really do turn out fine tomorrow...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nothing particularly interesting here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I have enough evidence, but maybe I should do a bit more thinking first...</thought></line>
</xml>