
<xml>
<title>The Cosmic Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Judge">.........I suppose... we should reconvene the trial of Solomon Starbuck or something...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............Oh, yes, um... My apologies. I'm still a little jumpy when it comes to trials involving bombs. I mean, first the courtroom exploded... ...and then Mr. Tonate self-destructed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess that's one way of describing what happened to Tonate...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Anyway, it seems that Mr. Justice was seriously wounded by Mr. Tonate's actions. So you, Mr. Wright, will be taking up the defense...? Do you have an understanding of what has happened in the trial so far?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. The defense is ready.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Is the prosecution also ready?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm? ............I take it you'd like me to give the opening statement this time?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Looks like the judge has become a pretty good mind reader.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, he's certainly seen more than his fair share of colorful prosecutors. You could say he's something of a veteran of sorts...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's see. In the previous part of this trial, we learned that the victim, Clay Terran... ...escaped from Launch Pad 1 carrying the defendant, Solomon Starbuck. There were explosions on the second floor of the Space Center and on the rocket itself. The two astronauts used the Launch Pad 1 corridor to reach the boarding lounge.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">And?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How could the victim climb down the ladder if he was carrying the defendant...? That was the mystery that needed to be solved. But Mr. Justice proved that the victim was killed in the boarding lounge. Prosecutor Blackquill, were you able to discover any new facts related to this point?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Upon further investigation, we discovered an oxygen tank fragment in the lounge. Surprisingly, it would appear that Justice-dono's argument was correct.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So that means the testimonies of the first two people on the scene are suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There were two people who claimed to be the first on the scene. But can we truly trust their statements?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's see. The two people were Detective Candice Arme and Yuri Cosmos, right? You think that one of them might have given a false statement to the police?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, it's certainly possible. We might have to do a little more digging.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And just as our team was about to cross-examine Detective Arme... ...the courtroom bombing incident occurred, and the trial was put on hold.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">That accursed fellow! He killed my witness! He killed Detective Arme!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He definitely put the kibosh on anyone asking her about what she saw.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Exactly. In other words, the question of "who killed the victim in the boarding lounge"... ...has, once again, become the main focus of this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's obvious Prosecutor Blackquill still thinks it was Mr. Starbuck. Fulbright said that Blackquill has a thing against the astronaut. Nevertheless...</thought> The defense argues that there was a third person in the lounge, and that's who killed the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">They saw a third person?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. I see my sister has been running her mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's right! I almost forgot that Aura is Prosecutor Blackquill's sister...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">No matter. She didn't see this mystery person's face clearly. Therefore, there is no evidence to indicate that this person was not the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I guess the possibility that the figure was Mr. Starbuck is still there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">In brief, we need to determine if a third person was there or not. To this end, we should hear the testimony of one of the first people on the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Director Cosmos, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Bailiff, please bring the witness to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, I believe I've seen you before in the newspapers.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Of course you have! Of course you have! For I am Yuri Cosmos! Director of the Cosmos Space Center, which was of course named after me, Yuri Cosmos! ............ Don't you have anything you wish to ask me?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Looks like he's all geared up to do some bragging.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Seven years ago, I successfully launched the HAT-1, and--</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Everyone already knows how brilliant you are. Even I am trying to hold back my tears at seeing such a great man standing before me. So could you please proceed directly to your important testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">............Ha ha ha! I see this fine young lad has a proper appreciation of greatness! Then allow me to begin my epochal testimony that will be recorded in the annals of history!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That speech of Prosecutor Blackquill's just now... It sounded more to me like he was poking fun at Director Cosmos.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's probably for the best that it sailed right over the director's head.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Director Cosmos, the condensed version of your illustrious testimony... please.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Detective Arme and I rushed towards the boarding lounge together.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, I see. So in your testimony you claim... ...you arrived on the scene after the two had escaped from the launch pad to the lounge... ...and just after the victim had been killed.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Oh, the horror! The humanity! But what I said is what I saw, and what I saw is what I said. Courageous action to take in the face of such terrifying explosions, wouldn't you say? To save my men, I went personally into the epicenter of danger... ...risking my own life for theirs! Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, what do you know. It sounds like the director really cares about his men.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... Although it sounds more like he was scared and just had a peek from far away.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is the defense ready to cross-examine the witness?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. <thought>............Director Cosmos's testimony is pretty vague. I'm going to have to press him and draw out more information before I do anything else.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Detective Arme and I rushed towards the boarding lounge together.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">The sixth floor. We were making sure any stragglers made their way to the fourth floor. It was then we heard about Starbuck and Terran, and hurried to the third floor lounge. On my... Galactic Scooter here, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why do you keep calling it "Galactic"? Does it have something to do with space?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Of course! It's specifically designed to be used on galactic battleships!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I see. Then I take it it works in Zero-g, too?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Sadly, no. With the current state of technology as it is... ...I'm afraid it would just float about and be galactically useless...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, that's a galactic bummer...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. So you rushed to the boarding lounge on your space-age pogo stick. And when you got to the scene, what did you see?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">We went via the Control Room and peeked in from there to see what was going on inside.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Yes, but in her haste, Detective Arme rushed ahead of me towards the Control Room. All I could do was merely follow behind her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">So we peeked into the boarding lounge from the Control Room door and...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">We saw a figure standing in the middle of the lounge, and Terran lying on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Sadly, the only thing I could tell was that it was a person, standing motionless.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The defendant, no doubt, staring aghast at his deed. What other explanation is there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! I'm so close, but without evidence, I can't prove that person's the third party!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">............I don't relish in this... and...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I hate to say it, but I can only imagine the standing figure mast have been Starbuck.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">...No, not clearly. The lighter they were holding illuminated the area around their feet at the time. But other than that, I could see little else. That's why I could see Terran, but I couldn't see who the other person was.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, for all you know, it might NOT have been Mr. Starbuck, isn't that correct?!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I would like to believe that. Starbuck isn't the type of man who's capable of murder.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Y-Yes, that's right... Only Starbuck and Terran were there by that time. After we peeked in, the lounge suddenly went dark and the figure vanished.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean they disappeared? That's odd.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Just for a brief instant, about as long as it takes for a shooting star to go by.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you took your eyes off the scene... ...then this third person could have escaped during that time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But what escape route could this person have used?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The direction opposite the control room: the southern door to the elevators. There's no security lock on that door, so it would've been possible to escape that way.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, well...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">If we're just talking "possibilities," we could each profess whatever we'd like. An inmate who used to be a university professor and lunar researcher used to say... ...that there is a kingdom of little green men who live under the surface of the moon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>As long as they don't punish us in the name of said moon for what we've done to it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">But I say, where's your proof that this quaint kingdom exists?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He's calling your theory a work of fiction, Boss.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And he's right. I don't have any proof yet. Still... The southern door was a possible escape route. I'd better make a mental note of that.</thought> Director Cosmos, may I ask you a question?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did you look away from the boarding lounge?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Ha ha ha! There's actually another tale of bravery behind the answer to that. It was when Detective Arme saw the figure and raised her gun. Being a great humanitarian and protector of mankind, I tried to stop her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? You're saying Detective Arme raised her gun as soon as she saw the figure?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">............I imagine her instincts as a detective told her they were the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I don't know about that...</thought> And were you able to prevent Detective Arme from firing her gun?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I'm afraid I was too late. I was unable to stop her. She identified herself clearly, and then... She fired two warning shots at the shadowy figure!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... This information about Detective Arme's actions sounds critically important. Please add it to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">...No, not clearly. The lighter they were holding illuminated the area around their feet at the time. But other than that, I could see little else. That's why I could see Terran, but I couldn't see who the other person was.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, for all you know, it might NOT have been Mr. Starbuck, isn't that correct?!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I would like to believe that. Starbuck isn't the type of man who's capable of murder.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Y-Yes, that's right... Only Starbuck and Terran were there by that time. After we peeked in, the lounge suddenly went dark and the figure vanished.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean they disappeared? That's odd.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Just for a brief instant, about as long as it takes for a shooting star to go by.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you took your eyes off the scene... ...then this third person could have escaped during that time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But what escape route could this person have used?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The direction opposite the control room: the southern door to the elevators. There's no security lock on that door, so it would've been possible to escape that way.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, well...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">If we're just talking "possibilities," we could each profess whatever we'd like. An inmate who used to be a university professor and lunar researcher used to say... ...that there is a kingdom of little green men who live under the surface of the moon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>As long as they don't punish us in the name of said moon for what we've done to it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">But I say, where's your proof that this quaint kingdom exists?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He's calling your theory a work of fiction, Boss.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And he's right. I don't have any proof yet. Still... The southern door was a possible escape route. I'd better make a mental note of that.</thought> Director Cosmos, may I ask you a question?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did you look away from the boarding lounge?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Ha ha ha! There's actually another tale of bravery behind the answer to that. It was when Detective Arme saw the figure and raised her gun. Being a great humanitarian and protector of mankind, I tried to stop her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? You're saying Detective Arme raised her gun as soon as she saw the figure?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">............I imagine her instincts as a detective told her they were the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I don't know about that...</thought> And were you able to prevent Detective Arme from firing her gun?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I'm afraid I was too late. I was unable to stop her. She identified herself clearly, and then...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Detective Arme fired two warning shots at the figure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">That is correct. The detective appears to have missed on purpose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... But did she really? There's something about this that bothers me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mr. Starbuck isn't the killer. And if that's true, then there must be a false statement in the director's testimony.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's press his statements and draw the truth out of him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So Detective Arme fired two warning shots, did she? That's the first time that info has come out. Wonder if I can find any inconsistencies?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure you were really paying attention to what Detective Arme was doing?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">You doubt my words, words that will someday be written down in history books?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Somehow, I don't think that those exact words... ...will ever be written down in any history books.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, could you please explain yourself so that we can all understand?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You say that Detective Arme fired two warning shots... ...and yet, only one bullet hole was ever found at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Only one bullet hole means the gun was only fired once. And yet Director Cosmos is saying Detective Arme fired two shots. No editor would allow such a glaring contradiction into a history book!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...You should know the answer to that already.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I should?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">During the previous trial, a certain oxygen tank was presented as evidence. We've already discussed that it was ruptured in the lounge, have we not? Well, it appears that the thing that ruptured it was a bullet. A bullet that was found near the tank, to be precise. This bullet was fired from a .38-caliber gun, the same caliber as the detective's gun.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The rifling marks also match up. There's no question that the bullet was fired from Detective Arme's gun.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Rifling marks"... They're like a gun's fingerprints on a bullet, correct? And examining the rifling marks on a bullet can tell us the gun it was fired from?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">One of the bullets the detective fired found its way into the holographic image display. The other bullet came to a stop near the victim's oxygen tank. The evidence confirms the director's statement that the detective fired two shots.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>My beautiful contradiction... Gone... All gone...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So that bullet hole was from a .38-caliber, huh? I'd better update the record.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very good. Now we know the fate of both of the shots Detective Arme fired. Mr. Wright, does that clear up all of your questions...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm............ Detective Arme fired two warning shots... One hit the holographic display and the other hit the oxygen tank... Does that really clear up everything about what happened at the scene?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, I guess it does, Your Honor. <thought>At least, I think so... But there's still something nagging at me...</thought> Um, actually... can I change my mind on that, Your Honor...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............You may, but only after you take responsibility for your first choice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better think this one through again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Your Honor, it doesn't! "Detective Arme fired two warning shots from a .38-caliber gun." But that doesn't explain the existence of a certain piece of evidence found at the scene. A piece... that points to the existence of a third person.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Oh...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. But it won't do to keep us waiting, Mr. Wright. What piece of evidence suggests the possibility of a third person at the scene?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, I don't think that at all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not even just an eensy-weensy bit?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No. What does seem incongruous to me, Mr. Wright, is your claim!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Urk... Looks like it wasn't this piece of evidence after all...</thought> Your Honor! Please let me give it a little more thought!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what is this metal pellet supposed to be?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just a little something of great importance we found at the crime scene, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You found it where?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In a floor gutter at the crime scene. It looks like the police and prosecution both missed it. Furthermore, this is a .10-caliber bullet... ...making it much smaller than one of Detective Arme's .38-calibers.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-Then that means...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. One more person must have been there in the lounge. A third person who had a gun that could fire .10-caliber bullets!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Grnk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And if that's true, it explains why Detective Arme fired warning shots. This third person fired at Detective Arme and Director Cosmos with their gun. And in return, the detective fired her warning shots. Isn't that how it really went down, Director Cosmos?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Ha ha ha! It looks like you've deduced my miraculous tale of survival! Yes, you're absolutely correct. The mystery person fired upon us!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's this now?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What? You never breathed a word of any of this to me before...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Ha ha ha! Well, all great men have a secret or two, don't you know!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........Tsk. Foolish old geezer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So Director Cosmos really has been hiding the presence of a third person all along?</thought> Director Cosmos! I want you to testify to the court about what you really saw!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You may be a very great man, but, in my courtroom, you are just another witness. You won't receive special treatment here. Now, please give accurate testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Detective Arme and I rushed to the Control Room together.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Given that there was no third person in the lounge when the witness entered it... ...does this mean the person who fired the gun had to have been the defendant...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not necessarily. It's still possible that it was someone else. Most likely, as soon as Detective Arme and Director Cosmos discovered this person... ...they escaped through the southern door, the one that didn't have a security lock.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Your reasoning could apply if Space Boy were the killer as well. Think about it. After being discovered, he could have fired the .10-caliber gun. Detective Arme would've responded by firing two warning shots. All he had to do was feign unconsciousness to invent the possibility of a third person.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Why, the detonator switch that was found in Mr. Starbuck's pocket, naturally. The most compelling evidence of all that tells us he is the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaaaaaaagh! <thought>I-I DID forget all about that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Look, Your Baldness, how deliciously obvious it is that they lack the evidence to rival mine.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, he sliced our third person theory to ribbons and served it to us, just like that...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, well, I have a question of my own, actually... That bullet that the mysterious figure shot... What did it hit exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">............It hit me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-So does that mean you're a-a-a-a gh-ghost?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I was wondering when you would realize it, Your Baldness. Director Cosmos is an authentic, bona fide ghost. He can even pass through walls.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Eeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. Your Baldness, it was all in jest. Please show yourself again.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-Are you sure...? I-In that case... How did you manage to survive being shot, Director Cosmos?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Ha ha ha! I'm glad you asked! It was a miracle! A miracle befitting a great, history-making figure such as myself! The bullet hit my glorious medal of honor, whereby it ricocheted, thus saving my life!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That's unbelievable...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I have to check this out! .........Oh, wow. Look at that. There's one extra GYAXA star...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The odds are literally astronomical... <thought>I guess it really was a miracle...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's beginning to feel like the cosmos is watching out for Director Cosmos.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But why did you conceal this information, Director Cosmos?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">A great man such as myself has to hide things on occasion, no matter how much it hurts. It is the plight of the truly great! It may be hard for this generation to understand...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't know, but it sounds fishy to me. What else is he hiding?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Let's just cross-examine him and see what we can find out.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Wright. Your cross-examination, please.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Detective Arme and I rushed to the Control Room together.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Well... Let me see... ...If you have an hour or two, I could tell you all about the HAT-1 Miracle!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Hmm... I see.... You want to know about incidents. ...Well then, let me tell you about... the many incidents that made me the man I am today! Yes, if you have the time, I will tell you all about the upbringing of this great man!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">............Hmm? Did I really already tell you all about my upbringing? I don't recall doing so...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Director Cosmos, perhaps you could save your boastful tales for later.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">If I must. Well, we peeked in through the Control Room door and...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">In the lounge, we saw a figure standing in the middle of the room, and Terran on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Yes, the room was as deep and dark as outer space itself. Speaking of outer space, during the HAT-1 launch seven years ago--</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">If it's about that "HAT-1 Miracle" again, you can sod off and tell it to a stray mutt.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Ha ha ha! Excellent idea! No reason why the animal world shouldn't hear of my greatness!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...And so they shall. But first, your testimony. What happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">We were still in the Control Room to the east when the figure fired at us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">That is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's something not quite right about that...</thought> Director Cosmos, the bullet this person fired hit you, isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Yes, it was a miracle! A miracle befitting a great, history-making figure such as myself! The bullet the figure fired hit me while I was in the Control Room. But as the cosmos would have it, the bullet bounced off my glorious medal of honor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>In that case, the bullet should've wound up somewhere around the Control Room door.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, so Director Cosmos was in the Control Room to the east.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And while he was there, he was shot at by someone with a .10-caliber gun.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But the bullet hit his medal, so he was able to escape with his life. He's a very lucky man. No wonder people think he's great.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey, I'm pretty lucky myself, so if he's a great man, then I'm the king of all cosmos!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Director Cosmos, I believe you are telling this great court a glorious lie!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">A great man like me, tell a lie?! Have you ever heard of such a thing in all of history?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My accusation is based on the positions of the people who were in the lounge. According to your testimony... ...you and Detective Arme were near the Control Room door... ...and the mystery figure was standing in the middle of the boarding lounge. If, as you say, the figure fired a gun at you from this position... ...then the bullet would have traveled in this direction. However, we found the .10-caliber bullet here.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The trajectory and where the bullet was actually found contradict each other! Director Cosmos! Where were you really when you were being shot at?!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">............GAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ladies and gentlemen, I present to you the human merry-go-round...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I didn't think so-- WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">O great Director Cosmos...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Yes?! Is there something you'd like me to expound upon...?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You were in fact NOT in the Control Room to the east, were you? You were looking into the lounge from the door to the south, is that not right?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">............Gaaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What are you getting at?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Use your own brain. Your head must have some use other than housing that bird's nest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Bird's nest...? Why does everyone pick on my hair?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Director Cosmos and the detective witnessed the scene from the southern door. The killer fired at them there, and that is why the bullet was found in the south.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah! <thought>Th-That makes some sense, actually...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Also, the witness being at the southern door is rather favorable for the prosecution.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? <thought>I've got a b-bad feeling about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">How about it, Director? If you don't tell the truth this time...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Yikes! H-His handcuffs...!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...you will become but rust upon my sword. I relish the chance to cut down a great man!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">All right! I'll tell the truth! Just put your sword away! You are correct... I, the great Yuri Cosmos... ...was looking into the room from the southern door!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat?! <thought>That's the complete opposite of all the testimony he's given so far!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">And now you have lost your possibility that a third person was in the room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have? How?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The director and the detective were near the southern door... ...meaning the killer couldn't have escaped through there. The western door required print recognition; the corridor beyond, was filled with smoke. The only escape route left was the eastern Control Room door............ ...And the only way to get through there was with Director Cosmos's fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">In short, there would be no escape for any "third person" had there been one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH! <thought>M-My third person just disappeared... like in one of Trucy's magic tricks...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court! Director Cosmos, why did you tell such an outrageous lie?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">............</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You were covering for the defendant... isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">...Yes. It was all for the love of my men! If I said I was in the eastern Control Room... ...it would mean the culprit could have escaped through the southern door. It would have meant that there could have been a third person. All I wanted to do was protect Starbuck! I said I was in the Control Room to invent an escape route for a third person!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What a convoluted lie... <thought>Was he really covering for the defendant?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">............It looks like we've come to a conclusion... ...that the defense's argument, the possibility of a third person, has crumbled.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-Nooo!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. It's over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yikes! The judge is about to hand down his verdict! Think, Phoenix, think! This is the perfect time to try and turn my thinking around! If a third person had no way of escaping the scene... ...then what if one of the people at the scene was this third person? ............Wait! What if the whole premise is all wrong? Director Cosmos said that he and Detective Arme rushed to the scene together. But what if that premise isn't true? What if one of them reached the scene before the other one? And if that person entered the lounge... ...then THEY would be the third person!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defendant is the only one who could've killed the victim and shot at the director. There doesn't appear to be any room for argument against these claims. I will now render my verdict--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh? This had better be good, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is one and only one person who could have escaped from the scene. And that person would be the first person who arrived on the scene. Then, upon entering the boarding lounge... ...the second person to arrive came via the southern door. That's why the first person fled from the room... ...using an escape route that was accessible only to them!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Let's hear more about this theory. Who is this one person who could have escaped from the boarding lounge?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............Um, somehow...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Fishing for an answer, are we? Well, congratulations on catching this prize penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please let me try again, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. But let's have no more of your fishy answers, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What? B-But that's............ Mr. Wright! Wh-Wh-What are you claiming here?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of all the people who were at the scene, only the witness could have escaped. The director is the only one with the authority to open the Control Room door, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But... But that means...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. The true identity of the third person is our current witness. Director Yuri Cosmos!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">GAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court, I say! Mr. Wright, you will explain yourself in more detail!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I assert that Director Cosmos arrived at the scene before Detective Arme... ...and entered the boarding lounge alone. Detective Arme arrived after that and... ...saw a suspicious figure, who was actually Director Cosmos, standing in the lounge. And that's why she fired those two warning shots!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Gaaagh! I've been hit! I've been hit on the starboard side!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Captain Wright! It's a direct hit on the enemy ship, sir! A magnificent shot!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Warning shots fired from the enemy ship! Prepare to intercept!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Cosmos! You have told a lie in this court once again!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I've been hit! I've been hit on the port side! The enemy has called in reinforcements!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Earth to Cosmos Control Center... Requesting permission to ask that you return to reality.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">But my ship will not go down to anything less than the ultimate weapon of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Nghrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If Director Cosmos is the third person Aura Blackquill saw...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This third person fired at Detective Arme and Director Cosmos with their gun. And in return, the detective fired her warning shots. Isn't that how it really went down, Director Cosmos?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Ha ha ha! It looks like you've deduced my miraculous tale of survival! Yes, you're absolutely correct. The mystery person fired upon us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Director Cosmos must've been the one who fired the .10-caliber gun. When Detective Arme discovered him in the lounge... ...it only makes sense that he would've turned and shot at her. Therefore... the evidence on the director's body is of a different kind of relevance than before!</thought> Once we compare it against another piece of evidence... ...the mark that you received from the "third party" will be all the proof we need... ...to prove that you were the one in the lounge!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Uuuuuuuuurrrrgh! Brace for further impact!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Comparison against this piece of evidence will prove that you were the one in the lounge!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Oh, uh... I would like to say that... this is not it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, please only present evidence that you think "is it!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk. <thought>I guess that really wasn't it... ...but I AM sure the third person was Director Cosmos.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The .38-caliber bullet found on the floor at the scene didn't hit the oxygen tank. It hit Director Cosmos's medal. If we have that ricochet mark on the medal analyzed, I'm sure the caliber will match up. And if that mark proves to be from a .38-caliber bullet... ...it will prove that you are the third person we've been looking for!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">GAAAAAAAAAAGH! The bridge is destroyed! Losing altitude! All hands, abandon ship!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that's true, then what about the bullet that hit the oxygen tank?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was the .10-caliber bullet... In other words... ...it was the bullet fired by Yuri Cosmos. Isn't that right, Director?!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Noooooooo! You've got it all wrong! What? The engines have started again? It's a miracle! I'm not going down yet!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! Stop this at once and confess the the [sic] truth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you don't want the history books to say that a great man was a great liar...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Then accept your fate and tell the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Are you giving me orders?! Me, the great director of the Cosmos Space Center?! GAAAAAGH! But the cosmos revolves around meeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee! Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh! Someone get me off this thiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiing!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court! And will someone please stop the witness from spinning?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Phew... Thank goodness we were able to stop him from spinning off the face of the Earth.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">While he was twirling, I took the liberty of running an analysis on the mark on the medal. It was made by a .38-caliber bullet, matching it with the size of Detective Arme's firearm.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">NGAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you ready to confess the truth, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">No! You've got it all wrong! This is just a misunderstanding!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Is he going to start piling on more lies?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like it... <thought>But no matter how many lies he tells, I'll just expose them one by one! I'll MAKE that big liar tell the truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Director Cosmos! A new possibility has been presented by the defense. They are claiming that you were this "third person"!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Aaaaaaagh! Forgive me! I'm so sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">So the great pioneer of space development is revealed to be just another fabulist cur. I only have one question for the likes of you: shall I send you off quickly or very quickly?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The evidence doesn't lie, Director Cosmos, so don't try to talk your way out of this!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">F-Fine! I'll tell the truth! It's all just as you say, Mr. Wright! I-It's true that I was there in the boarding lounge! I got there before Detective Arme, and when she arrived, she fired warning shots at me! I was afraid people would mistake me for the killer, so I escaped to the Control Room. I then went past the elevators and all the way around to Boarding Lounge 1 again. I came up behind Detective Arme and pretended to be the second on the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What a troublesome old man you are, with such convoluted deeds and thoughts...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see... So then... ...are you still insisting that you did NOT kill the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">O-Of course I am! When I arrived at the lounge alone... ...I saw the true killer! The great Yuri Cosmos was a history-making witness!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">No! It wasn't me! I saw the person as well! If I were the killer, why would I lie to cover for Starbuck?! I would just leave him to take the fall!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... That is an excellent point...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">All I wanted to do was protect Starbuck! I said I was in the Control Room to invent an escape route for a third person!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, it makes some sense if he told those lies to cover for Mr. Starbuck...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Still, a lie's a lie, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So Director Cosmos claims he's not the culprit... but where's the proof?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Ah! I just remembered! I have an alibi! Ms. Blackquill said that she saw the killer at 10 AM, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... And...?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Well! I was on the fourth floor helping with the evacuation effort! Ask any member of the staff you'd like! They'll corroborate me!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...The director is not fibbing to the court, for once. I confirm that he has an alibi for the time specified.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... you're claiming that Ms. Blackquill saw the killer commit the crime first at 10 AM... ...and that you arrived at the lounge after that?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Yes, and I believe the person I saw is the same person that Ms. Blackquill saw. Although, it was pitch black, so it was more of a shadowy figure and less of a person... ...and I couldn't actually see their face, but it was definitely the silhouette of an earthling.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... As long as he has an alibi... ...we can't very well claim Director Cosmos was the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, we can't. Then again, maybe we don't need to yet. <thought>I wonder if he was really covering for Mr. Starbuck...</thought> Your Honor, the defense moves to have the director testify about that person he saw.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well. Director Cosmos, your testimony, please.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">As I tried to enter the lounge, the true killer inside fired a gun at me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you were shot at by the killer as well? And then they disappeared?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Yes, though luckily, no harm came to my glorious body. Unfortunately, the bullet hit Terran's oxygen tank. I know because I heard a "pang!" That must've been the sound of the tank being ruptured.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, but I thought the bullet hit his medal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was Detective Arme's bullet, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">R-Right... What a mess this is turning into. So, let's see... Director Cosmos is claiming that when he found Mr. Terran and his killer... ...the culprit shot a .10-caliber bullet at him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right, but it actually hit Mr. Terran's oxygen tank and ruptured it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And then, the killer disappeared, and the director went into the boarding lounge... ...when Detective Arme caught up and fired those warning shots at him. Judging by his medal, it looks like one of them almost took him out, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good summary, but that doesn't explain where our mystery killer went. Director Cosmos, I was wondering if you could elaborate on when the figure disappeared.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I'm ashamed to admit I tried to hide myself when I was shot at, but... ...when I peeped back into the lounge, the real killer was... gone. I rushed into the lounge straight away to investigate... ...but what I found was Terran with a knife in his chest, and Starbuck out cold on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So we have a culprit who vanished from a scene that had no escape route...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Vanished without a trace. It's truly like one of the great mysteries of the cosmos.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. A riddle of the ages, indeed. But I'd rather know... ...how a fibbing leech such as you can be lauded as great.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">............A great man is always misunderstood in his own time. But he must remain true to himself, even if those around him don't understand!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, that might be the first true statement he's said all day!</thought> But how do you suppose this person managed to vanish so suddenly?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Simple. Because it was Space Boy himself. When he was spotted by the director and Aura, he quickly feigned unconsciousness. That would certainly take all the mystery out of the idea of a vanished culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I want to raise an objection, but I don't have any counterevidence.</thought> Director Cosmos, when you saw this person... ...did you also see Mr. Starbuck on the floor?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">No, because it was as dark as a black hole in there. I didn't see Starbuck until the other person vanished and I entered the room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... That wasn't exactly helpful.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. I'm prepared to accept your surrender, Wright-dono.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>............I can't find any holes in his testimony, but I can't give up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright, why don't you let me help?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">While the director was giving his testimony, I detected a cacophony of discord.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which means he's hiding his true feelings from us, huh... <thought>This just might help us find out what happened to our vanished killer...</thought> That'd be great, Athena. Let's see what you can do with him!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You got it, Boss! I wouldn't want to miss this chance to delve into a great mind! Yuri Cosmos, prepare to hand over the secrets of your heart to me!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">As I tried to enter the lounge...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">...the true killer inside fired a gun at me!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I hid to avoid getting shot...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">...but, when I tried to get another look, they had vanished into thin air!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You must have thought it was very strange that the killer vanished into thin air.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I did! That kind of thing just doesn't happen, usually!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And yet, at that time, you barely registered any shock at the occurrence.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">What?! Why are you--?! Nngrrrh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can only think of one reason as to why you weren't surprised the killer's vanishing act. You must've had a good idea of where they went. Isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Whaaat?! No! O-Of course not...! That's preposterous! Only I can enter the control room... ...and the area beyond the launch pad door was filled with smoke, making it impassable! And as for the southern door... ...I was standing right there. So there was nowhere for the killer to run to.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe, or maybe not. You went into the room to check on Mr. Starbuck and Mr. Terran, yes? What if the culprit took that opportunity to silently slip out through the southern door?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I highly doubt it. As you recall, right after I entered the lounge... ...Detective Arme came rushing towards it herself via the southern hallway. Anyone trying to escape through there would have been caught by her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And yet, the director wasn't surprised the killer vanished...</thought> So you're absolutely sure there was no escape route for the culprit to use?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Ngh...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's working, Boss! One more punch and it'll be a knockout! There seems to be one more emotion that's at odds with his testimony! Go get him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay! Back in the matrix it is! <thought>Time to pinpoint our way to victory!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You must have thought it was very strange that the killer vanished into thin air.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I did! That kind of thing just doesn't happen, usually!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And yet, at that time, you barely registered any shock at the occurrence.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">What?! Why are you--?! Nngrrrh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can only think of one reason as to why you weren't surprised the killer's vanishing act. You must've had a good idea of where they went. Isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Whaaat?! No! O-Of course not...! That's preposterous! Only I can enter the control room... ...and the area beyond the launch pad door was filled with smoke, making it impassable! And as for the southern door... ...I was standing right there. So there was nowhere for the killer to run to.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe, or maybe not. You went into the room to check on Mr. Starbuck and Mr. Terran, yes? What if the culprit took that opportunity to silently slip out through the southern door?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I highly doubt it. As you recall, right after I entered the lounge... ...Detective Arme came rushing towards it herself via the southern hallway. Anyone trying to escape through there would have been caught by her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And yet, the director wasn't surprised the killer vanished...</thought> So you're absolutely sure there was no escape route for the culprit to use?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Ngh...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I was near the elevator-side door...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">and, well, the Launch Pad 1 door...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Correct me if I'm wrong, but you seem to be afraid of the launch pad door.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Th-The great Yuri Cosmos? Afraid?! A-And what basis do you have for that outlandish accusation?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whether I have basis or not, you seem quite distressed by it.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I-I'm most certainly not!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Director Cosmos! There's something about the launch pad door you're not telling us, isn't there?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Nghhhhh............! Gaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, he's speechless! It looks like you hit the nail on the head, Boss.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Ngh...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's working, Boss! One more punch and it'll be a knockout! There seems to be one more emotion that's at odds with his testimony! Go get him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay! Back in the matrix it is! <thought>Time to pinpoint our way to victory!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Correct me if I'm wrong, but you seem to be afraid of the launch pad door.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Th-The great Yuri Cosmos? Afraid?! A-And what basis do you have for that outlandish accusation?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whether I have basis or not, you seem quite distressed by it.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I-I'm most certainly not!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Director Cosmos! There's something about the launch pad door you're not telling us, isn't there?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Nghhhhh............! Gaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, he's speechless! It looks like you hit the nail on the head, Boss.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Ngh...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">...and the Control Room door should've been shut tight to the killer...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Talk about mixed feelings! He must be trying to account for a number of contradictions. Mr. Wright. Maybe this time we shouldn't just look for contradictory emotions... We should also look for emotions that should be there, but aren't.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess it shouldn't be a surprise that his mind is a convoluted place, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">He must have felt very shaken and distressed at the time. Let's focus on the fluctuations in his emotions and see what we can uncover!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'll just input those two pieces of data, and... Yes! Just what I wanted to see!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Presto chango! Less discord! It looks like we're on the right track!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Athena. <thought>Now to make sense of what we've learned... Director Cosmos wasn't surprised that the culprit suddenly vanished from the lounge. Which point to the possibility that he knew where the killer had escaped to. Furthermore, talking about the door to the launch pad made him uneasy. In other words, he's probably hiding something about the Launch Pad 1 door. When we put these two pieces together, only one solution to this puzzle comes to mind!</thought> Director Cosmos, did the real killer escape through here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. There's actually a secret corridor hidden there!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">What are you talking about?! There are no secret corridors there... or anywhere!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's what I was afraid of.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! I want no more irresponsible answers from you, is that clear?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please let me give that another shot, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The culprit went through the Launch Pad 1 door to escape, didn't they?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Yes... I mean, no...! Disaster to starboard! We're going to crash into an asteroid!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A master tactician, you are not.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">But the area beyond that door was filled with smoke, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............True, but this is still the only logical answer there is. If we can just figure out what the director is hiding about the Launch Pad 1 door... ...we should be able to iron out the logical inconsistencies.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Ngh... Grnk... B-But that door requires fingerprint recognition! Only Starbuck, Terran, and I have access! I don't see how the killer could've opened that security lock! Do you?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's an easy one. The killer was right there in the boarding lounge, meaning... ...there's a way he could have easily gotten past that security lock. <thought>Come to think of it, we did examine the prints on the fingerprint recognition device...</thought> I propose that the killer used this person's fingerprints to get past the security lock!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">That person's fingerprints were not found on the device. You sounded so sure, only to produce this nonsense. What were you thinking?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, well... I was thinking my curl could use a trim... GAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough. Free haircuts are to be gotten on your own time, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. Though I can't recommend Barber Blackquill if you value your head... <thought>Being in the lounge, the killer would've had access to a certain person's prints...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Starbuck was lying unconscious there in the boarding lounge. Anybody could have easily gotten past the security lock by using Mr. Starbuck's prints. And actually, Mr. Starbuck's prints are exactly what we found on the device's screen.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">............AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looks like he DOES have something to hide about the Launch Pad 1 door. And I'm betting it's got something to do with the culprit's escape route! But I don't have enough information to see the whole picture yet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">............You know, something just occurred to me... Would you like to hear it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Oh, yes! By all means!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There's a security camera in Boarding Lounge 1.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right, the one that recorded the victim and the defendant. What about it, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If the true culprit escaped into the Launch Pad 1 corridor... ...then that might be recorded on the security footage as well! Then, the mystery would be solved! What do you think of my logic?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I hope you didn't strain your faculties too much for that, Your Baldness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I beg your pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Look, if we play the security footage beyond this point...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! The footage cuts off!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The camera was running on backup power, but apparently the power cables were damaged. Most likely by the aftereffects of the explosion. There is no footage after this -- be it of criminals or space aliens...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... And I thought it was such a good idea, too...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Just because your grandchild is watching from the gallery... ...it doesn't mean you should try to show off too much... Grandpa Baldness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor Blackquill! How did you know about my grandchild...?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think his grandchild just learned a little about the harshness of the adult world...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Setting aside the issue of grandchildren, I'd like to have the witness continue. Director Cosmos, could you tell us more about when you entered the lounge?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">...Ngh... Graaagh... If I-I must...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I hid to avoid getting shot...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">After the killer vanished, I went into the lounge...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">...but that's when Detective Arme appeared from the elevator-side door!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">And then, the detective shot at me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">So you see, the killer could've only escaped to the launch pad, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think about Director Cosmos's emotional responses, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............Actually, my cat is really sick, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? Oh, I'm very sorry to hear that.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And on top of that, my dog just doesn't seem to want to play with me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............Umm, why are you telling me all this now?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Just humor me, okay? Now, when you heard about my cat... ...and then about my dog, which story made you feel sadder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The story about your cat, of course. It's only natural.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Exactly. That would be the natural reaction. But there's nothing natural about the director's reactions. I think how each individual reaction changes across the whole testimony will be the key.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sounds unnaturally complicated... <thought>But that somehow doesn't surprise me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Director Cosmos. Why were you so surprised when Detective Arme found you, and again when she fired? Isn't that a bit unnatural?!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">............Sadly, even great men such as myself have ordinary human feelings. Our bodies are bound by the forces of gravity and emotions. Even a great man such as myself experiences surprise on occasion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Umm, yes, I'm sure you do. But my real point... ...is not the fact that you were surprised, but rather, what you were surprised by.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Pardon me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">First, you were surprised when Detective Arme found you in the lounge. And, just after that, you were of course again surprised when she shot at you. But, considering what you were surprised about, a strange phenomenon occurs here. Director Cosmos, what is strange about your surprised reaction is the fact that you were...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were surprised when the detective found you, a self-styled "great man." And then you were surprised again when she fired warning shots at you. Would such a self-professed great man such as yourself be surprised by such things?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">............It is my duty to lead the human race into the future. If my life is put in danger... ...it is also my duty to be surprised and take precautions to save my life! If anything were to happen to me, what would become of the future of mankind?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Well, he certainly has a high opinion of himself. It looks like I got it wrong, in any case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wasn't there something you should have been more surprised by?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Hmph. A brave man such as myself is not so easily surprised! But being shot at -- now THAT would surprise anybody!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, when you put it that way... I guess I'm barking up the wrong tree here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, you were surprised when Detective Arme shot at you... ...but the surprise you felt when she found you in the lounge was much greater.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Gagh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The fact that you were more surprised by simply being found than by being shot at... ...suggests to me that you were conflicted about whatever it was you were doing there!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">The enemy has acquired a new weapon! Commence operation Hide Under Your Desk! AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Please tell me I finally sunk his battleship...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Boss, I'm getting less discord now! That must mean... ...he really is hiding something about that launch pad door.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And whatever he's hiding most likely has something to do with the killer's escape.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wonder what it could be?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If he was doing something suspicious around that door... ...maybe we can spot some changes between before he came to the room and after.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Detective Fulbright gave us a photo taken after the crime. Let's run a comparison. Let's see. This is the footage of the door before Director Cosmos arrived. And this is how the door looked after the director entered the lounge.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............Hey, look at that! <thought>There IS a change! Something's definitely different!</thought> Director Cosmos.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">What is it? What have you two been up to over there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Finding the answer to what you were doing when Detective Arme found you, that's what. And that answer lies clearly in this footage. All we have to do is compare it to the photo that was taken during the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Don't be ridiculous! If you really do have an answer, you'd have pointed it out already!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's asking for it. THIS is what changed directly after the incident...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Hmm... And how exactly did that change?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's such a futuristic building, it wouldn't be surprising if something like that could change!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Um, I think it would be pretty surprising...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I... guess you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">After all this time, your claim is what's surprising to me, Mr. Wright. Penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Director Spacecase won't fess up to anything without proof of what he did in that room...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The answer is this knob.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Ngaaaaah! That's--!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor, please take a look at this footage.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Let's see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a look at the knob next to the launch pad door. As you can see, it's horizontal.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, it is, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However... ...when we investigated the scene of the crime yesterday, the knob was vertical.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... And what does that mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It means that sometime between before the director arrived and after... ...someone turned this knob!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">After the scene was discovered, you were the only one who could have turned the knob. Come on, now, Director Cosmos! Let's hear what you have to say! What were you trying to do by turning that knob by the door?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Ngaaaaah! Fine! I admit it! You're right. I did turn that knob. That knob is a safety lock meant to keep the launch pad in place. I was afraid there would be more explosions... ...so I wanted to move the launch pad away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You wanted to do what...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, didn't Ponco tell us something about how they prepare for launch? She said that once the launch pad's fully assembled, it's moved to the launch site. But the safety lock in the boarding lounge has to be disengaged first.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess that clears up what that knob is for.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! So, if the killer escaped into the Launch Pad 1 corridor... ...maybe they were transported along with the launch pad to the launch site?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think so... The Launch Pad 1 corridor was filled with smoke. I don't think they could've escaped through that corridor.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So then, where DID the killer escape to?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>............Hmm... I guess there are still some things we have to uncover...</thought> Director Cosmos! I request that you tell us about moving the launch pad in more detail!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Fine! But listen carefully! For I'm about to give history-making testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I had no choice but to disengage the safety lock.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I feared there might be more explosions...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">...so I had to cut the launch pad loose.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Surely, the only escape the killer had was through Launch Pad 1.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">But that area was a sea of smoke...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Confound it! Where on Earth could they have gone?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The director seems driven into a corner now. I can tell he's having a hard time hiding his true feelings!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just one final push, then!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">His attempts to conceal the truth shouldn't be all that hard for us to break through. If we keep at it calmly, I'm sure we'll cross the finish line!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"I had no choice but to disengage the safety lock." You make it sound like you were reluctant to do so. And yet, when you did it, you felt some joy, as if you were very pleased with yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaagh! H-How do you do it?! How do you know everything as if you were there?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Pretty impressive, isn't it? This is the power of analytical psychology!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, care to explain why you felt joy when you disengaged the safety lock? When I think back on the facts we've discovered up to this point... ...I have to believe that you were trying to fulfill some hidden agenda.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">.........Aaaaaaaaaaaaaagh! How do you know about THAT, too?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because I'm more or less a pro... <thought>...At guessing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">B-But, you have no proof that I had a hidden agenda! And even if I did, I would never, ever tell you! So there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know they say people regress as they grow older, but you, sir, take the cake...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">And how could you doubt a man with such great intensity, intelligence, and integrity?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............You? A man of integrity? Don't make me laugh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Prosecutor Blackquill? <thought>What came over him all of a sudden?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You've spouted nothing but falsities since you stepped up to the stand. You're not the kind of man that will be glorified in the annals of history. Not for greatness, anyway............ Unless you consider "greatest barefaced liar" an honor.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">L-L-L-LIIIIIIIAAAAAAAR?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*gulp* His words bite harder than his blade...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You moved Launch Pad 1 AFTER the explosions? My, how nave you are. You fail to realize how even the facts themselves have betrayed you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know... Just a thought, but modern English can be your friend...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">And here's a thought for you. Immediately following the bombing... ...Launch Pad 1 was on the Boarding Lounge 1 side. The police confirmed this on scene.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">L-L-L-LIIIIIIIAAAAAAAR?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So that means... the director DIDN'T move the launch pad?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Curse my judgment for calling history's greatest liar to the witness stand. Let us leave him to indulge in his lies and war games to his heart's content.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">L-L-L-LIIIIIIIAAAAAAAR?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You're "sure" it "must've" went somewhere? We "just might" find out? Your arguments are nothing but conjecture, bluffing, and wishful thinking. Stop chasing your fantasies, and see reality for what it really is. Or are you not man enough to, boy?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">GAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ha ha, talk about hitting below the belt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Y-Young'uns these days...! I don't understand it. I'm sure Director Cosmos must have moved the launch pad... The knob was definitely turned after we came to the lounge. But the launch pad is right where it's supposed to be... Argh! ............! Wait a minute. Maybe I have it all backwards!</thought> What if the director turned the knob -- not to move the launch pad away... ...but to bring it back to where it was supposed to be?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...What are you blathering about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What if the launch pad was at the launch site before the incident? And then, after the incident... ...Director Cosmos moved it back to its usual spot? All he had to do was turn the knob to call the launch pad back... ...and it would be right where the police found it! GAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You made him sigh like Mr. Starbuck.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was what I said really THAT off-base?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It pains me to have to explain how wrong your own logic is to you, however... ...our great liar turned the knob only after he discovered the crime scene. Indeed, the pad existed beyond the lounge when our astro-wonders made their escape. A fact that has been recorded for posterity on filmless film.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">So, to reiterate... Stop chasing your fantasies, and see reality for what it really is, boy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Get a grip, Mr. Wright, and focus! We know the launch pad must've been moved...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But our deductions and the actual facts of the case are in direct contradiction to each other.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, maybe the two astronauts never actually boarded the rocket! This footage could be fake -- taken with body doubles after the incident or something! ............On second thought, that's too far-fetched, even for me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............"Never actually boarded the rocket"...? ............Hey, wait a minute! Maybe, just maybe...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Prosecutor Blackquill! What if I told you that the two astronauts... ...never set foot inside the launch pad area, but instead, went into another place? And what if when the director moved Launch Pad 1 back, it was not from the launch site... ...but from another place. What would you say then?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Cut the existential bull or I'll cut you.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, you will explain yourself at once!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I know I'm right. It was all the other way around from the beginning!</thought> Very well, Your Honor. Let me explain. Director Cosmos's reason for moving Launch Pad 1 was...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because he wanted to hide Launch Pad 1!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, well, let's suppose he did move it. Where in the world would he hide it? An enormous launch pad like that... I highly doubt it could truly be hidden.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, uh... behind something, maybe...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Are you asking me or telling me?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk. <thought>Looks like I messed that up...</thought> Your Honor! Please let me give it another try!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because he wanted to trap the true killer!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Hmph. Wright-dono, need I remind you there was an explosion? And that the corridor between the launch pad and the lounge was thick with smoke? If the killer had been trapped in there, they would've been found as dead as their victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I guess you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I'm glad you both agree. Now here's a penalty for you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't agree with that penalty, though...</thought> Your Honor! Please give me another chance!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because he wanted to switch it with some other place!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sorry, but did you say, "switch it"? But what could he possibly have switched the launch pad with?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, you'd be surprised, Your Honor. All it takes is a little thinking outside the box, and the answer becomes clear as day! This is what was switched with Launch Pad 1!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I dunno. You know how these things work, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I don't.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't either. But I do know there is a penalty for you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What could've been switched with Launch Pad 1...? It really can only be that place?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Launch Pad 1 was switched with... the Space Museum?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In the past, the Space Museum used to be Launch Pad 2. It has all the same features as Launch Pad 1, and can even be moved to the launch site. Meaning, the Space Museum and Launch Pad 1 can also be switched with each other.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-You can't mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The rocket the astronauts boarded was not the one in Launch Pad 1. It was the one in the Space Museum!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">BALDERDAAAAAAAAAAAAAAASH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And yet, it's the only explanation that accounts for every riddle and inconsistency. This is how the Space Center was just before the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see Launch Pad 1 and the Space Museum have already switched placed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. And with the two switched like this... ...the astronauts entered the Space Museum from Boarding Lounge 1. This allowed the true killer to enter Launch Pad 1 from Boarding Lounge 2... ...and set the bomb on the rocket.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Come to think of it, the door to the Space Museum from Boarding Lounge 2...</line>
<line speaker="Ponco">Welcome! Welcome! The Space Museum is open to the public every day of the year from 9 AM to 7 PM!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. Anyone could pass through the door to the Space Museum. There is no fingerprint recognition system on that door. In other words, with the two launch pads switched like that... ...someone other than Mr. Starbuck could have easily planted that bomb!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">GAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">After setting the bomb on the rocket... ...the culprit snuck into Boarding Lounge 1 and waited there, concealed... ...in order to kill Mr. Terran when the two astronauts emerged from the Space Museum. Recall that Ms. Blackquill, Mr. Starbuck, and the director all saw a suspicious figure... ...who, we can suppose, after killing Mr. Terran... ...made their escape into the Space Museum. After that, Director Cosmos switched the two launch pads back... ...without realizing the killer was inside the Space Museum. The killer then left the Space Museum and made a clean getaway!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Ngaaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Wright-dono, I see you know how to handle a sword, and handle it well. Perhaps I should call you Swordmaster Bluff?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm a seasoned warrior who has cut down many a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">But unless you can prove your theory, it's no better than a rusty sword.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Th-That's right! You have no proof I switched the launch pads!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...SOMEBODY needs a better anger management counselor...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">If the launch pads really were switched, there might be a record of it somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At this point, Launch Pad 1 and the Space Museum were switched with each other.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So the corridor beyond the door should be the one that belongs to the Space Museum. Let's see. This is an image of the Launch Pad 1 corridor. Do you see anything different when we compare it to the security footage?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? <thought>Th-That number on the floor...!</thought> Well, what do you know? It looks like we have proof after all, Prosecutor Blackquill.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............And if this is just another bluff?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, don't worry. It's all right here. Right in this footage. Proof that, beyond this door, is the corridor to the Space Museum!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, then. Answer this for me, if you would. What in this footage proves that the corridor belongs to the Space Museum?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm? What about that constitutes "proof"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Doesn't it kind of somehow give you the feeling that a switch has been made?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not in the slightest! And please refrain from using the words "kind of somehow" when presenting proof!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well... Wanna take another look at the Launch Pad 1 corridor again? OK, here's the footage of the Launch Pad 1 corridor. Do you see anything different when we compare it to the security footage?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right! <thought>The number on the floor...!</thought> Please give me another chance, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, if I must. Now then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a "1" on the floor of the Launch Pad 1 corridor. But take a look at the floor of the corridor in the security footage. Do you see the number on the floor behind the astronauts? It doesn't look like a "1," does it? That's because what you see is actually part of a "2."</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Wh-What?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why is it a "2" and not a "1"? That's because the corridor you see is the one to the Space Museum!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">GAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaagh....!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And so that means... ...the corridor in this footage was NOT filled with smoke.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right, because the explosion didn't occur in the Space Museum. The explosion occurred in Launch Pad 1, on the side opposite the Space Museum. And now that we know the two astronauts escaped from the Space Museum... ...the mystery from the previous trial of how they got down the ladder is cleared up. Mr. Terran, carrying Mr. Starbuck... ...simply took the elevator from the upper level down to the middle level.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Just incredible. The two launch pads were actually switched... But you'd think someone would've noticed an event of this magnitude.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Everyone was down in the basement shelter when the launch pads were swapped back. There's no way anyone could have known what was happening on the surface.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">GNNNNNNNNNNNNNNGH! GAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No more lies, Director Cosmos! It's high time you told us the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">GAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH! My honor! My glory! Everything is slipping away! Time to deploy my ultimate weapon! Galactic Engine....... Ignition! WHAAAAAAAAAT?! It's gone haywire! AAAAAAAAAAGH! It won't st-stoooooooop! GAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH! M-My stars! My glory! Gaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh! GAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH! Ngaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah! No! Not that way! GAAAAAAAGH! NGAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-B-Bailiff! On your steed and after that witness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see we managed to retrieve you before you came to any bodily harm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Director Cosmos, do you admit you switched the launch pads?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Ngh... I admit it's true... I switched Launch Pad 1 for the Space Museum.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahh, it is good to hear words I can believe for a change.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............Before you do, Your Honor, two things. First, we don't know if Mr. Terran had prior knowledge of the switch. As for Mr. Starbuck, he was unaware of his surroundings thanks to his medication. Either way, Mr. Terran would've realized the instant he stepped into the Space Museum... ...that it had been switched with Launch Pad 1. So my first question is, if the Space Museum was perfectly fine... ...why did Mr. Terran feel the need to put on such a dramatic display? As for my second question... I'd like Director Cosmos to tell us... ...why he switched the two launch pads to begin with.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Nnngh... Please... I can't... I... I exercise my right to remain silent... But I will say... my hands were tied... I was only doing what I could to keep my men from getting caught in that blast. Nngh... Nnnggggh...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The director is... terrified. He must have one heck of a reason for not wanting to explain why.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Probably not a good time to try to pry it out of him, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">............Excuse me... but would you mind if I picked up my stars? Without my badge of rank, I'm nothing...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't see why not. Bailiff, help the director retrieve his stars.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It appears the possibility of a culprit other than the defendant has presented itself. Mr. Starbuck, is there anything you wish to say?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">............I don't get it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Don't get it"? What don't you get?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Director, why did you do all that? From the very beginning, you never meant for the launch to go ahead, did you? Y-You...! You tricked us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Starbuck...!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Starbuck, my boy. I'm sorry. I can't tell you the reason why... But I had to do it to protect the Space Center.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Director! Will I... Will I ever get the chance to go into space again...?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">...Yes. Yes, of course! I won't rest until it happens! I WILL get you into space again, my boy...</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Then the dream... is still alive...!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Hmph. You're not going into space, Starbuck, but prison. I won't have it any other way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why are you so hung up on him?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Yes, I accept that the launch pads really were switched... And if there were a third person at the scene, I suppose they could have escaped... But I have yet to see proof of this third person's escape via the Space Museum.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! That's a good point!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>............Argh! He's right... I don't have any proof!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Starbuck! You will spill everything you know!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">What?! Me?! Aaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Where did you get those bombs?! Tell me now! If you don't... my blade shall feast on your blood!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Gaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh! If I'm going to die! I want to die in space!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I have to do something...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Solomon Starbuck! ............Prepare yourself! NNN-GAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ha ha ha ha ha! Now, now, you know violence isn't the answer, Prosecutor Blackquill!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ngh. That annoyingly cheerful laugh... It can be none other than............</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Champion of Righteousness, Bobby Fulbright, here! In justice we trust!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Detective Fulbright?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Sorry to keep you waiting, Mr. Lawyer. I hope I'm not too late!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't believe we had an appointment...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">I tried to hurry, but I ended up helping a little old lady cross the street... ...and then I had to break up a catfight... I tell ya, justice sure is a full-time job!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was it a fight between cats, or...? ............*ahem* Why are you here again?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Because! The defendant isn't the culprit! And I came to make sure that justice is served!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Uh, I don't have any idea what you're talking about...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Fool Bright. I always thought you were a bit touched in the head, but have you finally succumbed?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Nope, but it looks like you've succumbed to this "phantom" of yours. Open your eyes, and let the Evidence of Justice uncloud your judgment!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Come to think of it, he did say something about finding us some evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Thanks, you two. I feel a lot better now that I've been able to get that off my chest. I'm going to work extra hard to find that perfect piece of evidence for you!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I didn't think he was serious, though...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what is it, detective? Is it something that will prove Mr. Starbuck innocent?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">It is, indeed! Have a look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this? A lighter?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's right! A lighter thought to have been used by the culprit, no less! The Space Museum's cleaning robot picked it up! It has the victim Clay Terran's blood, along with his killer's fingerprints on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WH-WH-WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">GAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Detective Fulbright! Can I assume that the fingerprints don't belong to the defendant?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">You bet! Mr. Starbuck is totally innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is it! This is just what I needed!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! This is decisive evidence that supports the defense's earlier claim!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Explain yourself, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">With pleasure, Your Honor. Recall where this lighter was found. Based on that, we can extrapolate that after the killer murdered Mr. Terran... ...they escaped with lighter in hand into the Space Museum... ...where they dropped it. The switching of the two launch pads occurred... Then finally, the killer left through Boarding Lounge 2 and made their escape. Meanwhile, Mr. Starbuck was found in Boarding Lounge 1 after the murder... A fact that Director Cosmos has testified to. Therefore... Mr. Starbuck couldn't have possibly been the one to drop the lighter there!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ah, but the defendant had free reign of the area until Director Cosmos appeared. Could he not have dropped the lighter in the Space Museum during that span of time?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ngrh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Most importantly, Mr. Starbuck's fingerprints were nowhere to be found on this lighter. I think you understand what this means, don't you? This piece of evidence unequivocally proves that Mr. Starbuck wasn't the culprit!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">GAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This does indeed appear to be decisive evidence that proves the defense's claims.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As for the remote switch that was found in Mr. Starbuck's pocket... ...we can assume it was planted by the killer on the unconscious Mr. Starbuck.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">N-No... There must be some mistake...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Frankly, Prosecutor Blackquill, I've been worried about you. You've been chasing this "phantom" for seven whole years. I understand your urgency because tomorrow--</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Fool Bright. You promised never to speak of that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? Tomorrow? What about tomorrow?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Given the body of evidence, I think it's safe to say the defendant is innocent... ...in light of the fact that it was impossible for him to have committed the crime. A few unanswered questions remain, so I look forward to seeing what you two uncover. But for now, this court finds the defendant, Solomon Starbuck...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes! We did it, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like we pulled it off somehow, huh? <thought>With some help from Detective Fulbright.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Mr. Wright, Miss Cykes, thank you! And please thank Apollo for me, too. You all are the best!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, I wish we could tell Apollo about Mr. Starbuck's verdict right now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, me too. <thought>But that's going to have to wait...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now that a verdict has been reached... ...I'd like to bring today's trial to a close. Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............It simply isn't possible... Something's wrong...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">P-Prosecutor Blackquill? Are you dissatisfied with the verdict...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Fool Bright! What were the results of the fingerprint analysis for the lighter!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Huh? The results...? Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Uh, well... I was in a hurry, you see, and then there was that catfight, and, well... ...I kinda got carried away when I heard the prints weren't Mr. Starbuck's, so...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Y-You have yet to read it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Prosecutor Blackquill! Can you read out who the prints belong to?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............ "Upon thorough analysis, the fingerprints... ............ ...were found to belong to Athena Cykes." So says the report.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">M-Me?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Order, I say! Order! Ms. Cykes! Tell me you have an explanation for this! We just finished proving that this lighter could only belong to the killer. So finding your prints on it can only leads us to one grave conclusion!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I don't know how they got on there! But I KNOW I'M not the culprit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Th-This can't be happening...! We built up our argument piece by piece... And I don't think any of our reasoning was faulty... So how could it have lead [sic] to this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Gaaaaaaaaaagh! Wh-What have I done?! Please forgive me! I'm sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Detective Fulbright! Stop your crying!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What in the world is happening here?! It's like the world's gone mad!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! I WILL HAVE ORDER!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Confusion spiraled into utter chaos. After all we'd fought for, the truth had turned cruelly on us to accuse Athena of the crimes. Somewhere, somehow, everything had gone terribly wrong... We had stumbled over the edge of reason and into the jaws of a twisted darkness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I'm afraid I just don't see it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not even with your sharp and discerning eye, Your Honor...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid not. But you claim to see it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, not really, Your Honor. I thought maybe you would...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh-oh. Now the judge is mad at me. Maybe I'd better take another look at the evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I hope you don't think waving your finger about aimlessly... ...is going to help you win this trial!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I agree. I see nothing inconsistent with that evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk! <thought>I must have the wrong evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It does?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Certainly, Your Baldness. The defense's bone-headedness. There is nothing untoward about that evidence, no matter how he blusters.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I agree. There is nothing compelling in that evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm definitely losing the judge's confidence in me here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright, I don't see any inconsistencies in the testimony. This might be a good time to--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Press for more information? I think you're right. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I just can't help but feel that there's more to these statements than meets the eye.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll put my faith in Athena and press them for all their worth, then!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright! I think I have something here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You sensed something wrong with the testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right. Let me show you which statement I thought was strange!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks. That would be a big help! <thought>Now I just have to compare the evidence with the statement she points out!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When we view your emotions alongside your testimony, we find the unexpected emotion-- <thought>Wait a minute... There really isn't anything strange here.</thought>    </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't know, but I think maybe we made a mistake, Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......I think maybe you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's take another look! There must be an unexpected emotion here somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The defense's case is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims! This court finds the defendant, Solomon Starbuck...</line>
</xml>