
<xml>
<title>The Monstrous Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Man">Night night, Alderman! Sweet dreams! At long last, the revival of Tenma Taro is at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hm.  Guess I'm a little early.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, hey, Apollo! Getting an early start today?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah! This is the first job I've had in a while after all!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, aren't we all fired up!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, it's not every day I get a call from Mr. Wright. What kind of work is it anyway? Mr. Wright didn't mention any details.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Work? Is that how he put it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Don't tell me he just wants me to clean the toilet again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You've really become a fixture around here, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Come to think of it, it's been almost a year since I was hired. A lot's happened since then... ...But I've settled in nicely despite a few bumps in the road.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">My name is Apollo Justice. I've been practicing law for about a year, but I still have a lot to learn. This is the Wright Anything Agency, and it's where I work. Don't let the name fool you -- It's definitely a law agency.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But don't forget that this place is a "talent agency" too, Polly!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uhh, it's the "law agency" part of this office that's usually forgotten... This is Trucy Wright, a budding magician... ...and adopted daughter of the agency's owner, Phoenix Wright. She sometimes makes me help with her magic tricks.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And what's wrong with that? You're one of the agency's "talents" as well!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I was under the impression that I was a lawyer...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, we'd better hurry. Doesn't look Daddy's going to make it, so let's get going.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Where are we going? What about the job he mentioned?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This IS the job, Polly! You're supposed to keep me company today! Now, come on!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Another day of not being a lawyer. Should've seen this coming.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, this is the "Wright ANYTHING Agency," y'know. And there's no law-related work at the moment, so...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Tell me again why I chose to "work" here?</thought> Where is Mr. Wright, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy said something about going to meet an acquaintance. But don't worry. Just focus on your job, and I'll tell you exactly what you need to know. Well, let's go. We don't have all day!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait a second! <thought>*sigh* And another day of "anything goes" begins at the Wright Anything Agency...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whew... So, what are we doing way up here in the mountains?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This is Nine-Tails Vale. Everyone's been talking about the yokai craze here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yokai? Oh, you mean Japanese monsters? Guess that explains all these weird things... Speaking of which, wasn't Nine-Tails Vale founded by Japanese immigrants?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah. They're holding a festival to boost tourism over at the alderman's manor. My friend who works there invited us. That's why we're here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">In other words, I'm your chaperon because your dad was too busy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy said that with those horns of yours, you'd make a great addition to their festival. I mean, you look just like a Japanese demon! Wasn't that so thoughtful of him, Polly?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I could do without thoughtfulness like that.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, it's almost time! Come on, Polly! The festival grounds are this way.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Alright, I guess it's time to move to the "Kyubi Manor's Garden"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This monster craze... Come to think of it, I think I heard about it on TV. It's supposedly how Nine-Tails Vale made a comeback from the brink of fiscal disaster.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... Our agency could sure use something positive like that. Oh, I know! Let's jump on board the monster craze! You and daddy would be a perfect comedy duo! You could call yourselves Agni &amp; Rudra, Demon Kings of Comedy! Daddy sets them up, and you knock 'em down! Hey, I think we hit the jackpot with this idea!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... Sorry, but I plan on staying a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You do?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>You don't have to act so surprised by that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, Trucy? Have you seen my attorney's badge?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">How could you lose something so important? Sometimes I really wonder about you, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is so weird. I wonder if I dropped it somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, look! What are these panties doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Forget about panties. I'm looking for my badge.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">3, 2, 1... Ta-dah! Did you forget? These are my magic panties!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......Hey! That's my attorney's badge! Wow! How'd you do that?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I set it all up while we were back at the office.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, I didn't even-- Wait, you took my badge?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Check it out.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You're so lucky, Apollo. Everyone can see what you do with just a flash of your badge.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What about you, Trucy? People can tell you're a magician by the way you're dressed.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah, but I can't always dress like this. Like when I'm at school and stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You could always show you're a magician by making things appear or disappear.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You mean like this? 3, 2, 1... Ta-dah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Umm, magic or no, aren't you a little old to be showing those things in public?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... Then maybe I'll become a lawyer, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're abandoning your dream just like that?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, this place is really something.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It definitely feels like a different world here.</line>
<line speaker="???">Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Jinxie!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And this is?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">My friend, Jinxie Tenma. She's the one who invited us. She just happens to be the maid here.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">...Two horns. A love of red. Are you a demon?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, ha ha. I'm Apollo Justice! Nice to meet you!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Eeeeeek! He IS a demon!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What the--!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Be gone, foul beast!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hee hee! You look great, Polly. Fills in some of that space on your forehead!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Argh... What is this thing?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's a warding charm. Jinxie puts them on all the monsters she finds.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, but I'm not a monster.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe I should have told her you're a good demon.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Or you could just say I'm human.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">*shiver* The red demon, emissary of the Underworld.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I got up early to do my hair for this?</thought> Um, can I take this off now?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">So you can eat me?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm not going to eat you!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Eek! Forgive me, O terrible one!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Tone down your Chords of Steel, Apollo. You're scaring her out of her wits!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, don't worry. I'm already full.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Please stay that way.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Great, now I'm playing along, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, so I wanted to ask you about Nine-Tails Vale...</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Eeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aaaaugh!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Be gone, foul demon!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Looks like you've been demonized, Polly, literally!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm starting to wonder if I really am a demon myself. Um...</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Eek! Please don't eat me. I have food if you're hungry.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This isn't working. We won't get anything out of her until we set the record straight.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmmm... If only we had some way to prove you're not as scary as you look.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ouch, unnecessary roughness... Looks like I have to present some proof. Proof that I'm 100% human!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Would you mind taking a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Eeeeek! No, thank you! Be gone, foul demon!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack, banished again.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's what you get when you flash a girl like that -- even if it was just your badge.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sheesh, you make it sound like I'm some kind of creep.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, I wanted to show you this.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Eek! What is it?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's my attorney's badge. You see? I'm not a demon, I'm a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Really?! …You're a lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Whew... Maybe now she'll stop calling me a demon.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Does it protect you from Enma Dai-O's judgment?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who's Enma Dai-O?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I read somewhere that's [sic] he's the demon lord who punishes the dead for their sins. Uh-oh! I think now she thinks you're a demon lawyer from hell, Polly!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can I go back to being just a normal demon?!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Please... Please don't boil me in a scalding cauldron. I'd prefer a Turkish bath if possible.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A Turkish bath? Isn't that more sauna than bath?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't worry, Jinxie, he's a good demon. He'll save you if you ever go astray!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Eek! Please, Mr. Demon Lawyer, sir, have mercy on my soul!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Argh! I told you, I'm not a demon! And Trucy, you're just making things wors--! <thought>Ack!</thought> Umm... You just leave that Enma Dai-O to me.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Isn't that great, Jinxie?!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. I'm no longer scared to cross into the afterlife.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Will someone tell these two I'm human, already!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, Jinxie, I hear this village is the epicenter of the monster craze.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. Barely anyone had even heard of it before, but now it's packed with tourists.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? So, the monster craze is the reason behind today's festival?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">It was the alderman's idea. But I'd be careful if I were you. There are lots and lots of yokai prowling about Nine-Tails Vale.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prowling about? You mean like wild animals or something?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. And they're hungry, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Man-eating monsters?! And they're all over the place?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. In fact, there was one at the manor yesterday. I heard the doorbell ring, but when I opened the door, nobody was there. It was the Ding-Dong Demon! How else could you explain it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well... When I was a kid, my friends used to play this prank called Ding-Dong Ditch.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Well, that doesn't prove yokai aren't real. There's even one here at the manor. The demon Tenma Taro -- he's imprisoned in the Forbidden Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tenma... Taro? The Forbidden Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, about that yokai you said was imprisoned here at the manor. Is it true?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. He's a super evil demon named Tenma Taro. Here, take a look at this scroll. Tenma Taro's the dark demon you see here. He's super evil and super scary.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So that's the yokai imprisoned in the Forbidden Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. He was defeated by the village guardian yokai, the Nine-Tailed Fox... ...and locked away forever.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... you're saying Tenma Taro is still trapped inside the Forbidden Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. But he's just biding his time until he can escape. Still, we should be perfectly safe! Because there's a reeeally powerful sealing charm on the door keeping it shut tight!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What a... charming security system.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">You can keep the scroll if you want. The alderman gave me this, but just holding it gives me the chills, so...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah, uh, thanks, Jinxie. <thought>Maybe I'll give this to Mr. Wright.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">So you really are a demon lawyer. Ummm... So, then, you must know Enma Dai-O, the Appraiser of Souls. What's he like?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's he like?! Well, uh... he's um... He's bald, has a white beard, and...</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">A-A-And what?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He shouts, "Guilty!" and "Order!", while banging his gavel. I call him "The Judge."</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Oh, wow, he's as scary as I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nah, he's just an old man who's wiser than you might think.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... I was wondering... Are those things on your forehead also warding charms, Jinxie?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Yes, they're to prevent evil things from getting inside me. Papa told me to wear them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Evil things?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo, don't you dare take those charms off her forehead! They HAVE to stay there... forever! Got it?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I wonder what would happen if I did take them off...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">It's time for me to get back to work.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Thanks for inviting us, Jinxie!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">You're welcome. Oh, and before I forget... There's going to be a surprise event today. Even I don't know what's to expect, but it's sure to be fun.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Better not be a yokai parade. She'd probably drop dead from fright.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">.........Hm? .........Eeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ahhh! D-D-Demon! <thought>Oh, wait... It's just someone in a suit... right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">T-T-Tenma T-Taro!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tenma Taro? <thought>The demon from the Forbidden Chamber?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Eeeeeek! Please don't hurt me! Be gone! Be gone! Be gone!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma Taro">Hissssssss! Better watch out little girl, or I'll snatch you away!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Eek! Charm charm charm...! Where's that "Die and Go To Heaven" charm?!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, she put it on her own forehead this time!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...She sure gives up quick. <thought>Huh? Why's everyone hiding their faces?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Villager">Hey, you there! You mustn't stare at Tenma Taro like that! Lower your eyes! He'll steal your soul if you're not careful!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? <thought>Steal my soul? Seriously?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Your devilry stops here and now, Tenma Taro!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now what?!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look, Apollo! There's somebody up on the roof!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah-ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Villager">That booming laugh! Could it be...!</line>
<line speaker="???">My nine golden tails are proof of my unassailable righteousness! With my band of 100 minions, I vanquish evil from the land! I am the wrestler of righteousness! Ya-ha! The golden lord of yokai, The Amazing Nine-Tails, is here! Fear not, good little boys and girls! For I shall defeat Tenma Taro! Ah-ha ha ha ha ha! Ah-ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Villager">Hurray! Hurray! It's The Amazing Nine-Tails!</line>
<line speaker="Wrestler">Up to your no good tricks again, eh, Tenma Taro?! Well, not on my watch!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma Taro">Aaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Wrestler">A-ha ha ha ha ha ha! There's nothing to fear now, my child! I have banished Tenma Taro! You and your people can now live in peace!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Th-Thank you, Mr. Amazing Nine-Tails, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Wrestler">Now, I must be off! Another match and another foe to vanquish, await!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-What was that all about? Did that wrestler just chase off a yokai? Looked like he came out of the alderman's manor.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">That was The Amazing Nine-Tails! He's a pro wrestler from right here in Nine-Tails Vale. But no one knows his true identity!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Jinxie sure seems chipper all of a sudden.</thought> What was all that about him banishing Tenma Taro?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">That was a yokai exorcism. It's an annual ritual where Tenma Taro is released, to remind us of his wickedness. In the end, the Nine-Tailed Fox drives Tenma Taro out, and purifies our village. But The Amazing Nine-Tails did the honors this year!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So that was the big surprise, huh? The Amazing Nine-Tails and Tenma Taro, huh... Well, whatever floats her boat.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Oh, would you look at the time. I'd better get back to work. Please excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She's a strange one, all right.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I think she's sweet in own her [sic] special way.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Knowing Trucy, she probably has lots of friends who are "sweet" in their own way.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, we still have some time to kill. Might as well see the rest of Nine-Tails Vale while we're here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The fun never stops, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I think I bought nearly every yokai souvenir that was for sale.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know, because my wallet's running on empty.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hm? What's with all the commotion over there?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Hey, isn't that your friend Jinxie?! I hope everything's okay.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">I-I-It's t-t-terrible! Th-Th-Thththth...! The--! The--!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Calm down, Jinxie! Tell us what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Th-Th-The demon T-Tenma T-Taro... ...He killed Alderman Kyubi!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait, killed as in dead?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Yes. And Tenma Taro did it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tenma Taro?! You stay here while I go have a look.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">P-Please, wait!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...? Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">It's a... Tenma Taro Warding Charm. It should protect you, but please... be careful. The alderman's in the Fox Chamber at the top of the main staircase.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, got it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What...? AAAAAAAAAGH! Huh? Are you alright?</line>
<line speaker="Man">Who are you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Help! Someone call an ambulance!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The police arrived soon after that, at which point I returned to the festival grounds. Apparently, the man impaled by the spear was already dead. But there was one other person there, and he was immediately rushed to the hospital.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thank goodness the other man's going to be fine. Sounds like he'd only been unconscious.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You think Jinxie's going to be okay?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sure she'll be back to her old self in no time. At least she's calm enough for the police to question her for now. <thought>And I'd sure love to know what crazy animal left those feathers and tracks...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, look, here comes Jinxie.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">...Hi, Trucy. ...Hi, Mr. Demon Lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Heya... Feeling any better? ...I was wondering if you're up to filling us in on what happened...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, the man with the spear in his chest was already dead?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. It was Alderman Kyubi. When I found him, he was already...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So the victim was the village alderman...</thought> And the one who was found alive? Who was he?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Damian Tenma. He's the mayor of the neighboring city, Tenma Town. They arrested him. *sob*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... he's the killer? Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Nuh-uh! Papa didn't kill anyone!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Papa? As in... your father?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right. Jinxie's dad is mayor of Tenma Town.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No way!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Errr... Yes, way, but he's innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This just got way more complicated. The victim was the alderman of Nine-Tails Vale. And Jinxie's father, the mayor of Tenma Town, was arrested for the crime. Sounds like we have some investigating to do.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I know this is difficult, Jinxie, but you need to hang in there!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">I know. I'll try my best.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Would you mind telling me a little more about the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So the victim was the village alderman? What can you tell me about him?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">His name was Rex Kyubi. They say his family has ties to the legendary Nine-Tailed Fox. He was really kind, and he always looked out for me. He was a former pro wrestler, and I even heard he knew The Amazing Nine-Tails.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A former pro wrestler, huh... Hmm... That's something to keep in mind.</thought> With your father being mayor and all, I guess you're originally from Tenma Town, huh? So then, why did you come work here?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It was to overcome your fears, right, Jinxie?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. Plus, Mama was from Nine-Tails Vale, though she's no longer with us. She loved these flowers. I always wanted to live where Nine-Tails flowers grew.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, what a beautiful flower. And with exactly nine petals, too!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Just looking at them gives me courage, even when I'm scared of yokai.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">They sell those at the village souvenir shop.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They really went all out, making it look like a real scroll and all.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">By rolling it up like that, you can't see Tenma Taro's picture. It's so you don't lose your soul if you accidentally gazed upon him. Even if it is a souvenir, no one in this village wants to accidentally see what's inside!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I've heard of losing or selling your soul for many things, but for the price of a souvenir?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">I wonder how many innocent shop girls have fallen victim. *shivers*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wouldn't it be better not to sell them at all?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">That warding charm is my supernatural security system. It protects me from yokai -- ghosts, demons, and other things that go bump in the night! Just the other day, I was chased down by a demented camera demon. But I drove him back with my trusty warding charm!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Camera demon? Sounds more like an overexcited tourist.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Still, I suppose it's not nice to repel every yokai I meet. I mean, there are some that aren't all bad. I learned that today.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Um... Why is she staring at me like that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Jinxie, when you first told us what happened, you said the killer was a demon.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. The warding charm on the Forbidden Chamber's door... It's been... removed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The Forbidden Chamber's door? That big door that was barred shut? There wasn't a charm on it when I check it out, so I guess it was removed by someone...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">That's how Tenma Taro escaped! Ooh... Ooooooh! But when... when I try and remember what happened, it all goes... fuzzy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Jinxie, you should do get some rest. You've been through a lot today.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Between the warding charm being removed, and the black feathers and weird tracks... ...I could see how a superstitious person might think a demon was the killer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Maybe this is your chance.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Chance for what?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">To do the right thing and defend Jinxie's dad in court!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who, me? Wouldn't a man like Mayor Tenma have access to more experienced lawyers?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Umm... You wanna know what the detectives said? They doubted there was a lawyer who could get a not-guilty verdict in this one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sounds like they're expecting an open and shut case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't worry, Jinxie! If anyone can prove your dad's innocence, it's Polly!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wha--?!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You'll accept the case, won't you, Polly!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Ooh... It's all over, isn't it? I'll... I'll be all alone... for the rest of my life.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, right... Jinxie already lost her mother.</thought> ...All right. Jinxie, leave your father's defense to me!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Atta boy, Polly!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">You're going to help Papa, Mr. Demon Lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yep, because that's what lawyers do. <thought>Plus, no toilet cleaning for a while!</thought> I'll do whatever it takes to make sure your father walks away a free man!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Th-Thank you, Mr. Demon Lawyer! I can tell you're one of the good ones. Red Demons are usually so mean.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's been awhile, but I'll be fine! Ready or not, here comes Justice! Guess I oughta go and meet my new client.</thought> Ah, but before I forget... <thought>Better jot this down in my notebook.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, Apollo, what's the notebook for?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, I just thought I should jot down some stuff about the case. And so I don't misplace them, I'm putting my Notes in the Court Record. I guess it's what you would call a "To-Do" list.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh? Sounds handy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>To read my notes, I just open the Court Record with R. Then I can switch between the tabs using L and R.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, I almost forgot! So, about Jinxie's father... No matter how scary he seems, promise me you'll resist the urge to run away!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, what?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">His angry glare can paralyze you with fear.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And some claim he can even shoot laser beams from his eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Well, maybe Papa isn't really THAT scary...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A paralyzing stare... Laser beams from his eyes... He sounds like some kind of monster.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hm, I think it's about time I see Jinxie off. I'll head back to the office after I'm done.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah, visiting hours. Perfect timing. <thought>Hope he's not as scary as he sounds...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...Who are you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yikes!</thought> S-So you're Damian Tenma, r-right?! I'm, uhh... I'm Apollo Justice, attorney-at-law! I'm here to, uhh... I'm here to help! Huh? Aaaaaaaaaaah! <thought>Lemme outta here!</thought> S-Sorry, sorry! I get a little loud sometimes!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">How... incredibly... RUDE!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Umm, sorry. Did I do something to offend you?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">A visitor when all others shun me like a common criminal! And here I am with nothing to offer! I am the epitome of rude!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>.........Wait, so he wasn't mad at me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Unworthy as I am, I, Damian Tenma, shall breach these walls... ...so that I may treat my benefactor to some tea, and maybe some cookies, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, wait! We can do tea and cookies after we prove your innocence! How about you start by telling me what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Hrmmm... I see. So tea and cookies can wait, can they?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Whew, that was close. We don't need "jailbreak" added to the list of charges. Seems like a good guy, but with a face like that, I can see why he's misunderstood.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mayor Tenma. Do you mind if I ask why you were arrested?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">! Grrrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa! S-Sorry! I guess some things are better left unsaid!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Bah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">To think a public paragon such as I could be treated like this! This arrest should have never happened!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Go on...</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">I fear the ill effects it will have on our youth! Now I've but one choice. I must leave here at once, if only to protect the moral fiber of our youth!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, wait! You can protect the moral fiber of our youth after you've been declared not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Hrmmm... I suppose you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Phew... Our youth just came this close to quite a scare.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tenma">My fingerprints were on the spear that killed Alderman Kyubi. That's why I was arrested.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your prints were on the murder weapon? That's never good. Any idea how they got there?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">None. For I hardly remember a thing, you see. I was fast asleep at the time. Someone must have slipped me a sleeping pill or something. What's worse, somebody clobbered me on the head.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I see... A drug induced slumber, and a blow to the head. No wonder you hardly remember a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">............Ho.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Huh? Was that some kind of strange laugh?</thought> Well, I think we can safely assume your prints were planted while you were unconscious.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do the police have on you as far as a motive is concerned?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Truth be told, there's been a bit of trouble between the alderman and I as of late.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh? Was it personal in nature?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Nothing like that. It's a long story... ...but suffice to say, I've been pushing to merge Nine-Tails Vale with Tenma Town. Surrender Nine-Tails Vale to Tenma Town now!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yikes!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">...That's what I told him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'd like to tell YOU to stop shouting like that, but I'm too scared!</thought> So, um, that's the motive the police have established for the alderman's murder?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Indeed it is. After all, Alderman Kyubi was dead set against a municipal merger.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And that's why they think you killed him, he was in your way.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Arrrrrrgh! Cuuuurrrrssseeees!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, M-Mayor Tenma? Are you okay...?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Jinxie! Forgive me! I never meant to worry you like this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It'll work out fine! Just leave it to me! <thought>If only it really were that easy. I don't even know where to start...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tenma">......Thank you for agreeing to defend me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, no thanks required. Just doing my job.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">............ ............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He's even scarier when he's not saying anything.</thought> Um... Nice day today, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">............Hrmmm.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I, um, love nice days like these. It's, uh, perfect lawyering weather, heh heh heh!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">The trial......... is tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, right, the trial! <thought>Why do I keep blabbering on like that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Those charms on your head... They're the same as this one, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Indeed they are. Jinxie applied them after the murder. She said they would keep Tenma Taro from possessing me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right! <thought>So it's not some creepy fashion statement.</thought> Still, there are an awful lot of them.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">That there are. Truth be told, my head's feeling a bit... itchy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can't you just peel them off?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Jinxie did this for me. I could not hurt her feelings like that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He really cares for his daughter.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wanted to show you this.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aaagh! Sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">...............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I hate when he clams up like this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thank you for meeting with me, Mayor Tenma.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Please, wait. My daughter, Jinxie...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">She... she already lost her mother. And now with me being held in here, I fear she'll be terribly lonely. I hesitate to ask, but......... I beg you, be a friend to her in her time of need.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leave it to me! Trucy and I will look out for your daughter!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">I shall rest a little easier, then. You know, you remind me of some of the new friends Jinxie has been talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">New... friends?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Yes. It seems she's made some new friends since she started working in Nine-Tails Vale. They're quite the unusual bunch, too. There's a lady with an exceptionally long neck... ...a young lad with an incredibly long tongue, and many other interesting characters.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Friends? Sounds more like a bunch of monsters to me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Now, if you would excuse me. It appears my time is up.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Whew... Why am I so tired? I must've been more tense than I thought... Still, I'm glad he didn't turn out to be as scary as he looks!</thought> A call? ...Oh, it's Mr. Wright. Justice here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apollo, is that you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hi, Mr. Wright. What can I do for you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trucy told me you've taken on a new case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, that. It was kinda spur of the moment. <thought>He's actually calling ME about a case?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's fine, but I have a favor to ask.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sure. What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm at the airport right now. There was someone I had to meet. A new addition to the agency, actually. Her name's Athena Cykes, and she just passed the bar.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's right. I remember hearing about her coming to join us. Guess that was today.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She took off as soon as I told her you needed help with a case. It was like there was no stopping her.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait... Whaaaaaat! Where is she now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Probably somewhere in Nine-Tails Vale by now. That's where that favor I mentioned comes in. I need you to go find her.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But I've never even met her before. What does she look like?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She'll be the girl in the yellow suit sporting an attorney's badge.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, I'll find her. A new addition to the agency... <thought>Well, I'd better get back to Nine-Tails Vale quick.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy, I'd like to hear your thoughts on what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You do? Does that mean I can join the investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I could sure use your help, but remember what Mr. Wright said? "Trucy, you're in high school now, so you need to focus."</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Right... I guess I better pull it together. It's time to forget everything else and just focus on my magic tricks!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, no! He was talking about your schoolwork!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Welcome to Trucy's Two Cents! Go ahead, ask me anything!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, um, okay... Jinxie's always plastering charms on my forehead. What should I do?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's an easy one, Apollo. Just do this... 3, 2, 1... Ta-dah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do what...? ......Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">See! She won't be able to stick any more on if there's already one there. Problem solved!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How's that a solution? Either way, I still have a charm plastered on my forehead!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Check it out.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You're so lucky, Apollo. Everyone can see what you do with just a flash of your badge.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What about you, Trucy? People can tell you're a magician by the way you're dressed.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah, but I can't always dress like this. Like when I'm at school and stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You could always show you're a magician by making things appear or disappear.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You mean like this? 3, 2, 1... Ta-dah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Umm, magic or no, aren't you a little old to be showing those things in public?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... Then maybe I'll become a lawyer, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're abandoning your dream just like that?!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Jinxie's warding charms... Hm, what if I incorporated it into my act? Might be fun.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean like having charms come out of your magic panties?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Exactly! And then I'd have them fly off and stick to audience members' foreheads!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Somehow, I don't think that would go over so well.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Then how 'bout I have them stick on my assistant? That would be you, Polly!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How does that make it any better?! And I'm not your assistant!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What?! But I could've sworn you were.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Where in the world did you get that idea?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Okay! Watch me make that disappear!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, wait! That's crucial evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But I wanted to show you my new disappearing trick! Oh, I know! If it's really so important, how about I make more of it appear!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Fabricating evidence is even worse than making it disappear!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, well. Too bad.</line>
<line speaker="???">I. Already. Told. You! I'm a lawyer assigned to the case! I need to study the crime scene, so if you would please tell me where Kyubi Manor is...!</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">You can't fool me! You're just some delinquent high school student playing hooky!</line>
<line speaker="???">You stupid, pig-headed...! This attorney's badge isn't just for show, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Looks like I just found Ms. Athena Cykes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Tsk! Why won't you believe me?! Don't expect me to defend you in court if you ever get arrested!</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Well, I'm the one who usually does the arresting, so... Say, shouldn't you be getting back to school?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I already told you, I'm a lawyer, not a student!</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">That's it! Enough of your lies! You're coming with me!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aaah! Get your hands off of me!</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Aaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What the-</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Urnngh... Think you can watch out for the bystanders next time...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whoops! Are you okay?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think so. <thought>But that police officer's out cold.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I am SO sorry! I do that when people suddenly grab me. It's like a reflex or something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Reflex? Sounds more like a felony!</thought> You're Athena Cykes, I take it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That would be me. And you are?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm Apollo Justice. I work at the Wright Anything Agency.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The Wright Anything Agency? What a fishy sounding name.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It's a long story, but it IS a law office, among other things. Didn't Mr. Wright explain it to you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, right, THAT Wright! So then, you must be...! Where have you been?! I've been looking all over for you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I could say the same thing to you.</thought> Well, here I am. Now how about telling me a little bit about yourself. Mr. Wright didn't really tell me much... as always.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">.........Ah, of course! Feel free to ask away!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, Athena, I hear you just passed the bar.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right! And here's my shiny new badge to prove it. Isn't it beautiful?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, so you must be a bit younger than me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Heh heh heh. A bit more than you might think, in fact! I'm only eighteen!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">E-Eighteen? How in the world did you become a lawyer at that age?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I skipped a few grades while I was an exchange student in Europe. And I got my license to practice law while I was over there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All I can say is, wow... <thought>She must be a genius or something.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I also studied analytical psychology! Thought it might help me be a better lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Psychology helps her be a better lawyer? How exactly does that work?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, tell me about our client. What are they like?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right, you haven't met him yet. Well...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...And that about sums it up.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He's more worried about his daughter than himself. What a wonderful father. *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, are you crying?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm not cr-crying! There was something in my eye!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Um, they're called "tears"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Moving right along... Let's get down to business! Helping our client is priority number one!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, Athena, you mentioned studying psychology.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right! I've always wanted to bring analytical psychology into the courtroom. The power of psychology will bring a breath of fresh air to the legal system.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, really? So how do you plan on using it to defend our client?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Um, well, for example, I can try to listen in on a witness's inner voice... ...and then analyze their psychological state with the help of my trusty partner Widget!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Widget...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This device around my neck here! Say hi, Widget!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Hi Widget!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">IT TALKS?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whoa, you need a volume knob! Anyway, the little guy will sometimes say what I'm feeling.</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Awk-ward...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't worry, you'll get used to it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now THAT I seriously doubt.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yep! That's your attorney's badge, all right! Its dull, grimy look makes me think of all the courtroom battles you've faced so far! I hope mine will look like that someday! Look out legal world, Athena Cykes is psyched and ready to go!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>Actually, I just haven't polished it lately... Maybe I should keep that to myself. No need to deflate her dreams about "work" just yet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">What an interesting picture! It looks like a one-on-one monster smack down! It must've been quite a battle. Which yokai do you think is stronger?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Seems to me Tenma Taro's ability to fly would give him an edge over the Nine-Tailed Fox.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But the Fox has powerful legs. He'd pounce before Tenma Taro knew what hit him!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He won't be pouncing on anyone after he's dropped from way up in the sky!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Errr... B-But the Nine-Tailed Fox is gold-colored! Gold is way better than black, so I'm sure he'd win!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do colors have to do with anything? <thought>Besides, everyone knows red is the best.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">*sigh* Sorry, Apollo. Nothing's coming to mind. But give me an hour and I'll have it analyzed Cykes style! I'll get started on it right now!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No need for that! I was just wondering.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Oh, I almost forgot. I have something you might be interested in. I got in on my way here. Think it might have something to do with our case?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A special edition covering our case? That was quick.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... Well, let's see what it says here... <thought>What's the deal with the Spanish?</thought> Tenma Taro was seen.... wha--? He was seen flying through the sky?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, somebody happened to snap that photo near Nine-Tails Vale. The article goes on to say it might be connected to our case. Apparently, that photo was shot right after the murder occurred.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, there were black feathers and strange tracks at the crime scene. I'm not surprised the locals think a yokai was involved.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait a second... Yokai as in one of those Japanese monsters? Mein Gott! You don't actually think it was a supernatural murder, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ha ha ha, n-no, of course not. <thought>Now German? Why not plain old English?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Andale, Apollo! Let's get cracking on that crime scene already!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, what's next on the list?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Investigating the crime scene, what else?! Well, what are we waiting for?! Last one there is a rotten egg!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We don't have to run all the way there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay... Then how about speed walking?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why does this have to be a competition at all?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Looks like this paper doesn't shy away from stories on strange creatures.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? What does it say?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">They claim to have produced photos of Gourdy and a Kappa water sprite thingie. And just the other day, they got one of Konaki Jiji crying his poor old eyes out... ...followed by that infamous shot of Tenma Taro.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't know about a Kappa, but I bet the Konaki Jiji... ...is just a shot of someone's grandpa lost and crying up in the mountains.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's not very nice! They should have helped him instead of publishing his picture!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Do you hear that? It sounds like a TV or something. Oh, look! There's a TV in that little room in the corner.</line>
<line speaker="TV">In other news... The mysterious masked wrestler The Amazing Nine-Tails... ...has been confirmed missing according to sources close to the wrestler. It appears he disappeared sometime after the special event held in Nine-Tails Vale today. He also failed to appear at a match today where he was scheduled to defend his title. Local villagers say his disappearance may be connected with Tenma Taro's recent escape.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, that wrestler's gone missing.</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey, you two! You don't belong in here!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't worry, there's nothing suspicious--</line>
<line speaker="???">What about them there horns o' yours? They look mighty suspicious if ya ask me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Horns?! That's my hair...! Anyway, we're lawyers, and we're here to--</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah! You're them lawyers come to defend Mayor Tenma, ain't ya?! Eh heh heh. Shoulda reckoned what with that expensive-looking bracelet ya got there. The name's Phineas Filch. I'm the caretaker here. Pleased to meetcha, eh heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, same here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, talk about a quick change of heart.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">So, tell me, Demon Lawyer! Betcha use them demonic horns of yours to scare the bejeebers outta witnesses, huh? Come here, ya lil' horned demon, you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Youch! These horns, er... I mean, my hair isn't meant to threaten anyone!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">They ain't? Seems a mighty big waste o' perfectly good horns if ya ask me. Then again, ain't none o' my business, so...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*sigh* <thought>That was fast. Guess he's done with me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Filch">Well, I'd best get back to work!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Huh? Me?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, your bracelet's gone!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Don't ya worry, Mr. Lawyer, sir! I'll check the lost 'n' found later!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Somehow, I don't think that will be necessary. Just check your wrist right now.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Arrrrrrrrrgh! The cat's outta the bag!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It was barely in the bag in the first place!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">That was a pretty pathetic attempt.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">S-S-Sorry! I'm sooooo sooooo sorry! Just couldn't control myself! Please, forgive me! I'm beggin' ya!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sheesh, I almost feel sorry for him now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">What should we do about him, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I got my bracelet back, and he seems sorry enough, so...</line>
<line speaker="Filch">I knew ya'd understand, Mr. Lawyer, sir! Ya obviously got a big heart! As big as the wad o' cash in your wallet, I hope, eh heh heh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You leave my wallet out of this.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Ho HO!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey! Didn't you just finish apologizing for stealing from us?!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Run away, run away! Head for the hills!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Get back here, you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Talk about a quick escape.</thought> ...Hm? Looks like he dropped a few things. Looks like a pair of diagrams. This one's of the crime scene, and here's one of the foyer.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He left his shoes behind, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The guy's the living definition of a bumbling thief.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's hang on to his shoes. We can give them back next time we see him. As for the diagrams, I say we keep them!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They look like something the police might draw. Wonder where the caretaker got them?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now then, as I recall... ...the Fox Chamber should be at the top of those stairs.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whoa! Where'd all these black feathers and weird tracks come from?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The popular opinion seems to be that they're from Tenma Taro.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You mean the great evil has returned?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Even if he did, I'd be laughed out of the courthouse trying to indict him.</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey, who are you and what are you doing here? This is a crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And who are YOU? Are you with the police?</line>
<line speaker="???">I asked first! Who are YOU and what are you doing here?! On second thought... I'm placing you under arrest for disturbing a crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! Under arrest?! B-B-But...</line>
<line speaker="???">Save it for the boys back at HQ! Now, come quietly or else! I don't want to be late for lunch!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">P-Please, wait! We're Mayor Tenma's lawyers!</line>
<line speaker="???">Well why didn't you just say so! So you're the lawyers I heard about. Ha ha ha! I almost took you two in! You two sure were suspicious, though!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't know how many more times I can take being called suspicious in one day...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sorry, we didn't catch your name.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">My name? I'm Bobby Fulbright! The heroic detective who defends our good citizens from evil! The champion of justice who comes running whenever you're in need! And my catchphrase? It's "In justice we trust!"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hoo boy... <thought>This guy's a story and a half...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">So! What can I do for you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, would it be okay if we had a look around?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Certainly not! No unauthorized personnel allowed!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Couldn't you make an exception?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Cease and desist at once, or you'll have to deal with my little friend here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! <thought>Yikes! Is he reaching for his...?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">In justice we trust!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>Phew, it's just his badge.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">You may be Mayor Tenma's attorneys, but you still need authorization to cross a police line!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, let's see if we can't change his mind!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Good luck! Let me know how it goes! <thought>I bet he's as dense as heroes come...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">You're wasting your time and mine! Nobody's crossing this line without authorization! I'm a wall of justice keeping injustice -- that would be you -- at bay!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*sigh* I knew it. Look, there's just us and you here, right?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Justice and me, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-That's right...?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Are you trying to say that justice and I aren't enough to keep you out?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, what?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...! No, silly! We're saying that you're an inspiration in our quest for justice!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">No!!! It can't beeeee!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You have him on the ropes now, Athena!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um, if we were on the side of justice, would you let us through?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">B-B-But, guarding the crime scene is a part of justice, too!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sure... but only a bad guy would stand in the way of justice, right?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Aaaaargh! Whose justice is the most just here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, we can't have a fair and just trial without a thorough investigation, so...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hrmmm... Oh, Lady Justice...! What would you have me dooooo?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think we really got to him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, he's [sic] seems pretty neurotic as far as champions of justice go.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Our pleas for justice must've had a huge impact. It's tying him up in knots! Now's our chance to start looking around.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>After all that about authorized personnel only... this was surprisingly easy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hrmmm... Should I stop them or let them through? Whose justice is more just?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Justice need backup sometimes, too! So I don't mind you asking for help, but you should start by thinking things over yourself. After all, the road to justice starts with your own first step! Ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If you don't have any information to offer, you could just say so.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, let's get to work! We're supposed to being finding [sic] clues related to the crime, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. A search of the crime scene should turn up some evidence we can use at the trial. Let's try viewing the crime scene from different angles.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You never know what's hiding just around the corner, right? Wait, but how do we go about changing our perspective?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Touch the arrows on the bottom screen or press left or right on [D-Pad]. If there's a particular spot you want to examine, just give it a tap.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, let's leave no stone unturned! Nous allons commencer! Let's get started!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The Forbidden Chamber... They say the demon Tenma Taro was imprisoned in there before his "escape."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Think we could get this door open?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's worth a try. Hrrrgh! ...No good. It's shut tight! I don't even see a key hole. Seems pretty hopeless.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">In justice we trust!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yikes!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Did I just hear the voice of someone in need?! Allow me to fill you in! This door simply will not open! We've tried and tried, but it won't budge! It's an essential part of the culture found in this manor, so we can't blow it up either!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So, an unopenable door. Right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">According to Ms. Jinxie Tenma, it was shut tight when she came across the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thanks for the tip, Detective Fulbright. We didn't expect you to be so helpful.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Aaaaaaaaaaargh! Forget I just said that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So, the Forbidden Chamber was shut tight at the time of the murder. Sounds like something I'd better keep in mind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, this is where Alderman Kyubi's body was found.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apparently, the murder weapon -- a spear -- had Mayor Tenma's prints on it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's not good.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Never fear, Detective Fulbright is here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yikes!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Of course, I can't offer you any information on my investigation, so... In the name of justice, I must say goodbye!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Umm... What was that all about?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow! This is a pricy-looking chair!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apparently, the mayor was found drugged and unconcious in it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, and when he came to, he was arrested for murder. Talk about your rude awakenings.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, he's the prime suspect in a crime he knows nothing about?!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">That stinks!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, poor Mr. Tenma. *sniffle* He must be feeling so scared and confused. Apollo, it's up to us to save him!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's like she's on her own emotional roller coaster.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look! This statue only has one tail.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe it's the Nine-Tailed Fox's sidekick. I bet the number of tails represents a yokai's power.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So... if you had two, Apollo, I'd only have one?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait. What?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Not that it means you're better than me, got it?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Like I said, what?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's something wedged under this chair. Let's see if we can't lift it up and...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Freeze!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yikes!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">No disturbing crime scene evidence! Even if you ARE the mayor's lawyers.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He does have a point there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey Detective Fulbright, did you hear about the attack over on Yokai Lane? I hear an elderly woman was assaulted by a strange yokai shaped like a roll of cloth!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">And you waited till now to tell me?! I better get over there at once. In justice we trust!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...That was surprisingly easy. Okay, Apollo, now's our chance to look around some more.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The more I get to know her, the scarier she gets. Hope she never finds MY weakness.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whatever this is, it's stuck on tight.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Looks like a large bloodstained cloth.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The blood's probably the alderman's, but it's pretty far from his body. Wonder how it got here... <thought>And why does this seem important?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Nothing much to see on this side. Maybe I should go check the other side.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">This one's a spear, but what about this one? It looks like a giant pair of pliers.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like something a demon might use. Saw something like that in a manga once.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really? What are they used for?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, things like pinching through cheeks...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeuuuw!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Pulling out tongues...</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Stop, stop!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, and you should see what they can do to a person's eyes--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, okay, I get the idea! But I'm sure THIS thing is just a simple can opener or something like that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Demons eat canned food? I always wondered what they are besides people.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">These weird tracks must've been made when someone stepped in the alderman's blood.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe the killer inadvertently made them when they were fleeing? They're pretty big tracks, almost bird-like. The feathers also point to a bird.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then it must be one big bird! And not one of the friendly yellow type, either!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe it's some mutant bird creature!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, your theory is a giant mutant bird murdered Alderman Kyubi with a spear?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's more plausible than saying a monster or yokai did it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sorry to burst your bubble, but a giant spear-wielding bird is by definition a monster!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's a folding screen. I wonder what they were using it for.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I read that the Japanese used to use these in drafty rooms, but now they're just for show.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You mean like... like my attorney's badge. *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Poor Athena...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That cop treating her like a child must've really bothered her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, what words come to mind when you watch that pendulum in there?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... Unsteady and umm... restless.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's a direct representation of your current state of mind.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait! That was some kind of psychological test?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">My diagnosis? This strange case has made you anxious, causing you to lose your cool.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're actually not that far off the mark.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hm? There's something behind the door. Whatever it is, it looks like it's broken. Probably broke when the door was opened. Why would anybody put something there?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, that wasn't very smart.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe it was Jinxie. She was the first one to discover the body. She must have heard the screams and come running in here in a panic.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, look at you, Apollo! Now you're using analytical psychology, too!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I am?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, you really learn quick! But I guess I shouldn't be surprised. You're the ace attorney of Wright Anything Agency!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I can't tell whether she's serious or not. Now, if Trucy said something like that, I'd immediately know she was messing with me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Doesn't this tanuki statue remind you of the manor's caretaker, Phineas Filch?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This raccoon-looking thing? Yeah, it does look like him!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, I just got the best idea! We should knock it over! It might transform back into Mr. Filch!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Filch is mischievous, but he's not magical, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Way to waste a brilliant idea, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh, that looks like an air vent. It's pretty high up there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What if you got a running start and jumped?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I doubt even a high-jumper could make it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Argh! Don't rule it out before you try it! Besides, I'm an excellent jumper.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Even so, that must be about nine feet high.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Like I said, you don't know until you try, Monsieur Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She doesn't know when to give up and when to stop using foreign words.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look, trophies! Ooh! This one was awarded to Alderman Kyubi! "The Amazing Nine-Tails, Yokai Div. Winner, Tenma Town Pro Wrestling Tournament."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yokai Division? I didn't know you could have a division of one.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, you should enter the tournament next time! And I have the perfect name for you! The Mysterious Firebrand! A mild-mannered masked lawyer by day... demonic masked wrestler by night!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No one's going to hire a masked lawyer, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, this window opens. And outside... we have ourselves a steep cliff.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The window only opens about six inches -- not wide enough for anyone to get in or out. Look, Apollo! There's something caught in the window frame! It looks like gold fur. What a pretty color! It must be from some kind of animal!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wonder what it's doing here. Did Alderman Kyubi have a pet fox?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's this gold fur caught in the window frame here? Could it be from some rare gold-colored fox found only in Nine-Tails Vale?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You think a fox squeezed out of this window?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nothing's getting out that way. There's a steep cliff on the other side.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... It's one mystery after another.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... What do we have here? Looks like a statue of the Nine-Tailed Fox and Tenma Taro battling it out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eek! Careful, Apollo, it's got blood on it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? ...Hey, you're right. Wonder if it's the alderman's blood?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">How can you remain so calm after seeing all this blood?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, this isn't the first time I've seen something like this, so...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're no fun at all! At least act surprised or grossed out or something for my first case!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm already a lawyer. You want me to be an actor, too?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look! A cat with two tails!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No such thing.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, and this lady has a really long neck! Ha ha ha! How funny is that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's no way a creature like that could ever exist. She'd have a tough time swallowing.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo... I bet you were one of those kids who didn't believe in Santa Claus.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's that got to do with anything?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Guess that about wraps it up.</thought> Now if only we could get that detective to tell us what he knows...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, Apollo... Do you hear something?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hm? .........I don't hear anything.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, right. Your hearing must not be as sensitive as mine.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, what are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A whooshing sound, like wind rushing through a narrow strait. And the echo of someone's voice... "In... In..."</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">IN JUSTICE WE TRUST!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! Someone's got a sharp set of ears! That was the sound of my righteous voice reverberating through the air duct!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I heard it through the air ducts?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yeah, check it out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But why would she hear you through there?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Why don't we go to the diagram? As you can see, that vent is connected to an air duct that leads out into the hallway! The wind must've rushed through there... ...and carried my monologue with it straight to your ears!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And what a... unique monologue it was. I was just thinking... Maybe the killer made their escape through the air duct or something!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Heh heh heh, a cute theory, but I don't think so. The air duct in the hallway is low enough to climb into, that much is true. But as you can see, the vent in the ceiling is very high. 9 feet high, in fact. I highly doubt that there's any way to get up there without a ladder or something. And I don't see anything of the sort in this room, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... I guess you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Speaking of things in this room...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can you tell us what you guys turned up, Detective Fulbright?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Not on my watch, buddy! In the name of justice, I cannot reveal facts pertaining to the prosecution's case!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aw, come on, throw us a bone here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Excuse me, Detective Fulbright, but I recall you saying earlier... ...that you would come running whenever we were in need.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yurk! I suppose I did say that! Helping those in need is what justice is all about, but... But keeping information out of enemy hands is also a form of justice! Hmm... Aaaaargh! Which justice is the most just? Why is this always so hard!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm......... Well, how about this? Let's do a little give and take. I mean, serving the public is part of justice, too, right? You know, like the police motto? "To serve and protect."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I doubt leaking information to the defense team falls under that motto.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yes, of course! I must serve and [sic] well as protect! Okay, I will share some information. ...In the name of justice!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We did it, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, we did it, all right. <thought>But I'm not sure that was entirely ethical...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Was it Ms. Jinxie Tenma who first discovered the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's right. And this photo shows what she saw when she opened the door. Ms. Tenma had a key, allowing her immediate access.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A key? So, then, the Fox Chamber was locked?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yes, and Ms. Tenma had the only key to its door.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? So, Alderman Kyubi didn't have a key to the Fox Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Actually, he had a master key for most of the doors in the manor, but... It disappeared after his murder.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Disappeared? You think the killer took it?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">It could very well be connected to the murder. We're looking into the possibility now. But it's the timing of Ms. Tenma's discovery that I think is most important. Of course, I'm not going to share that information with you, ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You think you're some kind of champion of justice, but you're just plain old mean!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">I won't fall for that, you shameless rascal! I only help good little boys and girls!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Shameless rascal? Who even says that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I wouldn't exactly call you a good little girl, either.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Those feathers and tracks look like something a yokai might leave behind.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">You don't actually think the murderer was some sort of monster, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's the name of that creature in the Forbidden Chamber? Tenma... something... Because from the black feathers and big tracks, it looks like that creature did it.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Our prime suspect would, no doubt, love to pin the blame on some imaginary creature.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Can Tenma whatchamacallit even be made a victim of slander?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I doubt the mayor would do something as childish as blaming a boogieman.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, the most likely scenario so far is... ...that Tenma guy left the feathers and tracks behind... ...to make it look like yokai Tenma was the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Wait, what? Now I'm as confused as you! <thought>At any rate, I doubt Mayor Tenma would plant evidence like that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, Mayor Tenma is your only suspect?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's right. Even his name, Damian Tenma, makes him sound like a villain. And he's really scary looking, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, are you telling me that's why he was arrested?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! Don't be ridiculous! He was the only one without an alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, is that so?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yup. Other than the victim, the suspect, and Ms. Tenma, the only others around were... ...Mr. Filch and Mayor Tenma's aide, and the two of them were together at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Filch... The guy who tried to steal my bracelet. Just living up to his name, I guess. We should go talk to him again when we have a chance.</thought> What about Jinxie? She's not being suspected at all?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">She may have no alibi whatsoever... but she also has no motive. It's unfathomable that she would murder the alderman, and pin the crime on her father. Besides, do you really think a little girl could lift up this huge spear?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">True enough. That spear looks even bigger than her.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, so this is my attorney's badge.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">No, no! Present it with more confidence and conviction! Like this... In justice we trust!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, um, how's this... Apollo Justice, attorney at law! H-Here comes Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That was amazing! But you know what they say, practice makes perfect. Let's see you do it ten more times!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, I'll try my best!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um, Apollo? What are you doing?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! How'd he talk me into this?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Justice need backup sometimes, too! So I don't mind you asking for help, but you should start by thinking things over yourself. After all, the road to justice starts with your own first step! Ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If you don't have any information to offer, you could just say so.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's about all I can reveal at this time. Well? You must admit, Damian Tenma appears to be the most likely suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I admit it looks bad, but I'm still not buying it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Oh, and one more thing... I must warn you about the prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The prosecutor assigned to Mayor Tenma's trial?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's the one. He's -- how shall I put it -- not what you'd expect. That is unless you've faced a convicted killer serving hard time as a prosecutor before.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What the--?! Is this some kind of joke?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can I ask why a man imprisoned for murder is serving as prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Because he's mastered the use of psychology in courtroom battles. Everyone's talking about how this murder was the work of some strange creature. But yokai are nothing more than a figment of the imagination. They're baloney! Who better to prove that than a master of psychology? He's the best man for the job.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But he's a convicted murderer! No matter how you look at it, that's just insane!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well, the chief prosecutor personally assigned him, so... ...none of us are in a position to question the matter, ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This really is the dark age of the law.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">This prosecutor... He wouldn't happen to go by the name "Blackquill," would he?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Bingo! Simon Blackquill. So, you HAVE heard of him?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...You could say that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's that supposed to mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well, I bet you don't know his unofficial title. Ever heard of the "Twisted Samurai"? That's Prosecutor Blackquill!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The "Twisted Samurai"...? Is that because he's a criminal?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well... Yes and no. You could say it also has to do with the effect his crime had on things.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How so...?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">His conviction is what twisted and warped the legal world into this dark age of the law.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?! And HE of all people is going to stand in court tomorrow?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! Never fear! I myself will be there to protect you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>That's reassuring, I guess...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well, you kids knock yourselves out! Can't wait to see how you do tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, Detective Fulbright. I've been meaning to ask you something. Um... Why are you barefoot? This doesn't look like the sort of place where you need to take your shoes off...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hm? Ah! Ahhhhhh! I hadn't even noticed. Why AM I barefoot?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>You honestly hadn't noticed until just now?!</thought> .........Wait a second. Those shoes we found earlier... Excuse me, Detective Fulbright. These wouldn't happen to be your shoes, would they?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yes! Yes they are! My favorite pair, in fact! Thank you for bringing them to me. You must truly be on the side of justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Don't tell me Mr. Filch actually stole from a detective?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Stealing shoes right off of someone's feet... That's pretty amazing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I find it more amazing that Detective Fulbright didn't notice. <thought>Well, looks like we've gotten all we can out of the detective, so let's see... Maybe we should go have a word with Mr. Filch. I want to hear what his "alibi" is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Filch">This is just awful! T-Terrible, I say! S-Somebody, help!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, look, it's mister-- what was it again? Finch?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">No, no, no! The name's Filch, Phineas Filch!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Keep on pilfering and you may wind up a jail bird instead.</thought> So what seems to be the problem, Mr. Filch?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Oh, it's just terrible! Terrible, I tell ya! Come quick!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">O-Okay...? <thought>What's the deal with him all of a sudden?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like some kind of mask.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">I-It's The Amazing Nine-Tails's mask!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The Amazing Nine-Tails...? <thought>Oh, right -- the wrestler who appeared during the festival's special event...</thought> What's his mask doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">He'd never take off his mask like this! Someone musta killed 'im!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whaaa--?! Wh-Who would do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's go talk over there in private.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hm? Look... There's some white hair caught up inside this mask...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, what makes you believe that The Amazing Nine-Tails has been murdered?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Ya really wanna know, eh? You're a studious one, ain't ya! Eh heh he!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, I mean, no. Er, I mean, just tell me, please.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Well, it's like this. I'd dreamed o' becoming a wrassler myself! Hey, how 'bout ya join me in the quest for the champion's belt?! Whadda team! Me in my bandit's mask and you in that demon mask of yours!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Demon mask? Heh heh. Wonder if I could make it big.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, let's save your pro wrestling debut until after the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?! Oh, no, no! I wasn't actually... <thought>Argh! Why did I let him pull me off topic like that?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Come on, Apollo -- ask him about The Amazing Nine-Tails's murder already!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">The Amazing Nine-Tails is our village's savior, and don't ya forget it! His trademark's a gold cape made to look like nine fox tails! He whirls through the ring, smacking down Tenma Town wrestlers left 'n' right! He sparked the monster craze, revitalizing Nine-Tales [sic] Vale in the blink of an eye. Yep, saved our village from becoming a ghost town. Now it's a yokai town, eh heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh, The Amazing Nine-Tails really does sound, well... amazing.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yeah, pretty amazing, huh? That's why he's worshipped like a hero 'round here! I'm proud to be from the same village as him.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Come to think of it, you look kind of monster-like yourself, Mr. Filch. Guess it makes sense since you're from the same village as The Amazing Nine-Tails!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Eh heh heh... I know! A lot o' people have told me I look like a yokai.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Since when was that a compliment?</thought> Ouch! What's the big idea!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Eh heh heh... Check your pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, how'd you do that?!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Keep it. I got lots more.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you keep saying that the Amazing Nine-Tails was killed. What's the story behind that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are you saying he was murdered because his mask washed up along the river outside?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">That's only part o' it. The main reason is no one's seen 'im since the special event. The word 'round Nine-Tails Vale is he was killed by Tenma Taro.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You villagers really are superstitious, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">That we are. We love conspiracy theories, too, like the mayor's diabolical plot.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The mayor? Of Tenma Town? What is he plotting?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Rumor has it he's planning on releasing Tenma Taro. That's why he wants the merger. He'll open the Forbidden Chamber once he's in control.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's quite a tale.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Ain't finished yet! There was only one person who could stop the mayor. Our hero, The Amazing Nine-Tails! He vowed to battle the mayor of Tenma Town and stop the municipal merger!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>I couldn't make this stuff up if I tried.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! We still have to ask him about the alderman's murder, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Filch, would you mind telling us what you were doing at the time of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">I was in the caretaker's office guarding the entrance like Mr. Kyubi said I should. And I made double sure no one came in. I have a clear view of the foyer from where I work.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He must be talking about the small room in the upper right. It definitely looks like you can keep track of the comings and goings from there.</thought> And you have an alibi to back your statement up, Mr. Filch?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Eh heh heh. I do, indeed! I was with Mayor Tenma's aide. Florent L'Belle's his name.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, the two of you were together... That's a pretty sound alibi, all right. And nobody came in or out of the manor around the time of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Kept watch here the whole time. Didn't see a soul pass by. And if anyone did, that there security camera woulda spotted 'em.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So no one came in or out around the time of the murder... That means we're dealing with someone who was already inside when it happened.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Filch">Hey, that there's The Amazing Nine-Tails's mask! Yer aiming to sell it, aint ya?! Why you sneaky, lily-livered--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, I'm not trying to sell it. It could be a key piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Aw, too bad. Thought I'd hook ya up with this buyer I know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, you WANT me to sell it?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mind if I ask you about this?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Hm? Oh, that... Right, right...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, does it ring a bell?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Eh heh heh heh... Oh, it's ringing, all right. Ya wanna thank me for all my hard work, and I humbly accept!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, this isn't a gift! <thought>Should've known this was a dead end.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, do you think this mask is the real deal?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Without a doubt. This here's the mask worn by The Amazing Nine-Tails.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What about that white hair I found inside the mask?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait! I just thought of something! Remember the golden animal fur we found at the crime scene? Could it have come from this mask? Look! There's even a spot where some fur is missing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... Then this places this mask at the crime scene at some point in time. Which means......... <thought>What does this mean? Someone with white hair who is linked with the murder and is against the merger? No way...! Could The Amazing Nine-Tails and the alderman actually be...?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Something wrong, Apollo? You should see the look on your face!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, no, it's n-nothing. <thought>Maybe Jinxie could tell us something, since she works here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Come up with anything yet?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! O-Of course I have! But it's not quite ready for primetime.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The truth will only be revealed once we've dotted all our i's and crossed all our t's. In other words, it's still just a theory, so I don't think I should say anything yet. It's the dilemma any great detective must face!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Whatever!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Tsk! Widget!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So basically, you have no ideas. Thanks for nothing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What are your thoughts on the case so far?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well... I think our killer is most likely highly intelligent and stone-cold cool. I mean, just look how they killed the alderman: one decisive thrust, no hesitation.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And you know this how? Psychology?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right! I've profiled the killer based on the evidence we found at the scene! I can almost picture the killer in my mind... A terrifying face twisted from hatred toward the victim... Big, bulging eyes full of murderous intent... A horrible gash-like mouth from ear to ear... And... wings, black and sinister.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wings? That sounds like Tenma Taro!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">On second thought, scratch psychology. That last part was just my imagination.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You think?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So who do you think is the man behind The Amazing Nine-Tails mask?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, there was that white hair we found inside the mask. I have a feeling it's going to be a valuable clue.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We should run a DNA test on it. Ooh! And what if the results show that the hair's not human? Don't you think it's fun to fantasize about stuff like that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sure, as long as you're prepared to have that fantasy shattered by the results, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">In that case, let's forget about the DNA testing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, look, there's Jinxie.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Milk, cheese, yogurt, ice cream, and...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sounds like she's out grocery shopping. She must really like dairy products.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">...a charm to make a better milkshake and another to cure my lactose intolerance.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe she should just stick to soy milk.</thought> Jinxie! Hey, it's me!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Eek! It's th-th-the demon lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! <thought>Not another warding charm... *sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um, Apollo? Who is she?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right. This is your first time meeting each other. This is Jinxie, Mayor Tenma's daughter. She was the first to discover the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, so she's the one who--! Um, hello. My name's Athena Cykes. I'll be helping Apollo defend your father at his trial. Pleased to meet you!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">P-Pleased to meet you, too. Uhh... Um, where's Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She went back to the office ahead of us. But don't worry. Athena and I are on the case!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">W-W-Wait, how do I know you didn't...! ...That you d-d-didn't gobble her up alive!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Relax, I didn't eat her up! And I wouldn't do such a thing in the first place!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Oh, poor little Trucy! *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm about ready for some tears of frustration myself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">She's quite an, um, interesting character, huh, Apollo...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Jinxie, do you remember any more of what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Not much. ...At least not yet.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But you do think Tenma Taro was the killer, right? That yokai we saw at the festival?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">I don't know anything about that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? But you said Tenma Taro murdered the alderman. ...It's okay, Jinxie. You can tell me-- Yikes! What was that for?!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">People see things when they don't get enough sleep. There's no such thing as monsters.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?! <thought>What's gotten into her?</thought> So, if there are no monsters, you admit I'm human?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">No, you're still a demon!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ Oh, I give up.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It seems like Jinxie doesn't want to talk about Tenma Taro for some reason.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But that's precisely what we need to know more about... Besides, she definitely thought there was a yokai there in the Fox Chamber. Jinxie, about this charm...</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Ah! That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You gave me this when I was heading off to the scene of the crime. You thought Tenma Taro was the murderer. That's why you gave this to me, right?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Errr... That's true, but...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If there's anything else you could tell us, it would really help. And it will help your father, too!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Umm... All right, then.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why do you think Tenma Taro's the killer?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">I saw him. Saw him with my own eyes. Tenma Taro was right there in the manor! He escaped his prison... ...and ran right by me!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Jinxie, tell us everything you saw!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">I called the police after I stumbled on the scene. I was just about to head back to the festival grounds when... ...I saw Tenma Taro. It was right around here. He was running right at me! I was... I was paralyzed with fear. But there was no one around to help me. *shiver* The foul beast raced right by me toward the foyer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Toward the foyer?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Filch and Mr. L'Belle were supposedly in the foyer at the time. That means they would've seen Tenma Taro, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sounds like we'd better get their statements. <thought>Considering Jinxie's mental state, her eyes could've been playing tricks on her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um... Apollo? Remember the picture in this paper? Someone caught Tenma Taro flying through the air. I wonder if it's the same Tenma Taro Jinxie says she saw.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Don't be ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">*shiver* Tenma Taro IS the killer. And he can fly, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Jinxie works at the alderman's manor, so maybe she can shed some light on this.</thought> So, no one knows The Amazing Nine-Tails's true identity?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. They say no one's ever seen him without his mask.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Doesn't that make you want to know even more?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. That's why matches where wrestlers try to expose their opponent are so popular.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait... you mean expose, as in strip them naked?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Eek! You even think like a demon! ...The only thing the winner removes is the loser's mask. To have your mask torn off is the worst humiliation a wrestler could suffer! That's why their masks are more important to them than life itself. So you see, these unmasking matches are life and death battles for the wrestlers.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That means this mask didn't just happen to wash up along the riverbank. There's got to be a story behind it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">No one can stop The Amazing Nine-Tails!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Bet she'd be shocked to find out he's really the alderman.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">About the yokai you saw at the scene of the crime... Anything else stand out?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Actually, I heard this strange jangly sound.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A jangly sound? Can you be a little more specific?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">My memory's kind of fuzzy... But I vaguely recall seeing Tenma Taro holding a staff or something like that. Maybe that's what was making the strange sound.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Does Tenma Taro usually carry a staff?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Good question. I've never heard anything like that and it's not shown on the scroll.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How about in other documents? Any of them show Tenma Taro with a staff?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">This is the only known document depicting Tenma Taro. After all, those who needless [sic] [recte needlessly] depict the demon are forever cursed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then what's the deal with the Tenma Taro you saw, Jinxie?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">The Nine-Tailed Fox is famous for imprisoning Tenma Taro, but legends say that he also... ...gave us the Nine-Tails Flower, and that he still watches over the village to this day.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, coming here is like traveling to ancient Japan with all the strange beliefs and all. All those yokai, the Nine-Tails Flower, the Forbidden Chamber, and the list goes on.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. It was like I should've been born here. Too bad the population is shrinking. But there's an effort underway to protect the yokai. It also helps the local economy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Protect the yokai? You mean like endangered species?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. There're even plans to create a yokai wildlife park in the near future.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now I'm really starting to wonder about this place.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Jinxie, I wanted to show you this--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, Apollo! You can't show that to her. Having her father arrested was bad enough.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Huh? Did you say something?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe this wasn't such a good idea.</thought> Oh, um, never mind.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait, Jinxie's a huge fan of The Amazing Nine-Tails. She'd probably freak out if I showed her this mask without the guy in it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">What are you thinking?! It would crush her if she figured out her favorite wrestler is dead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Guess I'll spare her the grief, although she really could use a reality check.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Ah! Th-Th-That's The Amazing Nine-Tails! He... he lives in the mountains right outside the village. But he often comes to visit.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? He doesn't sound very secret or reclusive to me.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">No, he's not. In fact, he visits the village bathhouse all the time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No way! The Amazing Nine-Tails goes to public bathhouses?!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. But like a true wrestling legend, he never takes his mask off.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He takes baths in his mask?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. And he also has a towel that says, "Wrestlers Wanted!"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If I saw a naked guy in a mask and a message like that on his towel, I'd run the other way.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">I saw... him... Tenma Taro. It nearly scared me to death.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Do you see a lot of monsters, Jinxie?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. *shivers* In fact, I encountered the Sunekosuri this morning. *shivers*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sune... kosuri? You know, I don't know that one. Tell me about it.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">It's a mean little beast that trips you by bumping into your shins. I keep tripping all the time because of that pesky little thing! When it gets really bad, I stick Sunekosuri warding charms on my shins!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, how about investing in some shin guards, and watching your step instead?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">What's this? A Tsukumogami?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tsukumo... gami?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">A yokai that inhabits objects that have been used for a really long time. The Red Demon and a Tsukumogami... What a strange combination.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is everything to her some supernatural phenomenon?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why didn't you tell me you saw Tenma Taro earlier?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Actually... Mr. L'Belle told me not to tell.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. L'Belle?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Papa's aide.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, right. The other guy who was supposedly in the foyer at the time of the crime.</thought> And what exactly did he tell you?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">"Keep the village superstitions in mind... ...before you go talking about seeing Tenma Taro at the time of the crime."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Village superstitions?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">They say you must not gaze upon Tenma Taro. But in the event that you do look... ...and then tell anyone what you saw, Tenma Taro will claim your soul.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And that's something everyone here knows?<thought>Sounds like a bunch of baloney to me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. Everyone from babies to the village elders know about it. But I didn't because I'm not from around here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, come to think of it...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Huh? Why's everyone hiding their faces?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Villager">Hey, you there! You mustn't stare at Tenma Taro like that! Lower your eyes! He'll steal your soul if you're not careful!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? <thought>Steal my soul? Seriously?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The guy at the special event thing said almost the exact same thing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, do you think this L'Belle guy actually believes in Tenma Taro?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I seriously doubt it. He's not even from Nine-Tails Vale.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Then why would he try to keep Jinxie from talking?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Good question. I think we'd better go have a word with him.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Time to unmask this monster of a mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">The last time I saw Mr. L'Belle, he was relaxing in the foyer.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Bueno! Next stop, the manor foyer! With any luck, he'll be there waiting for us!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There's no one here. Guess our luck isn't so good when it comes to Mr. L'Belle.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe he's out for a walk or something. <thought>Hmm? Somebody left something on the sill of the caretaker's office window.</thought> Oh, it's a TV program guide.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Looks like someone circled a pro wrestling match.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Hey, whaddya think you're doing!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eek! I-I-It's a...! Oh, Mr. Filch! Wh-What can we do for you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I bet she was going to scream, "Monster!" which really isn't much of a stretch...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Filch">Ain't nothing I need you to do for me. But what business do ya got with my TV listings?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, no, it just caught my eye. Can I ask if you watched this pro wrestling program today?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yep, 'twas a match between a couple o' rank amateurs, though. It was a complete disaster. I reckon even I coulda done better than that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I seriously doubt that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Almost forgot. There's something I wanted to ask him.</thought> Mr. Filch, did you see anything unusual around the time of the murder? For example, Tenma Taro or something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Huh?! T-Tenma Taro?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you did see him?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Errr... My, how clean and shiny your forehead is again today, Mr. Lawyer, sir! Bet ya shine it up every day real purty like. The ladies must love it, eh heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't change the subject! And FYI, that was a seriously bad attempt at flattery. Jinxie said she saw Tenma Taro flee toward the foyer. So you must've seen him too if you were here!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yi-Yi-Yiiiiiiiiipes!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wow, I really pushed a button there!</thought> Well, did you see anything or not?</line>
<line speaker="???">That is quite enough. I must ask that you not pester my friend anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yipes! Forgive me for being pestered, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And you are?</line>
<line speaker="???">I am Florent L'Belle... ...beau divine and PERSONAL aide to Mayor Damian Tenma.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Beau divine? More like yokai grotesque. This place is crawling with monsters.</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">OH! Excuse YOU!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! Wh-What the heck was that for?!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! It was just a little cologne. You had a look of stinky sweat about you. It's from my OWN original brand of cosmetics called "Je suis L'Belle!" *sniff sniff sniff* Oh, what a heavenly scent.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh. I think you just paralyzed my olfactory receptors.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! I suppose such a scent WOULD be difficult for a peasant to appreciate. I'll have you know, THAT is Brand No. 5 "Bonjour." It's MY way of introducing myself. Enjoy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Where's my bottle of "Adieu" so I can return the favor?</thought> Enough about the cologne. Please tell us what you saw around the time of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I heard you're the one who told Jinxie not to mention that she saw Tenma Taro.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Why that little--! So, she told you she saw the demon, did she?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. L'Belle, do mind [sic] if I ask whether you believe in the village superstitions?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! Oh, PU-LEASE! I was merely trying to keep with traditions. Nevertheless, I will say this... I wouldn't stick MY nose into this whole Tenma Taro business if I were you. Bad things happen to those who do. THAT much is true. He is one... scary... monster.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's crazy! You really expect me to believe that monsters are real?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! Well, YOU'RE real, and YOU sure look like a monster.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Look who's talking!</thought> So, Mr. L'Belle, you didn't see Tenma Taro? Aaah!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Little Jinxie has an ACTIVE imagination. Isn't that right, Phineas?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">That's right. I didn't see nothing, especially not Tenma Taro!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">As for ME, I only see things of beauty. That's why I can barely see you. ...Pwh! Ah ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I've got two words for this guy: total freak.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could I ask you what you were doing at the time of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">In other words, you'd like to hear MY alibi. Tsk, to think you'd suspect ME of all people!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, no, it's just a formality. We ask everyone the same questions. Aaah!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">How DARE you doubt me! That's an affront to beauty itself! You OBVIOUSLY can't see straight!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urnngh... Like that spritz really helped...!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">What were WE doing, you ask? Go ahead, Filchy, answer the question.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Errr... At the time of the crime, we were... um... uh... in this here foyer!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Exactly! Good answer, Filchy, good answer!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Eh heh he. Just repeating whatcha told-- Youch!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">You've said QUITE enough!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>.........What is WITH these two? Great, now he's got me talking like that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Yes? That's a warding charm, but why are YOU showing it to ME?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ <thought>Guess it doesn't work on all monsters.</thought> Yurk!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Shame on you, thinking THAT would work on ME!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Blech!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! You should be honored to be bathed in my beautiful scent, peasant!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack... <thought>Now I really wish it would work.</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Pffft, The Amazing Nine-Tails? What's so AMAZING about HIM? I mean, MY glossies are selling WAY better than his.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You sell glossies of yourself?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">That's right. I have one for all seven of my hair colors!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ <thought>Well, guess that's it. Civilization over.</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Tsk, if you WANT one, you need simply ask. I'll even let you choose the color yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, thank you!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Yes? Do you ALWAYS go around sticking your hand in OTHER people's faces?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, no, I just wanted to show you this.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah, yes, you DO have something in that grimy paw of yours. But I only have eyes for things of beauty. Now, if you would excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Guess he'll only look at stuff that interests him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Are we quite through here? I'm a VERY busy man, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Right. Well, thanks for your help. <thought>So, these two were in the foyer, but didn't see Tenma Taro.</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Come along, Filchy.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Where we goin'? Oh, right! Gotta practice them statements for tomorrow! ...Yipes! My eyyyes!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">You're going to dig your own grave with that big mouth of yours someday!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>What does he mean, "practice statements"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Now if would excuse me. [sic] It's time to touch up my makeup.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, I know this sounds strange... ...but Mr. L'Belle seems unusually preoccupied with Tenma Taro.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? How can you tell?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, it's kind of hard to explain. You see, I can read people's emotions from the tone of their voice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean you have good ears?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Something like that. People's emotions are expressed in the tone of their voice. And my ears can pick up even the subtlest of tones for some reason.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's an interesting skill... But what do you mean he's preoccupied with Tenma Taro?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm not exactly sure, but it was like he was... obsessed with the thought of Tenma Taro... That's what I picked up from his voice, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Everywhere we turn it's Tenma Taro this, Tenma Taro that. Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We should go talk to the mayor, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sounds like a plan. <thought>We need to get to the bottom of that rumor about him wanting to release Tenma Taro.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Something wrong, Apollo? Where did your enthusiasm go?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What am I doing asking the mayor if he has ever thought about releasing Tenma Taro?! At best, he'll think I'm an idiot. At worst... *shudder*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, he's here!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's so nice to finally meet you! I'm Mr. Justice's partner, Athena Cykes! I'm looking forward to working with you, Mr. Tenma... Taro!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Hm?! ...Oh, yes. I look forward to working with you, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Eek! Glad he didn't mind Athena calling him by a completely wrong name!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, he's just as kind and gentle-looking as I'd imagined!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Lucky for you, after that blunder you just made...</thought> Um, there was something I wanted to talk to you about. There are rumors going around about how you want to or did set Tenma Taro free.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">What utter nonsense!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yikes!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">They always assume the worst of me because of the way I look! But those rumors don't have a shred of truth, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A little touchy about his appearance, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What he really needs to work on are his people skills...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... So rumor has it that you want to push the merger through... ...in order to release Tenma Taro. Of course, that's just a bunch of baloney, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Grrrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! Sorry! Sorry! Sorry! Sorry if I offended you!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">So, that's the talk around town, is it?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I can see how that would make you angry.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">.........What if Jinxie's schoolmates start teasing her about this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">I must break out of here at once! Her tormentors must be taught a lesson!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, wait! First, we have to get you a not-guilty verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Don't try to stop me! This is about a father's duty to his darling daughter. Hold tight, sweet Jinxie! Daddy's coming to save you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Relax! We'll look out for your daughter until we can get you free.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Hrmmm... Is that so? You don't need me to... go straighten things out myself?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Whoo boy... They'd probably call in the SWAT team if he showed up at her school. Oh, right. I ought to ask about the reason behind the merger.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It seems like you were rather forceful in pushing for the municipal merger. Did you really want Nine-Tails Vale that badly?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Yes, well, it's quite an attractive prize in terms of tourism.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait... Am I feeling what I think I'm feeling?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Sure, I played a bit of hardball, but only when I deemed it necessary.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I knew it. My bracelet's reacting!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">What is it, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mayor Tenma may not be telling the whole truth.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really? How can you tell?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">People invariably tense up when they lie. That's where my bracelet comes in. I can sense when the person I'm talking to is feeling tense... ...because it begins to feel tight on my arm.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Noooooo waaaaaay! You can do that?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, so you believe me? Just like that?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sure. Each of us has our own special gifts.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh yeah. Athena has a gift, too: her special sense of hearing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Still, what do you think the mayor's lying about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't know, but it's our job to find out. <thought>It's been a while since my bracelet last reacted like this. Let's see if I still remember how to do this... First I touch my bracelet (X</thought>... Right! Now let's give it a whirl!)</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, I remember this feeling of intense concentration! The ability to see the smallest twitch, the slightest frown that no one else can see... Now, Mayor Tenma was lying somewhere in that statement he just made. And when he lied, a certain "habit" made itself clear just under his right eye. I just have to shift my viewpoint up and focus on that area! All right, I've got him now. His tic should appear when he's trying to pull the wool over my eyes. I've gotta pour [sic] [recte pore] over every word he says, and wait for his tic to appear. And when it does, I'll "Perceive" <thought>X</thought> it!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Yes, well, it's quite an attractive prize in terms of tourism.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Mayor, please, you can trust us with the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">The truth? I don't understand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When you mentioned tourism... ...the bottom of your right eye started twitching.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">What nonsense is this?! So what if it did?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Please, tell us more about your merger bid.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">What more is there to tell?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why were you really seeking to merge with Nine-Tails Vale?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">I already told you: tourism. The monster craze really revitalized the village, making it quite the prize.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You really don't trust us, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">What are you talking about? The village has been hot property ever since the monster craze started, has it not?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think you've yet to realize that what you're saying contradicts the facts. You say that the monster craze really revitalized Nine-Tails Vale, so... ...you felt it would be an attractive prize for its tourism. But that would contradict this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">...Oh, forgive me. There was a fly that was driving me crazy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If that's how he deals with flies, I'd hate to see him when he's really angry.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">So, you think I'm not being entirely truthful?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes... yes, sir. <thought>This guy is seriously scary!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The monster craze in Nine-Tails Vale is a very recent phenomenon. It was sparked when The Amazing Nine-Tails rose up against the municipal merger. The village was practically a ghost town before then.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Argh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you see, you couldn't have possibly seen it as an attractive prize for its tourism. What's the REAL reason behind your push to merge Tenma Town with Nine-Tails Vale, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">W-Well, umm... uhh... Ah... Ah... Arrrrrrrrrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are you ready to tell me the truth now?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Honesly, I never wanted to pursue the merger in the first place. But I had no choice if I wanted to protect my darling little Jinxie.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Protect her from what?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">I received a threat. It said either I go through with the merger or my Jinxie dies.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">How awful! Who would do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">I don't know. But whoever blackmailed me must be connected to the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, so you think the blackmailer and the killer could be one and the same?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Alderman Kyubi was immensely popular, so you have to ask, who would want him dead? The blackmailer who wanted the merger at all costs had all the motive in the world.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But why go from blackmail to murder?! The merger protests won't disappear just because the alderman was killed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah! <thought>Could it be...!</thought> What if there was another reason for the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Like what?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe the blackmailer discovered Alderman Kyubi's secret identity! And his secret identity was a threat to the blackmailer's merger scheme!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What do secret identities have to do with anything, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I have evidence revealing the alderman's secret identity. Maybe it's time to use it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... this is a photo of the crime scene. You didn't happen to see a yokai there, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">...What in the world are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, no, I'm not saying I believe in monsters or anything, aha ha ha.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I'm sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">............... Hrmm...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Heh heh... <thought>Please, somebody let me out of here!</thought> Ummm... so did you see one? You know, like, I don't know, Tenma Taro or... Never mind, just forget it, heh heh!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">............Huh... Huh huh... Huh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is he laughing at me, with me, or even laughing at all? It's kinda hard to tell.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mayor Tenma, please take a look at this if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">That's...! That's The Amazing Nine-Tails's mask! What is the meaning of this?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This mask was almost definitely at the crime scene. And there was some white hair inside.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">White hair... you say?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There was but one person with white hair in the manor that day.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Wha... What are you saying!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You know which man I'm talking about, right? I'm talking about Rex Kyubi -- The Amazing Nine-Tails himself!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No way!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">The alderman was--! Impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait! Come to think of it, Alderman Kyubi WAS a former pro wrestler! So the blackmailer turned killer when he discovered the alderman's secret identity!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, didn't I just say that? But yeah, The Amazing Nine-Tails was a threat to the blackmailer's scheme. He opposed the merger and as a result, single-handedly sparked the monster craze.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Even so, what was the mask doing at the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There had been an event at the manor... ...and maybe Alderman Kyubi had taken part in it... if you get my drift.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">This is absurd!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Mayor, do you have proof of the threat that was made against you?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Yes, a blackmail letter. Unfortunately, it disappeared after the murder. I'd been carrying it around in my briefcase but now, it's suddenly vanished.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The blackmailer must've taken it with them after they killed the alderman. Well, at least we've clearly established the killer's motive.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Mayor Tenma, visiting hours are over.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">It would appear this meeting is adjourned.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">.........Apollo, do you really think the Tenma Taro that Jinxie saw is the killer?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't know. All I know is there is no such thing as monsters.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What about that newspaper article? Could the killer have purposely freed Tenma Taro to do their dirty work?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, come on! There wasn't any Tenma Taro to release in the first place!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, but the only suspects the police have right now are the mayor and a yokai.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>We'll probably be arguing whether there was a yokai involved in court tomorrow.</thought> *sigh* I can already see that look of disbelief on the judge's face.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo? Are you all right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm fine! I'm fine! I'll, um... I'll think of something! <thought>I'd better because I can't very well say a flying demon was the killer. At this point, the only thing I know for sure is tomorrow is going to be one doozy of a trial.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nothing of particular interest here.</line>
</xml>