
<xml>
<title>The Imprisoned Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This badge's design is said to reflect the relentlessness and discipline of law enforcement. It comes from the authority vested in us as strict protectors of the law... ...and executors of sentences, much like harsh winter frosts and blazing summer days. To wear it is to identify oneself as a prosecutor, but I have no interest in doing so.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Each Prosecutor's Badge is engraved with the number of its owner on the back. Hmph. Numbers. As if we're not human on the inside like everyone else!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..........</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">..........</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...He's not coming.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He's not coming, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How long does he intend to keep us waiting...!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Now, now, Mr. Edgeworth. There's no need to get your cravat in a twist.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ethan Rooke's murder... Two days after the incident, we visited the detention center. Naturally, we were hoping to meet with the defendant, Horace Knightley. His trial was set to begin the next day, with me serving as the prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Still, he is rather late... You there! Do you know what's going on?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">I-It is certainly strange... I'll try calling him one more time...</line>
<line speaker="Guard">I-It's terrible! I-It's... Knightley! H-He's been murdered!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whaaaaaaat!? What did you say!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Murdered? <thought>Inside the detention center?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! Let's go check it out!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You there! Take us to the crime scene, posthaste.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Knightley's not in his cell? I thought he was being held there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guard">What are you doing, sir!? This way!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-Where are you taking us, pal? Through this door is the...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah... It's the prison.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Prison? Then what were the small rooms back there?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Those cells we just passed are part of the detention center. They're used for holding suspects temporarily, while they await for their trial. What lies ahead... is a facility that serves a completely different purpose.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is where criminals who have been declared guilty serve out their sentence, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the one place a Great Thief does not want to end up, Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">I'm opening the door now! Please, follow me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Th-There's no mistaking it... Knightley's... dead! Moreover, he was murdered inside the prison walls... How exactly did this happen!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">I-I can't believe something like this would happen to Mr. Knightley!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. I can't believe it either... But the scene you see before you is the unmistakable reality.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Besides... Wasn't Mr. Knightley supposed to be in the detention center?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. He was. Knightley hadn't had his trial yet. Before a suspect is found guilty, they're detained in the detention center's holding cells. <thought>They only enter the prison after they have received a guilty verdict. Knightley should not have been moved in here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Do you think he passed through those giant doors that we went through earlier, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Huge metal doors and a long passageway separate the prison and the detention center. As a suspect, Knightley wouldn't have been able to pass through.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What happened to Knightley... In order to solve this mystery, we must first investigate the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The sheets stacked here have a very distinctive pattern...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's the same as the bloodstained sheet!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-That's right... Kay. Don't steal my lines like that.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hee hee hee. Mr. Edgeworth, you shouldn't get caught off guard like that. I'll never lose my edge as the Great Thief!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I thought she was on hiatus?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, what's up?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So this is what a prison is like! It's been very educational!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're more enthusiastic than I am at gathering information.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth, you need to work harder at gathering information! Otherwise... you'll be in trouble when the "time" comes!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't think the "time" you're talking about will ever come... ...but I do need to gather more information. <thought>In order to complete my logic and catch the killer!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's a really cool badge. It depicts a blazing sun on top of winter frost, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. It symbolizes the severity of the criminal justice system.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">My badge has symbols too! U-Uh Umm... It symbolizes Love and Justice and Peace and Courage and Honor and Kindness!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What happened to "Truth"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">So, you want to see my amazing rope escape after all?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Isn't there anything else you can do with a rope besides rope escapes?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I can also... make rope ladders and tie up bad guys! There are many things you can do with just a piece of rope.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>All of those things are only useful to a Great Thief.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">I believe that even a Great Thief has rights. For example, we have the right to choose what we want to steal.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I guess she doesn't consider this valuable.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a reservation form that lists the inmates who are scheduled to use this room.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">There are numbers written here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Probably their prison numbers.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'd hate to be called a number, like T-4137...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. That is why we are born with a name.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'd rather be called "Great Thief" or "The Terminator!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What about your name...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is there anything out of place?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Yes, sir! If I had to say...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">There's a dead body over there.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yup! That's definitely out of place!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...If you notice anything else out of place, please be sure to tell me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This section of the room is covered in dirt.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The dirt is soft and has footprints on it, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There are too many footprints... It won't be easy to identify them all.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Until the forensics arrive, we probably shouldn't tamper with this area.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective, please don't trip and fall in the dirt.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'll be careful, sir! I don't want to get my favorite coat dirty.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'm more worried that you'll mess up the footprints...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He was arrested on the afternoon of the 25th, and was killed on the morning of the 27th... I never expected the criminal to become the victim, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... It doesn't leave a good taste in your mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Maybe De Killer killed Knightley? He couldn't let anyone who had seen his true identity live! ...Or something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Are you talking about Shelly de Killer? If he was the killer, then he would have left his calling card behind. Besides, didn't we also see his true identity as well?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's right... And we're still alive, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Still, to commit murder in such a place is not an easy task... How did the criminal murder Knightley?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's nice that the prison and the detention center are connected, sir. As they both get to share the visitor's room, it's actually quite convenient.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well... It is an unusual design, but it is convenient for the visitors.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Why do the detention center and the prison need to be separated in the first place, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The suspects go in the detention center, while the convicts go in the prison. They might seem similar, but they are actually two completely different facilities.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Those cramped, dark, and uncomfortable cells all seem the same to me, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...If you're still having trouble understanding the differences, why don't you step inside one?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Uhh... I-I think I'll pass, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Such a tiny object. I'm surprised you don't lose it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is an identification badge for us prosecutors after all.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I see... It must be tough. If it were me, I'd definitely lose it, sir! I'm always losing my police badge.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Having such a talent for losing things must be tough.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's a terrible way to go, sir. Being stabbed in the throat... He won't be able to eat instant noodles anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's true. Detective, you should also be more careful. At this rate, you won't be eating anymore instant noodles either.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What do you mean, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I mean you better start pulling your weight around here with the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ughh... I'm dreading this month's salary assessment.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">AAAAHH! EUREKA, SIR! I figure out why they say "Checkmate"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Alright. let's hear it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The patterns on a chessboard look like check marks, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I thought he would say something like that...</thought> Detective. Checkmate is derived from the phrase, "The king has been cornered". It has nothing to do with the patterns on a chessboard.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-Is that right, sir...? And I just thought I had made the discovery of the century...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Maybe it's about time that you discovered you're the one who has been cornered. Know when to give up, Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">*gulp* U-Understood, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ha ha ha! Mr. Edgeworth, you're such a joker! Even if you show that to me, I still have no idea what it is, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He proclaimed that quite proudly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">We won't rest until we've stolen every suspicious-looking nook and cranny!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed... <thought>This is quite a large area to investigate... Press the Y Button to switch screens.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm... It's a pulley.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Is that used for prison labor too?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It looks like it.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">There's something I want to ask you...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't even think about dangling on the hook.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eh? How did you know that's what I wanted to do?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Somehow, I had a feeling.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's a cage inside the cage that is the prison. It's like cage-ception!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe the correct term is "prison cell".</line>
<line speaker="Kay">They're the same thing! You need to look more at the essence of things.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Actually, it's more important to get the correct information.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There was a rope near the body as well.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">By the way, my special talent...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If it's about rope escapes, there's no need for that now.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Awww.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Does she want to show it off that badly?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Those are some colorful sheets <thought>Stacked sheets - Very colorful and stands out in the room. What are they used for?</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">They're the most eye-catching thing in this room.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>They don't fit in with the prison...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">There's a whip placed on top of the sheets! It reminds me of the Whip Lady! Maybe she left her whip here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. I doubt she'd ever leave her whipe behind...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Horace Knightley... Murdered right before his trial. Let me take a closer look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is... a rubber glove.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes. There's no mistake, it's a rubber glove. How come there's only one?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Let me take a closer look...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's covered in mud, up to the wrist.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Maybe someone was playing with mud in the prison...? I want to get in on the action too!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do it on your own time, when we're not investigating a case!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It says "FOR INMATE USE". That must mean...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">A prisoner used this glove?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. That's what I was thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The fingers of the glove are covered in blood...</thought> This glove was dropped after the pool of blood formed.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eh! Why is that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If it was on the floor before the pool of blood had formed... ...the blood would have formed an outside around the glove.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! I see. The blood would have only gotten on the edges of the glove!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This glove was discarded after it was covered in blood...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That must mean the killer left it behind!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. It's highly probable. At the very least, the person who dropped this saw the body. You there!</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Wh-What is it, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you recognize this glove?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Yes, sir! The inmates use these for prison labor. That's odd... Rubber gloves are usually kept in the inmate's rooms... They are strictly regulated, so you can't just take them out!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Indeed, there are no signs of any other rubber gloves in the room.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is... a rubber glove.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes. There's no mistake, it's a rubber glove. How come there's only one? There are some mud stains on it. And bloodstains too!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's a possibility that the killer left this behind...</thought> You there!</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Wh-What is it, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you recognize this glove?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Yes, sir! The inmates use these for prison labor. That's odd... Rubber gloves are usually kept in the inmate's rooms... They are strictly regulated, so you can't just take them out!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Indeed, there are no signs of any other rubber gloves in the room.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ugh... The blood from his neck has stained his brace bright red.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The cause of death was most likely from his neck wound. He probably died instantly. He couldn't even cry out in pain. ...Hm? There are small bumps on his head. Are these bruises?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Maybe after he was stabbed in the neck, he fell back and hit his head?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wonder... At this point in time, there are too many unknowns. Kay. Do you have your digital camera with you? I'd like the detective to take a photo of the body. Would you let him borrow it?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Sure thing! Here, Gummy!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Thanks, pal! Alright, I'm taking the picture, sir! Still... He's wearing some awfully dirty clothes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... There appears to be dirt stains in several places.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He's wearing those clothes even though they're dirty... He's just like me, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective... I hope you realize that not everyone shares your lack of hygiene.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ugh... The blood from his neck has stained his brace bright red.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The cause of death was most likely from his neck wound. He probably died instantly. He couldn't even cry out in pain. ...Hm? There are small bumps on his head. Are these bruises?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Maybe after he was stabbed in the neck, he fell back and hit his head?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wonder... At this point in time, there are too many unknowns.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Still... He's wearing some awfully dirty clothes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... There appears to be dirt stains in several places.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He's wearing those clothes even though they're dirty... He's just like me, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective... I hope you realize that not everyone shares your lack of hygiene.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh? What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth has something similar in his office.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a portable chessboard. It was probably the victim's.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! Mr. Knightley enjoyed chess, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He was probably using it to pass time in the detention center...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He's covered with a dirty sheet.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">There's a rope on top of the sheet.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Was Knightley tied up with this rope?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's take a look under the sheet. We might be able to find something.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yikes! This sheet is bright red!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...These appear to be bloodstains <thought>Bloody sheet - The bloodstains appear to belong to the victim. It has a colorful pattern.</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">We still might be able to find something. Let's search this area a little more closely!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? There's something on his finger.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Let's have a closer look! Oh! It looks like an expensive ring!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't steal it.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wha...! I didn't do anything yet!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yikes! This sheet is bright red!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It really is bright red, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...These appear to be bloodstains.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">A rope and a bloody sheet... There might be something else!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Let me check this area again in case I overlooked something.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">There's a wash basin over here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are there any clues that could be useful to this case?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I don't smell any signs of treasure!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm searching for clues here, not treasure!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">There are a bunch of strange tools here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't see anything out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'm kind of picking up the scent of animals.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you have special smelling abilities or something?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">No, it's just a feeling. But I can smell the scent of treasure!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Remind me to lock up all of my valuables in a safe.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Come on, Mr. Edgeworth. I wouldn't steal your valuables!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...So you would steal someone else's valuables?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This glove must've been dropped after the pool of blood formed. Otherwise, the blood would have only stained the edges of the glove.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You can open it from there! Hurry up and open it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why are you getting so excited?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What are you saying! Doesn't everyone get excited when they're opening a box?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think that probably applies to you only...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">These are chess pieces, right? I saw something similar in your office, Mr. Edgeworth. Huh? But the pieces here are black and white?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Those are the correct colors. My pieces were custom made.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">"Custom made"... That sounds like treasure to me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Her eyes are sparkling... Does she intend to steal it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well. We've collected quite a bit of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He he! With the three of us here, it's a piece of cake! Right, Gummy?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's right, pal! We're the Invincible Trio!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's too early to start celebrating. There is still something we haven't found yet.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Eh? What haven't we found yet, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What is missing from this crime scene?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This crime scene is missing bloodstains.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Have you been overworking yourself lately, sir...? I can clearly see bloodstains over there!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... I can see them as well. <thought>I was too careless...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! What's missing from the crime scene, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This crime scene is missing footprints.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Footprints? It's true, I don't see any. But are footprints really that important to this case?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hmm. <thought>They're not particularly important...</thought> Kay, this crime scene is missing one more thing.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eh! What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The murder weapon that took the victim's life has not been found yet.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! Now that you mention it, you're absolutely right, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective. Get your act together. Isn't that the most basic of the basics?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ugh. I'm sorry, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Don't worry about it, Gummy! I didn't notice it either!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's not much of a consolation.</thought> In this prison, dangerous objects that could be used as weapons are strictly regulated. It'd be quite dangerous if the inmates got their hands on them... Obtaining a murder weapon and carrying it around is not an easy task.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I see! You have a point!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What was the murder weapon? And where did it go? That could be the key to solving this case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Huh? There are visitors here already? Sorry to barge in like this. Is this the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're...!</line>
<line speaker="???">Huh? You... Aren't you... That piercing gaze... That furrowed brow...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It has been a long time. Mr. Shields.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Yes, yes. That frilly thing around your neck and that stiff greeting. There's no doubt about it! Prosecutor Manfred von Karma. Fancy meeting you here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What are you saying, pal! Mr. Edgeworth's not that old man!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective... It's fine.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Oh it's you, Prosecutor Edgeworth. I thought you looked a bit young. He he he. You two are so similar. Looks like your Uncle Ray got you two mixed up again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You never change. How many years has it been since we last saw each other...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hmm. I've already forgotten. Your Uncle Ray has been overseas these past few years. But you know... There's something I still haven't forgotten. About you... and your betrayal.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I-I'm getting some bad vibes over here. Do you know this guy, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Allow me to introduce him to you. Raymond Shields, attorney at law.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ace Attorney Ray Shields at your service. I'm pleased to make your acquaintance.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm Detective Dick Gumshoe, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Kay Faraday. Nice to meet ya! I'm a Great Thief! Ah, but I'm currently on hiatus.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Great Thief? Well, well. That sounds romantic, how wonderful!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh! Mr. Shields, you get it, right? I'm currently recruiting new members! The registration forms are easy to fill out!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">That's splendid. Uncle Ray would love to join your little gang!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'm sorry, but we're only accepting bright, cheerful, and energetic girls.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I see. That's too bad. Well, how about a hug then? As a sign of affection.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...No.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I guess not. He he he. This isn't Europe after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Shields. What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Oops. That's right! Sorry, sorry. Preventing the attorney from investigating the crime scene is the Von Karma way, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! You've been going on about Von Karma this and Von Karma that. What's your problem, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective! Restrain yourself. This... can't be helped.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Eh...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Shields. Are you the defense attorney for Horace Knightley?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">That's right. Or should I say... I was his defense attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Mr. Shields is the defense attorney. If Knightley had not been murdered... ...I would have been going up against him in court... I should listen to what he has to say.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, what's up?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Just as I thought, the security in the prison is very tight. Looks like... It won't be easy to break out of here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Instead of breaking out of here, perhaps you should consider not entering in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's all because those sensors that detect the bracelets... Hmmm.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She seems to be agonizing over it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, Mr. Edgeworth! Don't just space out like that! Help me think of a way out, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What. <thought>Why must I do such a thing...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The rubber gloves used by the inmates... It's unnatural for one to the end up in this place. This is in direct contradiction with the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eh? Why is that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">From what we just heard about the inner workings of the prison... The rubber gloves used by the inmates should not be present in this room. <thought>Let me present some evidence to support my reasonings...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this spot somehow connected to any of the evidence I hold...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence shows the contradiction with the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Could you be more precise about where the contradiction is?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Umm... Around here somewhere...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Please be more specific, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mm... Mmph! <thought>There is something in this room that should not exist. Do I have the evidence to support this claim?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Since you received the request to represent the victim, that must mean...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Yes. Your Uncle Ray was supposed to meet with Knightley-boy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As was I. I had planned to meet with him, but then we heard the report of the dead body...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I even brought him a California roll.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Shields... You can't bring food into the detention center.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ah. Is that right? Well then, would you like it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hmm... Still, to think that Prosecutor Edgeworth actually meets with the defendants. All defendants are guilty, wasn't that the Von Karma way?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That is a thing of the past.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Heh. Is that right? So... You sure you don't want it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I told you, I don't want it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Did you meet with Knightley?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">He he. We met yesterday. They called me over as soon as Knightley-boy was arrested. He was being quite hostile. Oh yeah... He mentioned you. He talked about how you interfered with his plans.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He probably said some nasty things about me. Even if he hates me, I'm fine with it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Man, the two of us had a great time talking about you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">M-Mr. Shields, you also talked about me...?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I frequent the visitor's room here quite often... It's been a while since I had such a good time!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Heh, so you're a regular at this prison!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hey, now. Don't get the wrong idea. I'm not here as an inmate. I'm here to visit an old acquaintance of mine. We usually meet in the visitor's room, but I've also been in here before.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Then... I should ask him about this room.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This room... was where the body was found. Do you know anything about it?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ah, this room, eh? Here's a pop quiz for our prodigy prosecutor. Which one of these three is the name of this room?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...The Lecture Room?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">So they tied up Knightley-boy and lectured him to death? As expected of Prosecutor Edgeworth! You sure have an eye for the details!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...The Morgue?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hmmm... Well, there is a dead body in here! Anyone who saw the dead body would naturally think of the same thing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...The Entertainment Room?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Wow! Prosecutor Edgeworth sees this place as an Entertainment Room! And why not! There are plenty of toys here!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Well, let's reveal the correct answer! Prosecutor Edgeworth's answer is... Wrong! The correct answer is the Workroom.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... <thought>All three choices were wrong. I hate it when he does that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">The inmates carry out various kinds of prison labor in here. It also serves as a rehab program, allowing them to receive job training in prison.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So... How do they monitor this room? Who is in charge of the keys to the entrance?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Prosecutor Edgeworth. Even your Uncle Ray doesn't have all the answers. Hey. You there, could you tell us?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Yes, sir! This room doesn't use any locks and keys! Instead of locks, the doors are equipped with sensors.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">All of the prison inmates are wearing electronic bracelets! When a bracelet passes through the door, it activates the sensor and... *wiii-uuu, wiii-uu, wiii-uu* ...An alarm will sound. After a certain amount of time has passed, the bracelet will emit a painful shock! If the bracelets are tampered with... it will emit an electric shock three times more powerful.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eeehh! Th-That's terrifying!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's to ensure that the inmates follow the rules. Although it seems a bit harsh.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guard">That's why whenever an inmate goes through a door, a guard has to accompany them... ...to deactivate the sensor first.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">...And that's that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Did any of the inmates use this workroom today?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">In the past few days no one has used this room. I'm sure of it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So not one inmate has entered this room today...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If that's the case... ...it raises a contradiction with the crime scene. There is something in this crime scene that should not exist... I will use my powers of deduction and inspect the crime scene again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">This room is the inmate's workroom.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The doors are equipped with sensors, in order to prevent the inmates from escaping.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">If they try to escape from the room, an alarm will sound. "wiii-uu, wiii-uu, wiii-uu, wiii-uu* The alarm has not gone off once today...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So, not one inmate has entered this room today... This raises a contradiction with the crime scene. There is something in this crime scene that should not exist... I will use my powers of deduction and inspect the crime scene again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Huh, are you giving this to me? I'm thrilled! A prosecutor's badge might make me more popular than my attorney's badge. Thanks for the present!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, I never said a word about giving it to you.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">He he he. That was just a joke. Uncle Ray has his own badge.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your attorney's badge... You don't wear it on your clothes?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hmm... In the winter, I wear it on my favorite coat. Your Uncle Ray only wears it on his "Victory clothes".</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What kind of "Victory" is he talking about...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Knightley-boy seemed to enjoy playing chess.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Had we met under different circumstances, I would've liked a chance to play against him...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I see. Your Uncle Ray's not so great with these mental games.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph, you must be joking. I've never been able to beat you once in a chess game.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Well, that... was in the past. Against the famous prodigy Prosecutor that you are now, I wouldn't stand a chance.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Let's just leave it at that. <thought>He's never been one to easily show his hand...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ah, Ah-hah, this, eh. This evidence holds the so-called key to the case, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Err... It's possible.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Yup. Then, hold on to it closely. Hurry, hurry, put it away!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...He doesn't think much about this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The inmates cannot freely enter this room. As they're wearing bracelets that set off the sensors. According to the guard, it seems that no inmates were scheduled to enter this room today. However, a rubber glove used by the inmates was left in here. That is a direct contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Then, who left this rubber glove in here, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't know... yet. However, it seems that this rubber glove is connected to our case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Guard! Aside from the inmates and prison guards, does anyone else have access to the room?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Umm. Well, this is a prison facility after all. Only inmates and prison guards come here...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Shields...?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">He he he. What are you saying? There are others that come in here. Aside from inmates and prison guards, there are certain things that can enter this room.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">! Are you talking about them? But. They're...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Shields! What are these "things" that you speak of?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">It should be obvious. You came all the way here without seeing one, Prosecutor Edgeworth? Usually you can find them walking around the prison facility... Well, you'll see once you leave this room, Prosecutor Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! You're just saying that to get Mr. Edgeworth to leave, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">What now? Don't you trust me? Mr. Detective. You have a big body, but a small mind.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What did you say, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ugh... S-Sorry, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Come on. Follow me. I'll show you what Uncle Ray has been talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">This place is a little different from your normal prison. There are more than just the prisoners and guards living here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Animals...!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Yep, animals. According to the guard... ...they introduced animal therapy here several years ago. Each prisoner is assigned one animal. In other words, they receive a pet partner.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh! That... seems kinda fun!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Plus, learning to take care of their pet is a great qualification to have.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! So you mean that workroom!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Yep. That's where the prisoners practice taking care of their pets.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">S-So then, the "thing" you mentioned, that could enter the crime scene is...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Right. These animals.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But that doesn't make any sense, pal! Why would an animal leave behind a rubber glove!?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">He he he. Quite right. But the fact remains that they could have entered the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! Can you please talk some sense into this man!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Shields, are the animals allowed to go wherever they please?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Most of the doors in this prison are fitted with sensors. The sensors not only sound an alarm in response to the prisoners' bracelets. They also respond to the animal's "microchip" and open the doors for them.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Microchip?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">It's like a tiny machine embedded under the animal's skin. All it takes is a simple injection, "psh!", and the microchip is inserted.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Whaaaa! Th-That sounds painful...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I've heard it's not that painful... But, anyway. Since the animals aren't criminals, they are allowed to move around freely.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>How ironic... The ones with the most freedom in this prison are the animals...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">But still, they can't go out of the prison. The prison's entrance does not have a sensor. .....Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? <thought>What's that? Is that a bell...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wh-What's this... This dog? It has a bell on its collar... Was this the sound that we heard earlier?</thought> ........</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! Why are you glaring at each other?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I mustn't lose!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth, you're not good with dogs, are you, sir? I'll tame that dog myself! Here boy, here boy! It completely ignored me, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Compared to the other animals, there's something different about this one. I'm sensing a great hostility towards me only...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Well, now that I've introduced you to the animals... What's next on the agenda?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course, we question those related to the case, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. We should gather information about the state of things when the body was discovered.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We'll start with... you in that cell! Tell us what you know!</line>
<line speaker="Prisoner">........</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-He's completely ignoring me, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-You there. Do you know anything about the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Prisoner">........</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Uuugh... H-He's scary!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">He he he. Don't be so cold. Come on, you can talk to us. Or, how about an introductory hug?</line>
<line speaker="Prisoner">.....It's... time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! <thought>Wh-What was that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">S-Sorry. Was Uncle Ray's joke a little too much?</line>
<line speaker="Prisoner">........ ......Exercise time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This man... is clearly odd! I need to get some answers from him.</thought> Your... name is?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Me... I'm prisoner number D-259. Jay Elbird. ...Gotta raise my metabolism. I can't let my muscles rest.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Muscles aside, it looks like you've lost a lot of weight.</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Half of the match is won even before it has begun. Yeah... Gotta make the weight limit.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Err... Are you entering some kind of tournament? Ah! Perhaps as a boxer!</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Yeah, I'm a former boxer, but exercise is just... a hobby of mine.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well then, it sure looks like it's the bear's hobby too! Hee hee... He's hanging on like an apron. So cute!</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">This is Rocky the polar bear. He's my partner.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He's loosened his tongue. Maybe we can try asking him now...</thought> Where were you and Rocky at the time of the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">......I don't know anything. I got nothing to say to you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's for me to decide. Now, answer the question.</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">D-Didn't I just tell you? I know nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh... He has no intention of talking.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">In that case, you've got no choice but to use "that"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. If he insists he has nothing to do with this, we'll just have to prove there's a connection. Mr. Elbird, by all means, you WILL tell us what you know.</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">...........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now... Let's analyze the situation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A fighting stance... It seems that he has become agitated. In these circumstances, a direct confrontation would be pointless.</thought> When my opponent becomes agitated, I should calmly wait and see... When I see an opening, I will not hold back! Now, let's question him about his knowledge of the incident. To start with, I'll ask about his movements today. I'll have to tire him out before the sound of the bell!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Can you tell me what you have done today?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">......</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A-Answer me!</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Huh? If you wanna fight with me... Get into your fighting stance!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Rocky, you hearing this? I got no time for jibber-jabber. Wanna eat a knuckle sandwich?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a wasted remark.</thought> When he gets worked up, he enters his fighting stance. During those times, I should calmly "wait and see"... And strike when he drops his guard.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">What, are you throwing in the towel already?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is not a fist fight. Welcome to the war that is chess. By the way... Hasn't all that moving around tired you out?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Don't underestimate my stamina! You wanna test me? With that body of yours!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Rocky, you hearing this? I got no time for jibber-jabber. Wanna eat a knuckle sandwich?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a wasted remark.</thought> When he gets worked up, he enters his fighting stance. During those times, I should calmly "wait and see"... And strike when he drops his guard.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.....</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">I ain't tired at all. Well, first off... I held back in my training today. I just stayed quietly in my cell.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Quietly? Then what's with all that sweat?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">...B-Buzz off! That's all I've got to say. I'm getting a little tired...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...........</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">If you don't wanna fight, get outta the ring!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... I was too passive... When he gets worked up, he enters his fighting stance. During those times, I should calmly "wait and see"... And strike when he drops his guard.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're a well-trained boxer... However, you need more practice in the art of lying. Getting a little tired? That's not possible! You said that you stayed quietly in your cell just a moment ago!</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">...! Rocky. It looks like this is gonna be a tough opponent.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This man... It looks like he's still hiding something. Next, I'll ask him about the time of the incident. I do not need to use fists. My words alone are enough for a K.O.!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you recall what you were doing at the time of the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">...Sleeping. Rocky was too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The incident happened just a few moments ago. You look wide awake to me.</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">......</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Rocky, you hearing this? I got no time for jibber-jabber. Wanna eat a knuckle sandwich?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a wasted remark.</thought> When he gets worked up, he enters his fighting stance. During those times, I should calmly "wait and see"... And strike when he drops his guard.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Muscles strengthen while they're resting. Sleep is important.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well then, I'm sorry to have woken you. Rest is a part of training... Right?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">...O-Oh? ...S-So you get it after all. Not bad, Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...........</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">If you don't wanna fight, get outta the ring!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... I was too passive... When he gets worked up, he enters his fighting stance. During those times, I should calmly "wait and see"... And strike when he drops his guard.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Oh? I don't recall ever introducing myself as a prosecutor. How did you know?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Th-That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The conversation we had when we first entered this room... Were you, by any chance, eavesdropping on us? In that case, there's no way you could have been asleep! You lied to us!</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">...! You got me there. You pack a nice punch. Yeah, I lied about sleeping. So what? I was just exercising in this room. You got a problem with that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Well, I now know he was awake. I should remember this clue.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've run this line of questioning to its conclusion... Let's try another line of attack.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">When the incident occurred, did you notice anything unusual about the prison?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">.....Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Rocky, you hearing this? I got no time for jibber-jabber. Wanna eat a knuckle sandwich?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a wasted remark.</thought> When he gets worked up, he enters his fighting stance. During those times, I should calmly "wait and see"... And strike when he drops his guard.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...........</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">If you don't wanna fight, get outta the ring!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... I was too passive... When he gets worked up, he enters his fighting stance. During those times, I should calmly "wait and see"... And strike when he drops his guard.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Answer the question! What was the situation like at the time of the incident!</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Sorry, but I got no answers for you. I was asleep then. Rocky was too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't have enough clues to proceed with this line of questioning. Maybe I should try another line of attack...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's try using that clue...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...........</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">If you don't wanna fight, get outta the ring!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... I was too passive... When he gets worked up, he enters his fighting stance. During those times, I should calmly "wait and see"... And strike when he drops his guard.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Stop telling such an obvious lie! Didn't you admit it earlier? You were exercising...!</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Tsk... Looks like I just ate a counter.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your back's against the ropes and there's no way out. Just confess already!</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">...! H-Hey, quiet down a bit. If outsiders like you make a racket, you'll frighten the animals again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Rocky, you hearing this? I got no time for jibber-jabber. Wanna eat a knuckle sandwich?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a wasted remark.</thought> When he gets worked up, he enters his fighting stance. During those times, I should calmly "wait and see"... And strike when he drops his guard.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...........</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">If you don't wanna fight, get outta the ring!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... I was too passive... When he gets worked up, he enters his fighting stance. During those times, I should calmly "wait and see"... And strike when he drops his guard.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You've been persistent. However, I'm afraid you're about to hit the mat. You said "again" just now. Did something happen earlier? To frighten the animals!?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Gyaaaaaaaaaaaah! D-Dammit...! How could I have gotten sucker punched like that! Y-Yeah... There was this great scream back then. It startled the animals. Dang! I would never have lost in a real ring!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Checkmate.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe this proves that you do know something about the case.</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">.......Damn. OK, I'll talk, I'll talk!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You did it, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't lose focus, Kay. The real game has just begun.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Let's just stop for a moment. Uncle Ray's got one important thing to say. It must be fate that has brought us together after all these years. I have received the opportunity to observe your skills carefully. And... ...I'll be giving a detailed report to "that person" about how much you've grown.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Err... Who is "that person"?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">You didn't know? The truth is...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This doesn't concern Kay. She doesn't need to know!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Whoa there. You scared me. Don't get so worked up.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You can do what you like. It doesn't matter to me.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">...How you have been leading your life ever since you were tainted by the Von Karma way... I'm sure "that person" would be interested. I feel that it's my duty to report it to him. I'll expose your mistakes here, I won't let you disappoint him any further.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">M-Mr. Edgeworth... Just what are you guys talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't concern yourself with it. Our only opponent now is Elbird. Well then, let's hear it. What do you know about the case?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">...You're gonna be sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Recreation time ended around 10 AM.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That's odd. You really weren't bothered by that shout?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Even if I was, there was nothing I could do. Look out for number one before you look out for others. That's the basic rule in prison.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Indeed. Even if he wanted to take a look he'd still be locked in his cell.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is all that training equipment yours? You seem to have quite a collection.</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">I get them from the Supplier.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Supplier...?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">You can get just about anything if you put in an order. It's our secret shop.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">That's quite convenient. So, if Uncle Ray wanted a cute girl...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In that case, you should order a book on how to give testimony. Hmph... Because I'm going to knock you down for the count in one hit.</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">You're gonna K.O. me? Stop kidding around...!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Heeey... Don't ignore your Uncle Ray!</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Recreation time ended around 10 AM.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Recreation time?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">There are "people from the outside" who come here... And sing and dance, to entertain the "people on the inside".</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's great! That does sound like fun!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And you participated in this event?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">There are few opportunities to mingle with the outsiders. After recreation time ended, I...</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">I returned to this room and went straight to my training.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, what exactly does your training entail?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">To build up stamina and rhythm... I jump rope.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Whaaaaa! In such a small room!? Isn't that dangerous for Mr. Bear... I mean, Rocky?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Rocky's a smart one. When he sees me grab my rope, he clings to my chest.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're able to jump rope, while holding a bear...?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">He's a weight I'll gladly bear. Rocky's... my best partner. So, today I started my jump rope routine as usual. However...</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Just as I'd counted to two, I heard a voice shout out, "AAARGH! I've been stabbed!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Could you describe that voice for me?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">It was the voice of someone whose life was in peril. ...I could tell.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">R-Really. That's no laughing matter.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And this voice, you heard it quite clearly?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">...You've never heard the scream of a cornered man before? I told you. The man was screaming for his life. Of course I heard it clearly.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Elbird">It sounded like someone in pain, calling out for help. But...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Was that all? Did he say anything else?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">...That was all. He didn't say anything important after that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's for me to decide. I'd like to hear it, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">...If you really want to know that badly, how about I recreate the scene for you right now?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Nonononono! Sorry, that was a stupid thing to ask. Miles, you should apologize too!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This point is vital... I'd like to clarify it if possible.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Come on! Please bear with us, for Uncle Ray's sake! OK!</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">...Hmph. Anyhow, I heard the voice, but...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Elbird">I couldn't do anything since I was locked up in my cell. So, I went back to my training.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You were able to concentrate on your training after that scream?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">If I were on the "outside", I'd probably go over and take a look out of curiosity... However, inside this stupid cell, I'd have to get permission to go anywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Have you considered breaking out of prison?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That sounds more like something you'd try to do.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">If this place wasn't a prison, Mr. Knightley might have been able to get help.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't believe he could have been saved.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eh! But, what if someone had come running to his aid...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Elbird is clearly lying. But... what possible reason would he have to do this? To find out, I'll have to point out the contradiction.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Elbird. Can you hear my voice clearly?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Why you... You mocking me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The victim received a fatal blow to the throat. Which means... he couldn't possibly have screamed.</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, why did you hear a nonexistent scream?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Th-That's...! There should have been a scream...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There should have been one?</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Dang it! I oughta rip that smug look off your face! Yeah. You're right! I never heard a scream! The one who heard it was the guy in the next cell!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The next cell...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Uhh, the next cell...</line>
<line speaker="Prisoner">Ah? What's up? Yeah, I heard the scream. Recreation time had just ended. It happened after we returned to our cells. So then, I tell that guy, "I heard a great scream."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Can you describe that scream for me?</line>
<line speaker="Prisoner">Sure, I never told that guy about the contents of the scream though... "AIEEEEEEEEEE! Someone! Come quickly! A man's been...!" Something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hmm. So, it wasn't the victim...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...but rather, it was the first person to discover the body who screamed.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I see! That solves that mystery! So, there was nothing wrong with Mr. Elbird's testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is that really true? Or is there still a problem with Elbird's testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. There is no problem with Mr. Elbird's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Jay Elbird's neighbor heard the scream, right? So then, why didn't Elbird hear it himself?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh! <thought>Looks like I need to think this over again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">What's the matter, Mr. Edgeworth? Is there really a problem with Mr. Elbird's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No... In this case, a new problem has presented itself. Mr. Elbird, why did you not hear the scream?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's odd that he didn't hear the scream, sir! Hey you! Why didn't you hear the scream, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">.......... Guaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aieeeeeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">...... ...You guys, do you suspect me? I was shut up in this stupid cell the whole time... How could I have killed someone in the workroom?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">! Th-That... would be impossible, wouldn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Prisoner">Yeah! None of us could've killed him! If we could've killed him, we would've already killed you guys by now!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aieeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">You guys, don't think you're going to get out of this prison alive...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I nearly forgot... Despite being locked inside cages, these guys are still dangerous criminals!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">He he... Looks like we got ourselves in a pretty bad situation here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What can I do? I can't talk to them in these circumstances!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-Who was that?</line>
<line speaker="???">...Please be silent.</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">What? Who're you? Can't you see we're busy here!</line>
<line speaker="???">Silence is golden.</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Wh-What the...</line>
<line speaker="???">Now, your hands. You shall remain silent while under the judgment of the law. You should be thankful. You get to live your life without the need of money. You are to receive the blessings of the Goddess of Law. Guard. ...If you would please.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Congratulations. You get to spend the night in the disciplinary room.</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Eh...! Th-That's! N-No! Not there! Anywhere but there!</line>
<line speaker="???">Accept this wonderful blessing! Let your heart be reborn! Cast away your sins!</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Stop it! Noooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, Goddess of Law. Give this man your blessings. ...I thank thee.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You are...?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">My name is Justine Courtney. I am privileged to be a Judge... An emissary of the strength of the law.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A judge, you say? Why are you here?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Prosecutor Edgeworth... I came to meet with you personally. I convey the will of the Prosecutorial Investigation Committee. That is my appointed task.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Prosecutorial Investigation Committee? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Do not use that name so lightly. Those are the sacred words of the Goddess of Law.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Since little Kay doesn't know, Uncle Ray will explain it for her! The P.I.C. is an assembly comprised of 11 members. Their job is to check if prosecutors are doing their jobs properly.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If I'm not mistaken, its members are elected from politicians and those of the legal profession. ...So, I take it you are one of those members?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...Indeed. I am thankful they judged me worthy of such a task.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I, too, am thankful that I was able to meet you here. Ahem. How about a hug of thankfulness?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">The Prosecutorial Investigation Committee also shares deep ties with the Bar Association.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hey, I was just kidding. No need to make such a scary face.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Errr. So your job is to find bad prosecutors and punish them?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Well said! May you be blessed by the Goddess of Law. Our job is to remove problematic prosecutors from their cases. And so, those people not fit to be prosecutors... ...will be stripped of their Prosecutor's Badge.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What business does this Whatchamacallit Committee have with Mr. Edgeworth, pal! We're in the middle of an investigation here...</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="???">Wow, you're thick. Seriously, how thickheaded can you be?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And just who do you think you are, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Me? I'm a prosecutor. Sebastian Debeste is my name. Haven't you heard of me? At the Prosecutor's Office, everyone calls me "The Best". Ah, I'm so beloved there...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...........I've never heard of you.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Hey you, Mr. Flatfoot. You've heard of me, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is the first time, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">...Oh well, It can't be helped. There's no way someone who's so thick on the intake could have good ears.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Don't you mean "slow on the uptake"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Courtney">I suppose it's only natural as Sebastian only became a prosecutor last month.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He's just a rookie prosecutor!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Right. The Best rookie prosecutor in the office...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...Or so he plans to be.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Mr. Edgeworth. I'm here to clean up the mess you made.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The P.I.C. intends to have me replaced... That much is clear.</thought> ...Mr. Debeste. I know what you're trying to say. However, I have not been informed of this. Your Honor. I would like an explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Very well. This judgment has been passed under the name of the Goddess of Law. The incident at the president's welcoming event, and the murder of Horace Knightley... The Prosecutorial Investigation Committee has decreed that you will be taken off this case... ...and Sebastian has been appointed to take over the case. ...That's all.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-Whaaaaaaat! You can't just take him off the case like that, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor... I thought I asked for an explanation?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">The judgement is guilty. The Goddess of Law's verdict is absolute.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have done nothing to warrant being taken off this case!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">You don't remember? Very well, in that case I shall remind you of your past crimes. You boarded the president's plane, which was protected by extraterritorial rights... ...and then, of all things, you ordered a search of the president's personnel.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">A single mistake could have sparked an international incident. You crossed the line as a prosecutor... You've gravely overstepped your authority.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll admit, my actions may have gone against the rules. However, if I had not taken that risk, I'm certain that the truth would never have been found. I have never considered my actions as a mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">So, you're saying that as long as the ends justify the means... ...it's alright to ignore the rules. That is an extremely dangerous way of thinking. No one is above the rules. That is the spirit of the law.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sorry, but... I cannot accept your way of thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">I see. That's a shame. Even so... ...the gavel must slam down at the conclusion of a trial. Even if you, or the defense attorney, or the suspect, do not consent to the verdict. All you can do is accept the blessings of the Goddess of Law. Or... will you fight it? And risk losing your badge?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She means to take my badge if I don't obey.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Awwwww. That's too bad.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">It seems you understand. Now then, guards. Please proceed.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hold it right theeeere!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Hey, what are you doing! Aren't you supposed to be on our side? You should listen to the new prosecutor in charge.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ehh! I don't wanna work for you, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">But, isn't that the job of a flatfoot?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>We're at an overwhelming disadvantage here... It's useless to resist any longer.</thought> Detective Gumshoe! You are now under Mr. Debeste's authority.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">B-But that's...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Yes? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This does not mean I have accepted your decision. We will meet again.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Certainly... I look forward to that day.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's go, Kay!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah...!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Wait. Don't forget. I'll be reporting today's events to "that person."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! Just what happened yesterday!? Those two people! Their attitude was just unforgivable!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Mr. Edgeworth. I'm here to clean up the mess you made.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">The Prosecutorial Investigation Committee has decreed that you will be taken off this case... ...and Sebastian has been appointed to take over the case. ...That's all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Judge Courtney and Mr. Debeste... They were certainly ruthless. But what I'm more concerned about is... ...just what is the P.I.C. thinking? ...I'm worried about what they will do from here on. I have a bad feeling about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, Mr. Edgeworth! Are you listening to me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I'm listening.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You're not going to give up on this case, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No. I don't plan on backing down, not with the current situation as it is. If I were to silently stand by, that would only validate their claims. <thought>But I no longer have investigation rights. What should I do now?</thought> What is it, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">B-Bad news, sir! I heard something down at the precinct... It sounds like they've already arrested a suspect in yesterday's case!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What! Who is it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't know yet, sir... But if we go down to the detention center, we can talk!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Let's get going! Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Even if I can't investigate, meeting with the suspect should not be an issue.</thought> Alright, we're heading over to the detention center now.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'll also head over on the double, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective. Won't that interfere with your job?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I gotta investigate the scene of the crime anyway, so it should be OK, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Alright. We'll meet up with you there.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Roger, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's go, Kay!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..........</line>
<line speaker="Kay">.......... ...He's not coming, is he?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He's not.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's happening all over again!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Don't joke about that.</line>
<line speaker="???">No way! I mean it! It's not happening!</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Yes. It's happening alright! There's just someone here to talk to you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">That sounds like a pretty screechy voice, huh?</line>
<line speaker="???">Nowaynowaynoway...!</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Don't be so stubborn!</line>
<line speaker="???">But aren't prosecutors crazy scary or something? Always giving you a death glare!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Um, pardon me, but would you happen to be the suspect...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Aaaaahhh! I knew ittt!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, why does this man seem so distraught?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, because you're, uh, you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That doesn't help me at all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hello, Mr. Suspect!</line>
<line speaker="???">!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Would you mind talking to us for a little bit?</line>
<line speaker="???">Wh-Who are you?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'm Mr. Edgeworth's assistant, Kay Faraday! Well, it's just a part-time job. I'm just taking a vacation from my real job!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I don't remember hiring you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">This is Mr. Edgeworth. He's a prosecutor, but he's not as scary as he looks, so it's OK.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmph. How rude...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">R-Really?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Really! Really!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Really.</line>
<line speaker="???">Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Anyway, can you tell us your name, Mr. Suspect?</line>
<line speaker="Simon">...Yeah. Uh... I-I'm Simon Keyes...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Nice to meet you, Simon! You can just call me "Kay", 'kay?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I am Miles Edgeworth, a prosecutor. I would appreciate a word with you.</line>
<line speaker="Simon">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Please! It's for your own good, Simon!</line>
<line speaker="Simon">...Really?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Finally. It looks like we'll be able to get something out of him, thanks to Kay.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">First, I'd like you to tell me a little about yourself...</line>
<line speaker="Simon">No way! Not that! I couldn't do that. Impossible! I'm not worthy! There's nothing interesting about me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your occupation?</line>
<line speaker="Simon">No way! Not that? It's no big deal, honest! Yeah! I'm just a regular employee.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Good grief...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">About the victim, Knightley... <thought>I don't think he's going to talk to me about this.</thought> ......Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Simon, did you know Mr. Knightley from some where?</line>
<line speaker="Simon">...Knightley? Y-Yeah, I did. He was... a friend...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A friend? So, did he know that Knightley was arrested?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Did you know that... Mr. Knightley was arrested?</line>
<line speaker="Simon">Yeah. ...I came here to meet him.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So he visited the detention center too. When was that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">When did you visit him here?</line>
<line speaker="Simon">It was two days ago, in the afternoon... I received a call from the police, so I came over right away...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>From the police?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Why did you get a call from the police?</line>
<line speaker="Simon">It was a request from Knightley. He had a message for me.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">A message?</line>
<line speaker="Simon">Yeah. He wanted me to bring him his pocket-sized chessboard. So, I retrieved it from his house and came here to give it to him.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Did he say... chessboard?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Did you say... chessboard?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is Kay...stealing my thoughts?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">No, Mr. Edgeworth. It's just written on your face!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He he he... I was just guessing from your facial expressions. See! I can be a useful assistant, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... So, do you know what we need to do next?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You bet! We gotta show "that" to Simon, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correct. Let's present it and see how he reacts.</line>
<line speaker="Simon">No way! It's really impossible! There's no way I could be a prosecutor! Even if you give that to me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That was never my intention.</line>
<line speaker="Simon">So, are you going to arrest me? Am I going to trial? No objections, your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is an objection. Please calm down.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Keyes, I would like you to take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Simon">Aaaaahhhh! I see nothing, I hear nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Once he calms down, I'll try showing it to him again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Do you recognize this chessboard?</line>
<line speaker="Simon">Ah! That's Knightley's!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Just as I thought...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">This was found near Mr. Knightley's corpse.</line>
<line speaker="Simon">...He always carried a chessboard with him. It's just like him to have one until his last breath...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It sounds like you two were really close, Simon.</line>
<line speaker="Simon">Yeah, we were best friends... At least, I thought we were... But, maybe I was wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Simon">Because I never imagined he would murder someone.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Having someone close to you turn out to be a murderer... Reality can be so cruel. It's not something most people can easily accept...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Simon">And I never imagined we would part ways like this. *sob*...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth. Something's definitely strange here! There's no way Simon could have killed Mr. Knightley!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed... I certainly can't see a motive at all. <thought>However... The fact remains that he was the one who was arrested on that charge. Just what was the justification for doing so?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Simon">Knightley loved chess... We would always play against each other. I-If only I hadn't brought that to him... ...it probably wouldn't have turned out like this.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm not so sure. To me, it's the proof of the friendship between you and the victim. I doubt it had anything to do with the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Simon">R-Really... *sob*... Aahh! I can't take it anymore! Just arrest me already!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Haven't they already done that?</line>
<line speaker="Simon">Even if you show me stuff like that, it's too technical for me. ...I-I don't get it at all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... I guess you don't have any new information about it?</line>
<line speaker="Simon">S-S-S-S-Sorry! Am I going to be arrested? If I start spouting some random nonsense now, will I be able to plead insanity later?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...If you want to be guilty of perjury, go right ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Simon">Th-That was a leading question! I knew it! I'm going to be arrested!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Good grief. He's not listening to me at all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, why were you arrested? <thought>Hm, I guess he still won't respond to me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Simon">........W-Well, I don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Looks like he's finally warming up to you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Whew, that's a great help.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Simon">This morning, a police officer barged into my house... And before I knew it, he had brought me here...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Was there a prosecutor accompanying him at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Simon">Ahh. I remember a prosecutor called Du-um... Best or something was there too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So, it was that rookie prosecutor...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Then, I guess the police haven't dragged you into questioning yet, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Simon">A-Are the p-police going to interrogate me?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yup. That's right. Because you're the suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Simon">Nowaynowaynowaynoway...! Aren't detectives like crazy abusive or something? Always bossing you around with their big bodies!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Detective Gumshoe is on the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Simon">Aaaaaaaaahhhhh! I knew ittttt! Please don't beat me with your thick arms! I can't take it anymore! Someone call the police!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">....... What's gotten into him, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well... It's because you're you, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? I don't get it, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I know Simon has to be innocent, Mr. Edgeworth! Can't we do something...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Simon Keyes.</line>
<line speaker="Simon">Y-Y-Y-Yes!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You were Mr. Knightley's best friend. You only just met with him two days ago... You say you didn't kill him. Are you certain about this?</line>
<line speaker="Simon">......Y-Yes, I am. I-I wouldn't harm a fly!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. That's enough for me. I shall offer my assistance in proving your innocence.</line>
<line speaker="Simon">Eh! Wh-What's the point in helping little ol' me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's not just for you. This case, I have a personal stake in it as well.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's right! We gotta get back at those two from yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah! I'm fired up, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But, I don't have any investigation rights at the moment. Since I won't be able to obtain information myself, your role is most vital. I'm sure we can rely on you to fill in any holes in the information we have. Help us help you... That's all I ask.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! I just had an idea! Why don't you just borrow a defense attorney's badge, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Come on! There's no way Mr. Edgeworth could do that. This isn't the time to be joking around!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">B-But I wasn't joking... Helping the suspect is a defense attorney's job, pal...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Jeez. Don't worry about that! It doesn't matter what Mr. Edgeworth's job is. All we gotta do is find the real murderer! So, let's get movin'!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OK, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sure you understand, but if the investigation results prove that you are the murderer... No hard feelings, but I will show no mercy...</line>
<line speaker="Simon">Eeeeeee...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But, you don't need to be scared. I believe in your story... At least for now.</line>
<line speaker="Simon">........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">All you need to do is believe in us and wait patiently... There's nothing to fear. Now, if you'll excuse me, I must be off.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...So, we're all fired up and ready to go. But we still can't enter the part of the prison where the murder occurred...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If you can't investigate, the only thing you can do now is defend him in court, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But how are we supposed to do that? We can't!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Huh? If it isn't Prosecutor Edgeworth and his merry gang. What are you guys doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Did you come here to harass Mr. Edgeworth again, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">He he he. What're you talking about, big guy? Uncle Ray's just here to do his job.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Your job? Oh yeah, you're a defense attorney, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Oh, Kay! You're as cute-iful as ever!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Cute-iful...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">I might not look like it, but your Uncle Ray's a hotshot defense attorney. I'm here to meet with a new client today. What was his name again? Shy Monkees or something...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What? You mean Simon Keyes?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">That's it! Kay! Looks like you know the deal.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! He's the defense attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I thought as much. Guess we have no choice but to resort to that method. In the past, whenever I had to investigate cases I was not placed in charge of... ...I was able to gain access by becoming a subordinate to whomever was in charge. Not my preferred opinion, but it's the only one I have now...</thought> Mr. Shields. If I may ask...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">By the way... I don't take on sidekicks.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I refuse to take on male assistants who lack charm. Especially... Someone who was like a son to Von Karma.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Mr. Shields... As I thought, he won't forgive me so easily.</thought> Mr. Shields. I understand that you cannot forgive me for what I've done. I am also fully aware of your hatred towards those involved with Von Karma. I don't know if you'll believe me, but... ...I am no longer the same as I was back then... Back when I idolized Von Karma.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, pal! Mr. Edgeworth is a changed man! Sure, he may have been a cruel, inhuman prosecutor in the past... ...but now, he's completely different, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>When you put it that bluntly, it kind of hurts...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's right! Mr. Edgeworth's not a bad guy anymore! I wouldn't even call him a prosecutor! He's more like... Uh... Umm... A hero! Yeah! He even helped me out in that big case last month!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">A hero... That's some pretty big talk there, missy.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He's a magnificent hero! Although he'd be no match for a Great Thief like me!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">......</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Shields, don't the actions of the P.I.C. appear... strange to you? I believe there may be something else hidden behind this case. I can't afford to... quit at this juncture! Please let me help you with the investigation. I am begging you.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">...... ...Heh. I never expected you to grovel like this. It sure looks like you've changed, alright. And I'm kinda interested... in the cause of all this.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're interested... in what changed me? If I had to say, it would probably be... the courtroom itself. All the experiences I've had and all the people I've met inside the courtroom. And perhaps... Reuniting with my old friends.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">...... He he he... I never expected you of all people to change. Who would've thought that you'd lay open your heart like that. I'm sure that man would be surprised as well. Guess I can't turn you away. It may be long overdue... But allow me to properly reintroduce myself. If you would be so kind as to read this...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Edgeworth Law Offices Raymond Shields, Head Attorney...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">E-Edgeworth...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Shields was an assistant to my deceased father... Gregory Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Really? Your father was a defense attorney? S-So that means that man Mr. Shields talked about is...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Correct, my cute little Kay. Prosecutor Edgeworth's old man. I never changed the name of the firm. It's my way of showing my appreciation for his help. Prosecutor Edgeworth. No, wait... Miles. Uncle Ray doesn't fully trust you just yet. It may have been temporary, but the fact remains: you were once a disciple of Von Karma. You say that you've changed, but you'll need to prove it to me with your actions. Even your old man... Would've wanted it this way.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes, I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Alright. I'm getting tired of all this stuffy talk, so let's give it a rest and move on... For now, I'll make you my temporary assistant. How does that sound?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sorry to trouble you...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">But... this outcome is kinda moving, yeah? The prodigal son returning to work in his late father's law firm.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What about me! What about me!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Of course, you can help too, Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Alright! Thanks a lot, Mr. Shields! I mean, Boss!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Now then, let's get right to work. Let's see.. First off... What do you think we should do, Miles?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's right... I had some unfinished business yesterday.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hmm. So, it wasn't the victim...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...but rather, it was the first person to discover the body who screamed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why don't we find them and listen to what they have to say?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Yeah, that's it! Uncle Ray thinks so, too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmph. Upbeat as always.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK! With that decided, let's hurry up and grill him!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um... Sir, what am I supposed to do? Detectives can't help defense attorneys!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... I can't just leave him be...</thought> Detective, I will give you a special assignment. I want you to assist Mr. Debeste in his investigation and follow his orders. And then, if you discover anything useful, I want you to share it with us. Detective. This is a job that only you can do. Can we count on you?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yes, sir! Leave it to me! I'm really good at leaking investigation reports to defense attorneys!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Normally, that would be a problem for me, but it may come in handy this time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Alright, let's get moving, shall we? Time to go to jail!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Now then, where's the person who first discovered the body?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For now, all we can do is ask around.</line>
<line speaker="???">Hold it right there!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Who is this woman?</thought> Umm... Excuse me, but...</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, you are simply irresistible!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Huh? Do you mean... me?</line>
<line speaker="???">Very nice, very nice, indeed! What an elegant mustache.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">It's a pleasure to meet you, mademoiselle. Defense attorney Ray Shields, at your service. How about we exchange greetings with a hug?</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh ho ho ho. But of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Mmf! Mmmmmmmf! Uncle Ray's... l-lips...</line>
<line speaker="???">A proper greeting should begin with a hug AND a kiss!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's almost like... it was stolen from him!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, a remarkable feat of quickness that would put a Great Thief to shame.</line>
<line speaker="???">I feel that close contact is very important. This goes for my family here in my home as well.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Q-Quite a splendid way of thinking there. He he he.</line>
<line speaker="Roland">I am the warden, Patricia Roland. But please, just call me Patty.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The warden...? So she's in charge of the prison and detention center?</thought> Nice to meet you. I am Miles Edgeworth. I'm a prosec... I mean, I'm Mr. Shield's assistant. Pardon me for asking, but were you here in the prison yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Roland">But of course! Yesterday was a day that I wouldn't have missed for the world!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Wouldn't have missed for the world"? Did you have some kind of important meeting...?</line>
<line speaker="Roland">Oh heavens, no! I despise meetings! It was the Animal Show, of course! A wonderful spectacle, featuring animals dancing and flying through the air! I always see it along with everyone else in our home! We're one big, happy family! We built a special stage in the courtyard just for this performance.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A performance for the prisoners' enjoyment... Yesterday, Elbird mentioned some kind of "recreation"... I suppose the Animal Show was what he was referring to.</thought> When did this show take place?</line>
<line speaker="Roland">It started at 8 AM and ended around 10 AM.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's exactly when the body was discovered... So whoever saw the show would probably have an alibi.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Roland">Now, if you'll excuse me, I must be going. I have business to attend to. Please take your time and have a look around our home!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So, where should we start, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There was a prisoner who heard the scream from the person who first discovered the body. Let's start by talking with him.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, what's up?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Here's our chance, Mr. Edgeworth! While that demon lady is gone, we can snoop around!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Demon... Is she referring to Judge Courtney?</thought> I don't approve of your words... But let us carry on with the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Alright! Let's do it!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">These doors open whenever they detect an animal... If I brought an animal with me, breaking in here would be easy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Before that... Sneaking into the facility won't be a simple task.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What you'd need is some special technique that lets you open any door you come across...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Do you possess such a special technique?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Umm... That's a trade secret!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I guess not.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm.. They even have a pony. Little kids could ride it.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">How nice. It's like a zoo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Although, it's the humans who are treated like animals in here.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Do you think they'd find out if I took one home with me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think that if you did that, you'd be the one behind bars.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">There's some information here about the prisoner of this cell! Let's see... Inmate number: D-259 Species: See cell on right.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That's a shoddy explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">His partner is Rocky the polar bear. He is a former boxer who enjoys training to lose weight. His muscles are tough, but he's a big softie. He's an omnivore. ...So it says.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Who is this information for...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No one's here.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">This person was taken to the disciplinary room. I wonder when he'll be back?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Who knows...? I'm sure he won't be allowed to return so easily.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He was on the verge of tears, he really didn't want to go...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. His reaction was quite extreme. <thought>I wonder... What sort of punishment awaits him?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">U-Uncle Ray's lips...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You seem to be in quite a shock.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Isn't Warden Roland the type of beauty Mr. Shields likes?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">...A hug is a greeting, but a kiss is on a whole different level. Your Uncle Ray needs time to mentally prepare himself.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I didn't think you would be such a shy guy, Mr. Shields.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Somehow, I don't think that's the problem here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hey, Miles... About your face, could you loosen it up a bit? Since you're going to be Uncle Ray's assistant, you'll need to smile more!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Being an assistant and smiling more have nothing to do with one another.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">That's not true. A smile is the first step to building trust with a client. First, show a refreshing smile to put them at ease, then give a wink to capture their heart. End with a hug, and exchange business cards! That's how you open up a client's heart.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Let's just keep that to ourselves, please.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Well, managing the law firm was quite tough at first. It was difficult inheriting the business from Gregory...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is that so... What kind of requests do you usually receive at the office?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Umm. Usually requests to defend suspects in murder cases and various sorts of legal counsel. Well, our basic policy was "We Welcome Everyone".</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Did you ever have to turn down any requests?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Well, if the client wasn't cute enough.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I thought everyone was welcome!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I'm kidding. That was a joke. We accept clients of all sorts. ...With Greg's name on the line. I couldn't do a half-hearted job.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...The Edgeworth Law Offices, the law firm that my father built...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, something's written here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, it's some information about this inmate.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">"Inmate number: D-258 Species: Convictus Brutus" "Despite his ferocious appearance, he is a herbivore. His partner is Gwen the penguin. He has good acting skills and a great stage presence. Delivers powerful testimonies." ...So it says.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's just like one of those information signs at the zoo...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Where is the person who first discovered the body, right now?</line>
<line speaker="Prisoner">Around this time, I think he should be in the workroom in the back?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The workroom... I should go take a look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It's a pot-bellied pig. <thought>Let's hope it doesn't become dinner.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">How nice. It's like a zoo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Although, it's the humans who are treated like animals in here.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Do you think they'd find out if I took one home with me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think that if you did that, you'd be the one behind bars.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This bench is quite rusty.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Only cats and Gummy would sleep on this bench.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed... No argument here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You can see the crime scene from these small windows.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! You can't just go peeping in like that! You need to be more... sneaky, and check your surroundings!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-Why... must I behave like a common criminal!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eh? I thought you wanted me to teach you my special "steal a glance" technique!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't need your techniques!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">There's a monkey on that hill, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hardly an appropriate spectacle for a prison...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">When you see stuff like this, you can really feel the tension rise!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I hope you're not expecting me to agree with you. Also, Kay... Just so we're clear, I don't want to see you climbing that hill.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But, someone's gotta show that monkey who's boss.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Don't provoke the monkey.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This door leads to the inmate's workroom.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What are these workrooms for?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Basically, they provide job training towards the inmate's rehabilitation.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But we found a dead body in the other workroom, right? Are you sure they really help in the rehabilitation process?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm... In order to answer that question, we must uncover the truth as quickly as possible.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hey, you there. I'd like to ask you some questions.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">So cute, meow~!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It really is, meow~!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hey, you!</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Meow~!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He finally noticed me.</thought> By the way...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What's this cat's name, meow~?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">His name is "Nermal", meow~!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's enough. Carry on with your duties. <thought>What we have here is a failure to communicate...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's a watering hole here.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Umm. This is hard to drink out of. They should have thought more about the end user when they designed this!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay... Can't you see that this is for the animals?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The courtyard lies beyond these shutters, but they are locked.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Freedom is right in front of them, but the shutters are locked up... Life is so cruel. I really feel sorry for them!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..Who are you feeling sorry for?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! What's a rabbit doing here... <thought>I almost stepped on it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">How nice. It's like a zoo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Although, it's the humans who are treated like animals in here.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Do you think they'd find out if I took one home with me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think that if you did that, you'd be the one behind bars.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Where does this door lead to?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Don't you feel some strange vibes coming from that door? Maybe... They've got a deadly criminal locked up inside!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That certainly is possible. It would be best not to get too close.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ehhh! I-I was just kidding...!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hellooooo! Is this occupied?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Kay, that's not a restroom. Hey, guard. Do you have a minute?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Sir! What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Is anyone using that workroom right now?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Presently, there is one prisoner working inside! I'm positive he's been there since the noon roll call!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We would like to ask the prisoner a few questions, if that is acceptable...</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Yes, sir! I will bring him out, so please wait a moment!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I'll leave this to you, Miles.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">'Cause I don't know what kind of scary guy will come out of that room.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Shields. You're a scaredy-cat? Even though you're an adult?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">He he he. Same to you, Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Here he comes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, good day to you, sirs. Are you the ones who requested my presence?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He doesn't seem like a dangerous criminal...</thought> My name is Miles Edgeworth. I'm a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="???">A prosecutor... Is that right? </line>
<line speaker="Ray">I'm Ray Shields, a defense attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Mr. Shields... His demeanor completely changed once he saw who we were dealing with...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Sorry about that. He he. My assistant says strange things sometimes. He's not a prosecutor, just my assistant. Hey! Get your act together, Miles.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, I guess I messed up... I forgot about my "new job".</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">No wonder I thought you were different from the prosecutor who visited me yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It looks like he's already spoken to Debeste.</thought> May we ask you a few questions?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">...Oh, yes. Of course you may. My name is Frank Sahwit.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">OK. Go for it, Miles.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I guess I'll be asking the questions after all... *sigh*...</thought> Mr. Sahwit, you are aware of the murder that occurred here yesterday, correct? Where were you when the body was discovered?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I was... in this room, where I had been working.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What kind of work?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Well, my goal is to become a pet groomer. An animal beautician, so to speak. Oh yes. I was inside cultivating my skills.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>In any other prison, such training would be unheard of...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">That was all. Honestly. I-I did not see a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm? Why did he say that? I haven't even asked him anything yet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Which is why, sad to say, I won't be any help to you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Sahwit... I haven't asked you anything yet.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">! No... Wait. That's... Even if you were to ask, I would not...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You... know something, doesn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">...! Oh, oh... That's... ........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It seems he is indeed hiding something. Let's try to press it out of him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">First let us assess the layout of the board. My opponent's condition is...</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I'm afraid I didn't see a thing. So, I won't be any help to you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This man's expressions do not change much. It's a true poker face. It may be difficult to read his emotions from his body language.</thought> Perhaps I should focus on how he phrases his words. It may reveal what's on his mind. Now, for the opening move... I'll start by asking about who this man is. Even if he hides his emotions, if I push the right buttons I'm sure I'll cause a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you... involved with this case?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Are you referring to the murder that occurred inside this prison? I had nothing to do with it at all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Is that true?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I-I would never dream of being involved in a murder plot. Hm... How should I put it... I'm... an upright, model citizen after all...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">If you have no more use for me... May I leave now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... I was too passive... Even if he hides his emotions, if I push the right buttons I'm sure to cause a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Common sense tells me... ...an upright, model citizen would have never ended up behind bars.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">W-Well, that is...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tell me what you know about the incident!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I already told you, I don't know a damn thing! Oh, er... I really don't know anything.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Whatever are you talking about? I really have no time to waste...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a wasted remark.</thought> Even if he hides his emotions, if I push the right buttons I'm sure to cause a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I apologize from the bottom of my heart for that outburst... But I will be of no assistance.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Pardon my rudeness. It's just that the murder occurred in this rather confined prison. It seems unnatural that you do not know anything about it.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">...Oh? Er... U-Unnatural... Is that so? I-If you're looking for the person who discovered the body... You should try someone else...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">If you have no more use for me... May I leave now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... I was too passive... Even if he hides his emotions, if I push the right buttons I'm sure to cause a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How did you know we were looking for the person who discovered the body? I don't recall saying a word about that. Are you sure you don't know anything?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">...! N-No... It was merely a hunch I had. I am but a humble pet groomer in training. I honestly have no recollection of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I am positive that this man is hiding something. For my next move... I'll ask him about his movements on the day of the murder. This man has suppressed his emotions. I will expose his true nature hidden beneath that suspicious smile!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's talk about what happened on the day of the murder. If you truly had nothing to do with it, there shouldn't be a problem, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Oh... Well... O-On the day of the murder... There was a lot going on...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tell me what you were doing on that day.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">A-As I mentioned earlier, I was cultivating my skills as a groomer in training... I was trimming the coats of the animals at the time...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Didn't the murder cause a panic? I imagine the entire prison must have been in an uproar...</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Well... But... Th-There was no panic... I could even hear someone's voice...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Whatever are you talking about? I really have no time to waste...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a wasted remark.</thought> Even if he hides his emotions, if I push the right buttons I'm sure to cause a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">If you have no more use for me... May I leave now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... I was too passive... Even if he hides his emotions, if I push the right buttons I'm sure to cause a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Someone's voice? Judging from the circumstances, I suppose it was a scream that you heard? So you do have a recollection of the murder! You kept insisting that you knew absolutely nothing about the murder... But you do not give credence to your claims!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Urgh! W-Well, I thought I heard someone's voice but... I-In any case, I don't remember it very well.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The scream at the time of the murder... It might be a clue. I better keep that in mind...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've run this line of questioning to its conclusion... Let's try another line of attack.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What was the state of the prison at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I don't remember it too well... My memory is rather poor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't have enough clues to proceed with this line of questioning. Maybe I should try another line of attack...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">If you have no more use for me... May I leave now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... I was too passive... Even if he hides his emotions, if I push the right buttons I'm sure to cause a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's try using that clue...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">If you have no more use for me... May I leave now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... I was too passive... Even if he hides his emotions, if I push the right buttons I'm sure to cause a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You don't remember? Ridiculous. Didn't you say earlier that you heard a scream?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">That wasn't... I could very well be mistaken... At any rate, I honestly do not remember.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You still do not remember? Enough with your lies!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I ain't lyin', you...! ...I mean, I'm telling the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Whatever are you talking about? I really have no time to waste...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a wasted remark.</thought> Even if he hides his emotions, if I push the right buttons I'm sure to cause a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">In any case... I was absorbed in grooming the animals.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">By the way... How skilled would you say you are in animal grooming?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">My techinique with the scissors still needs some work... But I am very confident in my handling of the animals. When the animals became frightened, I calmed them with my gentle hands...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Frightened? Why would the animals have become frightened? I don't think that's a common occurrence...</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">W-Well... That's a good thing... Isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Whatever are you talking about? I really have no time to waste...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a wasted remark.</thought> Even if he hides his emotions, if I push the right buttons I'm sure to cause a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">If you have no more use for me... May I leave now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... I was too passive... Even if he hides his emotions, if I push the right buttons I'm sure to cause a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps the reason they were frightened was because of someone's scream? Why are you trying so hard to hide the fact that there was a scream! Are you concealing some vital information from me?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Argh! I-I am doing nothing of the sort! I-It's true that I heard some sort of scream... But I'm not trying to hide it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He's starting to show his true colors. I should be more aggressive with my next move. I'll ask him about the scream. It's time to give him a taste... ...of the futility of keeping a secret from me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">When did you hear the scream?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Th-That's it! I just remembered! At the time of the murder, there was an event going on. It was the Animal Show. I had gone there to see it...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you're saying that since you were watching the show, you did not hear the scream? That's... completely different from everything you've said up until now!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Shut up! So what if it is! I mean... My memory is just so hazy...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Whatever are you talking about? I really have no time to waste...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a wasted remark.</thought> Even if he hides his emotions, if I push the right buttons I'm sure to cause a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Whatever are you talking about? I really have no time to waste...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a wasted remark.</thought> Even if he hides his emotions, if I push the right buttons I'm sure to cause a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">The Animal Show was very enjoyable.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What kind of animals performed in the show?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Well... Umm... I believe I saw a whale?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Whatever are you talking about? I really have no time to waste...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a wasted remark.</thought> Even if he hides his emotions, if I push the right buttons I'm sure to cause a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">If you have no more use for me... May I leave now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... I was too passive... Even if he hides his emotions, if I push the right buttons I'm sure to cause a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You liar! You didn't see the Animal Show at all!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Urgh! W-Well, that is... I sort of saw it, and I sort of didn't...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He didn't see the show. This could be a clue.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've run this line of questioning to its conclusion... Let's try another line of attack.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you know who the scream belonged to?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">W-Well, I was mistaken. When the incident occurred, I just happened to be in the courtyard. That's why... I did not hear the scream.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't have enough clues to proceed with this line of questioning. Maybe I should try another line of attack...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's try using that clue...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">If you have no more use for me... May I leave now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... I was too passive... Even if he hides his emotions, if I push the right buttons I'm sure to cause a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just how deep are you going to dig your pit of lies? It's obvious that you did not see the Animal Show!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Urgh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's no way out of this! Tell me what really happened! Confess everything you know about the scream!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I cannot answer... What I cannot answer... I-I didn't hear the scream... from the person who discovered the body...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Whatever are you talking about? I really have no time to waste...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a wasted remark.</thought> Even if he hides his emotions, if I push the right buttons I'm sure to cause a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">If you have no more use for me... May I leave now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... I was too passive... Even if he hides his emotions, if I push the right buttons I'm sure to cause a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's strange. Normally, if you hear a scream during a murder, it's usually from the victim. Why would you think the scream was from the person who discovered the body?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Oh! M-My mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How? How did you know the scream was from the person who discovered the body?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">W-Well... That's because...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Whatever are you talking about? I really have no time to waste...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a wasted remark.</thought> Even if he hides his emotions, if I push the right buttons I'm sure to cause a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">If you have no more use for me... May I leave now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... I was too passive... Even if he hides his emotions, if I push the right buttons I'm sure to cause a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Allow me to answer for you. That's because you're the one who discovered the body. And... ...the scream that was heard when the murder occurred didn't come from the victim... It came from you when you discovered the body!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Urrrrrrrraaaagh! J-Just who do you think you are!? I-It is just as you say, but... What gives you the right to do this?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Checkmate.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's now clear who discovered the body. You have no more reason to withhold your testimony... Correct?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">V-Very well, I'll tell you... B-But I doubt my testimony is worth hearing...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Whether or not it is worth hearing is for me to decide. I will expose the truth with my own hands. That is my sole duty.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Umm. I think you're a little off there, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">We're not trying to expose the truth, we're trying to save Simon! Isn't our goal to help out our clients? I mean, you're not a prosecutor right now, you're a defense attorney's assistant!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hmm.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Well said there, Kay! She's right on the money, Miles. The official task of the Edgeworth Law Offices is to defend our clients. Your old man, who founded the firm, truly valued the bonds he had with his clients. So, if you're not willing to do the same, maybe you aren't cut out for this job. I don't wanna fire you on the spot either. So have a heart, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...... <thought>The heart of a defense attorney, huh...</thought> In any case, it's important that we hear the testimony of the person who discovered the body. Start talking, Mr. Sahwit. Tell me what happened when you found the body!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I was in the workroom over there practicing my skills.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If I may confirm one thing... You were in the room... Right next to the one where the dead body was found?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Within the prison, we call it Workroom B.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And were you in there the whole time on the day of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yes. After the 7 AM roll call, I remained inside the whole time. In this prison, we have roll call 3 times a day. At 7 AM, noon, and 9 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And they check the workrooms during those times, too?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I see... So during the 7 AM roll call, there was nothing amiss. And Knightley's body was not in the workroom yet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">So it sounds like the murder occurred after 7 AM, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And that's right when the Animal Show started!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Correct. The other prisoners went to see the Animal Show.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Meaning anyone who did not see the show does not have an alibi... Do you understand what I'm saying, Mr. Sahwit?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Y-Yes, that is certainly true... H-However, I merely discovered the body...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>His testimony has a clear contradiction. I should press him about that first.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I was in the workroom over there practicing my skills.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">By practicing, you mean, of course...</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yes. My grooming training. For I am a model prisoner.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I somehow doubt that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">By some chance, I got curious about the adjacent workroom, and went up to the door.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You were curious about the adjacent room?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Precisely. I felt a need to look inside.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why did you feel that way?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Even if you ask me why... I just did it on a whim.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you weren't concentrating on your training?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">N-No! Nothing of the sort! For I am a model prisoner. It's just that... The other prisoners had left to see the Animal Show. Which is why... I was... feeling somewhat lonely.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah. That's like being stuck in a classroom after school's let out.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Y-Yes! That's right! And since I couldn't enter the other workroom...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I peeked in through the small window on the door.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The small window? So you couldn't get a clear look?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Indeed... As you can see, there is a grille covering the window. It does not offer a wide view at all.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Normally, the guards use it to check inside the rooms, right?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Precisely. You seem to be well-versed on this matter.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He he he! Well, I happen to know a thing or two about prisons, y'know!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What does she mean by that? I'll have to find out the details later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">In any case, I peeked into the room from the window.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Then I saw him lying there... A man... not moving... dead!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You knew it was a man right away?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">It was clear judging from his physique and clothing. Even the fact that he was dead was as plain as day.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You could tell he was dead through that tiny window?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Well... It's not the first time I've seen a dead body.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wha... WHAAAAAAT? S-So, you mean...! The reason you're in here is because...</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I'm ashamed to admit it, but it is as you say. However, this was my first time seeing a body that someone else had killed...</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I quailed in fright and found myself letting out a scream.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you remember what the scream sounded like?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">......Well. All I can say is that I shrieked at the top of my lungs.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Well, I guess that's what happens when you get scared.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yes, it is just as you say. In any case, I let out a scream.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He's pretending to be an innocent bystander, but parts of his testimony are odd. Considering his situation, and the place he's in... The contradiction should be quite obvious. I'll show him the evidence that proves it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Mr. Sahwit. Please stop telling such feeble lies. You don't seem to understand your position.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">My position? I-I used to be a newspaper salesman, but then I took up the pet groomer training...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What about that bracelet on your wrist? It proves that you are... unmistakably a prisoner. And as long as you wear that bracelet, you should not be able to move around as you please! As soon as you went through the door, the sensor would have sounded the alarm.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Oh, er... That is...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Peeking into the adjacent room is impossible... When you couldn't even leave the one you were in!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Argh!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Whoo-wee! Nice one, Miles! That was a real humdinger!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But does that mean Mr. Sahwit didn't see the body?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm not sure. Perhaps... We should let the man himself explain it to us.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Huh? Umm... You see... That is... Well... Forgive me. It appears my previous explanation was lacking... I shall clearly explain how I was able to see the body.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Very well, let us hear your revised testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">There is a rather well-known technique among the prisoners here...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, so that means... He kept his arm inside workroom B, while he peeked into the adjacent room.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I'd appreciate it if you didn't mention this to everyone. Especially the guards... OK?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Was that what he was trying to hide earlier...? I should try asking him for more details about a few other things as well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">There is a rather well-known technique among the prisoners here...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tell me more about this technique.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Certainly. Here's how it works...</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">If the hand with the bracelet stays in the room, you can step out without sounding the alarm.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">All you gain by doing that is a small degree of freedom.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Naturally. But it is all that we have left to enjoy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'm shocked that you enjoy such a thing. Have you truly reflected on what you've done?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">But of course! For I am a model prisoner!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Your definition of "model" is highly suspicious...</thought> Regardless, was that the one technique you used?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yes. That is correct. I made sure no guards were around when I did it.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">That's how I was able to peek into the adjacent room.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why would you do something so troublesome and potentially dangerous?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I heard a noise coming from the adjacent room... It seemed odd to me, as there should not have been anyone inside...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you peeked into the adjacent workroom as soon as you heard the noise?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yes. Yes. Of course. I peeked in as soon as I could.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... <thought>Is there a problem with that statement?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>No... There doesn't seem to be a problem with that statement.</thought> Please continue with your testimony, Mr. Sahwit.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Certainly. I peeked inside the workroom...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you looked into the adjacent room immediately after you heard the noise. If that was true, then you should have seen more than just a dead body. You should have seen the person who had made the noise.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Th-That is... Um... Well...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He looks really shaken!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Sahwit! Answer me! What did you really see?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you intend to remain silent... ...I will have no choice but to assume that you are complicit to the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">! Oh... Umm... Please forgive me. It's just that I couldn't even believe what I saw myself... It may have been just a dream. I hesitate to even recall it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tell me what happened!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Very well... I will be frank with you. I saw a dog. ...It was a nightmarish scene. A large black dog... ...was biting into the neck of the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wha-! What did you say!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">It was a truly hellish scene... That dog! That dog killed him!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ooooooh... I think I'm going to be sick...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">That's some Grade A trauma right there...</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I was chilled to my very core, and let out a shriek.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A man-eating dog inside this zoo of a prison...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">That was everything I saw. Do you believe me now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes, I do. I doubt one would be able to lie about something like that. Would you add that to your testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Certainly...</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"And to my horror, there was a black dog biting his neck!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just to be certain, allow me to reconfirm. Why did you look into the room next door?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yes, I will repeat it as many times as you would like, yes. I heard what sounded like faint footsteps coming from the adjacent room... In a flash, I was peeking in through the window on the door. I believe that is what being a model prisoner is all about. When you're a model prisoner, you must set an example for everyone to follow.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'm not sure I agree with his mindset, but...</thought> Very well. Then please tell me exactly what you saw in the room.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">The moment I realized that the man inside was dead, I let out a scream.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you remember what this man looked like in a detail?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">But of course. I am certain... He had blond hair... And his throat was covered in blood.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you take me for a fool? That should be obvious!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I am merely telling you everything as I saw it, just to be clear. ...Don't defense attorneys love nitpicking over every little detail?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I detect a tinge of spite here. Perhaps he had an unpleasant experience with a defense attorney in the past...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">And to my horror, there was a black dog biting his neck!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A black dog was biting the victim's neck...</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yes. Blood came pouring out, and as a result, the dog's mouth became stained with it...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ahhhhh! Stop! Stop! You don't need to get THAT detailed!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">At that time, was the victim...!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eeeeeeeeek! Mr. Edgeworth! Why'd you ask him that?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Kay... Why'd you hit Uncle Ray?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">The man did not even flinch...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He must have been dead already...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">But the blood continued to gush from his neck. He most likely had passed away already. His hands moved nary an inch...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Eeee! Way too much detail! Are you doing this on purpose?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Certainly not. I am just trying to give an accurate testimony... Mr. Edgeworth. Shall I add that statement to my testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you would.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">It was terrifying... A truly terrifying sight.</line>
<line speaker="Add statements">"He most likely had passed away already. His hands moved nary an inch..." and "The ring with the snowflake insignia glimmered, with no purpose but to catch my eye."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I would like to hear the details about that again.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Very well. That fearsome beast was gnawing away at the...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aaah! Enough already! I don't want to hear anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">...And then the blood, gushing out of the...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Eeee! Didn't you hear the lady? Uncle Ray's got goosebumps too!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">...And that was the state of the body. Do you understand the situation now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Those two were so noisy, I couldn't hear him very well...</thought> Mr. Sahwit. Please speak a little more about the state of the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">He most likely had passed away already. His hands moved nary an inch...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That was a very vivid testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">That is because I witnessed it up close, relatively speaking. I could feel the anguish he suffered in his death.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">M-Mr. Edgeworth... I won't be able to sleep tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Really? How terrible.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, come on! It's all because of you that my mind is filled with scary thoughts.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I may even have nightmares myself. Even now, I can still remember everything clearly.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">The ring with the snowflake insignia glimmered, with no purpose but to catch my eye.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A ring with a snowflake insignia... Impressive memory.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I was formerly a newspaper salesman. I had to quickly identify what a customer wanted based on his appearance and attitude... ...in order to form a successful sales strategy. It's the most basic of the basics.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But you are dealing with a corpse, not a customer. Are you like that with everyone?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yes, it has already become an ingrained habit of mine. It was an important point that could determine the success or failure of a sale.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's how you were able to easily recall such a minor detail.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Precisely. Even the engraved insignia is crystal clear.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is that really possible...? What was the state of the body when we found it? I should review my evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I have an unerring eye. That much I can declare.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So he was able to peek into the adjacent room by keeping one arm inside the workroom. But was that really what he was trying to hide? I should ask him for a further explanation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, Knightley was killed by a dog that was being kept here in the prison? I find that hard to believe...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">They say that pets take after their owners, yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It doesn't have to take after them THAT much! This completely defeats the purpose of the animal therapy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Perhaps I should ask about the dog a little more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A ring with a snowflake insignia...?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yes, that is correct. It was clearly engraved on the surface.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. Your testimony is very accurate, But it's a little TOO accurate, if you ask me.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">And what's wrong with being accurate?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You state that you saw a ring with a snowflake insignia engraved into it. And it is true that the victim was wearing such a ring.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">See? Was I not correct?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That is not the issue I have with your testimony. Take a look at this picture! As you can see, the right hand is covered by a sheet. It should not have been possible for you to see the engraving on the ring. Unless you had approached the body and lifted up the sheet for yourself! You said you only looked into the workroom through the door. And yet, you gave such a detailed account of what you saw.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Who do you think you are...? Acting all high and mighty. I-I'm telling you, I saw what I saw! Oh! The victim must have moved his arm after I saw it...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't think so. You said as much earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">The man did not even flinch...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He must have been dead already...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The victim was already dead. How would he have been able to move his arm?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">......!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">This guy's lookin' pretty suspicious now, yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Frank Sahwit! What are you hiding, you scoundrel!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">......Ooh. No, I ain't... I am not... That is... You're wrong. I know what I saw... ...Urrrrrgh... Gwaaaaaaaaaaaah! Shut up already! Stop making a fuss about every little thing I say! You're just a defense attorney's assistaaaant!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...He has finally shown his true self...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Whoa. I guess the cat's out of the bag. A black, hairy one at that. ...Just went flyin'.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I'm just your friendly neighborhood witness!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you really just a witness? I would you say that you are rather suspicious.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">What was that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You saw something that could not have been seen from the outside of the room. How is that possible? ...The logic behind it is simple. Mr. Sahwit. This is where you saw the body from!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is where you saw the body from.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He was able to see the body from a place like that? I get it! So you're saying Mr. Sahwit is psychic, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No... Nothing of the sort. <thought>Let me think it over once again. If he saw something that he could not have seen from the outside of the room... ...he could only have seen the body from that spot!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">When you discovered the body, you went inside the room where it laid! Since you saw the engraving on the ring, that is the only possibility!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">.......... Heh... He he! Even if you say that, you ain't got no evidence, do ya? Where's the evidence that shows that I was in that room? I was grooming pets at that time. In the room adjacent to where the body was found! I even went so far as to borrow some rubber gloves! Show me the evidence that proves I was in the room where the body was found!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">And what does that that prove?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... I guess you won't understand unless I explain it.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yeah, I don't get it at all! That evidence doesn't mean squat!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Urgh! <thought>I should be careful when I bluff...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Sahwit, what were you doing when the body was discovered?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Didn't I tell you already? I was practicing being a pet groomer!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. In that case... Do you happen to recognize this glove?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Oh! Th-That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This was found near the body. It is believed to have been dropped by the culprit. By the way... I noticed that you also have a rubber glove hanging out of your apron pocket...</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">N-No, this is... something else!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Looks like you're missing one of your gloves.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Y-You can find gloves like these anywhere in the prison! Your evidence proves nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Perhaps we should hand this glove over to the police for fingerprinting. I'm certain they will find some interesting results.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Grr... Grr... Grrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrraaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhh!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's over...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wh-What the...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">He he he. Pretty cool, right? My "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>" voice.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Shields. Could you save the jokes for later...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I'm not joking. Because it's not over yet. There's still something else. Something that's clearly odd. That guy's a prisoner, y'know. He's got the bracelet and all.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">..........</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's right! How did he get into the other workroom? The sensor would have set off the alarm, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...He's right. That's the only thing we don't know yet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Not so fast, Mr. Prisoner. Could you fill us in?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">..........</line>
<line speaker="Ray">That's pretty weird. The bracelet should have been his last line of defense.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Defense?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">That's right, Kay. It was useful evidence for Mr. Prisoner here. He could have claimed that due to the bracelet, he wasn't able to enter the room... But, he didn't say a word about it. Is there any reason why you didn't?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">..........</line>
<line speaker="Ray">The silent treatment, eh? Well, the Judge yesterday did say that silence is golden.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">W-Wow... You really are a hotshot defense attorney, Mr. Shields!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Defense attorneys always remain calm in a pinch, and smile in the face of danger. That's what your old man taught me. The Defense Attorney's Creed, yeah? ...So, what's the deal? Why didn't you mention anything about the bracelet?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">.......... ...The truth is... It's broken.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Broken?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Some time ago, I took a spill and the bracelet hit the floor with a loud bang. Ever since then, it was not been able to activate the sensor. Forgive me. It was so convenient, I didn't want to report it...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... So the bracelet was broken. <thought>But did it really break so easily? If that is true, then there is a problem with the prison's security.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You, over there. May I have a moment?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Here, kitty kitty. You're such a cute little guy! Yes, you are! Meow~!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Excuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Y-Yes! What can I do for meow?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This prisoner's bracelet appears to be broken.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">What! Really!? That's not good at all. I'll contact the person in charge and have it replaced immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thank you. I'll be holding onto the broken bracelet for the time being.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Yes, sir! Please take care of it.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Now that the bracelet's been taken care of, shall we move on to arresting you for murder?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">What? Perish the thought! I didn't kill anyone!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">But your bracelet was broken, right? Doesn't that mean you could have gone anywhere you wanted during the Animal Show?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">But all I did was find the body! Honest! And it is true that I saw the dog biting his neck! However, I entered the workroom after the dog had left...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why did you do that?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Well, it was just... I was curious if he had anything of value on him...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So he was planning to loot the corpse. That's why he remembers Knightley's ring so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Why are you looking at me, Mr. Edgeworth!? I am a GREAT Thief! Please don't put me on the same level as him!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">But! I didn't take a thing! The Animal Show had ended and the other prisoners were making their way back down here. I hurried back to my workroom, and let out a scream to deceive the others.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">And that's when you dropped your rubber glove.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's covered in mud, up to the wrist. What did Frank Sahwit use this for?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It says "FOR INMATE USE". That must mean...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">A prisoner used this glove?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Frank Sahwit was the one who used this glove.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I guess his story holds up. What do you think, Miles?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Whether he is the murderer or not, one big question remains. How did Knightley get all the way from his holding cell to the prison?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">You're right about that. It's a real stumper.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And there's something Mr. Sahwit said in his testimony that I'm very concerned about. <thought>If that dog had any part in the murder...</thought> Mr. Sahwit.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Y-Y-Yes! What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Were there any other prisoners who didn't see the Animal Show?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">...Yes. There is only one other that I know of.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And this prisoner wouldn't have been able to see the show even if he wanted to. Correct?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Y-Yes, that's correct. Why do you ask?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Just as I thought... I had my suspicions as soon as I saw that black dog. That fiendish criminal... I never expected him to be held here in this prison.</thought> Where is his cell...?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Err... Do you intend to meet him?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Him...? Who's him?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">He's a very special man. He receives very special treatment, and... ...Oh, forgive me. I need to watch what I say about him. However... If you value your lives, I would advise you to stay away from him.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! C-Cut it out already! You're giving me the creeps!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hm, a puppet master in the shadows, huh? Yeah... I still value my life...</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">He is being held in the special cell. Over there... In that direction...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The special cell...? It certainly seems like he receives special treatment.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, so just who is this "him" anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">...To protect my own life, all I can tell you is that he is the oldest prisoner here. My deepest apologies... But I can't say anymore... He is truly terrifying!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Care to fill me in? It feels like you're leaving Uncle Ray behind here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He is someone I knew in the past... Let's head for the special cell. I believe that black dog should be there as well.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, what's up?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What's so special about the special cell? Is it the super tight security that makes it inescapeable? Or is there a red carpet and a sofa and a bed... And you get the VIP treatment?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Calm down. We'll know when we see it. <thought>If I am not mistaken, "that man" should be in there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Uuugh... Just looking at him gives me the creeps.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So there are things that you're scared of, Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, of course! The police, security guards, sirens, there's lots of things!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Normally, those things give you a sense of security.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eheheh... Well, I'm not a normal girl. That's because...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"I'm the Great Thief." ...right?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! Please don't steal my lines!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm... That felt kind of nice.</line>
<line speaker="Prisoner">Hey, hey, you guys! The stuff he said, is it true?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Prisoner">All that talk about his bracelet being broken! Man, I'd kill for a chance like that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even in prison, this man has not reformed in the slightest.</line>
<line speaker="Prisoner">Dang it...! I just want to go around and pet all the animals in this prison.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Maybe he just loves animals?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Damn! I can't believe the truth about the bracelet is out of the bag...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Seems like, you still haven't realized the error of your ways?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">N... No, sir! I-It's nothing at all. Wh-Why don't you hurry towards the special cell?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let me give you some advice... It would be wise not to take any more unnecessary actions.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Y-Yes, sir. I'll take it to heart. Tsk... As if I need to hear that from you...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would also be wise not to say any more unnecessary words.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Who would have guessed that the bracelet was broken. I thought the security here was supposed to be tight.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">When I saw all those animals roaming around freely, I knew that something was amiss. At the very least, as long as that person is here...!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">The person that the inmate mentioned... Well, let's hurry up and head to the special cell. That black dog might be there... We should proceed with caution.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">How scary. A man-eating dog.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that is indeed the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Eh? Do you think the dog is innocent, Miles?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I still... do not know yet. However, in order to arrive at the truth... ...I won't avert my eyes from any questions that arise, no matter how small they are. The smallest oversight could shut the door to the truth forever.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hmm... You really have changed, Miles.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It might be more accurate to say that I have been changed. ...By that attorney.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm... A cat.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aww! It's so cute, meow~!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Kay. Could you please talk like a normal person?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">If I had this little guy with me, prison life wouldn't be so bad... No, no! I mustn't think like that, meow~.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Right now, all she can understand is cat speak...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, it's pitch black in here... I can't see a thing at all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aren't you always talking about how the Yatagarasu is able to flap even in the darkest night?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Even in the depths of night, when no other bird dares to take flight... ...one alone soars to shine the light of righteousness on the world's blight! And that one is me! For I am the Great Thief, Yatagarasu!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Oh-ho! That was pretty cool!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But still, I can't see what I can't see! I'm still just a human! Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Aahhh!</line>
<line speaker="???">.....Mr. Edgeworth, I presume?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That voice... It can only be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">It has been far too long.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you still remember me?</line>
<line speaker="???">Keh heh, it would be impossible to forget. Because it was you who did what none could do... ...and place me here in this cell.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Um... Don't tell me that the dog is talking to you, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Is there someone else there? I can't see anything though...</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">Down boy. It is rude to frighten the visitors. Here. Allow me to illuminate this dark room. Keh heh heh... Such noisy visitors. From the voices and footsteps... Two more in the back. But it would be rude not to introduce myself. I am called Sirhan Dogen. Mr. Edgeworth and I... We are old acquaintances. Keh heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This man is a former assassin.</thought> The blind assassin... Sirhan Dogen. His weapons are sharp knives and a ferocious dog. His appearance is always accompanied by the sound of a bell. It is said that the ringing of this bell in the darkness is the last sound his victims hear.</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">Would you be so kind as to share the reason why you have come, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That will not be necessary. You are already well aware of why we're here.</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">Keh heh heh. It seems we know each other quite well.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We suspect your dog of committing the murder. The witness who discovered the body saw him biting it.</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">There must be some mistake. My boy is obedient. He would never do such a thing. Right... Anubis? Good boy, good boy, good boy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Anubis may be your guide dog, but you raised him to be a vicious killer. He was one of the weapons you used as an assassin...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dogen">To begin with, is the witness of a reliable sort?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ugh. It's true that Sahwit is also one of the suspects. And it's difficult to say if we can trust his testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dogen">In any case, I think you have the wrong dog. Right, Anubis? Right, boy?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I wonder... If he knows who the witness is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I would like to hear your alibi from 8 AM to 10 AM yesterday morning.</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">During the Animal Show? Keh heh heh... I was in my humble cell the entire time. I took up whittling recently. My focus was solely on the wood and chisel in my hands.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prisoners have free access to chisels here? Normally, that's not allowed.</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">The warden is a kind soul. She has given me special permission.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Kind...? Ridiculous! Even five metal chisels... ...would become deadly weapons in his hands!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dogen">I started out by carving these Buddha statues. But I moved on to other shapes after the 674th.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Really? That many?</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">All it takes is time, which I have plenty of. Here is what I am working on now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I did not know that you played chess...</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">Do you play as well, Mr. Edgeworth? I would like to test your wits in a game sometime. I only started playing since my arrival here, so I am still inexperienced.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm? What is this piece? It's a three-headed... dog?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dogen">Just for the fun of it, I carved this hound piece. Chess is a game of war. Pawns, knights and castles... Each side pushing their forces to the limits to take the life of enemy's king. However, I found the absence of dogs to be strange. Hounds are an indispensable part of warfare. But... It is nothing more than folly. I still play by all the normal rules of chess.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Isn't it difficult for you to find opponents here in prison?</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">I always play correspondence chess.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correspondence chess... So you play chess through the mail.</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">Prisoners are allowed to send and receive letters, although they are subject to inspection. At the moment, I am waiting for my opponent's next move.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So he plays chess with people outside of this prison...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dogen">...Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">As the flower of death blooms, your request... ...has been accepted.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wha-? This doesn't have such a sinister meaning behind it!</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">Since we have a board and all the pieces here, why not indulge me in a game? It is exceedingly difficult to find opponents in this prison.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A very interesting proposition, but I must decline. I don't have the time for that right now. And I doubt you will play by the rules anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">Keh heh heh... You value the rules too much... Perhaps it is an occupational disease. How dreadful. Right, Anubis?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Even his dog feels sorry for me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have quite a few questions to ask you about your dog.</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">In that case, why don't you ask him directly?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very well. .........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wait! There's no way I'll be able to interrogate a dog!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dogen">Keh heh heh. That's what I thought. He won't be able to understand you. Right, Anubis?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...If he truly were unable to communicate with others... ...that would be a pity.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I want you to tell me what you know about this.</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">Keh heh heh. The only requests I accept are for assassinations. Do you want me to kill the person associated with that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No. I am not making such a dangerous request!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you know who was murdered?</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">It was Horace Knightley. A most unfortunate lad.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your ears are as sharp as ever.</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">They are all I can rely on.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>As I thought, he has full knowledge of everything that goes on in this prison.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dogen">On second thought, he might be fortunate after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Fortunate? How so?</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">He committed a grave crime, but he was able to avoid punishment for it. An assassination attempt on the president... What a bold man.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Assassination attempt?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! Mr. Edgeworth! Didn't Mr. Knightley just...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He may have killed his own superior, but he never attempted to take the president's life. <thought>Are they trying to conceal the fact the assassination was staged by the president?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Whoa, whoa, whoa! Hold your horses. Knightley didn't attack the president? But Uncle Ray was requested to defend him in court on charges of attempted assassination.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You didn't know either, Uncle Ray? So, they're trying to pin the whole thing on Mr. Knightley...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now I see why the P.I.C. is taking action.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! So that's why they removed you from the case...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">That DaPest guy was going to indict him on charges of attempted assassination.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And in doing so, they would have twisted the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">Keh heh heh. I suspected it was a false charge.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">?</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">I heard about it from one of the guards. About Knightley... He kept desperately insisting, "I didn't assassinate anyone!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...But the courts are supposed to bring the truth to light.</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">I may not be well-versed in law, but I can say one thing for certain. Some of the prisoners here were convicted on false charges.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ugh...!</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">...That's the reality of it. Right, Anubis? Right, boy? Leaving the truth in the care of the court can be dangerous.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Leaving the truth in the care of the court is dangerous... Huh. There was someone who said the exact same thing before... That investigator from Interpol who doesn't trust prosecutors.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">You're not twisting the truth behind those closed courtroom doors, too, are you? Fueled by those ideas, is it any wonder that courts produce nothing but falsities and lies!? Rest assured, the next time we meet, I won't be so forgiving.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I doubt his distrust has cleared up completely...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dogen">Keh heh heh... You feel the same way, don't you, Anubis? The truth of the courts and Mr. Edgeworth's reasoning both can't be trusted. Right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ugh...!</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">It is nothing to be upset about. You're not the only one who suspects me. Yesterday, the other prosecutor and that judge came here too. They brought the warden along. How they despise me.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh! It must have been those two rude people from before!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Prosecutor Debeste and Judge Courtney...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dogen">They thoroughly inspected my room, but left without finding a thing. Keh heh heh. It seems they were searching for the murder weapon. 'Tis a shame. They searched the other prisoners' cells too. Not just mine. Yet they were still unable to find anything. All that hard work was for naught. Keh heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">He he he. This is quite a problem. What should we do?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Sahwit's testimony alone won't hold up. In order to confront him, we'll need evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dogen">Now, if my guests would be so kind as to leave... Right, Anubis? Show them the way out.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ah, does this mean... What I think it means?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">L-L-L-Let's get going, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......We shall meet again, Dogen.</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">It would be a shame for our long-awaited reunion to end so soon. I'll be waiting. Keh heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Now then, we still need to find that murder weapon.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgewooorth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She went all the way up there?</thought> It's fine now, Kay. Come down from there. Where is Mr. Shields?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Beats me... He just took off running like death was after him.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Good grief. That man...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">What should we do now, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We'll continue investigating. <thought>First, we should... ...start by solving that one mystery. Knightley's body was found in a workroom inside the prison. However... ...he was supposed to be in the detention center's holding cell... How did he get to the prison under such tight security?</thought> Let's go investigate the holding cell at the detention center.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That was where Mr. Knightley was held, right!? But what about Uncle Ray?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Let's just leave him be for now.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I thought we were supposed to be his assistants though...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The victim's cell in the detention center was this way.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Let's check it out! Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, this is truly just dreadful!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm? What happened? That's the warden, Ms. Roland. She must have come from behind that "No entry" sign.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guard">So, he still won't talk? Even after all the trouble you went through to get the evidence transferred from the precinct...</line>
<line speaker="Roland">That's right. I don't know how many times I've tried. I can't report back empty handed...</line>
<line speaker="Guard">That assassin sure is one tough cookie, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Did he just say "assassin"...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Roland">Oh my.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Pardon me, but... Were you talking about Sirhan Dogen just now?</line>
<line speaker="Roland">Oh, eavesdropping, were you? You naughty boy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Did you question him personally, Warden Roland?</line>
<line speaker="Roland">Not just him. I try to have a heart-to-heart with all the prisoners and suspects. In my home, we're all family here! It's only fair I invite them to my Warden's Office!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Warden's Office?</line>
<line speaker="Roland">Oh, have you taken an interest in my room as well? It's just down this hallway. But outsiders are not allowed past this point.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Down the hallway... So around there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Roland">Hu hu hu. It's such a lovely room. People do enjoy being invited back here. I always show them the splendid view of my precious courtyard!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The courtyard of this animal-filled prison! I'd sure love to see it!</line>
<line speaker="Roland">I'm delighted that you want to see it... However, I cannot invite you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What?</line>
<line speaker="Roland">You're not a child of our home. If you want to come to my room, you'll have to be convicted first.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's a rather high hurdle to clear...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Roland">Goodness me! Look at how long we've been talking! I was just about to feed Ally her lunch!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ally...?</line>
<line speaker="Roland">She is my favorite little angel! Now, if you'll excuse me, I must be off to the courtyard! Toodle-loo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I never got a chance to ask her about Dogen...</thought> ...Well, let's head over to Knightley's cell.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This is the victim's cell...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">When did Mr. Knightley arrive in here again?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was after the president's welcoming ceremony, on the night of March 25th. <thought>So, when and how did he move over to the prison? There might be some evidence left that can answer that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Alright! Let's get cracking, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The floor here is clean. It was probably wiped down with something.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Did someone spill grape juice here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't know exactly what was wiped away, but I can imagine what was used to wipe it... It's very likely it was this torn up newspaper.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Couldn't he have asked one of the guards if he could borrow a cleaning rag?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps it was something he didn't want the guards to see.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, what's up?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">There are so many things in this cell.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Although they don't all appear to be Knightley's personal belongings. There's also a collection of books that belong to this cell.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow! This might not be such a bad place to live in after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...If you want to spend the night here, I won't stop you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Thanks, but no thanks! But... Since we're here, we might as well learn everything we can. Alright! Let's begin our investigation of the holding cell!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Chess seems to be popular here. Knightley even brought in a chess set.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No. From what I've seen, the only people who have an interest in chess... ...are Knightley and that man.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That man? Ah! You mean that scary guy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. <thought>Those two had a shared interest in chess... Is that... just a coincidence?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">I've been thinking about it. Since we still haven't found the murder weapon... ...maybe, there wasn't one to begin with!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh. That's an interesting way of thinking. Then, how was the victim murdered?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What are you talking about, Mr. Edgeworth! If there is no murder weapon, then no one actually died.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Kay. I understand how you're feeling, but we must not avert our eyes from the reality before us.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You're right... Mr. Knightley, he really is... Mr. Edgeworth! We've gonna catch the guy who did this!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Good work.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's fine, you don't have to keep an eye on us, 'kay? As you can see, we are the Great Thieves of Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is no "we" here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm! The reflection in the mirror...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! It's a security camera! A Great Thief's archenemy! I guess they don't take too kindly to thieves here...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's no reason for a detention center to be kind to thieves. Guard! I would like you to check the footage of this security camera. If you find any problems, report to me at once.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Understood, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The security camera is clearly visible in the mirror's reflection.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmm... I don't like it. It's like a constant reminder, "You're being watched!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I understand your feelings. However...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I definitely don't want to live in a place like this. Every morning, I'd reminded again while I'm at the sink... ...that I need to look good for the camera...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Don't get too worked up about it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! Is this a dining menu?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You can choose your daily meals in this detention center. However, unless you have the money, you won't be able to choose what you want to eat.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">In the end, the world revolves around money...! Doesn't this mean that the rich won't have to reflect on their crimes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... Well, those who come here haven't been declared guilty yet. There are a few good people who don't need to reflect... Probably.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It sounds like you're just making excuses for them, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Urk...! <thought>Why should I have to come up with excuses for the detention center!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">There are a lot of books here. What's this? "The Wonderful Warden of Ours". "The Hound Whistler", "The Animalshack Redemption". ...Mr. Knightley, he was surprisingly good person...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...No. The detention center provides these books for the visitor's own edification. These books are supposed to help you grow as a human being... Hmm. "Prison Life for Dummies". These books were written by model prisoners and former inmates.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! Here's a helpful book! "The Great Escape in 80 Days: Based on a True Story"! Oh! Check this one out! "Crime and Establishment: How to Make Money in Prison"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...The problems with this detention center may run deeper than I thought.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! There's something on the desk!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems to be some kind of memo... Let me take a closer look.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is... chess notation. It was probably the victim's.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What's chess notation?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a memo that records the positions of the pieces on a chessboard. This is a good match. My next move would be pawn to... No... Actually, before that...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! This is no time to be playing chess!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ahh. You're right. <thought>...Hm? The positions of the chess pieces recorded in this memo... I feel like I've seen something similar somewhere else. I should take a closer look at the evidence I've collected.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this spot somehow connected to any of the evidence I hold...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence contradicts the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Really? I don't see any contradictions.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay. As my assistant, you still lack training.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Same to you, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Urk! <thought>She called my bluff!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This chess notation... I've seen it before.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You're still thinking about chess! Focus on the investigation! Focus!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Chess is quite important to this investigation... Kay. Have a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Are these the chess pieces from Dogen's cell? I don't know much about the rules of chess...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The rules of chess are not important here. Look at the positions of the chess pieces in this memo and the pieces in Dogen's cell... Do you notice anything?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...AH! I don't know anything about the different chess pieces... ...but if you flip the board around, the positions of the chess pieces are completely the same!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... Although the memo doesn't include the Cerberus chess piece... ...the positions of the other chess pieces are identical.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wh-What's going on here?</line>
<line speaker="Dogen">I always play correspondence chess.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This might be hard to believe... but Dogen's chess opponent was...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! Are you saying he was playing against Mr. Knightley?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">With this, we now have the evidence to link Dogen with the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's not as dirty as I thought it would be. And the toilet paper shows no signs of use. Looks like there are no problems with the toilet.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ehh! There's a huge problem!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's the problem?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's totally awkward having the toilet out in the open like that. They need to think more about the end user!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This facility wasn't designed with the spirit of service in mind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">? <thought>...Something seems off?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">The floor here is clean. <thought>Floor wiped clean - There doesn't seem to be anything in this cell to wipe the floor with?</thought> Was it mopped recently?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems strange that only the area in front of the bed has been wiped clean...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This looks like an uncomfortable bed to sleep in. But the pillow covers are clean. Not a speck of dust on them.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Is this what the bed at Gummy's place looks like as well?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No... If my hunch is correct, he has an old, beat-up mattress lying around in his room.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's Horace Knightley's suit.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">According to the results of my investigation...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? What did you find out?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">A man who looks good in a suit leaves a more favorable impression with the ladies!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! Next time, I'll investigate men who look good in frills!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please don't bother...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hm? This newspaper. It's missing a few pages.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They appear to be torn out <thought>Torn up newspaper - Dated the day before the murder. Several pages have been torn out.</thought>. Why would someone tear out the pages from a newspaper?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Maybe they used it to clean the cell instead of a rag?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Clean the cell...? It's quite possible...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Windows with iron bars. There are no signs of tampering. It doesn't look like the criminal could have escaped through here.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hm hm. What if these iron bars are removable! Let me inspect them, for future reference.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay... Now's not the time for that, we're in the middle of an investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, this is what our investigation turned up. It seems we've found a major connection between the victim and Dogen.</line>
<line speaker="???">Th-This is terrible!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm? What happened?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guard">Th-The security camera recorded something terrible!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!? Can you let me see it?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Of course, sir! I have a portable playback device right here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then let me see it right away! <thought>This is...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Th-This black thing has got to be that doggy, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Up until this point, I thought the murder took place inside the prison. But it appears I was mistaken. The place where Knightley was attacked was...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes! Knightley was attacked here!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Really? He was attacked there? But the video showed that...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. I suppose it wasn't there...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was the detention center. And furthermore, he was attacked by Dogen's dog. <thought>This is the decisive evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If Knightley was killed in this room... ...then this piece of evidence we found in the cell takes on a new meaning! Which piece of evidence takes on a new meaning if the murder occurred in the holding cell?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Yes, the meaning of this evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth? Why have you gone quiet all of a sudden?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Umm... It's nothing. <thought>I'm overthinking this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>For some reason, someone wiped the floor clean. It's possible they were wiping away bloodstains.</thought> Thank you for your hard work. While I have your attention, may I ask for one more favor?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">What would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There should be a detective by the name of Dick Gumshoe in the detention center or the prison. I would like you to give him a message. Tell him to check this room for traces of blood and give the results to me.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Y-Yes, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">This should corner that old coot!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No... Not yet. We still don't know how Knightley and the dog moved from here to the prison.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's true. But once we figure that out...! Where should we check out next, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The guards here might know something about the murder... Let's see if we can learn any new details from them.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Alright! Let's continue our... Aah!</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh. Sorry to intrude... ...Well, if isn't Mr. Prosecutor and the little lady. Fancy meeting you here...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This man is Shi-Long Lang, an Interpol Agent. About two weeks ago, he was in charge of investigating one of my cases. I would have thought he'd returned to his native country of Zheng Fa by now.</thought> Agent Lang. What brings you here?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Just some boring work. Nothing you need to know about.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ha ha! On top of a black dog, we meet a black wolf! Huh? You came alone today, Agent Lang?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Usually, he'd have a huge police force with him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Mr. Prosecutor, seems you've been busy these past few days.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>These past few days... Is he referring to the incident with the Zheng Fa president?</thought> I would have thought you'd be involved in his security too.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah. Our president doesn't even trust his own country's police force. Look at the results of hiring a private security company. It's laughable.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Agent Lang doesn't trust prosecutors or the courts. That's why... ...he brings along a large force of capable policemen to thoroughly investigate the crime scene.</thought> Yes. If you and your subordinates had been there, the results might have been different.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">...My subordinates, huh... They're... no longer with me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They're not with you?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Funny, looks like I'm a real lone wolf now. Hahahaha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang. Just what happened exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Didn't I tell you? It's nothing you need to know about. Well, be seeing ya, Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Lang... I wonder what happened...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Yes, it troubles me too, but there's nothing we can do about it for now...</thought> Kay, let us continue with our own investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Got it. First, let's ask those guards a few questions!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, what's up?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I've found it! The "weak point" of this facility!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh...? Please, enlighten me.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">There are lots of people here, so it feels like you're constantly being watched. However, there are still many blind spots we can use to hide and avoid detection. All we have to do is aim for these blind spots... We can do it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I won't even ask what it is exactly that you plan to do. <thought>More importantly, I feel like there are still a few blind spots to this case. I'll need to gather more information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Lang looked kind of lonely, without all of his subordinates.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed... It appears that the Republic of Zheng Fa has its own issues to deal with. But, he has decided to follow the path that he has chosen. And... the same goes for us.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You're right... First, we must solve this case! After it's all over, we can go cheer Wolfy up!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... Well, I'll think about it. <thought>...I don't even know where he's staying at.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">That was some amazing footage.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The instant of the murder... This could be a powerful clue.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But, we can't see the victim's face.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Indeed. <thought>Yes... That is a problem. At this rate, we can't call this a decisive piece of evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! I see! If you cover your face, The security cameras can't catch you! If I covered my face, I could sneak into any place I wanted!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Besides your face, shouldn't you also do something about your attire?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">No can do. After all, wearing this outfit is the policy of the Yatagarasu!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Then, what is the point of covering your face?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's a security gate with a metal detector...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Don't you feel nervous whenever you pass through one of these? It's like how you get nervous when you see a policeman, but you've done nothing wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps you get nervous around the police because you're the self-proclaimed "Great Thief"...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This door leads to the surveillance room.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Surveillance... Does this mean... we're being watched? You'll have to tone down your shenanigans, Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What... are you trying to accuse me of!</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Hmm, this is a difficult case...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's wrong? Is something troubling you?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">S-Sir...! One of my uniforms has gone missing! But I'm certain that I placed it in this locker.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Maybe the uniform grew legs and walked off somewhere...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...What kind of logic is that?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">In any case, I wish you the best in your search. I'll be rooting for you!</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Yes! Thank you for your support!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">These are the guards' lockers.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I bet they keep their uniforms and snacks inside.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why snacks?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">If it were me, I'd definitely put snacks in there!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't know where you get that air of confidence...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You there, have you seen a black dog around here?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">O-Of course not. If I had actually seen it... I wouldn't be standing around here so carefree!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Umm, did something happen with that doggy?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, let's not press this matter any further. <thought>Hm... So Dogen's dog didn't come by the detention center.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A bunch of trophies are lined up here.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'd like to hand out one of these trophies sometime!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What kind of person would receive a trophy from a Great Thief...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Obviously the Rope Escape Champion! Ah! But if they actually held a contest, I'd be the champion.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Where would you hold such a contest...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This leads to the office.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">There's a sing that says "No entry". It's human nature to want to sneak in whenever you see a no entry sign!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And it is human reason that suppresses those urges.</line>
<line speaker="???">Ooh! There you are!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Shields. Where did you go?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Where indeed! I've been searching for you guys this whole time! Walking all around the prison is hard work, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...That's strange, seeing as you came from the opposite direction.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">.......... I've got some new information. You wanna hear it? Do you!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He sure changed the subject quickly.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">I heard a little something from the guards. It seems Knightley caused a bit of an incident two days ago.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">An incident?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">You know how Simon said he came to visit Knightley, right? After the visit, when Knightley returned to his cell... Naturally, a guard escorted Knightley back to his cell. While the guard was unlocking his handcuffs... All of a sudden, Knightley struck the guard and knocked him out. It seems he was going to attempt a jailbreak. By the time the other guards arrived, the key to his cell had disappeared.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But, there's been no reports of Knightley's jailbreak attempt two days ago...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Exactly. It's strange, isn't it. Right up until his death, he was still in his cell. What's more, Knightley claimed he never stole the key in the first place. In fact, they searched his cell, and the key was nowhere to be found...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Did the guard who was struck have anything to say?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">No one knows. He was taken to the hospital while he was still unconscious. He's still there now, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So, in the end, we still don't know what happened...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">It's youuuuu!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm. That voice...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">What are you still doing hanging around here!?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Err, well, you see. This is my assistant...</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Are you here to object our investigation and make me into a laughing stock!?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Sebastian. I believe "obstruct" is the word you're looking for.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>In a way, I think his expression was apt.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">A pleasure meeting you again, Judge Courtney. I am...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">I know. You are Simon Keyes' defense attorney, are you not?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Well then, let's skip the formalities, and celebrate our happy reunion with a hug... O-Or maybe not!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Incidentally... I heard you mention an assistant a moment ago.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah! We're assistants at the Edgeworth Law Offices!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Prosecutors are civil servants, to open a side business is to betray the Goddess of Law.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As long as profit is not our objective, there shouldn't be a problem, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Y-Yeah, that's it! Miles here is a volunteer worker! The purpose of my office isn't to make money... We're pro bono.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">What a wonderful heart you have. Defending others without demanding payment.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ah... Aha ha ha... I-I do have an amazing charitable heart.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">More importantly, I'd like you to explain your reasons for arresting Simon Keyes.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">There's no need to...</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Is that a challenge against me!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, I was speaking with Judge Courtney...</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">I guess it can't be helped. If you want to take on The Best, you will fall like the rest!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I haven't said anything yet. ...But this is convenient.</thought> Then I will hear you out. What were your reasons for arresting Mr. Keyes?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">I see no need to inform you. Sebastian, let us...</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Heh heh heh... Just watch, Justine. Watch as I run around in circles against this useless prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think you mean, "run circles around me"...</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Yeah! That's what I meant! Prepare yourself, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">So, you want to know my reasons for arresting that man?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...... <thought>How am I supposed to go about pressing that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">How's that? Got nothing to say! Speechless in my presence?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>*sigh*... This guy sure talks a lot.</thought> ...So, you're the one who arrested Mr. Keyes, I take it... Mr. Debeste. Do you have the right to do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Well, obviously it was the police who carried out the arrest. But, since it was under my direction, shouldn't it also count as my arrest?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>As I expected... It'd be difficult to deal with both of them at the same time. However... Her silence is troubling me. Just what is she thinking?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">So, you want to know my reasons for arresting that man?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's get one thing clear... You do know who you arrested, right?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">What? Do you take me for a fool? The one I arrested was... Simon Keyes! No doubt about it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I expected he'd at least understand that much...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"So, you want to know my reasons for arresting that man?" to "Obviously, we had a fatal reason for arresting Simon!"</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Obviously, we had a fatal reason for arresting Simon!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Really, that's quite a surprise. ...So, what is this fatal reason for the arrest?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Are you attempting to lure information out of me through flattery? ...A good strategy, but I'm afraid... it won't work on me!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">We have found vital evidence implicating Simon Keyes. That's what Sebastian was trying to say.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Yes! So because of this fatal vital evidence, I had Simon arrested!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">The answer is simple. Yes. We found "traces" of that guy over there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That guy... over there...? That's certainly vague...</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Well, don't they say... The Best hears one thing and understands ten?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're just being lazy... Explain it more clearly!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...Sebastian. If it's alright with you, would you please explain it to them in more detail? I'm sure that everyone wants to hear what you have to say.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">...Hm. Alright. If you insist, Justine. We discovered "that"... Perhaps you didn't know, but the victim carried a chessboard with him. From it, we found that suspect guy's... I mean, Simon Keye's fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Well done, Sebastian! I bless you on behalf of the Goddess of Law. Please amend your testimony. Are you alright with that, Prosecutor Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Y-Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"The answer is simple. Yes. We found "traces" of that guy over there." to "The victim carried a chessboard. From it, we found Simon Keyes' fingerprints."</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">The victim carried a chessboard. From it, we found Simon Keyes' fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Surely, it wasn't you who discovered the fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Hey, I'm just a prosecutor, aren't I? I leave that stuff to the forensics team.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>These fingerprints could be a problem, but wasn't the chessboard originally... Maybe I should take another look at the evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Precisely. You seem to be well-versed on this matter.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He he he! Well, I happen to know a thing or two about prisons, y'know!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What does she mean by that? I'll have to find out the details later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">In any case, I peeked into the room from the window.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">How's that? Perfectly simple, perfectly decisive... Right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's perfectly simple and decisive is how flimsy your testimony is.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">What are you saying? You just can't keep up with my train of thought!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">It may be presumptuous of me, but allow me to explain. The fingerprints found at the scene belonged to the guards and the prisoners. And the only ones that "should not have existed" belonged to Simon Keyes.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Yes! Exaaaaactly! Do you get it now, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The real question is, do YOU get it...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"How's that? Perfectly simple, perfectly decisive... Right?" to "The other prints belonged to the victim and the guards. Yes, only Simon's prints are unnatural!"</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">The other prints belonged to the victim and the guards. Yes, only Simon's prints are unnatural!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If there are other people's fingerprints then there should be more suspects!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Wah hah hah... I'm afraid that's not possible.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...And why is that?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Certainly, if not for Simon Keyes' prints, there would have been more suspects. However, his fingerprints "should not have existed".</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Th-That's right! After all, Simon... is...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Is neither a prisoner nor a guard. So naturally, he wouldn't have been allowed into the prison. And yet he left his fingerprints. I think that's enough reason for an arrest... Wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Yes! Well done, Justine!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">You're welcome.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Of course, I was the first to notice it because I'm the Best.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">First one to notice? Do you have any proof?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">I noticed it the very instant I saw the crime scene! Faster than the speed of light! That's the best kind of proof!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... And what does that prove?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Wah hah hah! You still don't understand. But, don't feel too bad. You're simply not "The Best", unlike me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I don't think I want to understand...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"Of course, I was the first to notice it because I'm the Best." to "My reasoning is faster than light. It'd take you a light year to get it. In short, I am the Best!"</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">My reasoning is faster than light. It'd take you a light year to get it. In short, I am the Best!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You do realize that a light year is not a measure of time?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Oh...? ......Uhh...?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Sebastian, a light year is a unit of distance.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">......Oh, right.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What! This isn't the time for this...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........ <thought>What is he saying...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's really vague and hard to understand...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">First, I'll have to teach him how to speak a language people can understand.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Teach it to him, Professor Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Fingerprints found on the chessboard... Is that the ace up your sleeve?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Ace in my sleeve? ...Oh! Ace up my sleeve...!? Yes! The methods I use are always "The Best". This ace is my trump card!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well then, allow me to show you that it is not, in fact, a trump card at all. Simon Keyes was the one who sent this chessboard to the victim in the first place... So, it's only natural some of his prints would be left on it.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">.......... Aaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...That took way too long.</thought> These fingerprints are hardly decisive evidence. Perhaps your arrest was a little too rash?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Rash......</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To begin with, this incident occurred in the detention center and the prison. To suspect Simon just because he isn't a prisoner or a guard is a little unreasonable...</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Aaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What? <thought>What's with him all of a sudden...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Wah hah hah hah. I finally get what you're trying to say. Rash... You mean we were too quick to arrest the guy, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He was stuck on that!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Sure, I was the first to lay eyes on him. And I was the first to notice the evidence. That was even faster. But, I am not rash! Sure, Simon Keyes isn't a guard or a prisoner. But...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...Sebastian.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Judge Courtney...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Wh-What are you doing Justine! Don't butt in like that.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Pardon me, Sebastian. Yes, your words on the suspect are very interesting. However... Shouldn't you get to the "Best" part first?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">The "Best" part...!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Why don't you tell them? About your wonderful reasoning regarding the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">.....Good one, Justine. Nice suggestion. Mr. Edgeworth, listen to my first-rate reasoning!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Will this reasoning explain why you arrested Mr. Keyes?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">I'm sure it will meet your expectations.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Judge Courtney just changed the flow of the conversation... Just what is she planning?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">It's obvious the murder weapon was a sharp metal object!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>At least it's clearer than his last testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">It's Debeste reasoning you can get from Prosecutor The Best. How do you like that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Now he's mixing up "the best" with his own name...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">But, could someone really hide a weapon inside a gift sent to a prisoner?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">He he. You'll find a good place if you examine the inside of the chessboard.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Inside the chessboard? Is there some place to hide a weapon...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As I thought, there are only chess pieces inside.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">He he he...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow. What an annoying laugh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Inside the chessboard, huh. Perhaps I should examine it a bit further.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is...! <thought>The top panel is removable.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's quite deep.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. There's more than enough room to hide a small knife.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Understand now? This is how the culprit smuggled in the...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's see, the top panel can be removed, like so...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">This hidden compartment is quite deep! I could hide my secret savings in there!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you even have any savings to hide?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Let's not talk about that...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph......</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Hmph! What's with the "hmph"! I wasn't even finished!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Mr. Debeste, there is something you have forgotten. There's a gate at the entrance of the detention center!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">...Eh? Well, there is, but...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">He means the security gates with the metal detectors, Sebastian. We had to pass through the same check when we entered the prison, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Ah... Aaaah! Yeah! That's it! I remember now!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It looks like he completely forgot.</thought> It would be impossible to smuggle a sharp metal object into the detention center. Therefore, your reasoning never held, even from the very beginning!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">That gate is only used on people. In other words, packages sent to the detention center undergo a simpler check.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...So they don't use a metal detector for that?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">This never should have happened... It seems the guards were too careless.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Right, Justine. Thanks for the assist.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">You're welcome. Now then, Prosecutor Edgeworth, your cross-examination, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Cross-examination. It's as if we were in the courtroom. ...Very well, his reasoning... Let's see how long it will hold up under pressure!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">It's obvious the murder weapon was a sharp metal object!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A sharp metal object... Do you have proof of that?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Didn't you see the victim's wound, worthless prosecutor? The fatal blow was a stab to the throat! And a knife perfectly matches up with that! There can be no other explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm... It seems they don't know about that piece of "information" yet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Wah hah hah... Nothing to say? Speechless, aren't you, Mr. Edgeworth! Right, next! There is plenty more to my reasoning!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">However, the prison maintains strict control over potentially lethal items.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even with the strict control, there were still some items that could be used, right?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">W-Well, yeah... Things like grooming scissors...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Of course, there's more to this. Right, Sebastian?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">E-Exactly! At the time of the incident, only one was being borrowed! However, there was no reaction when we tested it for blood!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Those would be the scissors Mr. Sahwit was practicing with.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">So, the inside of the prison was completely clear of sharp implements!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">So... That's why I've reasoned that the murder weapon was brought in from the outside.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Can you be more specific about where it came from?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Of course I can! It didn't come from inside the prison!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is he trying to sound smart?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Simon Keyes brought it in. That's what we mean.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Mr. Edgeworth... Can't you even figure that much out? I'm disappointed in you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>And you've disappointed me from the start.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">So Simon brought the murder weapon. But how, you ask?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Yes. It was hidden inside that chess board.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No weapon was found at the crime scene. Not even inside the chessboard. So where did the murder weapon disappear to... I'd like to hear your answer to that.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Th-That's... Well, after the crime, the culprit must have hidden it somewhere in the prison.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is there a problem with the statement Debeste just made?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>No... There doesn't appear to be a problem.</thought> Mr. Debeste. Could you continue your testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Oh! Err... What was I saying again? Oh, yeah. The murder weapon was hidden inside the chessboard.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">And since only the victim and the suspect's fingerprints were found on the chessboard...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Was it really just their fingerprints you found?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Hmph. My pops always says... "You may be foolish in youth, but you must not be stupid."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">I'm not stupid!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wh-What... Was that... uh...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Courtney">He means he's not stupid enough to tell a lie.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">......Oh? I-I-I, I knew that! I'm not stupid enough to lie! So the fingerprints are the honest truth!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Isn't it obvious who brought and used the murder weapon?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, can you tell us exactly "who" this person was?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Wah hah hah... The culprit..... is YOU!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Err, Simon isn't here...</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">.........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Such a pitiful man. We'd best go gently on him.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I see. I just wanted to tease him!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">......... D-Don't make fun of meeeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That last testimony sure seemed like faulty reasoning.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Judge Courtney helped him out... No, the argument was entirely her own reasoning.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">In that case, this'll be tough. Got anything up your sleeve, Miles?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course. They don't know all the facts. This reasoning doesn't appear to have any weak points at first glance, but...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">But on closer inspection, there is a hole, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I should press them to draw out more information, then find the hole in their logic. I'll strike first and take hold of any clues I find...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The murder weapon is hidden inside the prison? ...I don't think so. It's clear from this piece of evidence. <thought>What shows that the murder weapon can't be inside the prison?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Whaaaaat! That's your proof!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. This makes it clear.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Sebastian. That doesn't prove a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Oh... Ooooh! I knew it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gah! <thought>That wasn't right after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Well then, if you have proof, then hurry up and show us!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I must have evidence that shows the murder weapon is not inside the prison.</thought> Mr. Debeste. This evidence proves it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Have you completely forgotten your own actions? You, along with Warden Roland, conducted a search of the prison. But, you did not find the murder weapon, right?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Th-That's..... We must have overlooked something!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">This guy just completely contradicted himself!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You carried out such a sloppy investigation? I'm amazed that you call yourself "The Best".</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Are you mocking me...!?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...Sebastian.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Please calm yourself. Don't get caught up in the opponent's pace.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">.....I'm fine, Justine. Did you really think Debeste prosecutor would be shaken by someone Miles behind him?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I wish he'd stop messing around with other people's names...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, in that case, Kay Faraday is far, Farahead!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, don't you get caught up in this too!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Yes. If my best investigation didn't find anything... ...then there must not have been a single weapon in the prison! In that case, there's only one possibility! The criminal must have taken the murder weapon with him when he left the prison! So it's only natural we didn't find it in there. Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There was no way that the culprit could have brought the weapon out of the prison! And this piece of evidence shows why!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">D... Does that show why the weapon couldn't have been brought out of the prison!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. This is definitive proof that the weapon was not brought inside!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">When you say it like that, it has to be true!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Prosecutor Edgeworth. Your evidence does not have that kind of meaning.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh! <thought>Bluffing is no use here... The reason the weapon could not have been brought out of the prison... If you consider where you must pass through to exit the prison, the answer should be clear.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Have you completely forgotten your own testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Y-You! That's twice you've insulted me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? It seems you remember what I said earlier. But you'd do well to remember further than that.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">...! What is that!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Th-This guy, he really doesn't remember anything?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems that way... The detention center and the prison are equipped with security gates. Anyone leaving must pass through these gates. Gates... equipped with metal detectors.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Aaaah! That's what you...!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Looks like he remembers now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. There's no way someone could have brought the murder weapon through those gates. And so the criminal could not have taken it out of the prison either!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Aaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">So then, Prosecutor Edgeworth... Do you know where this murder weapon went to?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps the weapon is still inside the prison?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">But, we couldn't find it anywhere in the prison!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The reason you didn't find it... ...is because you believed it to be a sharp metal object.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">We saw the very moment when Mr. Knightley was attacked, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">If you can say that much, then perhaps you could enlighten us. What would you say is the murder weapon in this case?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">From this piece of evidence, the murder weapon of this case becomes obvious.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">What's that? Does this point out the murder weapon in this case!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Being "The Best", shouldn't you understand what this evidence means?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">O-Oh! O... Obviously!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Sebastian, don't be deceived.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gah! <thought>I knew she'd see through it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Courtney">As I thought, you don't have proof after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No. I do have evidence that shows the murder weapon for this case!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">We saw the very moment when Mr. Knightley was attacked, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Here is footage from a security camera. It shows one of the cells in the detention center... See it with your own eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">What! Th-This is! It can't be!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This tape clearly shows the moment the victim was attacked by a black dog. I believe this is sufficient proof, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...Indeed, this is vital evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Horace Knightley was killed in the detention center, by that dog! After that, the body was moved to the prison workroom. Our witness claims to have seen a dog in the workroom when the body was found. Of course, a dog couldn't have planned this crime on its own. However, there is someone who could have...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...That's enough. Prosecutor Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Judge Courtney...?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">It's true this camera footage is vital evidence. However, there is something else you must prove. Actually, you've already noticed it, haven't you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...It's just as she says. There is still a huge flaw in my reasoning.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Courtney">If that black dog is a prisoner's pet... ...how was it able to move between the detention center and prison?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">......Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What will we do, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I still don't know how the dog managed to move from one place to the other...</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">I knew it...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What! You're one to talk! You don't know either!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">If you do not solve this mystery, I'm afraid I cannot accept your logic. If this was a real courtroom, I would call for a recess now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wha-! Wait! I'm not finished yet!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Court has been adjourned. Leave at once.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This isn't a courtroom!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Well then, as I said, court is adjourned...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can't prove my argument, but isn't it the same case with Mr. Keyes?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Whatever do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just as I don't know how the dog entered the detention center... ...you also don't know how Simon Keyes entered the detention center and prison. Although he came to visit the victim, he was an outsider to the prison. Don't you think it would be difficult for him to commit a crime inside the prison?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Judge Courtney. Now the burden of proof lies with you. Show us evidence that Simon Keyes entered the prison!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">........Ha ha. You want me to present evidence? I'm happy to oblige.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What?! <thought>Does she really have evidence?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Courtney">It's about time I told you. Now that I know the basis of your reasoning, Prosecutor Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What is she thinking?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Courtney">It seems you don't even know Simon Keyes' real occupation... He is a circus performer.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A c-circus performer?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Yes. Have you ever heard of the Berry Big Circus?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Circus... Aaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Roland">But of course! Yesterday was a day that I wouldn't have missed for the world!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Wouldn't have missed for the world"? Did you have some kind of important meeting...?</line>
<line speaker="Roland">Oh heavens, no! I despise meetings! It was the Animal Show, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">It seems you've realized. On the day of the incident, an Animal Show was being performed at the prison. And the show was put on by the Berry Big Circus.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">S-So then! Do you mean, Simon is...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Simon Keyes entered the prison as a staff member of the Animal Show. That, we know for a fact.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-Nuguoooooh! <thought>Th-This woman! She's been concealing this fact the whole time! She only planned to reveal it after hearing my reasoning! Come to think of it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Wh-What are you doing Justine! Don't butt in like that.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Pardon me, Sebastian. Yes, your words on the suspect are very interesting. However... Shouldn't you get to the "Best" part first?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Mr. Debeste was going to say it then, but she stopped him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Wah hah hah hah! How do you like that, worthless prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You didn't do anything!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Well then, now it really is time for a recess. I'll end with some advice. I had already doubted your abilities as a prosecutor... ...which is why I relieved you of your authority. You'd best not forget that...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...What are you trying to say?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">The P.I.C. can still take away your badge. If you value your badge, I'd advise you not to show your face before me again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Is that a threat?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">The Goddess of Law is merciful, but that doesn't mean you can get away with everything. And one more thing... I must digress. I suggest you stop with this defense attorney act.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That's none of your concern. I don't intend to abandon a case I am involved in so easily.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">For defense attorneys, a relationship of mutual trust with their client is vital. It is very different from the way of the prosecutor... In any case... you didn't even know about your client's occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Well then, I must be going. May the blessings of the Goddess of Law be upon you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Did Simon... lie to us...?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">It seems he lied to Uncle Ray too. This complicates matters. Why'd he do that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hey, hey, Miles. Don't tell me you've got cold feet already? Courtney-pie is quite a handful, but giving up is still uncool. A defense attorney's creed is to never give up. Remember, you're my assistant.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Of course, I don't plan on giving up either. It's just... My theory that he couldn't enter the prison no longer holds. It looks like we'll have to investigate once more.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, the pieces don't fit together quite right... I need to reconsider the information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't see a clear connection between these two pieces of information. I need to think this over one more time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Not exactly a shining example of the perfect line of logic.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Elbird. I'd like you to take a look at this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It looks like Mr. Elbird's busy chasing a fly! He's not listening at all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... <thought>He doesn't feel like listening...</thought> In that case, I'll make him pay attention with a straight punch!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, let's settle this!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Elbird. Your testimony contradicts this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">Your fists are pathetic! You think you can break my guard with that jab!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nggh! That was supposed to be a hard straight punch...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Looks like he dodged it cleanly!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I won't miss next time!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Let's go for the T.K.O.!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Sahwit. I would like for you to have a look at this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Is there a problem with this evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Doesn't it show that there is a contradiction in your testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I do not particularly think so...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Argh! <thought>Looks like I was wrong...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">What's the matter? That wasn't like you at all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... I was merely probing for answers.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">C'mon, you can drop the "cool guy" act!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's not an act!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Sahwit. Your testimony contradicts this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">A contradiction... you say? I am not sure I understand what you mean... Are you not merely making a blind guess?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Urgh!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">He saw right through your bluff, didn't he? But you can't give up after a couple of failures, Miles!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... I know. <thought>And now he's trying to console me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Debeste. What do you think about this piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Why are you asking for my opinion?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't you see? This evidence contradicts your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">WH-WHAAAAAAAAAT!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">I don't believe this evidence has that kind of meaning.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Eh! Is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... <thought>With Judge Courtney here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Also, you don't need to yell ><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Debeste. There is a contradiction in your statement!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Eh! Is that true, Justine?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">It is not, Sebastian. It is Prosecutor Edgeworth's statement that is contradictory.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Of course! There's no way there could be a contradiction in my argument!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh! <thought>Isn't it full of contradictions!? My real problem is her rather than Mr. Debeste...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh! To come this far, only to lose the truth...! But... it seems there's nothing I can do now...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Elbird">...You're holding up my exercise! Get outta the ring!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sh-Shoot... I messed up!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can't give up now. I have to stand my ground... Now... Let's try this again!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I must excuse myself now. I have other appointments.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sh-shoot... I messed up!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can't give up now. I have to stand my ground... Now... Let's try this again!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's nothing unusual about this area.</line>
</xml>