<xml>
<title>The Resolve of Ryunosuke Naruhodo</title>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So...the time's finally come. Today...we unravel everything!</thought> I'll be counting on your support more than ever today, Miss Susato!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um... Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah! Oh no! W-What's the matter, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...nothing? I was just saying that I'll be relying on your support today, but...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm so sorry! Of course! I, I know I can be rather incompetent at times, but... ...I shan't let you down!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Would you mind helping me to my feet, then?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear! I'm really very sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Susato-san isn't her usual self at all. But that's hardly surprising, I suppose. She's just found out that her father is the partner of a world-famous detective. Not to mention...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah! G-Good morning, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! Lord van Zieks!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Thank you for all your efforts yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha... <thought>Did I hear that correctly?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Um, no, nothing. Just...I hope we can clear things up today. <thought>I really can't make this man out. His face says 'I hate you' but his words are...almost jovial today. In fact, he hasn't been very Reaper-like at all since this all began yesterday.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Lord van Zieks isn't the Reaper, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Good point.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The Reaper? I suppose in hindsight... ...I shouldn't have allowed that misconception to go unchallenged.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It was my tacit acceptance of the pseudonym... My failure to stop the Reaper becoming something more than a mere legend...that led to all this.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But you're not to blame for that, Lord van Zieks!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's only because serious crime in the capital dropped off so sharply when the public started calling you that. That's why you didn't say anything, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...To be frank, I'm not sure that was the sole reason.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">There was a rumour at the time that the Reaper was really the ghost of my late brother.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">That having been slain by that evil killer, Klint's restless spirit returned as some sort of demigod... ...to wield a deadly blade of justice where I, by dint of the law, could not.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...we've heard that story too.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">When I lost him... ...I felt as though I'd lost my guiding light.  I didn't know where to go or what to do. And so... ...in some small way, I wonder if perhaps those rumours made me feel his absence a little less keenly. Even if I knew it was just an illusion. Just some nonsense conjured up by an over-imaginative public.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">He was obviously extremely important to you. Lord Klint van Zieks...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...what's important now is uncovering the truth. That's all that matters. I...know that you didn't take anyone's life.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And I intend to prove that beyond a shadow of a doubt in court today.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... I never thought I'd say this... ...but I can see it in your eyes. That burning desire to cut through all the lies and deception. I can't deny it any longer. You...are a lawyer of absolute integrity.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Now tell me... ...why do I detect the scent of expensive tea leaves in the air?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Iris! When did you get here?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah! Um... I brought you one of my special blends. Hurley loves it. He says it helps him to clear his head!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...I thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh... Hee hee...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's surely the first and last time I'll ever see a sight like this...</thought> You seem different today, Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sort of...subdued, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I am not!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What happened yesterday is obviously still playing on her mind a lot. She's clearly very troubled about having stolen that autopsy report from Dr Sithe's laboratory.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Alright then...good luck to you both! I have to make a move now.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! You're not staying?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I thought you'd want to watch today's proceedings.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well...I'd like to cheer you on, obviously. But I've got lots to get ready.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Get ready? For what?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, yes. Would you take this?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Isn't that one of the little felt dolls that's usually dangling from your knapsack?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes! It's a lucky charm! A little Hurley that I made once.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A 'Hurley'? <thought>It looks more like a 'Hareley' to me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">If for some reason you completely run out of options in the trial today... ...then just pull this little Hurley's ears as hard as you possibly can!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...? Pull his ears?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's right! It's a way to bring good luck. ...I think you might need it!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Y-You think...what we'll need is luck...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What a charming little rabbity version of Mr Sholmes. Do you suppose this is how Iris sees him?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Are you alright, Mr Naruhodo? Your eyes are veritably boring into the poor doll's ears.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, sorry. I was just wondering... What do you suppose would happen if I were to tug its ears with all my might right now?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm sure that we'll find out...when the time is right. To become a proper gentleman, you really must learn stoic patience!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...But I want to know!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">I just sneaked a peek inside the courtroom. And...it seemed very different to normal.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yes, it would seem... ...that a certain someone has decided to pull out all the stops.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What does that mean?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What about Mr Sholmes, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I...don't know. He was out all night and he hadn't come home by the time I left this morning.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Was Professor Mikotoba out all night too, do you think, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, it would seem so. I telegrammed the hotel this morning... ...and apparently they didn't come back to their rooms last night at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'They'?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Father and Judge Jigoku, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge Jigoku, too?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's right. Nobody appears to have seen either of them since yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Counsel for the Defence and the defendant! Court is about to be in session. Please make your way inside the courtroom at once!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Good luck then, Runo! Good luck, Susie!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...thanks, Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And you, Mr Reaper. I hope it goes well!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Once again, I thank you for the delicious tea, It was very soothing.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, I'm so glad!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We must go inside now, Lord van Zieks!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Hm...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Lord van Zieks has always been the formidable prosecutor I've had to lock horns with in court. But not today. Today I battle with another in pursuit of the truth. My best friend, Kazuma Asogi, who I trust more than anyone else in the world. Now I understand what it was that drew me here to Britain all those months ago. Now I know exactly what destiny had in store for me. It's all been leading up to this one day... To this one trial... To this one final reckoning!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It feels even more oppressive here than it did yesterday... <thought>There are cold stares piercing me like knives from all sides today.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah! M-Mr Naruhodo! Look!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">L... Lord Stronghart!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Kazuma must have known beforehand...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">The ramifications of this trial now extend far beyond the murder of one Scotland Yard inspector. In fact, events have come to light that threaten to rock the very foundations of our country's legal system.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The escape of a condemned criminal on the night of his execution...the subsequent unlawful shooting of the man... ...and the revelation that prison staff must have been complicit in the jailbreak.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Britain is currently hosting influential members of the judiciary from countries all around the world. It is imperative that we uncover the truth in these proceedings to avoid international embarrassment. By royal decree, this will continue to be a closed trial... ...and one over which I, Mael Stronghart, exercise total and unequivocal authority.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The, the six jurors' flames just...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">As was the case in yesterday's proceedings, those here present in the public gallery... ...are distinguished members of our judiciary, assembled to bear witness to a fair judicial process.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">In other words...a collection of your acolytes, Lord Stronghart.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">......... On a personal note, I find this most distressing, Lord van Zieks. You were a prosecutor of exceptional talent. Much like your brother Klint in fact...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">In the name of Her Majesty the Queen, I hereby declare this court to be in session... ...for the trial of Barok van Zieks, who officially stands accused of murder.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Counsels for the prosecution and defense...are you in full readiness to proceed?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The defence is ready...My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">As is the prosecution.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Yesterday's proceedings brought to light a shocking and disturbing fact: There was a side to the victim, Inspector Tobias Gregson, that was unknown to his superiors at Scotland Yard.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, he was carrying out operations in secret, which Scotland Yard knew nothing about.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">And in those clandestine operations, he had an accomplice.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Mr Daley Vigil, who would be given the inspector's identification... ...and present himself around the capital in order to establish credible alibis for Gregson. In that way, Gregson appeared to be carrying out his regular Scotland Yard work when in fact he wasn't.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">At the end of yesterday's session, Mr Vigil, who had been suffering from amnesia, regained his memory. It would appear he buried his memories of the time deep inside himself as a means of self-preservation. Because whilst he was engaged as chief warder at Barclay Prison, he abetted the convict's escape.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Mr Vigil is currently recuperating at St Synner's. He's recovered enough to give a signed statement about his movements on the day prior to the incident. He's formally admitted to posing as Gregson whilst investigating the Red-Headed League.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Which brings us to the crucial issue of the victim's time of death. The defence yesterday proposed a suggestion that the victim may have been killed one day earlier. This was based largely on the discovery that the victim's pocket watch had not been wound.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The prosecution has something to report on that subject, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Really? Go ahead, Prosecutor Asogi.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I met once again with the coroner yesterday to discuss the issue. She confirmed that the defence's suggestion could not be ruled out.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's entirely possible that Inspector Gregson was killed on 31st October - the day before his body was discovered. I have here an updated autopsy report that includes the amended details.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">But the official opinion of the investigation team was made clear yesterday. That the time of death was 5 p.m. on 1st November.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">There are indications of an attempt to disguise the real time of death, however. It seems that the natural decaying process of the victim's body may have been slowed by keeping it chilled.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">That's out of the question. There are no refrigeration devices in that part of London large enough to accommodate a human corpse.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My Lord! This is more than just conjecture. There's evidence to support the idea. We must investigate it thoroughly.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...Very well. The court will accept the new report as evidence. However, if this updated report is deemed to be accurate... ...it would give renewed significance to the movements of the victim on the day before the Fresno Street incident.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It would, yes. Especially since on that day... ...Inspector Gregson was using Mr Vigil to cover up his real movements. It's conceivable that he was killed in the course of his secret activities.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Do I sense that the prosecution has some information regarding those activities?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Scotland Yard put an enormous effort into investigating that precise matter yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I think we should begin by presenting the results of that investigation work. So the prosecution calls its first witness now!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">State your name and occupation for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Inspector Gina Lestrade, reportin'! Reper...sentive o' Scotland Yard!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...A self-conferred rank, but never mind.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Gina? Again?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Wot's yer problem, 'Oddo? Wot's wiv that 'Gina? Again?' look, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">The boss meant the world to me. 'E done more for me than anyone else ever did!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Oh? Inspector Gregson, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">'E got me out the back slums o' the East End an' took me under 'is wing. Taught me that life can 'ave a purpose. So that's why I'm the best person to be standin' 'ere speakin' for 'im!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh Gina...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Right, all out of the goodness of Gregson's heart. Not at all that he had his arm twisted by Mr Sholmes. No...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What's relevant to these proceedings is that the outcome of Scotland Yard's investigations yesterday... ...has revealed that the victim was carrying out some assignment the police knew nothing about.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Very troubling...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That face... Lord Stronghart knew!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So...Inspector Lestrade! Let's hear exactly what it says in that report!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Comin' right up, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">All Yard detectives are s'posed to follow orders an' investigate wot they're told.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Smuggled goods?!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I dunno, do I? I'm just tellin' ya wot was written in the book!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Tobacco, tea, spices, medicines... Goods of all sorts flow into London by illegal channels from across the globe. It's well known that they're disposed of at regular black markets that take place in the capital. But the police are rarely able to locate them in time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So Inspector Gregson was investigating one of those black markets?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">It's been suggested that high-ranking government officials may be involved in black-market activity. No doubt Gregson was trying to avoid details of his investigations being leaked to the involved parties. That would explain why he was operating on his own authority, without the Yard's knowledge.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And do we know where the dealings were taking place this time?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In a particular room of a certain exclusive London gentleman's club. And on the day in question...the accused is known to have been there. That's the conclusion of Scotland Yard's investigation into the matter.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That can't be...! <thought>We haven't heard anything about any of this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Members of the club have testified to it. There's no question: the accused, Barok van Zieks, was present.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">That would be very significant testimony, then.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! But, but... ...Lord van Zieks made no mention of this! At all!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In short, Lord van Zieks had ample opportunity to murder the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Very well, then. Counsel for the Defence, begin your cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">All Yard detectives are s'posed to follow orders an' investigate wot they're told.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you follow orders, do you, Gina?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Nah, not me. I'm above all that, see.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">The boss always 'ad special orders for me. 'Grab us some fish an' chips' or 'Go an' give Toby 'is grub'... That kind o' thing.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...So 'errands' more than 'orders' then.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">This 'detective' is still an apprentice, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, well, this 'apprentice' ain't one to sit around an' wait to be told wot to do...even by the boss. That's why I've been doin' me own investigations into wot 'appened. I didn't find much at first...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">But a little search o' the boss's office turned up a notebook that 'ad a load of secret meetin's in it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you went through Inspector Gregson's things?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yup! As part o' the independent Lestrade investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm sure your superiors would be delighted that you're taking the initiative...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">So I snuck into 'is office when no one else was about. Cos if anyone at the Yard 'ad seen me goin' in there, they'd 'ave turfed me straight out on the street.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This is sounding less and less like an investigation and more and more like something else...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The prosecution understands that it was this very detective who discovered the notebook.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">You got that right! Nuffin' gets past Inspector Lestrade and 'er trusty assistant, Chief Inspector Toby! We found it 'idden in one of 'is desk drawers that 'ad a false bottom.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's...impressive!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">So then I went to 'ide meself where no one could find me so I could 'ave a butcher's at wot was written in it. Cos if anyone at the Yard 'ad found me out, they'd 'ave turfed me straight out on the street.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I've given it in now though, ain't I? An' if it weren't for me, it wouldn't never 'ave been found!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Accordin' to that, the boss was lookin' into some smuggled goods dealin's that day.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you have any idea where those dealings were taking place?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yup! It was all there in the boss's notes! Let's see if I can remember... Erm...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">As I already said, the illegal dealings were due to take place at a gentleman's club.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I remember. But I was hoping to find out the name of the club.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">That won't be necessary.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's conceivable that the club might be used again by the smugglers in future. Therefore...the prosecution has been asked not to reveal the name in these proceedings.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I dunno wot all the fuss is about. It's right 'ere. All I've gotta do is read it out. An' I could, too! I've got this readin' game buttoned up now! Can't I show ya wot I can do? Go on, wot's the 'arm?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The judge hasn't signalled his objection yet. I could try to find out... What should I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is a closed court. The proceedings are confidential. There shouldn't be any possibility of the information being leaked.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">As I explained, there is some possibility of politicians being involved in this affair. The prosecution is rightfully exercising caution, I imagine.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... No, My Lord. The prosecution has no objection.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">There's no question that Inspector Gregson was looking into these black market dealings. However... ...it's not yet been established that he was on that particular trail on the day in question. If the defence requires to know the club's name, the prosecution has no intention of being obstructive.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">.........</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Right then! I get to show off me readin' skills!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Gina's only just learnt to read. There's a good chance she might make a mistake... I worry she might mix up the letters 'p' and 'q' and 'b' and 'd'...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">That's enough o' your cheek, 'Oddo! I'm way past 'E' now! I've got all the way to 'V'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just to err on the side of caution, the defence will wait until the witness can read all the letters up to 'Z'!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Grrr...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In that case, let's get back to the witness's testimony, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Apparently the smuggled goods deal was gonna 'appen at a gentleman's club called 'The Grouse'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The Grouse? What sort of a club is that?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I ain't got the foggiest. Clubs ain't exactly my thing. But...I am kind o' curious!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">They're not places where a foreign student like you would be readily admitted.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Have you looked in the mirror recently?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I tell ya wot! Me and Chief Inspector Toby could go in undercover!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Could you, though?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I could pick out a few good marks an' see wot else I could find out while I was in there!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I really don't think you should go 'picking' out anything. Anyway, that's where these black market dealings were going to take place, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, it's gotta be. That's wot the lower-rankin' detectives at the Yard reckon.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Says the even lower-ranking detective...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Looks like it was a big job an' all. But the coppers weren't on to it yet.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So how had Inspector Gregson come to find out about it, in that case?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">That's the question, ain't it? But I'm just an apprentice, so...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And why didn't he inform Scotland Yard of his findings?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, that's wot I was askin' meself. Cos - ya know - I'm just an apprentice.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When it suits you, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Anyway, the point is, somefin' went on at that club, no question.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You can't say that for certain though, surely?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Wot matters most is, there's witnesses wot saw the Reaper at the place, too!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord van Zieks was at the club?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">He was. Detectives who visited the club yesterday to make inquiries have confirmed it. Several members report having seen the accused being admitted to the room in question as a guest.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It looks like there's no disputing that he was there then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well we know that Lord van Zieks was investigating Inspector Gregson, don't we? Perhaps he'd already discovered the inspector's secret notebook.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Which led him to the club, you mean? Maybe...</thought> Presumably then, there are also eyewitnesses who can testify that Gregson was there?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... None have been identified at this time, no.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So the all-important victim wasn't seen at this mysterious club...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Oi! Why ain't you askin' Inspector Lestrade 'ere, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So that's all I've got to work with... Gina's not holding back with that ice-cold stare of hers, is she?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I really don't know what to make of all this.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord van Zieks told us that he was investigating Inspector Gregson... ...but he never once mentioned that he met the inspector the day before the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You don't think Lord van Zieks could have been lying to us, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That's not the only way to explain this.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If everything Lord van Zieks has told us is true... ...then there must be a mistake in this testimony somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...! You mean, there are details we've yet to uncover?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Exactly. <thought>A clue perhaps, that even Gina hasn't noticed. That's what we should be looking for here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I've read about these clubs that exist here in Britain. As I understand it, they're places where well-to-do gentlemen socialise with friends and colleagues.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Don't imagine for a second that a foreign student like you would be admitted.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Seriously, is your mirror cracked or something?</thought> Do we know for sure that the contraband dealings were definitely happening at a club called 'The Grouse'?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...The police are currently looking for evidence... but haven't found anything definitive yet.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And I'm sorry to say that they probably won't.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I mean that the place Inspector Gregson was secretly going to visit on 31st October... ...may not have been a gentleman's club at all.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...You're showing a very irreverent attitude towards our country's police force there, Counsel. If it wasn't a gentleman's club...then what was it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...A steamship.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You think...it's a ship...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I have the evidence to prove it here!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Let me see that. 'This dark-suited young man is not in the least bit untrustworthy.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Um...the other side, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...Be more specific next time. ...! Ah... This would appear to be a ticket for passage upon a steamship, yes... The SS Grouse...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So there's a steamship named the Grouse that happens to share a name with the club. But I'm afraid to say... ...there's a flaw in your logic there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Look at the ticket. Notice the date of arrival in port.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">The ship arrived at the Port of Dover on 1st November. ...Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The day on which the sound like a gunshot was heard on Fresno Street. In other words... ...on the day in question here - 31st October - when the victim was on his clandestine mission... ...that ship hadn't yet docked on British shores!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">That would certainly make an undercover investigation somewhat challenging.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The fact that the steamship hadn't yet reached Britain... ...substantiates the defence's assertion that the victim was investigating the SS Grouse on the day in question!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Then show your evidence for that assertion!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">In that case, Counsel for the Defence, present your evidence to the court now. Evidence that substantiates your claim that the victim was investigating the SS Grouse on 31st October.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, this evidence proves it...I think...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The, the proof is in the pudding?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Those three equally nonsensical statements wasted fifteen seconds of the court's time. You will accordingly suffer fifteen seconds' worth of penalty, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">UWAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH! <thought>I need to work on picking a more succinct turn of phrase.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think you might need to work on picking a more appropriate piece of evidence first.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'm sure Gregson was on board that ship the day before his body was found. And we know the SS Grouse stopped at the Port of Dunkirk in France for the night...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I take it from your expression that you intend to risk further penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">What's this? A passport for travel issued to the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Dated 31st October? ...What are you suggesting?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm suggesting that just one day before the inspector's body was discovered... ...there's a distinct possibility he wasn't even in the country!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Order! Order! This document is for passage to France. It does appear to have been officially authorised.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The day before the SS Grouse arrived at Dover... ...it docked on the northern coast of France for a night.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">According to my father, who was on board...at the Port of Dunkirk.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Dunkirk, France... What could possibly have taken the victim there?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... Ha ha ha ha ha hah! I'm impressed, Ryunosuke Naruhodo! I certainly didn't expect you to get your hands on that passport.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? You mean...you knew about this?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... The prosecution's strategy for this trial has been laid down by the Crown prosecution office: 'On the day before the incident, the victim was investigating contraband dealings at a London club.' That's the outcome of Scotland Yard's investigations and the line the prosecution has been asked to follow. ...But personally, I don't agree. I think the Prosecutor's Office is trying to hide something.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And now that you've expertly disproven their assertion... I intend to reveal what I believe that something to be.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...What are you playing at, Prosecutor Asogi?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">A courtroom is a forum for the truth, My Lord. Which is why it's my duty to present all the facts, without exception.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Let me guess... This was your intention from the outset, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The reason Inspector Gregson secretly made his way to the steamship docked in France on the day in question... ...was to carry out a mission...for the Reaper!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The, the Reaper?!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Order! Order! What on earth are you saying, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The prosecution made an assertion in court yesterday:</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Inspector Gregson was investigating the identity of the Reaper. When he discovered the location of the man's secret hideout...he was killed. As I'm sure everyone can imagine...by the Reaper's hand!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">But in reality...the truth is the opposite of that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Inspector Gregson wasn't investigating the Reaper at all. He was in fact...acting FOR the Reaper!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you're saying the mission he was undertaking was...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Obviously...an assassination.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Barok van Zieks never carried out any of the actual killings. Whenever the Reaper's victims lost their lives, he always had a cast-iron alibi. Which tells us...that he must have had an accomplice.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">And you claim...that was Inspector Gregson?</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gina">W...Wot the 'ell d'ya think yer sayin', eh? My boss would never o' done nuffin' like that!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And yet...when you consider all the facts, it all makes perfect sense.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">No! It, it can't be...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We also arrived at the same conclusion, didn't we? That Inspector Gregson was operating as the Reaper.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Even so...there's no way that the person giving him his orders... ...was Lord van Zieks! <thought>No, the true Reaper is somebody else...</thought> Barok van Zieks is not the Reaper!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">A predictable response...from someone who's advocating for the man.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And even if it's true that Gregson was operating as an agent of the Reaper... ...the suggestion that he went aboard the SS Grouse on an assassination mission doesn't follow at all.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Oh? You have some solid reason for doubting the assertion, do you, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Absolutely. It's very simple. On the day in question... ...nobody was killed aboard that steamship.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Hm...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Professor Mikotoba and Judge Jigoku were on that very ship. If someone had been assassinated, I'm certain we would have heard about it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...Pfft!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's so funny?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You're right, of course. No suspicious deaths were reported on board the ship. But I think perhaps you've missed the point. That's precisely why Inspector Gregson himself lost his life!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Gregson did board the SS Grouse that night, with the intention of dispatching his mark. But his mission...ended in failure.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Failure...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It seems that the defence hasn't yet grasped a very important detail here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What are you talking about? <thought>What detail?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Inspector Gina Lestrade!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Eh?! Wot?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The victim's notebook that you read an excerpt from earlier... That doesn't contain details of secret investigations at all. It describes ten years of assassination plots to be carried out by the Reaper of the Bailey.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yer lyin'! Even if all them bludgers wot got taken out 'ad it comin'... ...the boss weren't the Reaper!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Poor Gina...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">There's no question that Tobias Gregson was heavily involved in the Reaper's activities. You may just be an apprentice, but if you've spent any time at Scotland Yard, you must have heard rumours...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I ain't 'eard nuffin'! An' I don't believe a word of it!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Then testify again. As a representative of Scotland Yard. Consider it...your chance to defend your 'boss'.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I, I don't...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I concur. The witness will give a new formal testimony. Miss Lestrade, you will tell the court everything you know about Inspector Gregson's secret notebook!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">.........</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, this notebook does 'ave a load o' stuff about wot the Reaper got up to these past ten years.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Keep personal opinion out of your testimony, witness. We require only established fact here.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This must be so hard for her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You can't deny it now, surely...Ryunosuke Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What can't I deny?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The notebook contained the name of the final mark and the location where the assassination would take place. That's information that the victim could only have known if he was working with the Reaper!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">So...who was to be this 'final mark'?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Go ahead, Inspector Lestrade! Read the name for the court. The name that's written alongside the entry that mentions 'The Grouse' on 31st October.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Eh? Oh, um... 'Ow d'you read this then...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Reading's still not her strong suit...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">That ain't the problem, alright, 'Oddo! It's a funny name. It ain't English. It's 'ard to read.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So it's someone from overseas?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Let me 'ave a bash at it. 'Seh...ish...iro...' is it? Yeah, 'Seishiro... ...Jig...ok...you...' maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...? <thought>It, it can't be...</thought> Seishiro Jigoku?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But that's...Judge Jigoku!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Seishiro Jigoku... Certainly not an English name, you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But that can't be right! I know Judge Jigoku! And I saw him the day before yesterday! Here in London! So I know for a fact that the man hasn't been assassinated!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">As I said...the Reaper failed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Gregson missed his chance to kill his mark and returned to British shores. But the Reaper wouldn't tolerate the mistake. So he killed the inspector...personally.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The Reaper of course being the accused...Barok van Zieks!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">It's...an undeniably logical argument.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Kazuma... You planned for the trial to go this way all along, didn't you?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">L-Lord van Zieks!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The accused has no right to speak uninvited in court. You will return to the dock.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I say nothing of whether or not I'm the Reaper. That's the task of this court to decide. But there is one thing I can say unequivocally: That girl is no detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Eh? Wha...? Nah, that's right, I ain't. I'm an inspector!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Repeating rumours heard around the Yard... Reading entries from a notebook of unconfirmed origin... That's not testimony. It's practically a script. No doubt the rest of this trial will go exactly as you've clearly planned.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Your hatred of me is understandable. In your mind, I'm sure I am the Reaper...who sent your father to the gallows all those years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">But you're in danger of becoming a far more sinister Reaper yourself... ...by attempting to have me condemned with this feeble excuse for testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What did you say?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo, this is our chance!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My Lord! The defence requests that the defendant be allowed to speak! He may be privy to important information relating to the testimony just given by the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">......... Very well. I'll make an exception and grant the request. The defendant may remain in the witness stand for the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Then allow me to toast the court's impartiality.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...Don't raise your glass in my direction, sir. Counsel for the Defence, begin the cross-examination immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">At once, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, this notebook does 'ave a load o' stuff about wot the Reaper got up to these past ten years.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In other words, it shows that Gregson was basically acting as the Reaper...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Not you an' all! That ain't the only explanation, is it? 'E could 'ave been investigatin' the Reaper in secret and that notebook said wot 'e found out!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">If I may... When originally people began referring to me as the Reaper, I didn't object. I believed the power to intimidate London's criminal classes into compliance with the law to be beneficial.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But you carried out your own investigations into the true identity of the Reaper, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yes. And those investigations proved conclusively that Gregson was one arm of the Reaper.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">One arm? Wot are you on about?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The Reaper's victims were all extremely shrewd criminals at the top of their game. There's simply no way one person could have taken them on alone. The 'Reaper'...is an organisation.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">With you at its head?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... I had spies at the Yard keeping me abreast of Gregson's movements, letting me know when he was elsewhere. So I'd been able to check the most recent entry in his book. I knew the location.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You knew it said 'Grouse'?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Believing it to be a reference to the gentleman's club, I went there on the day in question to investigate. Alone.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, so that explains why several members of the club claimed to have seen you there.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">But of course the inspector was not there.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Because at the time he was making his way to the steamship docked on the northern coast of France. As shown by the passport found in the victim's metal trunk.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Very well then. Back to your testimony about the contents of this notebook...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Fine...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Is something wrong, Mr Naruhodo? You seemed a little shocked by something a moment ago.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh... No, it's...it's alright. <thought>I'm overthinking this, aren't I?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Right, I've 'ad just about enough o' this!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gina?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">All this nonsense about the boss plannin' to kill people... It's cobblers! Come on, 'Oddo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">......... Why ain't you sayin' nuffin'? Why, why ain't you yellin' out 'objection' or summat?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">You've gotta find a flaw! You do usually! Someone's lyin' 'ere, no question! You've gotta work out who it is! Please... For the boss...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">That outburst was an insult to the court and to your own testimony. I might have known that a common pickpocket from the back slums couldn't make a detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">...!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">When this trial is over, you will forfeit your warrant card, Miss Lestrade. Is that clear?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Uh...uhhh... I've 'ad it wiv the lot o' ya! It's lies every bleedin' place ya look in this world, innit? Well I've 'ad enough!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gina...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So have I. After that little speech of Gina's, I've made up my mind...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">To do what, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There was one point in this cross-examination... ...when something that was said just didn't sit right with me. One statement that seemed odd.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Do, do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'm not going to let Gina's plea for help fall on deaf ears.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Names o' victims, dates an' places an' stuff... An' the last entry in there was 31st October.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Names of victims, dates, places and 'stuff'? What in particular?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Well, beside the victims' names, this other name kept croppin' up.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What other name was that?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">It's the one I told ya yesterday. The same name, written over an' over again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean...Asa Shinn?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, that's the one! She's a friend o' yours or summat, isn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Were you even listening yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Asa Shinn... ...The assassin.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Wot?! Like...a killer, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Gregson was the tactician - the one who came up with the plan of attack. He investigated the marks thoroughly, finding out when they would be vulnerable, and who to use to get at them.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">But the person actually executing his plans was someone else, you're saying. If that's true...then the 'Reaper' does indeed start to sound like an organised group of vigilantes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Then perhaps what it said on the passport document... 'Permission for the applicant and one additional person to travel'. Could that additional person have been...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Clearly the assassin, who was meant to take Seishiro Jigoku's life.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gina! Can you confirm that?! Against the final entry that listed 'Grouse' and 'Seishiro Jigoku'... ...what name was written?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Oh! Well...that's the only entry that didn't 'ave a name next to it, as it 'appens.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">It, it just 'ad like a question mark or summat there, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">In other words, Gregson himself didn't know the identity of the assassin in that case.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">But...Gregson was the one making the plans, was he not?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...how infuriating!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>A nameless assassin...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Right, I've 'ad just about enough o' this!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gina?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">All this nonsense about the boss plannin' to kill people... It's cobblers! Come on, 'Oddo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">......... Why ain't you sayin' nuffin'? Why, why ain't you yellin' out 'objection' or summat?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">You've gotta find a flaw! You do usually! Someone's lyin' 'ere, no question! You've gotta work out who it is! Please... For the boss...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">That outburst was an insult to the court and to your own testimony. I might have known that a common pickpocket from the back slums couldn't make a detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">...!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">When this trial is over, you will forfeit your warrant card, Miss Lestrade. Is that clear?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Uh...uhhh... I've 'ad it wiv the lot o' ya! It's lies every bleedin' place ya look in this world, innit? Well I've 'ad enough!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gina...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So have I. After that little speech of Gina's, I've made up my mind...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">To do what, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There was one point in this cross-examination... ...when something that was said just didn't sit right with me. One statement that seemed odd.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Do, do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'm not going to let Gina's plea for help fall on deaf ears.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">It said 'Grouse' for the place on that date, and then the name o' the mark.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And you're saying that the mark listed was Seishiro Jigoku?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">That's wot it said. Funny name, if you ask me. An' I thought your name was odd!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So pleased to have lost my crown there...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Mr Jigoku is the presiding judge of Japan's Supreme Court of Judicature.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I remember the man. He came to our country as a visiting student sixteen years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Studying international law and diplomacy under your tutelage, Lord Stronghart.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">That bearded young fellow was a very able man, I must say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So Lord Stronghart was Judge Jigoku's mentor...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">If I'm not mistaken, he returned to Japan ten years ago now.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ten years ago...after that fateful case...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...Precisely. In the aftermath of the Professor case, his repatriation was organised immediately.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">It's a mystery why such a man would be listed in the inspector's notebook.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I didn't think it was possible, but the mood in 'ere's got even worse now. Maybe I'll just keep talkin'...</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Right, I've 'ad just about enough o' this!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gina?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">All this nonsense about the boss plannin' to kill people... It's cobblers! Come on, 'Oddo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">......... Why ain't you sayin' nuffin'? Why, why ain't you yellin' out 'objection' or summat?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">You've gotta find a flaw! You do usually! Someone's lyin' 'ere, no question! You've gotta work out who it is! Please... For the boss...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">That outburst was an insult to the court and to your own testimony. I might have known that a common pickpocket from the back slums couldn't make a detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">...!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">When this trial is over, you will forfeit your warrant card, Miss Lestrade. Is that clear?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Uh...uhhh... I've 'ad it wiv the lot o' ya! It's lies every bleedin' place ya look in this world, innit? Well I've 'ad enough!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gina...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So have I. After that little speech of Gina's, I've made up my mind...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">To do what, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There was one point in this cross-examination... ...when something that was said just didn't sit right with me. One statement that seemed odd.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Do, do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'm not going to let Gina's plea for help fall on deaf ears.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">There was a note about 'im bein' a criminal wot got away from the Reaper in court ten years ago or summat.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean, a criminal?! Judge Jigoku is no criminal!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Well don't ask me! I don't know nuffin' about it!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, do you remember what Father told us? That Judge Jigoku did once appear in court here in Britain. It was related to the Professor case, I'm sure!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, of course! You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Seishiro was trying to mitigate Genshin's guilt, so he took to the stand to testify. But he...got a little carried away and, um...actually managed to break the witness stand. He also said some contemptuous words about the British Empire...for which he was charged.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... It was a pitiful situation, yes. I'd forgotten all about it. But I prosecuted that trial too, as it happens.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You did?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It was considered to be an adjunct to the Professor proceedings, you see. But he was acquitted after being told to make reparation for the damage caused to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And there you have it.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Have what?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Surely the accused hasn't forgotten his own rule? That there's no saving anyone who faces the Reaper in court...guilty or innocent alike.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...? Noooooo! Are, are you suggesting that the reason Judge Jigoku was targeted for assassination...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The man was sent back to Japan immediately after that trial. The Reaper had no time to do his work. But then - ten years later - the mark returns to Britain once more. Perhaps now you start to see...just how vindictive the Reaper is.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Come on, that's absurd! To take someone's life for that?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Isn't the whole premise of the Reaper absurd, killing those who have been found innocent? Clearly the rules by which the man operates...are beyond a sane person's comprehension!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Right, I've 'ad just about enough o' this!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gina?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">All this nonsense about the boss plannin' to kill people... It's cobblers! Come on, 'Oddo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">......... Why ain't you sayin' nuffin'? Why, why ain't you yellin' out 'objection' or summat?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">You've gotta find a flaw! You do usually! Someone's lyin' 'ere, no question! You've gotta work out who it is! Please... For the boss...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">That outburst was an insult to the court and to your own testimony. I might have known that a common pickpocket from the back slums couldn't make a detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">...!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">When this trial is over, you will forfeit your warrant card, Miss Lestrade. Is that clear?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Uh...uhhh... I've 'ad it wiv the lot o' ya! It's lies every bleedin' place ya look in this world, innit? Well I've 'ad enough!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gina...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So have I. After that little speech of Gina's, I've made up my mind...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">To do what, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There was one point in this cross-examination... ...when something that was said just didn't sit right with me. One statement that seemed odd.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Do, do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'm not going to let Gina's plea for help fall on deaf ears.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">But honest! The boss didn't do none of it! 'E was... 'E was just investigatin' the Reaper, that's all!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you have complete faith that Inspector Gregson is innocent in all of this?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">'Course I do! I mean... ...I owe 'im that, don't I? Because 'e's the only one wot 'ad faith in me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gina...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">The boss promised me, 'e did. 'E promised me that even though I was just a diver, 'e could turn me into a top-notch detective! A cove wiv a good 'eart like that ain't gonna go an' rob people o' their futures, is 'e?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Every single person killed by the Reaper was a criminal of the first order. Lowlifes like that have no compunction about robbing hundreds of others of their futures.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Their ludicrous acquittals in court give them the freedom to make hundreds more suffer.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I, I don't...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So what? You justified your actions because you were protecting innocent people's futures?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...I'm not suggesting that the Reaper's methods are justified at all. But life isn't black and white. That's all I'm saying.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Uhhh...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Come on, 'Oddo! 'Elp! You've gotta find a flaw somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I want to thank you, Gina. You helped me find my resolve.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Amongst everything we've heard during this cross-examination, there's one thing... ...that defies explanation. One inconsistency.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">What? An inconsistency?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Really, 'Oddo?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I don't quite know what it means yet, but...</thought> Yes, there's an inconsistency in something that was said by...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Gina">'Of course'? Wot's that s'posed to mean, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gina, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gina is the person giving testimony here, so... ...if there are any inconsistencies, they can only have been introduced by her!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... I don't know where you're going with this, but... ...maybe the evidence you're obviously about to show the court will clarify.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">In that case, the defence will present evidence to substantiate its claim. To which piece of evidence does this alleged inconsistency relate?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Gina">It...it is?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The only thing that evidence proves... ...is that the man advocating for the defendant is nothing more than an apprentice lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">AAAAAARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">That'll learn ya to go bandyin' that 'apprentice' claptrap about!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry... <thought>I really put my foot in it there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I think this line of argument has run its course. And let its failure be a lesson to all you apprentices.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Uuugh... <thought>I'd better listen very carefully to the testimony again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Me? What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your face has turned ashen. 'How could he know?' Is that what you're thinking?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">If my face has turned ashen, it's because I'm thinking, 'How could he!'</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... I don't know where you're going with this, but... ...maybe the evidence you're obviously about to show the court will clarify.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">In that case, the defence will present evidence to substantiate its claim. To which piece of evidence does this alleged inconsistency relate?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Your feelings were correct. Presenting that evidence was a mistake. I suggest you withdraw it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Good advice. Because you've turned decidedly ashen!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">AAAAAAAAARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I only hope the Reaper doesn't hold that against you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh...fingers crossed...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I think this line of argument has run its course. I suggest you learn from your mistakes...before you make a fatal one in the eyes of the Reaper.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Uuugh... <thought>I'd better listen very carefully to the testimony again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">People can only be inconsistent in what they say if they actually testify. But in case you hadn't noticed...the person you're accusing isn't even in the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">The defence appears unable to respond to that replication. Any further obviously deliberate obstructions to these proceedings will not be tolerated, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No! Wait! <thought>That's not strictly true, is it? A person doesn't necessarily have to be in the stand to say something that doesn't add up in court.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo, I'm quite sure... ...that you're just a step away from the right answer!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I just need to listen carefully to what people are saying again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So that's what we have to work with...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It may help us that Lord van Zieks is in the stand, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, perhaps. I'm sure Gina knows nothing she hasn't already told us. There's no point trying to get more out of her.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Did you notice how Kazuma-sama reacted to Lord van Zieks's words?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When he called him an even more sinister Reaper, you mean? Well, I'm sure Kazuma intends to eliminate any shred of doubt that the man is guilty. He's looking for revenge against the person he considers to be his father's killer, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I do worry that if we fail to find a discrepancy in this testimony somewhere... ...the trial may end and adjudication won't go in our favour. Let's listen carefully again to what everybody is saying...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">By you...Kazuma Asogi.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Me?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Is this some attempt at filibustering, Counsel? Prosecutor Asogi has given no testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What are you suggesting I said that was inconsistent?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You let something slip that you shouldn't have. When I present the relevant piece of evidence, I imagine you'll realise what you've done.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Very well then, Counsel, go ahead. What evidence reveals this alleged inconsistency in something Prosecutor Asogi has said?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Stronghart:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You accuse your best friend and back it up with that? Clearly...the Ryunosuke Naruhodo I knew is dead!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh...struck down by my best friend...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I believe what you intended to point out, Mr Naruhodo, was when Kazuma said...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Because at the time he was making his way to the steamship docked on the northern coast of France. As shown by the passport found in the victim's metal trunk.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's exactly it.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...I take it from your expression that you're not going to let this go.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Correct, My Lord. I made a mistake, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This...is a trunk that belonged to Inspector Gregson.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">A metal construction, is it? It's certainly very heavy. ...! What's this? A bloodstain? And a relatively fresh one, too.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Wot?! You, you mean that ain't grease from all the boss's fish an' chips?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Fresh blood on the inspector's trunk... That suggests that the victim was travelling with that luggage when he was killed.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">That can't be. There was no mention of any trunk in Scotland Yard's report.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, there's a reason for that. Immediately after the inspector's body was discovered, one of the street pedlars made off with the trunk... ...hoping to sell it.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">But I found it! Me, wiv me nose for trouble!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Hmph...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Which means that nobody should have known anything about the trunk. Unless of course...we're talking about somebody who was present when the victim was killed.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And yet...during the cross-examination of the witness just now, you said this, Kazuma:</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Because at the time he was making his way to the steamship docked on the northern coast of France. As shown by the passport found in the victim's metal trunk.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So the question is...how did you know about the inspector's trunk?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... We know the man went on a trip to France. Where else would he have put his passport?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But you knew it was a metal trunk! Answer me honestly, Kazuma! On 31st October...where exactly were you?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... At the Port of Dunkirk, on board the SS Grouse... Is that the answer you're looking for, Ryunosuke?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma! What did you...?! <thought>I hadn't considered the possibility before, but... ...if Kazuma was there on the ship, then...it can only have been for one purpose...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no, Mr Naruhodo! Surely...surely you don't think...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ha ha ha ha hah! Come on, Ryunosuke, you know the rules. The only thing that really talks in the courtroom is hard evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">As I understand it, Inspector Gregson always took that case with him when he travelled. So as it stands...you've proved nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma... ...are you challenging me to prove it, beyond all reasonable doubt? That you were there that day...in the same place as the inspector!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">He, he was there? With Gregson?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's a clue that you've overlooked! A secret that trunk can tell us. <thought>I can't be sure at this point. I'll need to verify it. But I have a nasty feeling...that I'm going to be right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">The accusation being made is deeply disturbing. But nevertheless...we must test it. The defence will identify for the court where in the trunk this alleged clue is to be found. Where is the evidence that ties Prosecutor Asogi to Inspector Gregson?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">31st October... So this passport is for the day before Gregson's body was found. He needed this document for his trip to France. And when it says 'permission for the applicant and one additional person to travel'... <thought>...I can't believe it was you, Kazuma...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Stronghart:</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Personally... ...I think tying the defence counsel to the inspector's trunk and tossing it into the sea would be more helpful.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">At least that way, London's courtrooms will be safe from his destructive accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I believe that was a rather long-winded way of telling you that you're wrong, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Very well. Then let us see if you sink or swim under the weight of this penalty, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">AAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! You can't allow yourself to be drowned at sea yet!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I...was hoping never to let that happen, funnily enough.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's a small piece of metal lodged in the wall of the trunk here. Like the tip of a blade.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Eh? A blade?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma, slung around your waist as ever today... ...is the esteemed blade Karuma!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Of course it is.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Won't you draw it? Here in this courtroom...for all to see.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Exercise caution, my learned friend. That man is the son of London's most notorious killer.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Bailiff! Watch Prosecutor Asogi like a hawk!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...That won't be necessary.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The tip...is broken...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If the fragment of metal from the trunk fits together with the end of the sword... ...the question of who was there with Inspector Gregson will be answered. Agreed...Kazuma Asogi?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Expertly done, Ryunosuke! That's a point to you, and well deserved.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Do you mean to tell the court, Prosecutor Asogi...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The tip of Karuma... So this is how it was broken. Kazuma's swordsmanship is second to none. I can't believe he'd misjudge it like that.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Clearly he wasn't in his right mind. He didn't have full control of the power in his stroke. Too distracted by malicious thoughts, perhaps...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, that wouldn't be surprising. After all... ...he was on an assassination mission.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, on 31st October, I accompanied Inspector Gregson to Dunkirk... ...in order to carry out a mission.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So the 'additional person' authorised to travel...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...Was me.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">And the mission was...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...The assassination of the mark.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha... WHAAAAAAT?! You mean...you're the killer whose name was omitted from this notebook?! You were following the Reaper's orders...to dispatch Judge Jigoku...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... Let me make one thing perfectly clear: I have killed no one.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Explain.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I accepted the assassination mission, yes. And I accompanied Gregson to Dunkirk. But I never had any intention of carrying out the plan.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You were never going to do it...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...We can believe Kazuma-sama, I'm sure. After all, Judge Jigoku arrived safely in London the following day.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Hmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">On the 31st, I boarded a train from London with Inspector Gregson. We travelled to Dover, from where we crossed the Channel to Dunkirk. Then we boarded the SS Grouse and made for the cabin deck - as indicated in the plan.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You went to Judge Jigoku's cabin?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Exactly. He wasn't there, though. We decided to wait, but...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But you've already told us you had no intention of going through with it anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I didn't come to Great Britain to take anyone's life. So I left Gregson and disembarked the ship. I spent that night at a boarding house in the town, and returned to England the following morning.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A boarding house...in Dunkirk?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">My signature will be in the register book. It would be simple enough to verify.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Then what became of Jigoku?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Gregson was no assassin. So the mark was spared. I'm sure it's easy enough to imagine what happened after that. Gregson returned to England as well, having failed to complete the mission. He met with the Reaper in that room on Fresno Street to report the failure... ...causing the infuriated mastermind to pull the trigger... ...and end his wretched agent's life. That's the real truth behind Inspector Gregson's murder!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... I don't need to answer that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The victim was killed by a gunshot. A small fragment of a Japanese blade isn't relevant to the case. And accordingly...I choose to exercise my right to silence on that matter.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Be that as it may, the court will sequester the sword as evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... As you wish, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">We must take immediate action now... ...to verify whether Seishiro Jigoku remains unharmed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Karuma, the great blade... It's such a thing of beauty, I want to gaze on it for hours.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The tip of the great sword...broken... It's such a shame. It's been so meticulously cared for over the years. I can almost hear Karuma's sobs...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Kazuma must have really taken a swing for that to happen...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! R-Remains unharmed?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I agree. That should be our first priority. It's recently come to my attention that he hasn't been seen since yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! H-How did you...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">When a foreign dignitary invited to Great Britain goes missing for twenty-four hours... ...it's only natural that the question of his safety should arise.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You don't mean to say... ...that you think Judge Jigoku may have been killed?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The Reaper has more than one assassin at his disposal. And he has the power and influence to give orders from the inside of a prison cell. Isn't that right...Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...If I were truly the Reaper, I'd be able to tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Order! Order in court! Order! We will take an emergency recess for thirty minutes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Now?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Guests of the symposium have been told to maintain regular contact with the organiser's office. If the man can't be located within half an hour... ...we will have to assume the worst.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no! Not Judge Jigoku!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">No one would want to kill a harmless Japanese man who'd only just arrived in the country. Except, that is... ...for the Reaper, wanting to finish off a mark that slipped through the net ten years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I would have to agree. Mr Naruhodo, for the defence's sake...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">M-My Lord?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...I sincerely hope we are successful. If we're unable to confirm Mr Jigoku's healthy existence in the next thirty minutes, you will face grave difficulties.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Court is adjourned for thirty minutes!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Kazuma-sama, the Reaper's assassin... I feel as though I'm in a nightmare.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can hardly believe it either. But on the other hand... ...Kazuma isn't in the habit of making up stories.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... I have such a terrible sense of foreboding. If something awful has happened to Judge Jigoku... ...then I feel as though things will only spiral further and further out of control.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I felt it from the moment I stepped into the courthouse this morning. That strange sensation that we were careering towards a foregone conclusion...</thought> Well, in the worst case, we might only have thirty minutes left. Unfortunately though, I don't think there's anything we can do but wait now. We're out of options.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Actually, there may be one last hand we can play. Or rather...one last ear.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of course! The little Mr Sholmes doll that Iris gave us!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">If for some reason you completely run out of options in the trial today... ...then just pull this little Hurley's ears as hard as you possibly can!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Perhaps now is the time. What should I do? Pull Hareley's ears or not...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This is one of Iris's inventions... There's no telling what might happen. For all I know, it could cause a huge explosion!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm not sure you should be thinking like that, Mr Naruhodo. Compared to the trial ending immediately after this recess, a huge explosion might be preferable!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm not sure you should be thinking like that, Miss Susato. But I suppose you're right. If there was ever a time for taking a risk, it's now!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Here goes then. I'm going to do it!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Good luck, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No looking back... HEEEAVE!!!</line>
<line speaker="???">OOOOOOOOOOOOW!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That scream...sounded like Mr Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">M-Mr Sholmes?! ...Where are you?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Here, my dear fellow! Here!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's...it's the felt doll talking!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Pull the ears again, Mr Naruhodo! As hard as you can!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright then. I'll put all my strength into it. HEEEEEEAVE!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">OOOOOOOOOOOOW! Please, my dear fellows! You don't need to pull my ear off!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes! Where, where are you?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Myself and my trusty partner... ...are presently in the first-class cabin area of the SS Grouse.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The, the SS Grouse?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">She left Dover last night, after the final pieces of cargo were loaded. We are currently docked at Dunkirk, but due to be underway again in half an hour.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You've...taken a ship to France?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Please, even with my athletic prowess, I would struggle to jump the Straits of Dover. After we left Baker Street last night, we hurried by cab to the station and by train to the port... ...in order to board this vessel in time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you mean...you'd already worked it out? That the steamship was where everything really took place!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo...pray, what is my name?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Herlock Sholmes...world-famous great detective!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Recited to perfection. Well done.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You're a genius, Mr Sholmes! That's the only word for it!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ow ow ow ow ow! M-Miss Susato! Gently with this genius's ear, please!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! I'm ever so sorry!</line>
<line speaker="???">If I may, Sholmes...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, there you are, Mikotoba.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">You may remember that it was in fact I who made the connection to the SS Grouse. At Scotland Yard yesterday, when we examined that notebook and I recalled my steamship ticket.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah ha ha ha ha hah! But of course it was, my dear fellow! And not once did I controvert that fact. I merely had our court-bound companions utter my name.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">......... Yes, you did, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We've just entered a recess. The trial resumes in thirty minutes from now.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And if we're unable to present any new leads then, I'm afraid to say...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Do not fret, please. It's for precisely that purpose that my partner and I have made this journey. I have no doubt we shall have welcome news for you within the half hour.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you, Mr Sholmes! That would be wonderful.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Until later, then.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes! You'll be hearing from us if you're not in touch first.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ow ow ow ow ow! I shan't be hearing anything if you keep tugging my ear in that mindless fashion!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Whatever was the idea behind making a receiver operated [sic] in that way in the first place, Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Why the deuce would I know?! It's Iris's invention, not mine.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Whilst I know how much you enjoy being the hero of the hour, Sholmes... ...we have but half that now before the Grouse puts to sea again. If we don't conclude our investigations rapidly, we shall find ourselves in Naples before long.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm...there are times, Mikotoba, when you make a surprising amount of sense. So, let us begin!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">'First-Class Cabin No. 2'... Yes, this is the one. But I don't believe an investigation of the cabin is going to be plain sailing. <thought>That crewman standing in front of the door is an angry-looking fellow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Why are you loitering here? Who are you?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow, do you not recognise a world-famous great detective when you see one? The question really ought to be, who are you?</line>
<line speaker="???">Do you not recognise world-travelling great sailor Tchikin Strogenov when you see?</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">Great detective? Hah! I don't think so.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Do you see that, Mikotoba? It would appear that this man is a devoted follower of mine.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Goodness me! Is, is that a tattoo? That says 'Sholmes'?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...I must say, whilst such adoration is flattering, naturally, it does leave me a little cold.</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">What are you talking about? Leave! Now!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">How distressing. My loyal devotee knows me only by name and not by appearance. And yet I already know a great deal about you, sir. You have a brother, I believe. Like yourself, he's a shipman. Currently travelling the world aboard a Russian steamship, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">H-How could you know this?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Elementary, my dear Mikotoba.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">...I'm sure it was. Three days ago, I was bound for London aboard this ship, you see. We're looking for one of my fellow passengers. A man by the name of Jigoku.</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">There is no one with this name on board.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">But we know that he purchased a ticket for passage.</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">......... Ah, you mean Eastern man. He left ship two hours ago. Here at Dunkirk. He said something about emergency, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">What?! Are, are you sure? <thought>So Seishiro's realised that we're after him, has he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">His cabin is the one behind you. We should like to investigate, please.</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">No! I have orders not to let even mouse inside!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Mikotoba, be a good man and draw this sailor's attention away, would you? Make up some excuse so that he leaves the area.</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">......... Doesn't great detective see...? That even sailors have ears. Both left and right.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Curses! The plan is ruined!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">...And you have only yourself to blame, I'm afraid, Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">Forget it. Cabin door is locked. Even if I am not here, you cannot get inside.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Mikotoba... ...I'm sure you haven't forgotten my 'special talent' have you?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">...! <thought>Opening any lock?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Within a mere five seconds. So if you'd be so kind as to afford me the requisite time, old friend, in your typically accommodating manner.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">How could I refuse such a typically unappealing request, old friend? <thought>So I need to distract that burly sailor for five seconds, do I?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Good man! So...the game is afoot!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">That's another first-class cabin, and yet its door is completely unguarded.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Empty as well. I had a quick look inside earlier. Though I confess, I didn't investigate the wardrobe. There may very well be a young Japanese fellow inside, perspiring merrily.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">If you're referring to Naruhodo, you know very well that he's currently perspiring merrily in court.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Does it not strike you though, Mikotoba? Why the man stands guard only in front of this cabin, when both are apparently vacant...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">This would appear to be an alarm bell. <thought>All hell would break loose if that thing were to ring. The whole crew would know about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>No, I think not. That would never work, surely...</thought> I need to concoct another distraction...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">This must be a mousetrap, I think. <thought>Perhaps I could distract the crewman's attention with this somehow...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Chuuuuuu, chuuuuuu!</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">......... That sounds like big mouse in trap.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Chuuuuuu, chuuuuuu!</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">I will bring bucket of water later and put out of misery.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">......... <thought>I don't like the sound of that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In any case, my dear fellow, that was quite unconvincing. Only Japanese mice make a 'chu' sound.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Oh really, Sholmes? And pray tell, what sound do Russian mice make?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">'Pii pii' naturally. Though also quite unconvincing, I readily admit. So go ahead, Mikotoba. Do a 'pii pii' this time!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">...No thank you. I'm sure I can come up with an alternative solution.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>No, I think not. That would never work, surely...</thought> I need to concoct another distraction...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>He's like a Nioh temple guardian statue, this fellow, the way he's glaring at us so fiercely.</thought> Tell me, why are you standing guard here if the cabin is unoccupied?</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">Because this area is only for first-class passengers. We must look out for suspicious kriminals.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>He was looking straight at me when he said that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow, as you can plainly see, we are quite unsuspicious as criminals go.</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">...But still kriminals.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">No no no! For goodness' sake, Sholmes, tell the man! We're neither suspicious nor criminals!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah yes! Quite right, Mikotoba. Curses! This seaman is far too able for his own good! ...Be extremely careful in what you say!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>One of us ought to be, yes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Ah, the switch for the electrical lights. <thought>Perhaps if I were to turn off the lights, the crewman wouldn't be able to see what we were doing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">Agh! What is happening? Where is light?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Now, Sholmes! Now!</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">Hmph. Nobody there...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>That was a close shave.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Quite a knack you have, stumbling so violently in an apparently empty corridor.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">...Do be quiet, Sholmes. I shall have to think of another approach.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>No, I think not. That would never work, surely...</thought> I need to concoct another distraction...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">That's a speaking tube for members of the crew to communicate with one another around the ship. <thought>If I could persuade our stocky sailor friend that he needed to use it... ...Sholmes could unlock the door whilst he was distracted.</thought> The question is...how?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>That's the way back to the deck. But we certainly can't give up on this now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>Here goes, then. Pardon me in advance!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">You! What are you doing? If we were at sea, that would be very bad problem!</line>
<line speaker="???">What's going on down there?! Seaman Strogenov! Report at once!</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">...! Sorry, sir! Nothing to report! It was just stupid trick! ...No, not by me! By world-famous- No! As I told you...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Now, Sholmes! Now!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Done.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Not even five seconds, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well don't stand there gawping at my brilliance, Mikotoba! In we go!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Oh! Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Good gracious...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It would appear that the occupant of this cabin did indeed disembark rather hurriedly.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Those clothes on the floor there... They're Seishiro's, without question.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, it seems we are just a little too late.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Yes, by about two hours.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Still, whilst we're here, we should investigate thoroughly. There may well be two hours' worth of clues to find in here.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">But that burly crewman may return at any moment, Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed he may. ...Which makes this all the more thrilling!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">According to the report I was given, Naruhodo was concealing himself in Asogi's wardrobe.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed he was. And it was of a similar size to this one. Ah! You must climb inside yourself, my dear fellow!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">What? Whatever for?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It was the site of my first fateful meeting with Mr Naruhodo. You can experience the moment for yourself now! Complete with my dramatic rhetoric! Come along now! In you go! This will only take a moment.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Really, Sholmes, surely you can just tell me what you said!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Well...I uttered some brilliant remark and opened the wardrobe to reveal the stowaway murderer!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">...I think I'll just read about it in 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes.'</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Quite the exquisite glass, I must say. See here, how it.........</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Is, is something wrong, Sholmes? You suddenly trailed off...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ice, Mikotoba, ice! What opulence the first-class passengers enjoy: chilled drinks.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Could it be that this steamship is equipped with an electrically refrigerated cold room, do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well...it is a luxury liner, after all. They have enormous refrigerators for storing all sorts of lavish produce as well as ice. On our voyage from Japan, we enjoyed culinary delights from all over the world.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Hm, suddenly, Mikotoba... ...the sight of you is making my mouth water.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">......... I haven't taken on the flavour of the food I ate, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">There's a speaking tube here, look. Though it's been stoppered with some cloth. So the voices of the crewmen on the bridge aren't an annoyance, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Or indeed so that the voices in this cabin aren't heard elsewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">...! Could something have happened in here that was for no one else's ears, do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Either that, or... ...it could be to prevent snakes from entering.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">...That's really become a favourite case of yours, hasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">This is the wastepaper basket, look. ...And there's still rubbish inside.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed? Then let us pry... I've discovered recently I have a penchant for exploring the contents of others' wastepaper baskets.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I sincerely hope only for your work.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Ah. Here we have a notice issued to passengers from three days ago.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Three days ago? The night before we arrived in London, then. When I was still aboard myself. Ah yes...there was an evacuation drill. I remember now. For our safety and security, all first-class passengers were constantly under the watchful eye of the crew. So it was a welcome relief to have some privacy for once.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">This is the wastepaper basket, look. ...And there's still rubbish inside.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed? Then let us pry... I've discovered recently I have a penchant for exploring the contents of others' wastepaper baskets.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I sincerely hope only for your work.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Ah. Here we have a notice issued to passengers from three days ago.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Three days ago? The night before we arrived in London, then. When I was still aboard myself. Ah yes...there was an evacuation drill. I remember now. For our safety and security, all first-class passengers were constantly under the watchful eye of the crew. So it was a welcome relief to have some privacy for once.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">That's a substantial heap of clothes on the floor. An overcoat, shirts, a dressing gown...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Momohiki work trousers, a tanzen robe, a haramaki waist band... Clearly the clothing of a Japanese man.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And clearly, Japanese men are unaccustomed to the culture of the wardrobe.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">It looks to me as if they've been thrown in a heap like that in something of a hurry.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed. You could help yourself to a Japanese man's shirt perhaps? I'm sure you made mention of packing too few.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I'd very likely drown in one of Seishiro's shirts. No, I'll just buy any extras I need, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">That's a very sizeable trunk indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Seishiro is partial to all things large.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And a rather clumsy fellow, if he failed to notice he'd left that behind.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Perhaps he left it on purpose. It's lighter than you might think, but still a hindrance to a speedy escape.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Hm, pity. It's locked, so we can't look inside.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Surely five seconds from now the situation will be quite different though?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Sadly not. It has a seven-digit combination lock. And I'm not in a morose enough mood to work through all the combinations at present.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">These are the 'Rules of Passage'. 'Passengers must not keep weapons or other dangerous objects in their cabins. Pets are also strictly forbidden. Additionally, there are severe punishments for stowing away in wardrobes and/or travel cases.'</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I feel the rules have increased since I last read them. ...Probably just my imagination.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">What about the fact that they're not straight on the wall? Doesn't that strike you?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm, you may be right. ...Probably just your imagination, though. A trifle. And you know what I always say, Mikotoba: there is nothing important about trifles.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">...It's probably just my imagination, but I think THAT might be slightly off.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Plenty of reading material to keep passengers occupied on the long sea voyages. I found the mixture of classic literature and easy reading to be most satisfactory, I must say.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Tsk! Whoever stocked this bookcase was a hopeless heretic. There's no copy of 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes', my dear fellows!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Um...I'm afraid it's just me. But no, you're quite right. More blasphemous than overlooking the Bible.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I shall leave a copy behind. I just happen to have one with me.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">You're a true missionary of the Church of Great Detectives, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">The wall is a slightly different colour just here. Do you see?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed. What you have observed arises when a frame that has been hanging for some time is removed. ......... Perhaps your friend is an art thief.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Now there's a bold deduction worthy of a great detective, I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">He may very well be the illusive thief who has been plaguing France's galleries of late.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">...I think perhaps we should focus our attentions elsewhere, Sholmes, don't you? <thought>That outline on the wall... I feel as though I might have spotted something of a similar shape and size elsewhere.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">All the doors on this vessel have locks, I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">A wise idea. You never know where and when criminals may strike. But of course, to the great detective Herlock Sholmes... ...lock, bolt or shirt button, it makes no difference. All are unfastened with equal ease!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">The way you go on, you sound rather more like a great thief than a great detective.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear Mikotoba, as long as there is greatness, I am quite satisfied.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Haah... Of course you are.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Ah, Able Seaman Strogenov. Hello again.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...I was beginning to think you'd never materialise.</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">Eh? You...you are waiting for me?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Of course! I was expecting you to burst in with a hearty Russian profanity far sooner.</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">I was in trouble with captain because of trick you play before!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>Poor, innocent Tchikin...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">It is all your fault! Ship is leaving port soon. Get off! Now!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Of course, we shall disembark presently, my dear fellow. But first... ...there is something that must be done.</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Why naturally... ...the debunking of your deceit and the baring of the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">Kakoy?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm afraid I see through your lies. For one thing... ...Mr Jigoku has not yet left this vessel at all.</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And for another, my dear Seaman Strogenov... ...you know exactly where the man is even as we speak, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">......... How, how can you...?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Good gracious, Sholmes! You mean...you've worked it out? All of it?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... It's really been too long, hasn't it, old friend? Ten years, no less!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So...would you care to join me for a dance...of my inimitable logic and reasoning?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">......... Nothing would please me more!</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">W-What is this?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">We have but minutes until the vessel puts to sea. No games now.</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">Da! That is what I said!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Sadly, that was a rather clumsy lie. You see, there is something in this room that quite clearly contradicts it.</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Ah! <thought>Yes, of course...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I see you've noted it too,  Mikotoba. Then please, do take the lead... What in this cabin shows the impossibility of Jigoku having disembarked two hours ago? Let's see what the last three years have done to your observational skills then, Mikotoba!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">It's been ten years since we last did this, Sholmes, not three.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Why, of course it has! Quite! Now, all the clues are here in this cabin for your eyes to see. But as I always say, you must not merely look, but observe. Observe and the answers become clear. So...impress me!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I think I can manage that!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Sholmes:</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Hmph. Come, Sholmes, where's the fun in life without a little fooling around, hm?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Ah ha ha ha ha hah! Quite right you are!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>That was a close shave. I'd better rethink that before I'm the fool here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Jigoku didn't disembark two hours ago at all. That was a lie, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Of course it was. And I had hoped you would be quicker to point out why. Otherwise...the evidence itself may melt away before our every eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Perhaps you should have cleared away that glass?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">How curious that the ice shouldn't have melted despite it being abandoned two hours ago?</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It would appear that the man was here in this very cabin until moments before our arrival... ...with this well-chilled glass in hand!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>Get your mind off the refreshments, Sholmes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">One might even conclude that somebody informed him of our boarding. Wouldn't you agree, Mr Strogenov?</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">Errr...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">But...why would Seishiro run from us?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Before we consider that question, allow me to confirm one small matter: Would I be correct in saying that these first-class cabins of the SS Grouse... ...are the same ones in which you and Mr Jigoku were accommodated on your voyage from Japan?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Ah! That's...that's right, they are. I was in the cabin next door, and Seishiro was...yes... ...fifty days in this very cabin during our voyage!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As I suspected. For you see... ...there are traces in this cabin of a dark secret that Mr Jigoku had to hide.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">What traces?</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">I, I know nothing about this!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, this is news to you, is it, Mr Strogenov?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Sholmes, what exactly are you getting at?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As I said, there are traces in this cabin of some nefarious activity. Something that appears out of place, which I'm quite sure won't have escaped your notice.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>Something out of place in here...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">That's the key to this, Mikotoba. The remnants of the dark deed that took place in here are being masked by something quite incongruous! I must say, I didn't foresee ever doing this dance of deduction with you again, Mikotoba.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">No, quite. But life is full of unexpected twists and turns, as we well know. Now then, let's see if I can't uncover the truth here...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, you have the floor, my dear fellow!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Sholmes:</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Hmph. Come, Sholmes, where's the fun in life without a little fooling around, hm?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Ah ha ha ha ha hah! Quite right you are!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>That was a close shave. I'd better rethink that before I'm the fool here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You must tilt your head to one side and listen carefully to the faint cries of the scene. Hear the evidence calling out for you to find it. 'Here I am,' it cries!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well, your methods were never conventional. But you know I've always been willing to give them a try! .........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Dear God, Mikotoba, open your eyes! It was a metaphorical listening that I was suggesting!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>Ah...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">It's the Rules of Passage in this frame here. They're obviously out of place. The way they're hanging crooked on the wall...as if they were put there in a hurry.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, as I'm sure you've already concluded... ...that frame was originally over here. The shape and size are a perfect match.</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">Da! You are right! When did frame move...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hardly the most observant of crewmen, are you, Mr Strogenov? I would think your captain is quite justified in having his reservations about your reliability.</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">Grrrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>Oh dear. That really seemed to touch a nerve.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So, Mikotoba...why don't you lift that frame off the wall?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">That...that looks... ...like a bullet hole!</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">What?! Who has been shooting walls?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I see the projectile has been removed. Clearly the careful occupant of this room has already disposed of it. Now then, Mr Strogenov...</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...I have the distinct impression that you're attempting to shield said occupant.</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">I don't know what you are talking about! Why would I try to protect Eastern stranger?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, so we're talking about the same man, I see. Good.</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">Ugh!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm sure we can get to the bottom of this in no time... aren't you? Because there's some very noteworthy evidence that explains the reason why you're lying for the man! Yes, you've been told to keep up this pretence, as clearly shown by...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I really don't know how to approach this one, Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, my dear Mikotoba, simply keep first principles in mind. Study your subject from every angle... ...and I'm quite sure that you'll see it. In fact, I'd put a wager on it!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">So I'm to glare at the fellow from all sides? Well, I can certainly do that...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Sholmes:</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Hmph. Come, Sholmes, where's the fun in life without a little fooling around, hm?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Ah ha ha ha ha hah! Quite right you are!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>That was a close shave. I'd better rethink that before I'm the fool here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">So a Russian crewman is aiding a Japanese man to evade capture by an English detective...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Nationality needn't come into it. In this respect at least, all humans are the same. Ask yourself what can spur a man to do the bidding of another about whom he knows precious little. There is only one thing in the whole world with such repugnant, bottomless power!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Let's not get carried away now, Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">It's almost too obvious for words.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Quite. The universal language of the world: money.</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">And I'd wager that the Eastern fellow in question... ...is Seishiro Jigoku. Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">Gaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">So, I presume you realise what this means? There are clear signs that a crime has been committed in this cabin. And the way you're going, sir, you'll find yourself accused of being an accomplice.</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">B-But...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I believe you know, Mr Strogenov... You know where Mr Jigoku is hiding at this precise moment in time!</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As always, Mikotoba, in matters of deduction, the furtive glance is your unfaltering ally.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Yes, I think you're onto something there, Sholmes. You've found the chink in this burly fellow's armour!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">We need only follow the man's gaze to know where our prey is hiding... The slightest flicker of the pupils... A minutely delayed blink... Nothing escapes my attention. Even that which is barely perceptible.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">You could hardly call this barely perceptible, Sholmes. The man's turned his entire head. It's not exactly what you'd describe as a furtive glance, is it? It's almost too obvious...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">We shall let your tapping toes decide, my dear fellow!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Sholmes:</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Hmph. Come, Sholmes, where's the fun in life without a little fooling around, hm?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Ah ha ha ha ha hah! Quite right you are!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>That was a close shave. I'd better rethink that before I'm the fool here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">So...you really think he's hiding in here as we speak?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Curled up in a ball at this very moment! But as I said earlier, we've no time for games today.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">No, I quite understand. I'll make this as quick as I can. Seaman Strogenov will be suffering neck fatigue before long, I should think.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">You turned immediately to look at this large trunk, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">Aaah!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">The truth is, Seishiro Jigoku was unable to escape from the ship in time... ...and is, at this very moment, doing his best to stifle his breath inside this trunk!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">If he still has a breath to take. I fear he may be running dangerously low on air.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I imagine he didn't count on us making a nuisance of ourselves for quite so long. I think it would be in everyone's best interests for us to open the trunk as quickly as possible.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">B-But how can we? Are you forgetting about the combination lock? We don't know the seven-digit code!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The combination lock can't be opened from inside the trunk. Therefore there must have been an arrangement for somebody to open it after our departure.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Of course...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In short, before Jigoku hid himself inside that trunk... ...he must have told somebody the seven-digit number for the lock. As I'm sure you can confirm...Mr Strogenov!</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">*Gulp!* No! I know nothing about combination code!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Don't move a muscle, my good seaman!</line>
<line speaker="Tchikin">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Now, Mikotoba...would you do the honours and open the trunk?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">H-How on earth do you expect me...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It's a seven-digit number, remember. Quickly now! We have little time!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"> </line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">No...it's refusing to open.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Tell me, what number did you use?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well...to begin with I thought I'd try my birthday.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Your birthday? Interesting, since as of today with that absurd guesswork, you're dead to me.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">...As measured as ever in response, Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">If you would only look in the right place, Mikotoba, the answer would be staring you in the face.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">The right place...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But if you're having a spot of bother, I always find standing on my head aids the cognitive processes.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>That did it! It's open!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">You had to meddle, didn't you...</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">Well, Yujin, you've found me now.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Seishiro...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">...I was really hoping beyond hope not to find you here, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">But you're not entirely unsurprised, I take it?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">No, quite. I just wish it were some other way.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Well? Are you ever going to introduce me?</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">Ah, your reputation precedes you, Mr Sholmes. I've read stories of many of your exploits.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Excuse my manners, Sholmes. This is Mr Jigoku, my old friend and travelling companion.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The devil is in the details, Mikotoba. I believe you meant to say: your old friend and travelling companion... ...who made the cowardly decision to flee the country without a word to anyone when things turned sour.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">...I see my reputation precedes me as well. What an honour.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well, Seishiro? Are you going to explain all this?</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">You know it all by now, I imagine. What you didn't know, of course, is that three days ago... ...on the night before our arrival in Britain, an attempt was made on my life here on this very ship.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">By the Reaper of the Bailey? Yes, I've since heard. Because you were once prosecuted by the Reaper, weren't you? Ten years ago now, mind you.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">And I had no idea at the time what a dangerous individual he was. Anyway, when we arrived in London to find the symposium was postponed until goodness knows when... ...it became all too apparent to me that I might very well be targeted again.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">So you decided to flee the capital, without saying a word to me about it?</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">I'm afraid so, yes. Of course, I realise now... ...that I really ought to have confided in you.</line>
<line speaker="???">It's somewhat surprising, I must say...</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">What is?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, first-class cabins aboard luxury steamships are in very short supply. It's more than a little hard to believe that this one just happened to be available.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">So says the protagonist of some colourful short stories. Well, I don't care for your opinion. The cabin did just happen to be available. So I purchased a ticket and here I am.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I've just seen for myself the obvious remnants of that incident in this cabin. So you'd already purchased your return ticket before we even docked in Dover, had you? To prevent anyone else taking this cabin and seeing the evidence. Is that it?</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">Yujin...I have nothing to say to you.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, in a mere five minutes, this ship will set off on its onward voyage and not make port again until Italy. I'm afraid we must insist that you disembark with us at once.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">...You have no jurisdiction over my movements.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">We have this, Seishiro. Take it.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">It's a subpoena from the Old Bailey. You're a man of the law. You know what the ramifications of ignoring a document like this from the British courts would be.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">...You came prepared then, Yujin.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Come on, let's go.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">One moment...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">What is it, Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Inside Mr Jigoku's trunk... ...I found this rather fascinating trinket.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">What is that? Seishiro...?</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">I can't help you, I'm afraid. Some small component from something. But what, I have no idea.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>By the look on his face...I think he genuinely doesn't know.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, let us pocket it as a small souvenir of our brief sojourn in France.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>Well, young Naruhodo, I think we've done as much as we can, I'm afraid. The rest will be on the shoulders of you and your assistant!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You see these little things all over the place, don't you? It's the part on the top of a pocket watch that you twist to set the time, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's called 'the crown', I believe. A watch would be quite useless without one.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The crown? Like what sits on top of a monarch's head? That's a very grand name for such a tiny part. But actually...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...if this is a crown... ...I have a feeling I might have seen a monarch around here somewhere with a very bare head!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...If by monarch you mean pocket watch, then I'm quite sure you have!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So this little part of Inspector Gregson's pocket watch was found inside Judge Jigoku's trunk.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's right. Which it cannot possibly be denied is extremely significant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And what do you call it again? This small, round piece of the watch.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The crown. A pocket watch is quite useless without it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's right. The crown. What a very grand name for such a tiny part.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...That's exactly what you said the last time we discussed it, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you think, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I feel sure I know exactly what will fit here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">R-Really?! I was just thinking precisely the same thing!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We're about to see that the little round component... ...is actually part of Inspector Gregson's broken pocket watch!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">R-Really?! I was just thinking precisely that, too!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... A perfect fit!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I knew it!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Alright, perhaps you knew it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'll make a note of this new information at once!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So a small part of Inspector Gregson's pocket watch was found inside Judge Jigoku's trunk...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I believe that could be very significant indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And, um...what do you call it again?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The crown. A pocket watch is quite useless without it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's right. The crown. What a very grand name for such a tiny part.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...That's exactly what you said the last time we discussed it, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Kazuma Asogi... I know you, and I know you wouldn't lie. But still, there's no doubt... ...that you're holding something back. You know more than you're saying!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">During the past thirty minutes while this court was adjourned, all possible efforts were expended... ...but sadly Mr Jigoku's whereabouts could not be ascertained.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">We must accept the unfortunate conclusion that the Reaper has already done the deed.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">There's no sense in wasting any more of the court's time. The prosecution calls for an immediate verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No. The trial cannot end now.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You're a Japanese man, Ryunosuke. You should know when to lay down your sword.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And you should know never to presume when the battle is won.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The court has already been presented with all the evidence and heard all relevant testimony. And there can only be one conclusion: that the accused is guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">All relevant testimony? Far from it. There's still a crucial witness from whom the court is yet to hear a single word of testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">In that case, call your witness to the stand at once, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes, My Lord. ...Tomorrow. ...If possible.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The witness is already on his way and scheduled to arrive tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Who on earth is this crucial witness?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Seishiro Jigoku. The very man allegedly murdered by the Reaper!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">J-Judge Jigoku?! You've found him?!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">But the investigations of every policing resource in the capital suggest that Jigoku is already dead. How in the name of God did you find the man?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He was located in France during the recess. At the Port of Dunkirk... ...thanks to one of Mr Herlock Sholmes's famous deductions.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Herlock Sholmes...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Inspector Gregson almost certainly met with Mr Jigoku on the night of his death. Because along with Prosecutor Asogi, Gregson was on a mission to assassinate the man.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Which means that Seishiro Jigoku is the sole witness... ...who can clarify exactly what happened aboard the SS Grouse on the 31st October!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Well...it would appear that it's too soon to move to adjudication at this point.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... The prosecution concurs. The court must hear Mr Jigoku's testimony. No judgement should be passed until all testimony has been considered.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">......... In that case, I hereby call the end of today's proceedings. Court will reconvene at the same hour tomorrow. ...No objections from either side?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">No objections, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...We live to fight another day...by the skin of our teeth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't find anything out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The witness's last statement...exhibits a fundamental inconsistency!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Not one that any British court would recognise, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...?!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Remember, this is a closed court. Whatever fate befalls you in here, no one outside will ever know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Should I be wondering if I'll make it out of this courtroom alive?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My Lord! As counsel for the defence, I must object to that last statement!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">And as the judge, I must deny your objection. There is no contradiction here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">No contradiction, other than the fact that a Far Eastern lawyer is practising in a British courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Put there by a not-so-far away Lord Chief Justice, if you remember.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That last statement...seemed a little questionable to me. What do you think, My Lord?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I see no inconsistency there. ...Do you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">You could span the Straits of Dover with those wide eyes, Counsel. And be gone from this island forever, I hope.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Do you want me to fill the English Channel with tears?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you have something to say about that, Gina?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gina...?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">...'Ow'd it come to this, eh, boss...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>She's lost in her thoughts about Gregson... I suppose I shouldn't be surprised. I probably shouldn't pursue her too hard unless she really reacts strangely to something.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Let's focus on the testimony, please, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord van Zieks!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Let me guess: is there something about the witness's last statement that troubles me? Is that what you wish to ask?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Y-Yes... Exactly... You're very perceptive.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Whereas you...would appear not to be.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">You really need to learn how to read your fellow man... my Nipponese friend.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Read them...or 'reap' them?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">We've wasted enough time! It's clear to me that any further discussion of this case will be fruitless. Barok van Zieks, I would like to think that however misguided... ...you acted out of a sense of justice nonetheless. Though it pains me to have reached this conclusion...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No! Wait, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">In accordance with the findings of this court, I hereby pronounce the defendant, Barok van Zieks...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">That concludes business. Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba"><thought>Nothing much of note here, I'd say.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It seems we've followed this single strand of reasoning to its unsatisfactory conclusion. Perhaps you're a little out of practice after ten years of absence from brilliance.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well, it's a long time to go without a paradiddle. I confess my feet are a little rusty.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Your feet are the least of your worries. The oxidation has gone to the brain, I fear. Let us take to the dance floor again, with renewed vigour!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Try to stop me! I'm itching to tap out the true answer to this riddle!</line>
</xml>