<xml>
<title>The Stolen Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Get a load of this! Hey, are you listening to me!? You can clean the toilet later! This is important!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*sigh* What are you freaking out about now?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey hee. Today will be the last time you talk to me that way!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We're about to hit the big time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Big time"? And what do you mean by "we"? You don't mean you and me are...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ha! Don't be silly. I'm talking about me and Pearly, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hello. It's a pleasure to see you again, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls! You haven't changed a bit! Wait... What are you doing here anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hey hee. Haven't you heard, Mr. Nick? Here! Take a look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's this...? Some kind of poster?</thought> Kurain Village... Isn't that...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's right. It's our hometown... Pearly and mine, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this about "treasures" from the boonies?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ha ha ha. Very funny. You can laugh all you want... But you'll be singing another tune tonight!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tonight? What about tonight?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">The "Treasures of Kurain" exhibit doesn't actually start until next week, but... ...the promoter sent us some special VIP entry passes!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's why I dressed up extra special today! What do you think, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Heh. Same Maya. Different Day.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This young lady here is Maya Fey... The younger sister of Mia Fey... ...My friend and mentor. I first met her two years ago... I was working on the case surrounding Mia's death, and ever since then...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I've been the one who's been keeping this law office afloat from behind the scenes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually that's just a cover for her true identity... In reality, she's a spirit medium, and a bit of a shady character.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Who are you calling "shady"!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And this little girl is Pearl Fey, but I usually call her "Pearls". She's Maya's cousin and a spirit medium in training herself.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I know I'm a bit young, but I want to help in any way I can, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Kurain Village is the home of the mysterious Kurain Channelling Technique. And Maya here is the daughter of the Kurain School of Channeling's Master. ...I know it sounds ridiculous, but it's no joke. I've seen her power with my own eyes... It's the real thing alright.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Earth to Nick! How long are you going to make two gorgeous women like us wait!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes, Mr. Nick! I can't wait any longer! I want to see the exhibit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sigh* Looks like I don't get a choice here. Might as well head on out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Lordly Tailor"... The city's fanciest and most expensive department store. Treasure Exhibit, huh... I have to admit I'm pretty impressed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>On a family heirloom...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A piece of cloth with a ton of finely-written characters jammed onto it. Probably esoteric knowledge only mediums would know. ...Hmm, let's see... Here's the title in English... "108 Ways to Save Money." ... I'm pretty sure the number has gone up since the last time I saw it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, we're always looking for new ways you know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Being a medium sounds like a rough way of life...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's with this big cushion? It's just lying around, with nothing on it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Well it must be for the greatest treasure of all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Greatest treasure"...? Is there something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Why... Of course there is! Right, Pearly?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! Um, yeah! Of course!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, I'll bet it would really take your breath away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think I remember this old folding screen here... I'm pretty sure it was an important piece of evidence... ...in that murder case that happened in Kurain Village.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">This folding screen is the greatest of all the spirit channeling secrets... The Six Leaf Kurain Sacred Writings folding screen!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If it's so secret, why is it the most prominent thing in the exhibit?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They're just a bunch of old urns... Are these really "treasures", too?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Of course they are! This is a "Treasure Exhibit", isn't it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well yeah, I guess so. ... <thought>So all it takes to be a "treasure" is age? No wonder nobody like museums...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! Mystic Maya, look! I can't believe it! </line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! It's so cute! It's a little diorama of Kurain Village!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, look at that. But somehow, it seems to reek of dreariness.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! Mystic Maya, It's your house! It even says, "Fey Manor" on it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yikes! You're right! I kinda want to add "The Famous" in front of it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't do it, Maya. ...They might get mad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yup. This is a basement warehouse alright...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Th-This place is scary... I feel like a monster could jump out at any time...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't be scared, Pearly! I'll protect you!</line>
<line speaker="???">...Oh... ...Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eeeeeeeek!! A monster! You were right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a security camera. It's trained on the warehouse door.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It's set up to take a picture of anyone that enters or exits the door. An ounce of prevention is worth a pound of cure, they say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This computer... It looks like it's hooked up to the security camera above.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And that means what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The camera is set up to take a photo of anyone that goes in or out of the storeroom... Then the data from the camera gets uploaded to this computer here. That's what.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see... That's some pretty high-tech stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like a part of a big signboard. All I can read on it is the "bur".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aha! I've got it! Maybe it's supposed to say, "Hamburger"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why would anyone write "Hamburger" that big?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Like, maybe for the "World Hamburger Festival" or something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I kinda doubt it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aha! I've got it! Maybe it said, "Spaghetti"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Why are you talking about food? Oh, wait. That's normal for you. Anyway, it says, "bur". There's no way it could be "Spaghetti".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, maybe it was a typo! It might have said, "Spaghetti Festival". What do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK to me... Besides, Spaghetti is the only thing more tangled than your reasoning.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look, a ladder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a "step"-ladder.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So? What's the difference? You need to stop judging things based on narrow-minded cultural assumptions, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Right... sorry. <thought>Why do I feel like we've had this exact same conversation before somewhere...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick, what's that big door over there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like it's the door to the actual storeroom. I can see lots of big boxes and stuff back there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? Let's go in! I wanna take a look!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Oh... I'm sorry! Unauthorized personnel aren't allowed in there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Did you hear that, Nick? We're unauthorized personnel.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why are you telling me that?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mystic Maya! Take a look next to the door! That... That's Mystic Ami, right?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes, that's a statue of the woman who invented the Kurain Channeling Technique, Ami Fey. This statue is on loan from one of the training halls of the Fey branch family. In fact, it just arrived this morning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's that creepy-looking thing she's holding?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't ask me! How should I know...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well, you ARE the future Master, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe so, but this is the first time I've ever seen this statue.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">That "thing" is the Kurain Shichishito. It's a ceremonial sword. It's not a real weapon, so the blade isn't sharp.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Aww, phooey. I wanted to cut something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why are you eyeing me for!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It says "ORGANI".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No it doesn't, Nick! It says, "ORGANIZE"! You just can't see the last two letters.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, well I guess no one else could read it either, because this place is a mess.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. You must feel right at home, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It really has been a long time, hasn't it, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! What's going on!? Who is this woman!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-Why are you spazzing out on me!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What? I just thought it'd be more dramatic if I got all worked up. That's all.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mystic Maya! You shouldn't let him of the hook so easily!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Mr. Wright was there for me when I really needed help. It... It was something that happened 7 months ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You remember, don't you? The "Nickel Samurai" case.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Not really... I was stuck in a dark wine cellar... Did that escape your memory, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">After that, I quit being a manager and started this job.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow, that's tough. I'm sorry, Ms. Andrews. If it wasn't for us...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">No! Don't say that! I'm glad the whole thing happened. Thanks to you and everyone else that was involved, I was able to change my whole life. ...I really am grateful.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm really impressed, Ms. Andrews. Handling a huge exhibition like this must be very tiring.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Well, Lordly Tailor is celebrating their 200th anniversary this year. The works on display in the main exhibition hall are worthy of the finest museums.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Woohoo! Did you hear that, Pearly!? The finest museums!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes, I did! That's really wonderful.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this basement warehouse is pretty well-protected, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...Of course it is. After all, there are some priceless treasures here. The security guards are very highly trained as well...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I owe a great deal of thanks to that badge... ...It's the only reason that I'm still here today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, come on now. That's not true...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I think what Nick means to say is, "It wasn't thanks to the badge, it was thanks to ME!" Tell the truth, Nick! I know that's what you were thinking!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No way, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I wanted to do something nice for you and your friends, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that's why you arranged this exhibit...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I knew that Kurain Village was the hometown of your assistant, Maya. I thought it would be great to let the rest of the world know about it, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... But that's not exactly thanking me, per se, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe, but who'd wanna see an exhibit on the "Treasures of Phoenix Wright"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess I can't argue with that one.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">You've certainly changed since I last saw you 7 months ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Really?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes, you look like you're bulked up a little.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, now that she mentions it... I guess I have gotten a little stronger...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're such a dork, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I've finally managed to put the events of 7 months ago behind me. I really love the work that I'm doing now... Honestly, I owe it all to you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, it was nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">And to this little girl, too.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Th-Thank you for saying so!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... ...I guess I wasn't much of a help, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">N-No, that's not true! You were ALL a big help to me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She shouldn't take it so personally. It's not like she was exactly "free" to help...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... So what about this?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Sorry I can't be of more help, but I really don't have anything to say about that.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I'm sorry, I don't know as many people as I used to. So there really isn't anything I can tell you about that person.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is a giant building just outside the window. It's the Gatewater Hotel, a high-class, luxury hotel. The chain is getting so rich that they brought a whole chunk of the next town over... ...and started building a huge theme park. It's going to be called "Gatewater Land". ...And to think that two years ago, it was just a little hotel for businessmen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An old movie poster. Apparently, this was the first movie that made Mia cry when she saw it, a long time ago. Maya watched it recently, and said she cried all night, too! ...Which, I guess, is why it's back up on the wall. I'll have to check it out one of these days.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Charley. A quite decorative plant. When she was alive, Mia really loved it. She even went so far as to make it our mascot. It must be nice to be a plant, being able to just sit in the sun and photosynthesize...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Nick! No time for daydreaming!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That's right, Mr. Nick! No time for daydreaming!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh man. Until I find that urn, they're not gonna give me a second of peace...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's my desk. I don't get to use it much, so the dust bunnies are starting to mount their assault. Maybe I should wipe them out with a few well-placed swipes of my cleaning rag...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Nick! Are you trying to make me upset!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yeah, Mr. Nick! If you're worried about the cleaning, please leave it up to me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>At least Pearls is good at cleaning. *sigh* Guess I'd better go find that urn...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Difficult-looking legal books stand in a formidable row. They mock me. ...Actually, I've neglected them for so long that they're covered in a layer of dust. I guess I should at least read them once in a while.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! This is no time for reading!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes, Mr. Nick! You can always read later!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I won't be getting any peace and quiet to even read until I find that urn...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Refresh my memory a little... What's this "Sacred Urn"...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah, it was terrible! I was arrested and everything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One year ago... The murder in Kurain Village.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A man was killed during one of Maya's spirit channelings. And this urn wound up being the key piece of evidence that proved her innocence.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... Mr. Nick? Would you mind not telling Maya about that? You promised, remember? You said you wouldn't tell anyone I broke the urn...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh yeah, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now I remember. This urn used to say "AMI" on it... Until Pearls accidentally broke it into a million pieces. She tried to secretly fix it... Let's just say it didn't work out so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Sorry... I'm not so good at arts and crafts... Spelling either...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Anyway, this is how her gluing project turned out. She put the pieces together wrong and now, instead of "AMI", it says, "I AM".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I can't believe no one's noticed this until now, a whole year later.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I can't believe it myself...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, hey! It's my Magatama! So what do you think, Nick? Isn't it neat?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It sure is. Being able to peek into people's minds is definitely a nice advantage.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What? How do you do that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean? You gave me this thing...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, I knew Pearly put some sort of spiritual power into it... But I had no idea that it let you do something as cool as that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Some future leader you are.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Next time you use it, let me know, OK!? I want to see into people's minds, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is this thing really all that valuable? It looks kinda... well... junky, if you ask me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But it's got the soul of Mystic Ami, the founder of our channeling technique!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So how much do you think you could get for it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? Sell the Sacred Urn!? You know, I never thought about that... Hey Pearly... Make a note of that. "Ways to Save Money, Tip 109: Sell treasures whenever possible."</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Whenever possible, check!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Somehow, I think Maya's going to be searching for a buyer for a long time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, even I didn't know this statue existed until a little while ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Didn't Adrian say it's from a Fey branch family's training hall or something?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes, there are actually a lot of training halls scattered all over the country. Hidden away deep in desolate mountains...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why does it always have to be "desolate" mountains...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're not very photogenic, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I guess that's the end of that conversation!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">S-Sis... *sniffle* I really miss her...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Was Mystic Mia... Was she a really good lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, she was awesome! She taught Nick everything he knows.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You should train hard and try to make her proud, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, I'll do my best.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You can join me on my next trip to a freezing waterfall!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I hate to break it to her, but I don't think being frozen to the bone helps in court...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm going to have to really buckle down and get serious.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, you're the future Master of the Kurain Channeling Technique, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah... That, and I have to play the part of big sister, too. For Pearly... and you, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wha-?? Do I look like I was born yesterday!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pearly is such a cutie, isn't she Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And she's smart too, just like yours truly! She's got quite a future ahead of her! I bet she could be President some day! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A President that can channel past Presidents... Hmm... That just might come in handy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">She certainly seems grateful to you, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, she was in a pretty tight spot during that terrible ordeal. Actually, I'm grateful to her, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... It sounds like you're not telling me something. I'm going to take a good look at the case file next chance I get...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what do you think about this?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... What about it, Pearly?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm not certain. What do you think, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe three heads aren't better than one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what do you think about this person?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... What do you think, Pearly?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm not certain. What do you think, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think the saying I'm looking for is, "never seen them before in my life"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Umm, Mr. Detective Dick! Can you tell us about what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, you're trying to remember my name! Atta girl! ...Um, just... It's "Gumshoe", OK? Anyway, the thief stole something called the "Sacred Urn..."</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I know about that.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh. W-Well, the criminal's name is Mask☆DeMasque...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I know about that, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Detective, can't you tell us something other than that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">W-Well... I guess I sorta kinda owe you guys... in a way... The crime occurred last night at around 1:30 in the morning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How exactly do you know that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We got an emergency phone call from a guard at the scene of crime, pal. He said, "The urn was just stolen!"</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The scene of the crime... You mean here, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wrong. That urn was being kept under careful guard in the basement warehouse.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Basement warehouse, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Umm, so who was guarding the basement warehouse...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That guy! It's all his fault that the thief got away, pal! He solves one case and gets a swelled head, thinking that he's an Ace Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A-Ace Detective...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Detective Gumshoe, about this Mask☆DeMasque... Is he famous?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaaat!? You're joking, right Nick? Mask☆DeMasque is the hottest thing since sliced bread!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sometimes he appears as a museum guard! Sometimes he appears as a big brown bear known to surprise unsuspecting victims. But underneath those disguises is... the true Mask☆DeMasque!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...So he's some kind of master of disguise, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And he only goes after the finest work of art, pal. Last night was his 5th heist! If Lordly Tailor had only cooperated, I could have caught him this time...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? Then you knew he was planning on stealing the Sacred Urn!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course I did! The guy always sends his calling card before he steals something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Calling card, huh... They mentioned that on TV...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So why do you call him an "Ace Detective" anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's what he calls himself, pal... I didn't make it up.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So? What's he like?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, like I told you, Mask☆DeMasque has made five heists so far. On the 4th heist, Mr. Ace Detective managed to get the stolen treasure back.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow, that is impressive! All by himself!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. I gotta admit it, pal. Maybe he really is as good as he says. Every time the thief sends one of his calling cards, we send our men on a stakeout... But none of us has ever gotten so much as a glimpse of the guy...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But Mr. Ace Detective was able to retrieve the stolen treasure from the thief...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Anyway, he's at the scene of crime right now, looking for clues.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So he's down in the basement warehouse, huh...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what's this "calling card"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Here it is. But don't show it to anyone! It's top-secret, OK, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this mark on the front?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's Mask☆DeMasque's signature emblem, pal. You could say it's his "mark". All of his calling cards have got it on them.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They didn't mention THAT on the news flash.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We're withholding that detail from the public for "operational reasons"... The only way we can tell if a calling card is real or not is by this emblem.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...That makes sense. When you get famous, there are always imitators.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick, if you work a little harder, maybe you can have your own copycats someday!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, uh, thanks... I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here, take a look at my attorney's badge.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Are you still showing that cheap little thing off? A real man keeps his mouth shut... and carries a suave police badge, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...To be honest, pal, there's something that bugs me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">All the other items that were stolen by Mask☆DeMasque were ones even I had heard of. They were all world-famous treasures. The "Tear of Emanon" or the "Crown of Bongora"...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The "Sacred Urn of Kurain" is famous, too! ...Right, Pearly!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Of course! Everyone in Kurain Village knows about it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like we've got an unpredictable thief on our hands...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Remember! Don't tell anyone about that emblem. OK, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Does the thief ever send these to the police?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No, always to the victims. Up until now, the victims have always come to us looking for help though.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...That's not what happened this time, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You got that right, pal. Listen up! If you guys ever get one of these calling cards... ...I want you to come to us right away! Got me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, sure.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Pretty goofy-looking face, if you ask me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you doing carrying that around with you anyway? It's not like we ever need it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She has got a point...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! That's Ms. Mia Fey! She was a truly beautiful person, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? You knew her? You knew my sis?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure. Everybody in the police force knew her. ...We all lost a great friend that day...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Scruffy Detective...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-I just got something in my eye...! ...I'm not crying!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I've been on this guy's tail ever since his first heist, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, you're doing a really great job. I can see.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Oof! Listen pal, if you wanna jump high, first you gotta crouch down, right? I'm a little frustrated now, but it'll make it that much sweeter when I catch him! ...Anyway, that's what I keep telling myself every day.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Well good luck, Mr. Detective Dick! I believe in you!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aww, ain't you sweet. You're the only one that's ever said that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...The only one? That's kinda sad if you think about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm, what about this...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Sorry, pal. I didn't get much sleep last night and my brain's not really working right.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Somehow I don't think sleep would really fix the problem.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, keep it down. He might have really good hearing for all you know, and might get mad if he heard.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ummm... I can hear everything you are saying, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm, what about this person...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Sorry, pal. I didn't get much sleep last night and my brain's not really working right.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Somehow I don't think sleep would really fix the problem.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, keep it down. He might have really good hearing for all you know, and might get mad if he heard.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ummm... I can hear everything you are saying, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? What the heck does THAT mean...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Game"? Why does the phrase "one short of a baker's dozen" come to mind with this guy?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Tsk! Sir Lawyer! Please refrain from such crude behavior.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">This criminal is an artist! The crime scene is the canvas upon which he paints! Only I, Ace Detective Atmey, have an eye which is educated enough to read the signs!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Could you translate that for me, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think he pretty much said, "Don't touch anything amateurs!"</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">If there's something you wish to know about, you have but to ask Atmey! ...I know everything there is to know about my rival, Mask☆DeMasque.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What do I do now...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Does he have any top-secret information? Stuff that only a real crime buff would know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll think about what to ask while I listen to what Mr. Ace Detective has to say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... So are you really as famous as you say?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Of course! For a lawyer, you have a rather shocking lack of knowledge about the world. I had no idea anyone was left in this city that had not heard of me! Look at me! I am Mask☆DeMasque's arch-enemy, the Ace Detective Luke Atmey! At this moment, there are two mighty figures which loom large over this grand city! One embodies the nefarious forces of darkness. The other the angelic cherubs of light!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Boy, now I'm really lost. What is he saying, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">I have been personally on the heels of this villain since his first crime. After learning this criminal's patterns, I thwarted his very latest loathsome larceny! I even returned the target of his tyranny, the "Portrait of Mejeena" to the crime scene! And I did it all by myself! I took it back from Mask☆DeMasque... With my brawny mind and my brilliant muscles!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! They mentioned it on the news, in the "Great People of the Town" segment. They said that the museum gave you an incredible jewel as a reward!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...Well, compared to the treasure that I retrieved for them, it's not much.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So... in the end, the only thing that makes you great is your own self-praise...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! Tell us what you know about Mask☆DeMasque! ...And keep it simple, please!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Like about how I have devoted my life to thwarting his dastardly deeds? Last night, here in the bowls of this store, we were locked in a most glorious battle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... ...Huh!? Hang on a second! You were here last night? Here? In Lordly Tailor!?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Naturally! Wherever DeMasque goes, you will find Atmey laying his elegant traps.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Elegant traps? More like DeMasque out-eleganced you and made a beautiful getaway.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">But this time, I allowed him to escape with the illusion of victory.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if I should ask him about what happened last night in more detail...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Can you tell us exactly what happened here last night?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">But of course. After all, I always say there should be no secrets between "aces".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Flattery will get you nowhere, Pinocchio...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">I first received the request for my services 20 days ago. And it was 10 days ago that we received Mask☆DeMasque's calling card...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? You were hired BEFORE the calling card even arrived?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Yes. You see, the person who hired me is quite rigorous and thorough.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's Adrian for you...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">A mere 10 days after hiring me, her worst premonitions were realized!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A calling card arrived, right?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Yes! So, Ace Detective that I am, I set a trap for the thief right in the warehouse. And waited for him... alone.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Alone? ...But why? Why didn't you go to the police for help?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Ridiculous! Why would I seek help from such a singularly useless group of nincompoops?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You've got a lot of nerve. After all, it was you that let DeMasque get away.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">I always operate alone and concealed. Out of the sight of others.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...? "Corn Sealed"...?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Precisely! Even the guards on duty here were unaware of my presence. "To fool your enemies, first you must fool your friends." It's my own original proverb!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Anyway, back to what happened last night...</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">As I was saying, I hid here in the warehouse and waited for the thief to arrive. But I swear to you... Not a solitary soul came through that entrance! Nevertheless... The Sacred Urn disappeared!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But that's impossible! How could it just disappear!?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">"How?" you ask? Don't be ridiculous, Sir Lawyer. If I knew the answer to that question, I wouldn't be here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>For someone who seriously messed up his own stakeout, he's rather full of himself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So you're saying that even though on [sic] one came through those doors last night... ...our precious urn still somehow vanished from under your nose?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Th-That's just not possible!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Do not fear, young lady. I promise I shall retrieve your urn!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Thank you, Detective Atmey! I'm counting on you!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">The final round between Detective Luke Atmey and Mask☆DeMasque is set to begin.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Still, there's something funny about this guy...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, but don't forget he managed to retrieve the treasure from the last heist.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Yes, I even have a video that details my role in the whole affair. I recorded it directly from the news on TV. Can I interest you in a copy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...No thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mask☆DeMasque's calling card... It's got his emblem printed on it, right?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...Quite impressive! But I would expect nothing less from my arch-rival! I'm surprised to see you in possession of such a top-secret piece of information.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, we've got an Ace Lawyer, an Ace Spirit Medium and an Ace Cousin-Apprentice here.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Yes, indeed... I think I could learn to like you, my fellow ace professionals!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't know if I really want this guy to like us... ever.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's pretty amazing the way you were able to tell what I do for a living.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Oh, it's elementary, my dear Wright, elementary. If you're really interested, the first clue was the hair. ...It points backward. It shows you're prepared to take on an attack. Such as from a criminal, for example. From your clothes, I knew you weren't a policeman, so I deduced you were a lawyer. After a combination of cold logic and intuition... Zvarri! Only the truth remains.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, impressive...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Or maybe he just took a look at the attorney's badge on your lapel, genius.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">This woman... She is a true beauty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You don't say.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">I would be honored if you would introduce her to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">I assure you, Sir Lawyer, that my interest is strictly professional!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eww, this guy's even creepier than I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">I assure you, my dear, all Ace Detectives are perfect gentlemen!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... So how did you know I was a spirit medium?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Oh, that was child's play. First, your hair. It's not of the type one sees every day. Both rare and enchanting... Almost... otherworldly. I thought it likely that you were either a fortune teller or a spirit medium. But I didn't quite detect the wisdom one usually sees in a fortune teller... And so... Zvarri! That left only one possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, they also have a bio about me on the Treasure Exhibit Poster...</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">As for this child... Zvarri! Elementary school student.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow! That's right!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">I can also see that you will be a middle-school student within the next few years!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Th-That's incredible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No doubt about it. This guy is good!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Now you can see how I have earned my reputation as an Ace Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Ah, the charming young lady responsible for security, Ms. Adrian Andrews.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? You know her?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Yes, well I should... She was the person who hired me for this job. A very intelligent woman. After all, she hired Detective Luke Atmey, did she not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I'm not entirely convinced that was an intelligent move on her part.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...Oh, him. Yes, well I saw him earlier. That wretched detective has let the thief slip through his fingers every single time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wretched, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...Now that I think about it, I wonder if they aren't working together.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">If you ask me, Luke Atmey, I believe the two of them are "co-conspirators".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If Detective Gumshoe heard that, he'd probably cry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He is a surprisingly sensitive guy...</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">This will surely be Mask☆DeMasque's final heist! Last time I came close and managed to retrieve the stolen treasure! Mark my words, this criminal of humanity will be found guilty in due time! And then I, Luke Atmey, Ace Detective, will dance with joy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have no clue what you're blabbering about... But I guess I'll find out soon.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">This person is... Zvarri! A great Ace Detective! Am I correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, but I was the one asking you...</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">This photo simply isn't enough information. I'm afraid I can't be absolutely certain... But the intelligence in those eyes indicates a man of deep wisdom and insight.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Stop messing around, Nick, and just ask him already!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But this guy is scary.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...I'm sorry I can't be more helpful. But I have no interest save that of finding evidence against my arch-rival!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nah, it's OK. Nick is just a bit of a piddling evidence hog. That's his defense style.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">A "piddling evidence hog", you say? In that case, I'd simply be wasting my breath!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, I guess you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Maya. Why couldn't you have said I was a "rival", and not a "piddling evidence hog"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well, I'm not sure would say that exact--</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's right! We're going to find the Sacred Urn no matter what we have to do!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...Excellent. I will trust you. I permit you to take a look around while I investigate elsewhere. If, perchance, you should discover something of value, return then to my office... To my office of Earthly Delights, the "Atmey Detective Agency"!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Of-Office of Earthly D-Delights...?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Well then Sir Lawyer, if you'll excuse me, I have much to do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait a minute...!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">He's gone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't like the idea of doing this guy's work for him.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, Nick. Don't worry about it. It's no big deal. Let's hurry up and investigate before he changes his mind!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I wanna go to his office, too! Take me with you, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a security camera. It's trained on the big door to the storeroom. It's set up to take a photo of anyone that goes in or out.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">A "se-kure-ity" camera...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, go stand in front of that door and it'll snap your photo too, Pearly.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Umm... Mystic Maya... Do you think I should smile?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nah. It's for criminals, so I think you should make a really scary face!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">L-Like this...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Pearly, do you know what this is? It's a computer!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">A "kom-pu-ter"...? Oh! I've heard of those! It has such a cute name!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like this computer is for storing the data from the security camera. When someone comes in or out of the warehouse, the camera takes a photo of them.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It's probably the "trap" that the detective set up.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's see if we can find last night's data on this thing. We might even find a photo of Mask☆DeMasque!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, let see here... <thought>Man, I really stink at working these things...</thought> ...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What's wrong, Mr. Nick? You're sweating an awful lot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I don't know how to pull up the photos...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I had no idea you were so pathetic with high-tech stuff, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, well I managed to print out the camera data anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess you have to learn to crawl before you can walk, right, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, sure... Anyway, it looks like the camera only went off once last night.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Pearly, do you know what this is? It's a computer!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">A "kom-pu-ter"...? Oh! I've heard of those! It has such a cute name!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like this computer is for storing the data from the security camera. When someone comes in or out of the warehouse, the camera takes a photo of them.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It's probably the "trap" that the detective set up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That pathetic-looking wooden box...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ahh!! That's the box that had the Sacred Urn on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't touch it! There may be clues to the thief's identity on there!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Grr... I worked so hard to make that box!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!? You MADE that poor excuse for a box, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's that supposed to mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That urn has always been on its stand in the Winding Way of Fey Manor. So there was no box suitable for it, Mr. Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And I-I was so proud of it... *sniffle sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Maya. Maybe it'd have been better if Mask☆DeMasque had taken the box, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, this is awesome. What did Ms. Andrews say it was called again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Shichishito". It's literally "7 Branch Sword" in Japanese. Or so says Ms. Andrews. Whoa... It's pretty heavy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"One hit, seven times the fun!" Pretty catchy, huh? I bet it'd sell like hotcakes!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, there's something about it that bothers me...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! You're really firing on all cylinders today, Pearly!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">This sword... Wasn't Mystic Ami holding it last night?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">And other thing... The sword wasn't bent last night like it is now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You're right...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Awesome, Pearly! I wouldn't expect any less from my little Ace Apprentice!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The sword is bent, so that must mean... Last night, someone "used it" somehow...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aha. I just thought of something! Maybe Detective Atmey smashed Mask☆DeMasque with it. Like this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">YEOOOOOUCCCH!! WHAT THE HECK!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you think, Pearly?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I think it's even more bent than it was before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh man... My head... MY HAIR!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick, what's that big door over there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like it's the door to the actual storeroom. I can see lots of big boxes and stuff back there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess that's where they were keeping the Sacred Urn.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Remember, Maya. Ms. Andrews said we're not allowed in there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look what you did, Nick! You spilled paint over here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I didn't do that!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well it wasn't here last night. I would have noticed a color this outrageous.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But this paint has already dried up.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well then, you should have cleaned it up before it dried, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Paint doesn't dry that fast! Besides, I told you it wasn't me! <thought>It looks like it's been several days since it was spilt.</thought> Hey, look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's some kind of shape left in the bottom left side of this stain.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? ...You're right. I wonder what it could be...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This statue of Mystic Ami is sooo cool. I want a gold statue of myself! We could put it in the office!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! It's WRIGHT &amp; Co.! How about a gold statue of ME?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, Mr. Nick? I'm sorry, but I noticed something strange...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What is it, Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">The statue of Mystic Ami... Was this where it was last night?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm pretty sure it was closer to the door...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, I think you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Great job, Pearly! I wouldn't expect anything less from my Ace Cousin!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So the statue was moved on the night of the crime...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, Nick! Your cell phone's ringing!</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hello, Phoenix Wright here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho! It's me. Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gumshoe! What is it? What's so funny!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'll tell you what's funny, pal! I finally beat him! I beat Mr. Ace Detective! Finally! This underdog is the alpha dog today! That stuck-up detective's met his match! Yup! I finally caught him! Lock, stock and barrel! There's no escape for him!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You "caught him"? ...Are you saying...? You... You captured Mask☆DeMasque!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Bingoooo! Well... Actually, he surrendered... ...But I still got him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mask☆DeMasque surrendered?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That's great! So when can we come and pick up the Sacred Urn?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, ahh, well ya see... I was gonna tell you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What...? Something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Do you think you can swing by the detention center sometime?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detention center...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He wants to talk to you... Mask☆DeMasque, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaaat!? He wants to talk to Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'll be waiting for you, pal. So get over here soon.</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The detention center, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is a detective agency? Looks like more like the set of some B-grade horror movie.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-Hello? Is anyone here...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like nobody's home.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmph. What a waste of time. Hey! I know! Let's take that framed picture back with us as a memento!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't you dare, Maya! <thought>Guess we'll have to try back later...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick. What's this thing here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's called a "gramophone". In the old days, people used them to listen to music.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You can't be serious! I think it's probably for purifying the air or something. I'll bet you 50 cents! Come on, what do you say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Forget it. You never pay up when you lose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What a creepy painting. It's like he's looking right at me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe we should put up a big portrait of you in the office, Nick! I can even paint it for you. Maybe you can pose while cleaning the toilet?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I think I'd prefer something a bit more dignified.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa! It's a huge hearth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a fireplace.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So? What's the difference? You need to stop judging things based on narrow-minded cultural assumptions, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Right... sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's one impressive bookshelf filled with some very impressive books!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"My Life as an Ace Detective: Unabridged Edition" by Luke Atmey, Ace Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, he's even got one of those ships in a bottle thingies.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! Would you look at that! There's a little Luke Atmey doll at the helm! How cute!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a microscope here, too. I wonder if he was researching something. The glass slides have different names on them.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This one says... "Atmey Virus", ...Hmm. This guy is just dying to make a name for himself, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's getting kind of irritating, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This desk is literally covered with all sorts of chemistry equipment.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I just love chemistry! Say, Nick, I bet you didn't know this, but... Water is made up of carbon and hydrogen!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, no. Not carbon! Oxygen! Oxygen and hydrogen!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh? Well, there are always alternative theories, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If by "alternative theories" you mean the ones you make up inside that head of yours.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal! Welcome to the detention center!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're sure in a happy mood, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup. After all, we got Mask☆DeMasq--</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right, but... Um... So where's the Sacred Urn?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, Sorry about that, pal... I guess I didn't really think about it before... But you're the "victim" in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I guess I should let you guys hear the story straight from the horse's mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, he's right, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He is?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If you think about it reeeeal hard, we are the victims!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... I guess so... In a way...</line>
<line speaker="???">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm so used to thinking of the victim as a dead person 'cause we're always on murder cases.</line>
<line speaker="???">Ex-Excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But anyway! I have to get the Sacred Urn back!</line>
<line speaker="???">Pleeeeease! Don't just ignore meeeeee! ...Err.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Um, who are you?</line>
<line speaker="???">...I, err, umm. I-I-I... I-I'm Ma-Ma-Ma... Mask☆DeMasque...? ...O-OK?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Hey, Nick... Doesn't he look kind of... Well, gangly?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">I'm Ron DeLite... Th-The famous Mask☆DeMasque.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I don't think this guy could punch his way out of a wet paper bag.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Smile, you're on candid camera.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitors the visitor's room. He looks nervous being this close to an alleged thief.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you're the Masque DeMask guy?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Y-Yes! You bet! ... No... Err, that's wrong. You see... it's complicated. Sort of yes, and sort of no. If you know what I mean</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hm? What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Well when I say "wrong", what I really mean to say is that it's "not right", per se. You see it's not spelled "Masque DeMask", it's actually "Mask☆DeMasque"...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...What's with this guy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, he's a timid little weakling, we know that much.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">D-Don't do that... Don't look at me like that! I don't need your pityyyyy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And a major crybaby, too.</thought> So... Why did you give yourself up?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Well, you see... It's because... Well...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I know why! It's because you stole such a priceless treasure! And now you're overwhelmed with guilt. Am I right!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Priceless treasure"? That broken old urn...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">Umm... I have a little favor to ask...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Could you... go and talk to Dessie?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...D-Dessie?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look, we really want our urn back, so where is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">I'm sorry! I'll give it back! I really will! ...Err, maybe not. No, I can't... I can't make promises I can't keep... I'll just end up hurting people</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, Mr. Nick...? I couldn't hear what he just said... Especially the last part.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Mr. DeMasque? Do you think you could speak up a little?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Y-Y-Y-Yes, sir! I will... I promise! ...Err, maybe not. You see, I'm already speaking in my normal voice, so I really can't do anything</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mr. DeMasque? About the urn...</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Oh! Yes! The urn! Right away! ...Err, actually no. I wouldn't mind telling you, but actually I'm afraid you wouldn't believe me anyway</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Enough already! Just tell it to us straight!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Please... Please don't yell at meeee! *huff huff huff* I... I... I'm so sorry... That urn... I... I-I lost it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-Wha-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So who is this Dessie person?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">...! Pleeeease don't talk about my wife like that!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...I-I guess she must be his wife...</line>
<line speaker="Ron">*huff huff huff* I'm sorry! The truth is... It was my life that told me to have you all come here... Um... Do you think you could go and visit her at my hideout?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H... Hideout?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! What does he mean by "hideout"...?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Oh, sorry. Naturally, I meant to say my "secret base".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Secret Base?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Well, my apartment actually. Palazzo Pelpepe, 3rd floor...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's go have a look, Nick! To Mask☆DeMasque's hideout!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something tells me she just likes the sound of the word "hideout".</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What did you just say? Did you say you "lost it"?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Yes... Er, no. Umm... Maybe so. I mean, yes, I lost it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-What do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Well, you know... I lost it, like I said... These things just happen... You're on the train and you get distracted and you forgot your bag. You know...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? You forgot our Sacred Urn on a train!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a minute! You went on the train dressed like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">N-No! I... I... I was just speaking hypothetically, that's all. A-Anyway... I'm sooooorry! I just lost it somewhere! I don't know where!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>This guy's story is more surreal than a Dali painting.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Are you really sure this creep is Mask☆DeMasque?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, don't call him a "creep". <thought>Although I do have to admit, I understand your doubts about this guy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">I'm really sorry I caused so much trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If you're so sorry, then you shouldn't have stolen it in the first place!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">B-But... The only thing I did wrong was lose it! ...Err, that's not right. I was wrong either way. I'm sure the owners of the other treasures fell the same</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...He sure seems sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Who would have imagined that such a famous thief would have such a pure heart...</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Oh! That's Mask☆DeMasque's calling card! Pretty nice-looking, huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He looks so happy...</line>
<line speaker="Ron">I'm not very good at writing, you see... So I bought a book called "How to Write Business Letters" and studied hard!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I guess you could call thievery a type of business...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">Ever since I was a little boy, I've always been interested in mysterious masked men!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that's what you wanted to be when you grew up?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Yes! ...Err, no. Sort of, but not exactly... I never imagined I'd feel as bad as I do now about the treasures being stolen...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...People sure can be complicated, can't they.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">H-Him...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know him? He claims to be your arch-enemy and rival.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Th-That person... He... He's not my arch-enemy OR my rival! ...Well, actually, no. Now that I think about it, the terms arch-enemy and rival are the same thing</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They ARE rivals! Only people who have it out for each other would disagree like this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think about this?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Hmm... I don't really think I can help you with that. Err, no, that's not it... Well... The thing is... I don't really know if I can say one way or the other</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I didn't really catch that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry, you didn't miss anything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Wow, check this place out!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No doubt about it, this is Mask☆DeMasque's hideout alright.</line>
<line speaker="???">Who is it? Is that you, Ronnie? Huh? Who are you people?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Err, umm... Are you Desirée DeLite?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">That's right. I'm Desirée. ...Ah! Oh! You must be the lawyer... and the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, that's us. Your husband told us that you wanted us to stop by.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm Maya Fey, and this is Phoenix Wright, attorney at law.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">"Nicky boy" and Maya, huh? I can't tell you how grateful I am that you decided to help my Ronnie.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, um... Aha ha... You're welcome.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Did she really call me "Nicky boy"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, that's so cute! It's called a hot air balloon, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Wow! There's no fooling you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I want to make my own balloon now! I'll even let you ride in it, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That emblem on the balloon is supposed to be top-secret. That's proof enough that Ron DeLite really is Mask☆DeMasque. I'd better not tell Maya. She gets kinda... scary when it comes to "celebrities"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a whole bunch of stuff piled up over here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Duck and cover! It-It's a missile! Did you know there's d-dynamite in missiles!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But they're not heavy enough to be real... Oh wait. They're just really well-made toys.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Did the police even investigate this place...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Look on top of the chair!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like an envelope... And a letter.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, don't just stand there! Come on, let's read it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, you know we shouldn't do that!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you talking about? That letter could be an important clue!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No way. You can't just go reading a private letter because you feel like it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Hmph! It's not just because I "feel like it". It really could be important!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I was sure it was a clue, I guess I wouldn't mind...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a bunch of cheap costume pieces arranged inside a nice frame.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">L-Look, Nick! It's a fake beard!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's also a mask made out of cardboard...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Try on this fake beard! Come on! Try it on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Hey! Cut it out...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now put on the mask! ... Aha ha ha ha ha ha! It's Phoenix☆DeMasque! Let's borrow it for a while.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No way! I'm not stealing from a thief! I have enough bad karma as is!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmmm... This thing looks vaguely familiar.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I know! It's a fishbowl! Well, an upside-down one, anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think it's a helmet. ...An alien helmet.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And that looks like a tape recorder or something next to it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think it's a transceiver. ...An alien transceiver.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... Do you think maybe you could act like a grown-up for a little bit?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Getting lectured by Maya to be more of an adult. That's a new low...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's Mask☆DeMasque!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a tape recorder hanging from his neck.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let me see that!</line>
<line speaker="DeMasque">Aha ha ha ha ha ha ha... I'll be taking this crown now! Better luck next time, gentlemen! Aha ha ha ha ha ha ha...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... I don't get it... What's this supposed to be, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! It-It's a torpedo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It's hard to believe, but it sure looks real.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Where could he have picked up something like this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please don't say that torpedoes are things people just leave lying around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are a bunch of books lying here. They're all romantic-sounding novels about famous heists and fantastic thieves.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Look at all the bookmarks and notes stuck into them!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see here... "Note: Must remember this thief's way of laughing. Very useful." "Note: A calling card is an important part of any good thief's modus operandi!"</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wow, Ron really studied his stuff!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm, about your husband...</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Hee hee, isn't he cutest? A bit weak sometimes though...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">..."A bit"?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">By the way, did you know they mentioned Maya on TV?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">They said you own the urn and that you're doing some shady training at a law office now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Remind me not to watch that channel's news program.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">After I saw that, I thought it might be a good idea to meet the lawyer they mentioned.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I see.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">My Ronnie... He has a powerful imagination and gets deluded easily. He kept insisting he was going to surrender to the police. I didn't know what to do! "It was me! I stole that urn!" he kept saying! As if it was even possible!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh...? B-But... Are you saying he didn't?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Ha ha ha. Of course he didn't! Why would my Ronnie ever do something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-Well, you know... It's a p-priceless treasure! And-And he's... You know...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Is it possible his own wife doesn't know his secret identity?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Me? I'm the kind of woman that needs excitement in her life!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh... Excitement, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Yes. I'm at my happiest when I'm racing along with my bike going at full throttle. Riding a motorcycle is like putting your life on the line. You know what I mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I think that depends on how you ride it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">I'm the type that can't stand living a boring, dreary old life with no action.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No offense, but your husband, Ron, doesn't exactly look like the risk-taking type himself.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">You're right about that. He's definitely not one for thrills and danger. But I do have to say that he makes up for it in other ways.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Other ways...?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Yes, money... Ronnie is incredibly rich... And super generous. He bought me a bike that's so fast it would make our head spin. And shopping? I like to shop so much it makes Ron's head spin. The other day, it actually happened. His head actually started to spin.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Man, talk about a high maintenance wife...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So where does Mr. DeLite get all this money from?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Ronnie is a security guard. They put their lives on the line, right? So they get paid tons of money in return. Tons of it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's a security guard...? I think it's my turn for my head to spin...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you tell us about what happened last night?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Hmm, what time did that incident take place again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What time was it again, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, according to Detective Gumshoe, it was around 1:30 in the morning.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Ah, last night was horrible. I got pulled over!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">P-Pulled over?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Yes... I always do my best flying at night!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H... Hideout?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">"Flying"...? Um, you're talking about your motorcycle, right?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Yes. Anyway, last night I got pulled over. By a policeman. I can't believe he caught up to me! It was a great chase, let me tell you! When he finally caught me, the poor man was as white as a sheet. It was about three in the morning when I finally got home.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like she's got an airtight alibi...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, what about Mr. DeLite?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">I don't really know... We weren't together at that time of the night. But when I got home, he was already fast asleep.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So basically he's got no alibi...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... When did Ron first become Mask☆DeMasque?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">What are you talking about? He's not Mask☆DeMasque!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? But... W-Wait a second! Look around at this room! This place is obviously Mask☆DeMasque's hideout...</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">No no, you're totally wrong. A real thief's hideout wouldn't look like this! It's because Ronnie is so timid himself that he looks up to heroic figures.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Heroic figures? But Mask☆DeMasque is a bad guy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So he's "deluded", huh... Could that really be true?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Anyway, if he really had stolen the urn, wouldn't he still have it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well, I suppose so...</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Then why don't you ask him if he has the urn or not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She has a point. Mr. DeLite isn't exactly the criminal type... But something about Ron's behavior bothers me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe it's true... Maybe Mr. DeLite isn't Mask☆DeMasque after all.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Ooh! That's so mysterious looking... I love old stuff like this!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really!? That's one of our most treasured possessions! There's going to be a whole exhibit at Lordly Tailor with these types of things!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya looks so happy. She's lit up like a 1,000 watt bulb.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Terrific! You can count on Ronnie and me to be there! Sounds like fun!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh! ...Oh, err, yeah... Ha ha ha...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oops, looks like that light bulb is starting to flicker.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm, so what do you know about this...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No! You can't show her that, Nick! That emblem is top-secret! Don't you remember!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Doh! Oops, sorry about that. <thought>But the way she just said "top-secret" was a worse giveaway than what I did...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Ooh! When I hear the word "top-secret", it just piques my interest like nothing else!</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Could you please give that to my Ronnie? The contents are very important.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sigh* Back to the detention center I go...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">So, Nicky boy, you're a lawyer, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">How do you like it? I bet it's SO exciting!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, sometimes. Actually, a little too exciting at times.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Oooh! I just love a good thrill. Hmm... Nicky boy... It sounds like you have it so nice...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Um... This is starting to get awkward.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">That's really amazing! A "Master" at your age!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh no, you've got it wrong. It's my mother that's the current Master!</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Oh, I see... So what exactly is she the master of anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, you see, it's li-</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't say it, Maya. If you say "spirit channeling", she'll laugh.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ouch... That hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Um, Ms. DeLite. You must know, right? About your husband and Mask☆DeMasque...</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Mask☆DeMasque? Of course. I know all about it. My husband is his biggest fan.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup... Wha...? ...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-Biggest fan?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Yes, and Ronnie can be pretty delusional sometimes. That's how this whole misunderstanding happened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait a minute! Did you say "delusional"!?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Yes, that's right. I just don't know what I'm going to do with him... You see, Ronnie actually believes that HE is Mask☆DeMasque!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">WH-WHAAAAT!? What are you talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">I know he doesn't look it... But he can really get things done when he puts his mind to it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? So when exactly does he put his mind to it?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">...Well. Not very often, I admit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What exactly does Ms. DeLite see in her husband anyway?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, you must've really seen skyrockets when you first met to love him so much!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Skyrockets...? I didn't know people still used that word.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">As long as I've got my motorcycle and my Ronnie, I'm happy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! That's so sweet!</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Oh, that plus a little excitement and a little shopping money! ...THEN I'm happy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now she's starting to sound a bit greedy... Don't you think, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, but would you take a look at this...?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Oh, I'm sorry... I haven't the faintest idea. I guess I just don't get out enough.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">I know I may seem like a "bad girl" on the outside... But the one thing I won't stand for is illegal activity.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I had the feeling you didn't! You're tough... But I can tell you've got a good heart.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Somebody framed my poor Ronnie, I just know it. Umm... Could you give this to Ronnie for me?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A letter?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Yes, for Ronnie. I want him to fight back.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ms. DeLite... OK, you've got it! Just relax and leave it all to us!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">That's my lovely wife! Isn't she beautiful?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, she sure is...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">... *glare*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoo boy. The one topic I didn't want to get into in front of Pearls...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">But... Dessie doesn't approve of my... "interests". So I'm afraid she doesn't like me anymore... What should I do? If I want to win her back, I'm really going to have to be super honest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh boy. he's gone back into his own little world again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Oh, that's right! Here. This is from your wife.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Oh? From Dessie!? Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">"My dear Ronnie, how are you? I'm doing fine..." ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's clutching onto that letter so hard, the ink is going to be squeezed out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">He looks so happy...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You should write a letter to Mystic Maya too, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">In the letter that Dessie wrote, she said... "Ask this guy to be your lawyer!"</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Err, umm... I know this would be asking a lot, but... Could you please take my case? My trial starts tomorrow...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, hang on a second! He can't be your lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you mean, "why not"!? We're the victims in this case, right!? Victims of this DeMasque guy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, yeah... But according to Desirée, he didn't do it...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">She said, "Poor man, he's deluded himself into thinking he did it." Right, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on! She could be lying to protect her husband!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well, that's true. ...Err, no actually not. Actually it's hard to say <thought>...Oh no, it's spreading!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">Oh, please! I'll give you the treasure of your choice in return...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... What should I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well, Mr. DeLite, I've decided to give it a try. I'll defend you.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Really? You will?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! What're you doing, Nick!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">He... He's a thief! You can't trust him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, he may be a thief... But I think there's more to this case than meets the eye.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't do it, Nick! He's a thief!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! I agree with Mystic Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I admit something about this guy stinks like last week's sushi. I guess I really should say no. But... If I do that, this poor guy will have nobody on his side!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well, Mr. DeLite, I've decided to take your case.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Really? You will?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-Mr. Nick...! I-I was wrong about you... I shouldn't have trusted you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Pearls...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I can't believe you'd defend this person after what he did to Mystic Maya...! I-I... I'll never forgive you... EVER! WAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHH!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">P-! Pearly...! Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is going to be ugly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-I'll go after her!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Umm... Sorry about that. I didn't mean to cause any trouble...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... You couldn't have known she'd react like that. <thought>I guess I might as well start investigating...</thought> Oh, Maya... Where's Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She said she's going back to the office. Go check in on her later, would you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what about you...? Are you OK with me taking Mr. DeLite's case...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-Yeah... I'm fine, Nick. I believe in you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... *sniffle* <thought>I think I'm going to cry.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">Umm... I, err... I know you have a lot of work to do... I... I really appreciate it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">OK, Nick! Let's get this show on the road!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Smile, you're on candid camera. The camera doesn't seem to have a lot to tape right now. The only thing it's watching now is that guard over there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitors the visitor's room. It looks like he doesn't have much to do right now. I can tell because he's looking at the camera and making funny faces.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah... Mr. Nick! W-Welcome back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, hey Pearls. You're back too, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I, um... I went and bought us a strawberry cake! I'll go make some tea to go with it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, uh Pearls... ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It looks like she feels really bad about what happened at the detention center...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-Mr. Nick...! I-I was wrong about you... I shouldn't have trusted you! I-I... I'll never forgive you... EVER!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mystic Maya! The tea is ready!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh... Thanks...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Come on, Mr. Nick! Please have some of this cake!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... Thanks. Umm, Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! Ex-Excuse me... I was in the middle of cleaning the toilet...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, it's OK! I just cleaned it this morning...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Too late...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...This might be a good time for me to ask about her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Charley. A quite decorative plant. When she was alive, Mia really loved it. She even went so far as to make it our mascot. No matter how busy I get, I never forget to water this little fella.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's my desk. I don't get to use it much, so the dust bunnies are starting to mount their assault. Hm? Today it's sparkly clean. I guess Pearls must've wiped them out for me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Difficult-looking legal books stand in a formidable row. They mock me. These were all Mia's... Wow, I just realized I didn't buy a single one of these.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I first met Pearls a year ago... It was when that murder happened at Kurain Village. I still remember what she said to me when we first met...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You... You're Mr. Nick, right? You're... You're Mystic Maya's "special someone"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Hey, Maya. I've always thought it was because she was young, but... </line>
<line speaker="Maya">But what...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls... I think she's got the wrong idea. About... you and I.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh!? Err, I... ...Umm...There's something you need to understand...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... It's kind of like a Kurain Village custom... Sort of.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls seems to love you a lot.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, it's because I'm her only cousin. And... Well... Because of the murder case last year, Pearly's mother is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I remember now... Pearls's mother, Morgan Fey... She's serving a prison term in isolation right now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So you see? I'm the only family Pearly has right now... But... It's the same for me, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">My mother's gone, too...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There are hardly any men in Kurain Village.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now that you mention it, I actually saw any men there when I visited.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm pretty sure I told you about it a long time ago... About how spiritual powers run very strong in the Fey family.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, you did. And that's why you're undergoing training to be a spirit medium, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah... The thing is, only women can actually inherit the spiritual power. That's why the whole culture of Kurain Village kinda revolves around its women.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, that's understandable... Nothing wrong with that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, but because of that... There tends to be a lot of unsuccessful marriages.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, men start to feel left out after a while, and then they just start leaving. ...Especially if the man has a daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you saying that Pearl's father...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...He's gone. He left the village when she was very young.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Boy, that's tough...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, and she grew up seeing nothing but unhappy marriages all around her. That's why she's so sensitive to things like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So your mother's still missing...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah... And no one has any idea where she is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya's mother... Misty Fey. The current Master of the Kurain Channeling Technique. She disappeared 17 years ago after getting involved in a certain police case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...But you're sure she's still alive, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah... I know she is... It's sort of a spirit medium thing...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And if your mother doesn't come back, then what...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then according to the laws of the village, I'll become the next Master.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mystic Maya... The Master of the Kurain Technique... Sounds like a heavy responsibility.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, but there's no one else with the blood of the Fey main family who's a spirit medium.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So you've still got that badge, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Well, I'm a lawyer, aren't I?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, but I guess I just didn't think you'd keep on being one for this long. You have to admit, you've had some close brushes with death because of your job.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I fail to see how being a lawyer is more dangerous than channeling dead people.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, I thought we'd finally found the urn.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, if only Ron DeLite were Mask☆DeMasque, we'd have figured it all out.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? You mean he's NOT Mask☆DeMasque?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Desirée says he isn't and I believe her.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... The mystery gets deeper and deeper.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, and the trial starts tomorrow... as usual.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this was made by the real Mask☆DeMasque, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup, Detective Gumshoe said it was the real thing. "One look at this mark and you know it's the real deal, pal."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, but you do realize whose deductive reasoning skills we're talking about, right...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This sword... It has a strange aura surrounding it. It's like it's infused with a spirit of both anger and tragedy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I'd be mad too if somebody bent me the way they bent this sword.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Yeah, I guess that could be it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">When did you first get that porcupine cut?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Um, it's been like this ever since I was a little kid.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? You mean that's the way your hair is naturally? I thought you had some sort of special "Phoenix Cut" deal with the barber. I mean... You usually only see hair like that in a video game.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If it wasn't for Mia, I wouldn't be the person I am today.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, she told me you used to really be useless. Compared to how unreliable you were then, you actually seem responsible now. ...Actually, you haven't changed that much, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya praised me for a change! ...Hey, wait a second...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm so sorry that Pearly said what she did.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, It's fine... It-It was nothing... <thought>I'm going to have to smooth things over with Pearls later somehow...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Detective Gumshoe's on this case too, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He seems to show up during all of our cases. It can't be a coincidence.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe it's a sign that our fates are destined to be woven together for all time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, that'd be a real Beauty and the Beast kind of fairy tale, wouldn't it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So the real identity of Mask☆DeMasque is... ...Ron DeLite, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what Mr. DeLite claims. ...But I'm not too convinced about something he said.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? About what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About the Sacred Urn. Didn't he sound a little vague on the subject?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, now that you mention it, he said that he simply "lost it", right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have this distinct feeling that he's hiding something. I just know it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">That Detective Atmey guy really surprised me. There was this certain something about the way he said, "Zvarri!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well he did manage to get back the treasure that the Mask guy stole last time, right? And he did it by himself, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, I guess. ...That case has certainly made him famous.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like he does deserve to be called "Ace Detective" after all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That Desirée sure is cool! I love that whole motorcycle thing! The way she laughs in the face of death... I want to try it myself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I thought you only knew how to ride a bike...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Don't forget, Nick, that it's an electric bike!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...E-Electric? So young and already so lazy. Whatever happened to good old exercise?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think about this?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmmm... It seems like it has something to do with this case... But I'm not really sure...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I know... But... First I want to talk to Pearls...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Umm, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... I acted like a baby.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I doubted you... Even though Mystic Maya trusted you completely... I guess I still have a lot of training to do. Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I... From the bottom of my heart, I apologize for what I said!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aww, it's OK! I'm the one that should be apologizing!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Well, I'm going out now for a little bit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!? Wh-Where are you going...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I may be small, but I still have a lot of spirit channeling power! So I'm going to show you I can be useful too... By finding some evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! W-Wait a...! <thought>Ack! She sure runs fast...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... Let's back off and give her some room, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">M-Maya...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, Ms. Andrews...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I'm so sorry! It's my fault! ...Your precious urn! Your... precious... UUUUURNNN!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please! C-Calm down! What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">*sniffle* It never ends! Everything I touch ends in failure! Maya, I'm sorry...! I'll do anything to make it up to you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-No, it's okay, don--</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I know I don't look it, but I'm good with my hands. I could make you another urn.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hold on, just wait, OK? Breathe, calm down and talk to us.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">F-Forgive me! Forgive me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's probably where the Sacred Urn was going to be displayed.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, I guess so...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Should I put my attorney's badge there? You know, as a replacement? </line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... I think it's a little too small for that. What about my Magatama?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now you're being silly... That's definitely too small.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's the folding screen of Kurain Sacred Writings. But I can't read what it says on it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? But I thought it was some kind of important spell!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ahh, yeah. My mother read it and taught me to memorize it. I'll be in trouble if I ever forget it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like the Kurain Channeling School is teetering dangerously on the edge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, this is incredible! It's a tiny version of my Kurain Village! Hey! I've got a great idea! We can make a miniature of your office, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know about that. The whole place is overflowing with junk. You'd be die before you finish painstakingly recreating that mess.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, we could always clean it up first.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*shrug* true.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... So when did you get the calling card from Mask☆DeMasque?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Let's see... Exactly 10 days ago. I was going to show it to the police... But that detective stopped me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, so you asked Detective Atmey to help with security?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes. In fact, it was about 20 days ago that I hired him. He seemed to know much more about Mask☆DeMasque than the police.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you hired him for security even before the calling card arrived?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Well, yes. I had a premonition that something bad might happen... I've learned to trust my hunches!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that's why there are security cameras, even in the basement warehouse?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes. Lordly Tailor is very serious about their security measures. It was their way of saying, "Bring it on!" to any potential thieves... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, he sure "brought it" last night... And even left with a nice souvenir.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, can you tell us a bit about the security for the Treasure Exhibit?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It was all my fault! I never should have called this paltry little collection a "treasure exhibit" anyway... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why do you say that? The urn that was stolen is a pretty important object...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Maybe, but it's actual value after appraisal was... well, practically zero.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Zero!?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I polished it until it was just about glowing... I thought maybe I could make it looks more valuable!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-But that urn contains the soul of Mystic Ami...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Anyway, I left all the security arrangements to Detective Atmey. But... Five days ago, I began receiving all sorts of other exhibit items from Kurain. Lots of people started going in and out of the warehouse down there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So maybe one of them was actually Mask☆DeMasque in disguise...!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">No, I personally checked out everyone that came through here, so that's not possible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Knowing Adrian, she probably even checked out what they ate for breakfast that morning.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Ms. Andrews?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I know, I know! It's all my fault! But what's done is done... I'll make it up by making a new urn for you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm just wasting my time. She's too far gone...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder if that detective brought this camera in with him?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Good question! Let's take a look at it. ...Huh? It says "Property of Lordly Tailor" on it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So it's borrowed...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Kind of strange for an "Ace Detective", don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to the computer data... ...someone did in fact go through those big doors last night, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, I guess so. The shutter did go off once, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That pathetic-looking wooden box...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ahh!! That's the box that had the Sacred Urn on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't touch it! There may be clues to the thief's identity on there!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Grr... I worked so hard to make that box!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!? You MADE that poor excuse for a box, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's that supposed to mean!? And I-I was so proud of it... *sniffle sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Maya. Maybe it'd have been better if Mask☆DeMasque had taken the box, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm really starting to like this thing. It's so cool-looking. I'd like to strap it to my waist and walk around town like a samurai.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Careful. Gumshoe will lock you up and throw away the key if you're caught.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Our precious urn was right there on the other side of these doors.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. and according to the security computer data...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Someone was in there last night. Grrr... What I'd like to do to him...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks to me like it's been dry for several days.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's something suspicious about this paint mark. The bottom left part of it is shaped oddly and it's shocking pink.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I don't see how the color of the paint is in any way important.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When we were here with Ms. Andrews last night, the statue wasn't there it is now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, it was right next to the door, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, if someone moved it, it was probably the criminal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe he didn't like being watched by Mystic Ami while he stole the urn.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Hey! Cut it out! You're giving me the creeps with that kind of talk!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hello?</line>
<line speaker="???">...Well, well. How lovely it is to see you again, my dear.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Welcome to my abode! Relax! and soak up the atmosphere...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Err, umm... We're actually kind of...</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">SHHH! SILENCE! ... Hee hee hee hee hee... Precisely as I expected.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-What is?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...Zvarri! The truth has once again been elegantly revealed to me! A lawyer, and... a spirit medium. ...Am I correct?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Umm. I think we've already been through this.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Ha! So my estimation was correct! Zvarri! ...How truly elegant. Now then, what can I do for you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aaah! So the music in this room is coming from here!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">"Luke Atmey Elegy" composed by Luke Atmey. This lovely device is called a "gramophone". In days of yore, people listened to music on them.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aha! That's just what I thought! I told you so, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's quite a large portrait of yourself you have there...</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Yes. I wanted it to say to everyone who saw it, "Look at me, Luke Atmey!" With a model so fine, I knew the portrait would also be aesthetically pleasing!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Um, that's nice.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aaah! There's a cold breeze coming from this hearth!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Hee hee hee hee... It seems you've fallen for my little deception. You see, this fireplace conceals a rather unexpected device. ...Yes! A high-tech air conditioner!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-Why would you put an air conditioner in there?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">In the summer it acts as an air conditioner and in the winter, it's a heater. Clever?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mentioned before that you were on guard all alone last night.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Precisely. This is my fifth encounter with my arch-enemy. I refuse to allow anyone to interfere with the rightful pursuit of my prey.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I heard you've been after Mask☆DeMasque since his very first theft?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Yes, my dear. I see you've done your homework. In his very first heist, that vile thief pilfered the famous jewel, the "Tear of Emanon"! I first encountered him in the museum's sacred hall. The crime scene itself!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So... that's why you were hired as security for the Treasure Exhibit?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm pretty sure he said that Adrian Andrews hired him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Yes, I borrowed some equipment from Lordly Tailor and set the perfect trap.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You must mean the security camera...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But I thought you were watching the area yourself, too. So how did Mask☆DeMasque manage to steal the urn?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's the million dollar question... What is DeMasque's modus operandi?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... Mr. Atmey? Did you know about the Sacred Urn?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">I'm interested in only one thing my dear, and that is Mask☆DeMasque! Sacred Urn...? Pfft! That has nothing to do with this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... wasn't that what Mask☆DeMasque stole this time?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">I am hunter, sir! That urn was nothing more than a lure to catch my prey. Do you yourselves remember the shape of the individual peanuts you throw to pigeons?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...I don't think I like this guy's attitude, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Well anyway, it looks like he doesn't know about the urn.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... There's something that's kind of bothering me.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Please, my dear, ask me anything you like. After all, we are all but seekers, wandering alone in the dark.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, I was wondering how Mask☆DeMasque managed to steal the urn. I mean, isn't it strange that you don't seem to know?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, now that you mention it, it is strange. After all, you were on guard that night at the scene of the crime. Unless you were sound asleep, you should have at least seen Mask☆DeMasque.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What the!? It's a Psyche-Lock...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ps-Psyche Lock...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Atmey... You must know more than you're letting on. How did Mask☆DeMasque manage to steal the Sacred Urn...?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">In order for a secret to remain a secret, it must be kept secret.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Last night Luke Atmey must have encountered Mask☆DeMasque... But why would he be trying to hide it...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Go for it! Let's break that Psyche-Lock of his!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I don't really think she understands what she's talking about. Well, it's been a while, but let's give this a shot...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick, what is the Psyche-Lock thing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, your magatama lets me see when people are keeping secrets. By breaking their mental "locks", I can find out what those secrets are.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaaaat!? This Magatama has THAT kind of power!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Maya, you're the one who gave me this Magatama last year...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Well, it's true that this Magatama is a prized Fey family heirloom, but... Pearly was the one that actually imbued it with spiritual powers, right? That's why I don't really know much about what it can do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is the woman that's going to take over the Kurain Channeling School someday!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So how do you do it? How do you break the Psyche-Lock thing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well, you present the Magatama to the person with the secret.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Cool! I can't wait to see it in action! Come on! Try it out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh boy... I think the future Master still needs to learn how to be patient...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">This man surrendered to the police, admitting that he was Mask☆DeMasque.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe so... But I'm not convinced that he's really behind the thefts.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">He is.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...He sounds pretty sure.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Just look at his forehead. It's all in the shape of his mouth and eyes... This is the classic face of a thief. It is unmistakable!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is there anything that isn't "unmistakable" to you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about this person here, Detective Atmey?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is something wrong? Did the cat get your tongue or something?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">That photo leaves me with a distinctly indistinct feeling.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ummm...</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">In this case, I'm afraid my perspicacity has been left wanting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think he's trying to say that he doesn't have any information...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Atmey, you were standing guard at the scene of the crime... There's no way you didn't see Mask☆DeMasque commit the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Well now, I can hardly see why you're so positive about that. Yes, indeed I was guarding the warehouse. That much is true. But I can tell you for certain that not a single person passed through that door.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not sure why... But this Atmey guy is lying through his teeth. ...I know. I'll show him some proof!</thought> Detective Atmey, I have here proof that someone went through that door last night!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">How very interesting that you would present such a thing to me, Luke Atmey, Ace Detective. Unfortunately... It is meaningless. You need to go home, take a long, cold shower and get a good night's rest, Sir Lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess that's a miss...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Well then...? Is there something else I can do for you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Maybe I don't have enough evidence yet. If that's true, it could be dangerous for me to push on. But I need to break him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was a security camera set up at the scene of the crime. It should have automatically taken a photo of anyone that went through that door.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...Precisely.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I hope you don't mind, but we've already gotten our hands on the camera data. As you can see, the camera went off exactly once last night.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Wha...! B-But my monocle didn't catch anyone in its flash! It must be some kind of computer malfunction... It-It must be...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe it was your monocle that malfunctioned.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Wh-What!? Are you saying that I didn't do my duty properly?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...I'm afraid that making a guess is not enough. Time to put your money where your mouth is. Show me your evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...May I give you a piece of good advice, Sir Lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...A guess is not the same as a theory. Not scientifically, anyway. You need to go home, take a long, cold shower and get a good night's rest, Sir Lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! I guess I need to think this over again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Atmey... You were knocked unconscious by the thief, weren't you!?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Ha ha ha! Surely you must be joking... You think that I, Luke Atmey, could be knocked unconscious so easily!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This sword proves it!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...! Th-That's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Before the theft, this sword was in the hand of the statue of Ami Fey. Furthermore... at that time, it was not bent.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Aaah... Err...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...There's only one explanation. You were struck on the head and knocked unconscious by this sword! Well, Detective!? What about it!?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...I'm impressed. You truly are an "Ace Attorney"...</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">I can't deny that there may be a small hint of "truth" in what you say.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, you were knocked out when the thief first clobbered you?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Clobber... What an ugly way of saying it. But I suppose you could put it that way. The coward struck at the precise moment that I turned to look at the computer.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So you never noticed that the thief had entered the warehouse?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">No, the coward must have wormed his way in through somewhere besides the door... Perhaps the air ducts or the sewer pipes... Then my arch-nemesis struck me on the head from behind with this gruesome item here!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ouch. He should have his poor head examined.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can say that again. How could he have underestimated the thief that badly?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? What? That Atmey is the greatest Ace Detective in the world?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, that he never actually saw the thief.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh... that's right! So the thief may not even be Mask☆DeMasque...</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Just one moment, Sir Lawyer! The thief was unquestionably Mask☆DeMasque!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But you never actually saw him!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Perhaps so, but I installed a security camera for just such a contingency.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Last night, the camera went off exactly once. Behold! This is a photo of the dastardly thief, taken by the security camera!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Th-That's him!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">M-Mask☆DeMasque...!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">The thief can be none other than the arch-criminal, Mask☆DeMasque. After all, he has a very good reason for committing such brazen crimes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... What did you mean by he had a "very good reason"?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Exactly that. Mr. DeLite had a very good reason to dress up and commit those crimes. There should be a green envelope somewhere in his room. ...You'll need to go and investigate.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-But how would you know about that...?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Hmph. Have you forgotten? You're speaking to the finest Ace Detective ever to walk on the face of the earth! The most brilliant mind since ...well, EVER! Luke Atmey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sigh* Well, I guess we'd better go take a look, just in case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Nick! Remember what Detective Atmey said!?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Exactly that. Mr. DeLite had a very good reason to dress up and commit those crimes. There should be a green envelope somewhere in his room. ...You'll need to go and investigate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A green envelope, huh... Looks like this is it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">OK! Let's have a look! "If you don't want your true identity revealed to the world... ...come to KB Security at 1:00 AM on October 12th and bring $50,000." F-F-F-Fifty thousand...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-Th... This is a... B-B-Blackmail letter... <thought>It sure looks like a major clue alright!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Oh! Someone's at the door! I'll be right back. Won't take but a second, I promise. <thought>Oh, thank you for coming! That's so nice of you!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???"><thought>When I see a damsel in distress, I just can't help myself!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée"><thought>Please, come on in! I'll make some coffee.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???"><thought>Really? OK, I guess I'll make myself at home, pretty lady!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Wait a minute. I know that voice...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Oh, Nicky boy, I'm so sorry, but I've got another guest!</line>
<line speaker="???">Aaaaaaaaaaaah!! You... You're... Nick, it's you! And Maya, too! What a fluke!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah...! Larry! Long time no see!</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">What? You know each other?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Ni... "Nicky boy"!? Nick, do you and this girl have... you know... something going on?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"S-Something"? If you mean what I thin--</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I underestimated you, Nick! A gorgeous lady like this? ...And married, too? Way to go, dude!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I knew it. Just when things can't get any worse, it's time to cue in the Butz.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry Butz... Ever since grade school, he's been... Not exactly a close friend, but yeah, we know each other.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey, man, that wasn't nice! I was your very first client!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's been 25 years since I first met Larry. And what we used to say still rings true. When something smells, it's usually the Butz.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey, come on now! You're embarrassing me! And in front of this pretty little thing here...</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">So you two are old childhood friends, I see. That's so sweet! You two go ahead and catch up on old times. I'm going to go check on my bike. </line>
<line speaker="Butz">Nice girl, that Dessie... So how have ya been, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Too busy if you really want to know...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So Ron received a blackmail letter, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you think Ms. DeLite knows about this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well if she did, I don't think she would've been smiling like that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder if we should tell her about it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think it'd be smarter if we didn't.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what have you been up to this whole time? It's been two years since I heard from you. And what's with these clothes? You look... well, weird.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey man, that's uncalled for. This is my uniform, from a my part-time job! But I can't believe it's been two years. They say time flies when you're having fun. Ha ha ha ha... Ah ha... Ha... ...ha?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Nick... I gotta tell you. Women. ...I don't trust'em anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You got dumped again?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, you know Bennifer? I followed her all the way to Tibet 2 years ago. That's where I met the famous Katty Tom, and my whole life changed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Bennifer"? "Katty Tom"? I never heard of either of them.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Anyway... Dude! Katty Tom chose Hollywood over me! Can you believe it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, actually... Anyway sounds like you had quite the adventure.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Women! They're so... so... Aaaah! Oh... B-But you're different, Maya. You're not like the rest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Looks like he's still the same old Larry.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what are you doing here anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh...? What do you mean by that? I'm just a natural-born nice guy, that's all. Well, actually... I picked this up last night while I was working.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...A wallet? You say you found this last night?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah, it had a driver's license in it, so I figured I'd just return it myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on... Let me see that for a minute. ... I know it. Dessie's picture is in here.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah, I guess he really digs his wife, huh? ... Hey, Nick... It's not what you're thinking at all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I'm pretty sure it is. You haven't changed a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Aw, no way man! I mean, she's a married woman! That's just bad news!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's really IS here just to check out Ms. DeLite...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So you said you found it at your job, right?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah! I'm working for a private security company as a guard! Chicks just love a guy in uniform, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A security guard, huh. So that's what that uniform is all about...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what time was it when you found this last night?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh? Why are you asking that!? Trying to see if I've got an "alibi"!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Umm... You're not the one on the hook for a crime this time, buddy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">I guess it was around 1:00 in the morning on the first floor of our company building.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What was Mr. DeLite's wallet doing there...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">...Anyway, there's nothing weird about that. After all, he works here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He... works there? You mean... Mr. DeLite?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Sure. Here, take a look at this. It's right there in his wallet.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's this card?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">It's a key card for the security company. Hey! It's got a serial number on it right there. There's no mistake about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You said you were working part-time at a "security company", right?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's right. ...Wh-Why are you making that scary face?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Security company", huh... Something's not quite secure about Larry working there... I need to find out as much as I can about this key card...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">KB Security, the company in the blackmail letter! You know about it!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's where I work, yeah. In fact, I'm on the job right now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh...? So what are you doing here then?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, the boss is away right now, and you know what mice do when the cat's away...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes, yes. *sigh* Anyway, how far away is this company?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Lemme see... About 30 minutes by car, I guess... Well, if you fly down the road, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm. Well, this apartment building is pretty close to Lordly Tailor, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And it would take roughly an hour to go from here to KB Security and back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If Ron DeLite was at KB Security when the robbery occurred, then...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa...! Then he couldn't have stolen Sacred Urn!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry, this is one of the treasures from Kurain Village...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Be serious, Nick! I couldn't care less about mystic mumbo jumbo stuff!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Ah! Of course Maya is a different story!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Talk about your mixed messages...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey Larry, what about this?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What? If you've got something to say, then say it already! ... Huh...? A blackmail letter!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know anything about this?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wh-Wha-What? I don't know anything about Alexis! And that's the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Huh? What?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I-I can't believe you'd do this to me! I thought you were my friend! Fifty thousand dollars! I don't have that kind of money!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, you don't understand! This blackmail letter was sent to Ron DeLite!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wheeeew! Man, you scared me!! I almost had a heart attack, you idiot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, I'm the idiot!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Man, I was totally confused because it says, "KB Security" right on the envelope.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, yeah... So what?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's where I've got a part-time job! At KB Security!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh... Whaaaat!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like I should really find out some more about this KB Security company!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You didn't touch anything in the wallet, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey man, be serious! You know what I was interested in!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If Mask☆DeMasque doesn't look out, he's gonna be the victim of a robbery himself!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you're sure about this key card?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yup. That's the key card they use at the building I work in. According to the serial number, this one is for the CEO's office. You need it to get into that room, and every time you use that card, it leaves a record.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It leaves a record?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah, it tells you exactly who entered the room and when.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry! I need that data...!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Whoa! Slow down, man! Sorry, but that data is off limits to outsiders. If I lost this job, I'd never have a chance with Dessie...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's times like these when I wish lawyers weren't so powerless...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">You're 26 years old, right? Don't you think it's about time you took a long, hard look at your life?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Coming from a guy who can only brag about how many times he's been rejected... I find that kind of... ironic.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey, I remember her! That's Maya's big sister!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! You really do remember!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah, who could forget! A couple of gorgeous sisters! Hubba hubba!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You hear that, Nick! Gorgeous!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh yeah... That's right. When I defended Larry... Mia was still alive...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wow! You've even cuter than the last time I saw you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, really!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah, you look totally different than two years ago. Don't you think Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe it's 'cause we're always together, but she looks pretty much the same to me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh! What a cutie! Hey, Nick! So what's the deal between you and this girl?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! That's my cousin! Her name is Pearl Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Pearl, huh... Too bad. Never date two girls with the same name... That's one rule I can't break.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I'd think the fact that she's only 9 years old would break some rule somewhere!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">WHOA! WHO is this! Come on, man, don't hold out on me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Forget about it. It's on a need to know basis and you don't need to kn--</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey now! I thought we were pals! I got a MAJOR thing for girls with black sleeveless shirts and glasses! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How do you know that!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">And if they have an orange-colored memo pad, I really lose my cool!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He has to be making that up... He can't really know Adrian... Can he...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">I just thought of something! What if it's actually a hot chick under that costume!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Forget about it. It's a guy, trust me.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Man! You're killin' my buzz, dude!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Boy, talk about someone who has a one track mind...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That Dessie is one awesome lady alright! It's been a long time since I've felt this way... I think I'm really in love this time!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A long time, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah! Well, err... Except for what I feel for you, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think even HE knows what he's saying anymore.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Even you could learn a few tricks from me, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah? Like what?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Look at my hair for example. It points up straight, right? But your hair, on the other hand, points backwards. That's no good at all, man! It's defeatist! You gotta aim high... for the stars!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I... I can't find a counter-argument to that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What about this? Does anything come to mind?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Listen, I'm a security guard. I'm not here to sell you juicy bits of info and chew the fat, man.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Funny, you had no qualms about selling Samurai Dogs just 2 years ago.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry, what about this person...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Beats me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What the...? All of a sudden, he's got nothing to say...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, Nick! Your phone!</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">H-Hello? Is this the Wright residence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah! Pearls! Where are you!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I-I thought I'd go to Lordly Tailor to try to find some more clues, but... ...I'm afraid I've gotten lost.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaaat!? Give me that phone, Nick! P-Pearly! Where are you right now!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... I was walking along and I found myself in front of that person's office.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"That person"...? Who!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, the person who doesn't act his age and always says, "Zvarri!" when he's excited...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Luke Atmey, Ace Detective...</thought> OK, stay right there! We're coming to get you!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">A-Alright... I-I'm a little scared...</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright! Let's go, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wait a second, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That phone call just now... Sounded like real cutie... Another one of your, ahem, ..."special friends"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.......... Say goodbye to Ms. DeLite for me, would you Larry?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah! Mr. Nick! Mystic Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pearly!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I never thought I'd see the two of you again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...So is Mr. Ace Detective out of the office?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes, when I arrived here... ...there wasn't a single soul in sight.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Say, Nick... Doesn't look like something's changed since we were here last?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that you mention it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">This bag... I'm sure it wasn't here before.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It looks quite full... I wonder what could be in here?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Come on! Open it up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! Wait a minute! We can't just open his private property!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't be such a fuddy-duddy! This is an important investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's true... And truth be told, I have to admit I am kind of curious...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well? What's in there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Hang on a sec. I'm taking it out now... <thought>Whatever it is, it feels... kinda hard... and smooth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...Well, hello there!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">EEEEEEK! H-He's here!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...What are you doing, Sir Lawyer? I'm shocked to see a servant of the court ignoring the law so flagrantly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm really sorry! M-Maya made me do it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! I can't believe you!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">A gentlemen never uses a lady as an excuse for his own poor behavior... The real question is... Can you afford to waste time lollygagging about here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Perhaps I should make myself more clear? Tomorrow's trial... Zvarri! Shall we say the figurative Sir William will be dropping his panties before lunchtime.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, Nick! Sounds like it's gonna be really exciting.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So what's in there, Nick? What's in the bag?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The way Atmey barged in like that, I never actually got the chance to look!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I know. I thought I was going to collapse of shock, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But from the feel of it, it was something hard...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... What's going to happen at the trial tomorrow that's so dramatic?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Do you know what your biggest mistake so far has been, Sir Lawyer? ...It was becoming a lawyer in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...That certainly does sound like a big mistake, Mr. Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Tomorrow will be a day to remember. I, Luke Atmey, will take the stand! And then... Zvarri! My testimony will prove to be the undoing of the lot of you! Yes! All of you! I will unmask you as the thief's co-conspirators!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">C-C-Conspirators!?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Hee hee hee hee hee... You're quick on the defensive, I see! However! It is not I that is your greatest enemy! There is a far more dangerous threat that you will face during the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-What are you talking about...?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Sir Lawyer... If you truly are who you say, I'm sure you've heard of him. ...His name is "Godot".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">G-Godot...?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">You have taken a step down the path of foolishness. To try to defend a career criminal who deserves nothing less than the death penalt--</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Last time I checked, no one knows for sure that Mr. DeLite really is DeMasque!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Hee hee hee hee hee... My dear lady... Times may change, but people, sadly, do not... ...Well. You will understand this when you are more mature.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um... Who is this "Godot" person...?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...It's not surprising that a spirit medium has not heard the name. Godot. The prosecutor whose equal cannot be found in this country, but in heaven. Godot. A legend or myth... Men pin a lifetime of hopes on the chance to simply meet him.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Prosecutor...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But the best prosecutor in the country isn't Godot, it's Mr. Edgeworth! Isn't that right, Nick!?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...It's no surprise that a spirit medium such as yourself would know nothing of this. But Ace Prosecutor Miles Edgeworth is currently traveling aboard.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">In fact, it was Mr. Edgeworth who acknowledged Godot as the best in this country.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">And you agree with that?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Most certainly. In fact, you could call him the Luke Atmey of the Prosecutor's Office.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, that's good to hear! The prosecution has a fighting chance tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick, is this "Godot" really that strong?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... I seem to remember hearing about something like that...</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Not surprising... Some people spend their entire lives idly waiting for his appearance.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ummm, Mr. Atmey...? Could you take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Oh please. You can drop the pretense already.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">You and I are already fated to fight each other... And the only true weapon for warriors in a court of law is information! Surely you don't expect me to sharpen your sword for you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Creep.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Hee hee hee hee hee... Sir Lawyer... The stage has been set and all the pieces are finally in place. All that remains now... is for the dance to begin!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A new prosecutor, an Ace Detective and a thief... This will be one tough trial.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think I have enough evidence yet... I should investigate and gather some more clues before I try again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nnrgh! I've made too many mistakes!</thought></line>
</xml>