<xml>
<title>The Return of the Great Departed Soul</title>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm right in thinking that these scales are a symbol of the defence in law, aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">They're supposed to symbolise treating everything equally...and fairly. That's why they're always in the middle, balanced. Equal measures on both sides.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Recently though, whenever I see a set of scales, I can only think of the enormous Scales of Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's entirely understandable. They are such a powerful symbol in the courtroom, aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And the thing about the Scales of Justice is... ...they're always leaning one way or the other. They're only ever in balance right at the start.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...It must be something peculiar to the British... I'm afraid I can't shed any light on it, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's very fine embroidery here that shows the name of the armband's owner. In this case...Kazuma Asogi. So I'm always carrying my best friend's hopes and dreams with me on my right arm just here. All the time. To be honest, it's something that weighs very heavily on me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Oh, I didn't realise it was such a burden, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I think it's why my right shoulder aches so much.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Are you sure that's not to do with you reading in bed or the like?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, this room! It's been too long! It hasn't changed in the slightest, though. And it's been some six months, hasn't it? ...That's a long time for things to stay so...familiar.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I didn't know when you might return, and I wanted everything to be as you'd left it. ...But it has been some six months, it's true.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">So is your father alright, Susie? What happened?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">My father?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes! Professor Mikotoba! I mean, it was half a year ago, but that's why you went back to Japan! Because of the telegram you received saying he'd fallen ill with a very high fever for some unknown reason.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's right. So I was surprised to learn you'd be coming back so soon. Surprised but happy!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... I think I wrote about it in my letter to you. That it was all a trick. My father is in fine health. And I'm obviously very relieved...about that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, we're all delighted to have you back.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was quite by accident that I've been able to return to Europe, actually. It's because of a very grand conference called the International Forensic Science Symposium.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The International Forensic... <thought>That's the same symposium Lord Stronghart mentioned.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Anyway, I've arrived safe and sound, and all that matters is that I'm here now! After all, I haven't yet fulfilled my promise to you, Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You must tell us everything that happened while you were back in Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, of course, I shall.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And...there's one other thing... Something you wrote in your letter that particularly grabbed my attention. About...you-know-who. <thought>About Kazuma...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I know. I'll tell you all that I can.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It must be about a year ago now. I wrote a really long story based on some of my father's old notes. It's about one of Hurley's greatest exploits. I called it 'The Hound of the Baskervilles'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...But then Mr Sholmes forbade you from publishing it... ...and put the manuscript somewhere nobody could get their hands on it.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">So nobody knows anything about it, apart from Hurley and I. But for some reason... ...you knew the title of it, didn't you, Susie?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, it sounds so exciting! 'The Hound of the Baskervilles'! I should love to read it!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And you wouldn't tell me...how you'd come to know it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Yes. But I made you a promise that I would explain one day, didn't I? I think it's time.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm only sorry I've had to keep it from you for so long, Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was completely by accident that I came to know the title of your manuscript, Iris. It was a short while before we left Japan. I was cleaning Father's study, and I saw something on his writing desk. A large box of papers. There was a label affixed to the box that was written in English. It read... ...'The Hound of the Baskervilles'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">My Baskerville story?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Of course, I had no idea what it was at the time. But Father came in, and...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! F-Father...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Did you look at those papers?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No! I, I simply read the label, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">......... Well, put it out of your mind.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Forget that you ever saw it, and certainly don't tell anybody else about this. ...Do you understand?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...what was Iris's manuscript doing...in Japan?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I have no idea. But when I heard Iris mention the word 'Baskerville' that day... ...the title just slipped out. I would never have guessed... ...that it was an unpublished account of one of Mr Sholmes's exploits.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">When I returned to Japan, I asked Father to explain. But he refused to answer any of my questions. And there was no sign of the big box in his office.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's really all I know about it. I've no doubt that Father has a very good reason for being so secretive about it. But still... ...I made up my mind to explain myself to both of you.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">......... Well, thank you for being so honest, Susie.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thinking back, that spade's been in here since we first moved in, hasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm sure I've told you before, Mr Naruhodo. It's not a spade; it's a shovel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, shovels are for digging. That's for scooping up loose material. It's a spade.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, spades are for digging. That's for scooping up loose material. It's...a...shovel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The great spade-shovel war rages on...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, I'm so looking forward to making you some tea again, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Which you'd think I wouldn't like, given that I'm not keen on bitter flavours. But it is Susato-san's tea. And it's amazing what a little cake or something on the side can do...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I would dearly love to serve you some sort of Japanese sweet alongside your matcha green tea... ...but I suppose that's simply not possible given how long we've been staying here in London.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...I do like the little chocolates you put with my tea. They go wonderfully.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Mr Naruhodo! You would, wouldn't you?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That gives me a warm glow inside for some reason...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">You have water gently boiling on the stove, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It feels wrong somehow if I can't hear the water bubbling away. And we have plenty of logs. It's not like we have to worry about paying for gas.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's important to open the window for fresh air when the fire's burning, though. You can't keep it closed just because it's cold outside. It could be a matter of life and death!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Avoiding the freezing winter air is a matter of life and death too, if you ask me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh well, perhaps a nice cup of tea will warm you up later.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You see? I've been keeping my desk beautifully covered in papers as always.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You really must tidy it all up, Mr Naruhodo. No more excuses.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But Miss Susato, the way I see it... ...all these papers building up on my desk like this are a reminder of my wonderfully diverse daily life. I like to leave them as they are so I never forget how lucky I am to have such varied experiences.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">In that case, you should definitely have a thorough tidy. Then you'll be able to see your papers building up all over again and feel that joy renewed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Still can't beat her in an argument. Even though I'm the lawyer here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I see your daruma still has only one eye filled in.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, we agreed that it's something we'd do together, didn't we? We could do it right now if you like. I'd be happy with that.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I rather like the anticipation, I think, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That was taken when I left London, wasn't it? I have the same photograph on display in my room at home in Japan, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I wondered if we'd ever all be together again, to be honest.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, I know... So did I. But here we are! And I'm quite sure there's a reason we've been brought back together.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I can't deny that having Susato-san back again... ...makes me feel as though fate has something big in store for us...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your room through there should be exactly as you left it. I've still never been inside. I've never been invited.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Of course not. Only Iris is allowed in my room.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>No doubt I'll be hearing you two giggling away in there again, then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm so pleased to see all our sea creatures doing so well in the aquarium.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, the prawns are still swimming and the anemones are still swaying. Obviously, I've been looking after them carefully. At first, I used to drool whenever I looked at those juicy prawns, but not any more. They're like part of the family now.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I don't suppose they'll never know how close they were to meeting their maker.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I left your desk completely untouched, Miss Susato. So it would be ready for you whenever you returned.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's beautifully clean. There isn't a speck of dust on it anywhere. You've been cleaning in my absence, Mr Naruhodo? Whatever next!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I couldn't allow my great assistant's desk to sit there gathering dust, could I?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It really is exactly as it was when I left. I'm so touched! But sadly... ...your desk is also exactly as it was, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, that's how it should be, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear...I'd forgotten how that clean-cut smile can be so disarming.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">When I first arrived back in Japan...I really thought I'd never be allowed to return to Britain. But curiously... ...after that awful trial at the Supreme Court, Father's mood changed entirely.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The awful trial? Oh yes... ...for the murder of Jezaille Brett.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ooh, you dressed as a man then, didn't you, Susie?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Well...yes...since women are forbidden in the courtroom. I had no choice.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Wow! Amazing! I wish I'd seen it! Don't you, Runo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...yes, I...suppose so.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I want to play at being a lawyer now! I could wear a false moustache, maybe!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I don't think any moustache could hide the fact that you're just ten years old, Iris. There's something else I've been wanting to ask you, Miss Susato... It's about the real reason why Professor Mikotoba summoned you back to Japan. You said in your letter it was something to do with that convict's loot we found in Mr Natsume's lodgings...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's right. The very large dog collar we found with the 'B' emblem on it. It seems Mr Natsume included a drawing of the collar in the report he submitted about his time in Britain. I understand that when Father saw the report, he turned as white as a sheet.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Why would that be, then?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Father came to Britain himself, of course. To study. It was some time ago now, but he stayed for six years. I can only imagine that something must have happened during that time. But if he refuses to tell me what it was, then I intend to find the answers for myself. And I've decided that I, for one, won't keep any more secrets.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! Susie...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's a very meaningful look Susato-san's giving Iris there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord Stronghart mentioned something about that symposium, too. I think he said that investigative authorities from forty different countries would attend.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, and from Japan, my father and Judge Jigoku have been invited. It's something of an honour, I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, Professor Mikotoba is the leading expert in forensic medicine in our country, after all. But...who's the other person you mentioned? A judge, did you say?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes. His Excellency, Judge Seishiro Jigoku. You've met him, Mr Naruhodo. Last year...in the Supreme Court... You can't possibly have forgotten! That terrible trial of yours, when you were accused of murder.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Aaah... Yes, I...try to think of that as a positive turning point in my life these days...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, it was Judge Jigoku who presided over that trial.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...If I'm perfectly honest, I'd be happy never to see that man's face again in my life.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, well anyway...as Father was invited to the symposium, he agreed to me returning to Britain, too. He won't actually arrive until next month, but... Well, I couldn't wait! So I pleaded with him, and in the end he agreed to me going on ahead!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, about the symposium... It seems as though Lord Stronghart has put in an awful lot of work to make it happen. It's obviously very important.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I believe it is, yes. As I understand it, Lord Stronghart organised the entire event himself. I think...he's hoping that by achieving exceptional results, he'll get the job of Attorney General.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The most senior position in the British justice system...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">He's hoping to use his power to create the world's finest policing institution. That's what Father said anyway! Apparently it's Lord Stronghart's lifelong ambition!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Does Professor Mikotoba know Lord Stronghart personally then, I wonder...?</thought> Actually, Lord Stronghart gave me a long speech all about this very subject only yesterday. But I sort of lost the will to live early on and didn't really listen to much of it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...How trying for you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Jezaille Brett... The woman whose unforgivable actions ended in me being wrongly accused of a crime I didn't commit. The murder of Dr John H. Wilson.</thought> Yes, Jezaille Brett... That's a name I won't forget for as long as I live.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The extraordinary thing is, though... ...it seems it's a name we should all forget.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Since the incident, our government's intelligence services have been investigating Miss Brett. But it turns out that an Englishwoman by the name of Jezaille Brett didn't actually exist.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">D-Didn't exist? But...how can that be?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was a pseudonym. Her real name was Shinn. And she wasn't a visiting student, either. That was a front.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A front? Who, who on earth was she, then?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Miss A. Shinn. Her name is literally all our intelligence services have been able to ascertain about her. Nobody knows why, or even how, she came to be in Japan. It's a complete mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but that makes no sense! It's no easy task to be accepted as a foreign student anywhere! What could the woman have been up to?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm afraid I really don't know. The only thing we can be sure of... ...is that she had some business in our country that we don't yet understand.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... And now she's been killed... ...while all the questions surrounding her existence remain unanswered!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I'm afraid so.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A. Shinn... <thought>Who on earth was she? And why do I feel as though...I've heard that name before somewhere...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">After my friend Rei's trial... ...the reporter who actually killed Miss Brett said something very strange.</line>
<line speaker="Menimemo">I know the truth! I know you had a hand in what went on! In that visiting student's fate!</line>
<line speaker="Menimemo">Nobody here in Japan knows anything about it! They don't know that the guy never made it to England! That he died on that steamship! And that he'll never-</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Obviously, I couldn't ask him to elaborate at the time... ...but later I visited the man in his prison cell and asked him what he was going to say about Kazuma-sama.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And what did you learn?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... After he died on the voyage to Great Britain... ...his body should have been unladen at the port of Hong Kong and passed into the care of the consulate staff there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Should have been?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, it turns out...that his body never arrived. It just...disappeared.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! Kazuma's body...vanished?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Our government tried to cover the fact up, it seems. They erected a grave on the cliffs by our home town... Except...Kazuma-sama isn't there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Did, did Professor Mikotoba know about this?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes. It would seem that he did. But...he didn't tell me. They're still investigating what happened to Kazuma-sama's body as we speak.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I just don't believe it... <thought>And what is this acute feeling of apprehension I have all of a sudden?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thinking back now, some of the things that happened on the SS Burya were definitely strange. I mean, after he died, we never saw his body again, did we? ......... Could it be...? Could it be...that he's actually still alive?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Stop it, Mr Naruhodo! It's too much to bear!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm sorry, I didn't mean to...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Just thinking about the possibility pains me. So very much. ......... Cast your mind back for a moment, Mr Naruhodo... When Kazuma-sama was discovered, Mr Sholmes was there, wasn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And he definitely examined the body. I remember it clearly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! You're, you're right... So if Kazuma hadn't actually been dead at all... ...it would mean that Mr Sholmes had lied to us.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But there's no reason why he would possibly have done such a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I suppose that's true, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... The idea that he might still be alive somewhere... It wants to fill me with hope, but I can't let it. Because if it turned out not to be true... ...then I'd be back at the bottom of that awful pit of despair again. I'm...I'm terrified of what that might do to me...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, Miss Susato... <thought>I know she's given the idea the thought it deserves. It's Susato-san we're talking about, after all. So I probably shouldn't push it now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">You're still taking good care of that armband, I see. I'm so pleased.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well yes. It feels like I wouldn't be me without it now, to be honest.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Oh dear. There seems to be a thread coming loose just there, look. I'd be only too happy to mend it for you, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Thank you... I must have scraped it against something again. I'm always doing that.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Then take better care of it, please.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...It was all going so well...until I ruined it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">About this paper, Miss Susato...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, it's all about the Great Exhibition! I've been dreaming about it, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I was sorry that you were going to miss it when you were called back to Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So was I. I felt desperately unlucky. But here I am, back in London while it's underway! It's a dream come true!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Perhaps you're not as unlucky as you thought, then.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Once we've helped Professor Harebrayne out of this terrible situation, we should all explore it together! And of course we must invite the professor's good friend Lord van Zieks as well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Your luck might not stretch that far.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">This...was used to shoot down the balloon, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, with a flaming arrow. It's quite a formidable weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm quite accomplished with a longbow myself, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No! Really?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">If you were to balance an apple on your head, Mr Naruhodo... ...I'm quite confident I could hit it from a good fifty metres away!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... 'Quite' confident, you say? Does, um... Does the apple necessarily HAVE to be on my head?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Susato! Do you see...this?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...You have such great expectation in your eyes, Mr Naruhodo. But I'm afraid... ...nothing particularly useful comes to mind at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh. Sorry. I'm, I'm not sure what I was expecting, really.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you're fully abreast of the situation already, Miss Susato. I'd expected nothing less, to be honest.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I would think our first port of call should be to investigate this Mr Drebber. The engineer responsible for building the elaborate machine that was used to effect this extraordinary trick.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, a conjuror of sorts, by the sound of it, well known in the fields of science and magic.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Then we need to go and arrest him!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, yes... ...he must know the truth behind this case, so I agree we really do need to find the man.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hm...it sounds like it's a case of tracking someone down. Which is a job for the police...or a great detective!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Are we supposed to guess who she might be thinking of?</thought> We don't have much time, so we need to get started straight away, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Good idea. Well, best of luck, then!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, you're not coming today?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I'm going to Brixton Road shortly for the herb market. But let me know later how you got on, won't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That was a little abrupt. The pull of the herb market must be strong...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Do you know...? I honestly thought I might never have the opportunity to return to Great Britain. And certainly not so soon.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's funny. For the past six months, I haven't been able to work in court. Meanwhile, you've been raising a storm in the Supreme Court of Judicature back in Japan!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Please, Mr Naruhodo! I may have been dressed as a man, but it was a very reserved performance!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So what your father said in his letter about a 'Ryutaro Takedown' is...reserved?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well anyway... ...I'm back here in this great capital now... ...and ready to assist you again in any way I can!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Thank you, Miss Susato.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's my pleasure, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I've finally managed to remember this behemoth's name. The Great Analytiscope.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I don't think it was here when I left for Japan, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, because it was with the pawnbroker.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, of course...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! That's given me a wonderful idea! I could pawn everything that's on your desk! The office would be tidy at last!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Don't even joke about it, Miss Susato. ...You are joking...aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's all sorts on these shelves: chemistry apparatus, books, papers and...lots of things I've never seen before. It's all heaped up so high, I can't help feeling that the whole lot is going to topple at any moment.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It looks as though it might topple, and yet it doesn't. The epitome of Mr Sholmes's brilliance!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I don't get it. As it happens, I'm quite well practised when it comes to stacking shelves myself. Just the other day, the shelf in my office finally gave way under the strain, though.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It looks as though it might topple, and it does. Yes, the epitome of your disarray!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I really don't get it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is Mr Sholmes's famous violin. The one he found being sold for a song at a pawnbrokery. What's it called again? A 'Shodi-something'...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes, this wonderful instrument features in 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes'. It's a world-famous Stradivarius!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Stradi...what?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Stradivarius, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Stragi... Stragivor...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Are you even trying now?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We'll come back to this another time, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I do like this fireplace. It's one of the best things I've seen since we arrived in the country, in fact. Although...I do yearn for a Japanese kotatsu. Putting your legs under a warm, blanketed table is so comforting.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Do be careful, Mr Naruhodo. Don't mistakenly put your feet into the fire, will you? You'd suffer terrible burns, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>I worry sometimes about how Susato-san sees me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My eye is always drawn to this big metal chest that Mr Sholmes and Iris use as a coffee table.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Isn't it where Iris keeps her very important papers?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It is. So you'd think that they'd treat it with more care, really. But only the other day, I saw Mr Sholmes kick it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I suppose something must have been frustrating him.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What a shame to mistreat the furniture, though. Was it damaged?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The chest was fine, but Mr Sholmes was doubled up on the floor for almost ten minutes!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... That is a painful tale.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah yes, Mr Sholmes's curious collection of trinkets from the various mysteries he's solved.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's one of my favourite parts of this room. Full of items with such exciting tales to tell! And I do believe he's added to it since I last looked. Now there's a mysterious pince-nez, a mysterious little box, a mysterious horseshoe, a mysterious biscuit...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think that last one might just be one of Iris's unfinished snacks.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Iris's pretty little tea set is set out beautifully as ever, look.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, it's only by carefully taking care of a tea set that you can make good tea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is...that a roundabout way of telling me I need to tidy my desk?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Mr Naruhodo, you do overthink things at times.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This blackboard is where Iris scribbles down her latest ideas, isn't it? Let's see... Oh, she seems to have drawn a lot of little stick figures all lined up, look.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">'Cheap apples at the market' is what all of them say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! The little figures can speak?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">All your questions would be answered if only you would read this month's Randst Magazine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...So I'm the only one who can't make any sense of this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's Iris's wonderful collection of medicines, potions and chemicals. Just look at all the little bottles she's squeezed onto the shelves.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, and there are charming little ribbons tied around the bottles, too. But the labels aren't quite so charming, are they? This one here reads 'Deadly Poison'.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, I've been so excited about the idea of helping Iris with her experiments, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just try to avoid any bottles labelled 'Deadly Poison' or 'Highly Explosive'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If I've remembered correctly, this large and imposing lump of iron is called a 'typewriter'.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">To think that every single one of 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes' blossomed from this very machine! Ah...it's such a dreamy thought...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I actually had a go on it the other day. The metal bars that move when you hit the keys got all tangled up somehow and that made Iris angry.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo... ...you're ruining my dreamy thoughts. Please don't do that again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh...now I've made Susato-san angry as well...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's...he doing?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">He's... Oh my! The whole wall of the cell is covered in mathematical equations!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And he's still writing more now! Um...Professor! Sorry to interrupt...</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Oh, ah... M-Mr Naruhodo... ...! And who is this young lady?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">My name is Susato Mikotoba. I'm Mr Naruhodo's judicial assistant. It's a pleasure to meet you, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... OH, IF ONLY! IF ONLY I'D MET A REFINED YOUNG WOMAN LIKE YOU SOONER! ...None of this would have happened. N-No, that's not logical... That makes no sense at all.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear, I'm...I'm sorry if my presence here upsets you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I owe you an apology too, Professor. I didn't manage to deliver what I promised you I would in court this morning.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Oh no! No no no! No no no no no! The whole thing... The whole miserable affair... It all happened because I've been such a complete and utter clot!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Um, Professor Harebrayne...what have you been working on in your cell?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Oh! Ha ha, you, um...you mean that? Oh dear, how embarrassing... I, I was suddenly struck by an idea, you see, and I simply had to write it down. The wall was all I had to hand.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Is it some new hypothesis? Something to surpass super-high-voltage instantaneous kinesis, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ah...no, actually. This...is my autobiography.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Your autobiography?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">'How I was Diddled and Fiddled'...by Albert Harebrayne! I've found I can represent my odd fortunes with only odd numbers in an ambitious set of simultaneous equations!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Really?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I'm going to have to pay back all the loans I took for the kinesis machine, you see! So it's going to be a new serial publication from next month! 'Part 1: An Odd Birth; an Odd Upbringing'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...You can't beat the man's optimism, that's for sure.</thought> I see. Well...for now, would you mind if we talked a little more about the case?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Oh yes! YES! Of course! I've been working through the numbers! I WAS DIDDLED! I WAS FIDDLED! BY THE PAIR OF THEM! By Asman! And by that aloof engineer, Drebber!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>We're not going to have to sit through an explanation of all these equations...are we?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">...Everything I believed in has been turned on its head. My research...Mr Asman...the kinesis machine... My hypothesis, even...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm sorry it's come to this. There was really no other way.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">No, it's not your fault. I wanted to protect my work, but in the end, there was nothing worth protecting. ......... It was never my intention to deceive anyone. I didn't want to trick the public.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No...of course you didn't...</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">But in court this morning, I realised something.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">If you've done something wrong without knowing it... ...you've still done something wrong. Logically, it makes no difference if you were aware of it or not. Ignorance is a poor excuse. The blame still lies with me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Professor...</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">He believed in me this morning, you know. Barok did. He believed in my hypothesis.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I think... ...that was just a necessary factor in the prosecution establishing its case.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">No no, Barok wouldn't do something like that. I'm sure he genuinely believed it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Did he...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... I think I understand now. Why it was that he decided to take on the prosecution in my trial, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">After the terrible accident happened, nobody would believe in my hypothesis any more. Not the police. Not the prosecution service. Not any lawyers, even...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...I feel like I dealt some kind of finishing blow there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">So if any other prosecutor had taken the case... If it was anyone other than Barok... ...I'm sure the prosecution would have declared my hypothesis a c-complete and utter nonsense.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And in that case, you would have been declared a fraud yourself, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Exactly. Which would have been a fate worse than death for me. But Barok insisted that I was a proper man of science from start to finish.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You, you think that's why he...?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I know him very well indeed. He's an extremely kind-hearted soul.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But...that extremely kind-hearted soul... ...spent all morning trying to paint you as a murderer, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... Well...admittedly, that part of the analysis appears to have some flaws in it...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And what about the whole Reaper side of things? How does that fit in with the 'kind-hearted soul' idea?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Do, do you think he set out to trick me from the very start?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm sorry to say...that does seem likely, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... When I first met him, he introduced himself as a wealthy financier. He looked over the paper I'd written and said my work would benefit all humanity and MUST be pursued! He was so enthused! He was so emphatic!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But in reality...he was the mastermind of some vast criminal network, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I, I still can't believe it...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">As the machine was essentially a set decoration for some stage magic... ...it probably didn't require a large amount of investment, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But the scale of it! It wasn't just some small trick. It was a very elaborate feat of deception.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">All young scientists are full of hope about their burgeoning ideas. Full of zeal. But none of us have any money! We want to do research, but we can't afford it! Many of us take on barely legal part-time work to try to earn just a few measly pennies to carry on! To go through all of that, only to be taken for a complete fool! It's too rotten to believe...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It is, I agree. And that's why we have to find those responsible and bring them to justice. Mr Asman is no more, of course. Which leaves only the engineer...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Mr Enoch Drebber.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is he an engineer...or a magician...or a swindler?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">It, it was about a year ago when Mr Asman first brought Drebber to meet me at my laboratory. Since then I've met him many times to discuss details about the kinesis machine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But at no point did you have any inkling that he was just an illusionist?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Oh, he definitely wasn't just an illusionist.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">He was a wealth of deep scientific knowledge. There's no question that the man's a genuine scientist. It's instantly apparent in conversation.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But the wretched man deceived you, Professor. It's unforgivable! We must do everything we can to find him and bring him to justice! Are there no more clues you can give us as to his whereabouts?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... I'm sorry. We only ever discussed the kinesis machine. Nothing else.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm...</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... Although...just once... ...I did visit his workshop.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What workshop?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Drebber's enormous fabrication laboratory, where he constructed my great machine!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Why...why didn't you mention this before?! <thought>Enoch Drebber's workshop... There's every chance we might find the man there!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you've been to Drebber's place of work, then?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yes...just once, you understand. It, it was an enormous place. Plenty of room to construct the kinesis machine, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Where can we find it?! We have to go there at once! There's a good chance that we'll find Drebber there!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... Well, yes... Definitely. I'm sure! As in... I'm sure you're not going to want to hear this... ...but I have absolutely no idea where the workshop is at all. I'm so sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I was more than half expecting that.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">You see, I was blindfolded in the carriage the entire way there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He blindfolded you? He wasn't taking any chances then...</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">The place was incredible! The pinnacle of modern engineering! E-Even the oil he used was the very best. A special French machine oil that's impossible to obtain in Britain. Aah, the indescribable scent of that imported oil... Perfumers across the world should forget their secret formulae and use that instead!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you think, Miss Susato? Eau de Machine for your next birthday?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I've never used any kind of perfume, Mr Naruhodo. And I'm not sure I'd like to start with that... I don't suppose you know even part of the workshop's address, Professor? You...don't have a business card from Mr Drebber, for example?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The man was clearly very cautious, Miss Susato. I'm sure he would never have-</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">AAAH-HAAAAAAAAAH! Yes, I do! He gave me his business card once! It's right here, look!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Let me see that!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Throw etiquette to the wind, why don't you?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No... Oh well, I can't say I'm surprised. <thought>Still, this could be useful...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you've been to Drebber's place of work, then?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yes...just once, you understand. It, it was an enormous place. Plenty of room to construct the kinesis machine, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Where can we find it?! We have to go there at once! There's a good chance that we'll find Drebber there!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... Well, yes... Definitely. I'm sure! As in... I'm sure you're not going to want to hear this... ...but I have absolutely no idea where the workshop is at all. I'm so sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I was more than half expecting that.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">You see, I was blindfolded in the carriage the entire way there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He blindfolded you? He wasn't taking any chances then...</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">The place was incredible! The pinnacle of modern engineering! E-Even the oil he used was the very best. A special French machine oil that's impossible to obtain in Britain. Aah, the indescribable scent of that imported oil... Perfumers across the world should forget their secret formulae and use that instead!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you think, Miss Susato? Eau de Machine for your next birthday?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I've never used any kind of perfume, Mr Naruhodo. And I'm not sure I'd like to start with that...</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ugh...how could this have happened?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You must feel awful. As well as a man losing his life, the Crystal Tower was greatly damaged, too.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I, I know what happened! It must have been that!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'That'?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">The day before the demonstration, I had my usual meal of frankfurters at the hotel restaurant. When I paid the bill, they gave me three shillings too much in change. But...instead of saying anything, I just slipped the coins into my pocket! They're still there now! It's divine retribution for my wrongdoing, that's what this is!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>For a scientist, he has some very illogical anecdotes. Long and illogical.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Professor, do you recognise this?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Oh, it's Andrew! My faithful friend! How have you been? Are you alright? Nobody's mistreated you, have they?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Don't worry, he's being very well looked after.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I always rub him with machine oil until he's gleaming.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Right.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">And then, when I come to tighten a screw with him, he slips in my hand and I can't do it! Haha, it's that age-old problem faced by driverphiles the world over, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I...really wouldn't know, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Professor Harebrayne, what do you make of this?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Oh yes! That's just what we need to prove my hypothesis, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...no. It's nothing to do with your hypothesis, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Then take it away! I don't want to be bothered with anything that doesn't assist my science!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Alright...keep your abundant hair on...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This dark smudge here...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think perhaps it's machine oil.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, yes, possibly. Professor Harebrayne mentioned something about the oil Mr Drebber uses, didn't he? He said it was specially imported very high-quality oil that's impossible to obtain in Britain.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's right. But more importantly... ...that it's more fragrant than the finest perfume! So...excuse me a moment... ......... Oh, it doesn't appear to have any scent at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Don't worry, I, I expect that's just because there's such a tiny amount on here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This dark smudge here...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think perhaps it's machine oil.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, yes, possibly. Professor Harebrayne mentioned something about the oil Mr Drebber uses, didn't he? He said it was specially imported very high-quality oil that's impossible to obtain in Britain.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's right. But more importantly... ...that it's more fragrant than the finest perfume! So...excuse me a moment... ......... Oh, it doesn't appear to have any scent at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Don't worry. I, I expect that's just because there's such a tiny amount on here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Oh, who's that standing beside Lord Stronghart?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I wonder... I've never seen her before.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Ah, the young champion of the court. You had some success this morning, I understand. And you've thrown the entire government into disarray as a result.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! You, you mean because of Professor Harebrayne's experiment?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Sham science being demonstrated at London's Great Exhibition! The country's been made to look foolish, and now politicians are scrabbling to respond. Lord van Zieks is in Whitehall as we speak, giving an emergency briefing.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh dear, I, um... I didn't mean to cause any trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">None of this is your responsibility. The government is entirely to blame for having been taken in. The special dispensation that prevents investigation at the scene will be annulled later today. Once that happens, my Forensic Investigation Team will move in and deal with that scrap metal in no time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It's scrap metal now, is it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Until later then, Lord Stronghart.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Yes. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...who was that?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">That was Dr Courtney Sithe, Scotland Yard's esteemed chief coroner. She's leading the Forensic Investigation Team's handling of this case. She was just delivering her report about the victim, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, I see... <thought>About Mr Asman.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Following the outcome of the trial earlier, I asked the coroner's office to re-evaluate its findings. I don't have time to tell you what she concluded. If you want to know, you'll have to ask her directly. You can find her in the forensics laboratory.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, right.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Now, what were you here to see me about? I can give you...seven minutes and thirty-nine seconds of my time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So he's not running quite so spectacularly late any more...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You couldn't read all of these books even if you were reincarnated six times over as a bookworm! <thought>Can Lord Stronghart really have read all of these?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Thinking about it...Father's study is full of books that look as though they've never been read, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, really?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Pedlars of books are forever pushing their wares on him, you see. And I think he's just too kind-hearted to refuse them.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's a phrase for that in Britain. People would say they 'saw him coming'.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It makes me wonder if perhaps the vast number of books on the shelves in here... ...are a sign of Lord Stronghart's overwhelming kind-heartedness.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'm not sure you could afford to have a kind heart if you had to keep Lord van Zieks in line, could you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">These very European suits of armour are still glaring at each other across the carpet, I see. In a way, they feel like guardians of the Lord Chief Justice's office.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I suppose...they're rather like the lion-dogs that guard shrines in Japan, aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Aren't they a bit too human to be called 'lion-dogs'?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Did you know that it's a dream of mine to keep two cats one day?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I feel as though we've gone off at a bit of a tangent, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As ever, the enormous clock is diligently maintaining its rhythmical tick-tock today.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Watching machinery at work can be quite mesmerising, can't it? Ironically, you can completely forget the time. What I particularly enjoy is watching the enormous wheels of a steam locomotive turning. When I was a little girl, Grandmother often used to take me to watch the railway engines, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's an open fire for me. I could sit and watch the flames for hours.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! We could install one in the office! An enormous wheel, turned by an enormous steam engine!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Perhaps we could start with a simple fireplace?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just sitting behind that desk must make you feel so important, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Would you like to have an office like this, Mr Naruhodo? With such a grand desk?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Who, me? No...I don't think so.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, imagine if you suddenly found yourself needing the toilet. You'd have so far to go!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... How...true. Perhaps the important people who work in ostentatious offices like this haven't considered such things.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...I'm going to take that as a compliment.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What exactly is the Forensic Investigation Team that you mentioned before?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">The British Empire's police force must become the most exemplary in the world. For that to happen, it's imperative that we embrace forensic science and everything it has to offer. I first created the Forensic Investigation Team a year ago now - unofficially of course - to pave the way.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Goodness! A year ago?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">At next month's symposium, I intend to present the results of their work to the world. Once I do that, the House of Lords will be powerless to oppose the creation of a full-scale forensics division. And once that happens, the position of Attorney General will be mine...and criminals will suffer dearly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">For too long, those scoundrels have made a mockery of our legal system with false evidence and bribes. But London's scum is about to be rounded up and burnt in the fires of Hell. I intend to see to it personally. By creating the finest police force the world has ever known! To protect our honour...and our future!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Look at those eyes... He means every word.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Doctor Sithe is an extremely reliable coroner. When I officially establish the forensics division at Scotland Yard... ...she will run it as my right-hand woman. Now then...speaking of the symposium, Miss Mikotoba...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Yes, My Lord?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Your father should be on the high seas as we speak, making his way here to represent the Empire of Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's right. I understand he will arrive at the beginning of next month.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Are you acquainted, Lord Stronghart? With Professor Mikotoba, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">......... It was many years ago now, but yes...I remember Dr Mikotoba very well.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">If my memory serves, it was some fifteen years ago now that your father came to Britain as a visiting student.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was the year I was born. So yes, sixteen years ago in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Mikotoba was a young practitioner of forensic science. And Jigoku accompanied him as a young, promising judge. The punctiliousness and politeness of the Japanese at the time impressed us greatly. ......... Not that I wish to imply impoliteness or carelessness on your part in any way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I didn't think that you were.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Dr Mikotoba studied forensics at one of London's large hospitals. St Synner's, if I'm not mistaken. Dr Sithe was also there then, as it happens.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Then, Dr Sithe knows my father, does she?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">She was a young medical assistant at the time, so I doubt their paths crossed regularly. But I've no doubt they knew each other superficially. After all, Dr Mikotoba was here studying his subject for some six years in total.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Six years... That's a long time to be studying abroad, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I lived with my grandmother in those years.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So he left his newly born daughter behind and went overseas for six whole years...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was a rather turbulent time at home...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps Father wanted a reason to get away.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well... ...clearly something was going on at the time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I wanted to ask you about Lord van Zieks, actually. I heard that his older brother was killed some years ago. By a mass murderer known as the Professor, who targeted nobles and royalty. Is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...You Japanese are a thorough lot. You've done your research well. Yes... ...and you could say it was that very incident...that gave rise to the Reaper.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">When his brother, Klint van Zieks, was murdered... ...it was just after young Barok had graduated from the University of London and become a prosecutor. When obvious criminals who managed to evade conviction in court started 'disappearing'... ...rumours quickly spread throughout the capital. Londoners started to say that wherever Barok van Zieks went, the ghost of his dead brother wasn't far behind.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my word!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...Lord van Zieks isn't the Reaper... It's the ghost of his brother?!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Ever since that time, he became a very aloof figure in London's legal circles.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...Another to fall foul of the Reaper's curse.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Odie Asman... The ink was barely dry on the man's acquittal papers. He'd just emerged from a trial in which he was being prosecuted...at the hand of Lord van Zieks.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you think the verdict was wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">......... The law is final. Verdicts are final. However, as long as mere mortals are the ones making the decisions...there is always room for error. The influence of large criminal organisations is sometimes felt even in our highest courtrooms.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That would be the dark and devilish side to London, I suppose? </line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, could I show you this, Lord Stronghart?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...I'm the Lord Chief Justice. I'm not here to offer advice about evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Especially when the evidence in question is so dull.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ah, so that's the real reason.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Go ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's about Professor Harebrayne's experimental machine. We'd like your permission to examine the remains, if possible!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">......... Are you well versed in science, then?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Not in the slightest! In fact, you could say I was barely aware of the subject at all until recently.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...Well the special dispensation legally preventing investigation of the machine is currently being annulled. Within a few hours, Dr Sithe's team of forensic experts will begin their own investigation. But I suppose until then, there's no harm in you looking at the wreckage, as long as you touch nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you! <thought>Being able to look at it is better than nothing!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">And I'll be able to see it, too!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...Your time is up. You'll have to excuse me now, I'm afraid. My next engagement calls.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We are extremely sorry to have troubled you when you are so busy, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I have important matters to attend to in preparation for the symposium, you understand.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I believe this is it... Dr Sithe's laboratory. <thought>That chemical smell really assaults the nose. And there's plenty to assault the eyes in here, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It looks as though the doctor isn't here. But we're here now, so we may as well do some... sightseeing, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What a seasoned tourist you've become, Miss Susato. <thought>We could just have a little look around...being careful not to upset any restless souls...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A table and a set of sharp tools... When you consider each in isolation, it all looks quite innocent. So why is it that when you put them side by side, they seem so horribly disturbing?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...It might be best not to ponder it too deeply. Seeing the large tome that's open on the desk does make me wonder, though: How can anybody concentrate on bookwork with this acrid odour of chemicals in the air?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You'd either have to have a cast-iron constitution... ...or a really terrible sense of smell.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Those large jars seem to have pale things floating around inside them. I suppose they're fruit liquors or something. Or like the pickled umeboshi plums we make back home.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, Father had jars like that in his laboratory as well. I expect they're human organs in a preserving solution. Probably as examples of some rare medical condition.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Miss Susato. There are some things in the world that it's perfectly fine never to know about. Ever.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So as I said, I'm sure they're fruit liquors or umeboshi. Aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Of, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at all the bottles on the shelves in these cabinets! What an assortment of chemicals!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">These ones here are labelled 'Highly Toxic'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh, that's worrying. Because there are also things that look like salt and pepper shakers in there.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes! And they actually say 'salt' and 'pepper' on them! The doctor probably spends a lot of time in this room, I suppose. Perhaps she has meals here sometimes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Life goes on...even when you're surrounded by death...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I suppose this is Dr Sithe's desk.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh. I would NOT like to work in a place like this.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's very tidy though, isn't it, Mr Naruhodo? Imagine how efficiently she must work.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The lighting is poor, which is bad for the eyes. And the chemical smell can't be good for you. Not to mention the skeleton watching over you as you work. Which is definitely bad for the nerves.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, yes...those are valid concerns, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can just about cope with a one-eyed daruma doll watching over me, but that's all!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at this big thick book here.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, it appears to be an accounting ledger. It's a record of the Forensic Investigation Team's spending, I think. ......... Oh...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's clear that the team purchases various equipment and supplies on a monthly basis, but... Well, one entry seems rather strange.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? In what way?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">They're buying five hundred scalpels every month!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Five, five hundred?! They must be working really hard on dissecting corpses.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I don't know... Judicial autopsies are only carried out in certain special circumstances. And scalpel blades can be sharpened, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It, it does seem a bit strange, you're right... <thought>Five hundred scalpels a month... What could they possibly be using all them for?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, look at this! What a magnificent display case! The cherry wood has been polished to a high sheen, and the intricate carving is a joy to behold. Western cabinet makers really are very skilled, aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Do you have nothing to say about the skeleton inside, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Miss Susato... ...can't you tell that I'm trying very hard to avoid talking about the terrifying contents of the case? It's how I cope!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'll...be sure to remember that from now on.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That looks like an owl and a crow up there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know. And they haven't even twitched since we came in here...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well no, they wouldn't have. They're taxidermy mounts, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...I was afraid you were going to say that. I've been trying very hard to tell myself they're just sleeping with their eyes open.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I think perhaps you were wise to put something like your daruma doll on display in the office instead...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Sorry! We, um, had something we wanted to ask you, but you weren't here, so...</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">So you thought you'd snoop around? That's acceptable to you people from the East, is it? Well? What do you want?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, um... Lord Stronghart told us, you see... ...that it was you who examined the victim's body. Erm, Mr Asman's body, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So we came to ask you about your findings. On Lord Stronghart's advice.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">......... Very well. If the Lord Chief Justice has given his consent, I'll tell you what our investigation revealed. But when we're done, you must leave immediately.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">So, you want to know what the Forensic Investigation Team determined from its examination of the scene? The victim, Mr Odie Asman, who disappeared from the experimentation stage amid an explosion... ...and the Mr Asman who appeared moments later part-way up the Crystal Tower... ...were without question one and the same person. That is the team's conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...but that can't be right!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">If it was an elaborate trick, we can only speculate about how it was carried out.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Let's see...if two people who looked very similar to each other were involved... ...they could have made it appear as if one single person had switched places, couldn't they?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Very true. But sadly in this instance...that was not the case. The man who disappeared and the man who subsequently reappeared was the same person. The fingerprints at the scene make that quite evident.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, fingerprints...</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">They're not yet officially recognised as forensic evidence in the British justice system. But one day...they will be used as an investigative aid as a matter of course.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! But that would mean... ...that the instantaneous kinesis actually took place! So...where does that leave us?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">......... My team was tasked with investigating. Not drawing conclusions.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Instantaneous kinesis is impossible...and yet the body did move from one place to the other. This hasn't cleared anything up at all. It's made the whole thing even more of a mystery!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Dr Sithe, would you be good enough to take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Oh, you think I'm 'good enough', do you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! No no, I didn't mean...</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">So I'm not good enough? In that case, why would you show me anything?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh, clearly you're too good for me to show you anything again...ever!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Agh! <thought>Wh-Where did SHE spring from? And...did she just call the doctor, 'Mama'?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sithe">This is a 'lawyer', dear.</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...hello. ...To meet you. P-Pleased to meet you. Yes, I'm a defence lawyer. Ryunosuke Naruho-</line>
<line speaker="???">Mama...</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="???">Can I cut this one up?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="???">I've never seen inside an Eastern person before. I want to know what it looks like.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Of course you can't. It's a live specimen, as you can very well see.</line>
<line speaker="???">......... Hmph. Boring.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>I, I think... ...I just had a near-death experience!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear! Mr Naruhodo, you're as pale as a corpse!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Then let's leave before I'm mistaken for one!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...what are you doing at the moment, Doctor?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Keeping a close eye on things so no impertinent Easterners think they can look around my office.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Are there such impertinent Easterners around? How terrible.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Yes. You.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">She doesn't mince her words, Miss Susato.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think perhaps it's time we left...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I had no idea there were so many people in the world.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know what you mean. It's really packed here today.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It feels as though it's taken us two hours just to make our way through the crowds to this point.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Has it? I shut my brain down so I didn't really notice, to be honest.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gosh...I do wish I had your absence of mind sometimes, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="???">...There you are. I had a feelin' you lot would show your mugs before long.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Inspector Gregson! I see you're hard at work as usual!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Warm greetings to you. I do hope you've been keepin' well since last we met.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's with all the ceremony? We just saw each other in court this morning.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Not you, sunshine. The gentlewoman so loyally at your side.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Why, thank you, Inspector. How good of you to notice.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He might be a bit rough around the edges, but he's still a proper English gentleman at heart...I suppose.</thought> As you've probably guessed, we were hoping to investigate the scene some more.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Right. Well, that's the young trainee's domain. Oi! Get over here, Gina!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...She seems to be busy playing with a puppy. <thought>Probably giving it a traditional 'East End' training...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">G-Gina?! She's a police officer now?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Amazing, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">She's a good kid, actually. Heart's in the right place, anyway. She's got the detection bug, if you ask me. Yup, I think she'll follow in my footsteps nicely.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I'm bein' transferred. It's time for me to say toodle-oo to London.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no! Really?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's, that's a bit sudden, isn't it? I had no idea. Where are you going to be posted, then? We'll come to see how you're getting along.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Haha, not likely. But you're welcome to try. If you don't mind a trip to France, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">To France?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I'll be workin' in the Paris Police Prefecture. ...Should be right up my alley.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but France! It's an entirely different country! I don't understand. Why would you be sent there?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">That's the way the adult world works, sunshine! Now, don't go pokin' your nose in where it's not wanted. ......... I'm intendin' to take the kid with me when I go.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? You're taking Gina to Paris?!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Well I can't leave her here in London. Who knows what'd become of her.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...I suppose he's worried she'd slip back into slipping her hands into people's pockets and purses...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I don't think he's worried about her pickpocketing, Mr Naruhodo. I think he's worried about the Reaper.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! <thought>Of course! So that's playing on Inspector Gregson's mind too, is it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Anyway, I haven't mentioned any o' this to Gina. So don't go blabbin', you hear me?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">N-No, of course not.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I've gotta keep that divin' diva safe an' sound. ...Until all this is over, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Oi! Did you just call me a bloomin' 'divin' diva' again?!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">So you heard that, did ya? Right, well... Any questions about the scene, you can put 'em to my capable detective diva here.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Alright, you 'eard the boss! Inspector Lestrade's in charge 'ere now!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...I suppose I'd better keep my word and not mention anything about Paris.</thought> So, um, Gina... You've got a new dog, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Isn't 'e great? Toby's 'is name.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, how delightful! He's absolutely adorable!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, the dog does seem lovely. But it's the not-so-lovely Inspector Gregson that's playing on my mind, to be honest...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Oi! That's off limits up there! Try to sneak past me again, an' I'll stuff yer gob full o' the boss's fish an' chips!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes please. I love fish and chips.</thought> I suppose we need special permission...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">These stairs lead up to the experimentation stage. ...Let's go and see what we can find out.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The stage up there is where the experiment was set up. It's very high, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">About thirty feet, I believe. Or nine metres, if you prefer. Craning your neck to see up to it starts to hurt after a while, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, we need to get up there and look around properly. Although if I'm honest, climbing all those stairs makes my chest hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... I think perhaps you should exercise more, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, the Crystal Tower... I can't believe I'm seeing it at such close proximity with my own eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You've really been looking forward to the Great Exhibition, haven't you, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes! When I found out that I had to return to Japan, I'm afraid I cursed my luck.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But here you are, back in London, gazing up at the magnificent tower.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I know. ...Perhaps I was wrong to curse my luck so harshly.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What a shame that the symbolic landmark of the Great Exhibition has been damaged like that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, unfortunately the birdcage crashed in the most prominent position possible. It's the gods giving us a warning, if you ask me: 'Man must travel under his own steam, and not cut corners with instantaneous kinesis.'</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But imagine what might have happened if the birdcage had landed in a slightly different location. The death toll could have been far worse. So I think perhaps it was a blessing in disguise.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, the gods are benevolent, obviously. I did say it was just a warning. 'Man must travel under his own steam, or next time birdcages will rain down on all of you.'</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Your faith is much stronger than I realised.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, how do you think I passed the entrance exam for Yumei University? It wasn't by studying alone!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh look! A flying balloon! I've never seen one in the flesh before!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't understand how they can fly...and so high up as well.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, but think of the view, Mr Naruhodo! You must be able to see for miles and miles.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I do think of it. And it terrifies me. I mean, it would be certain death if you fell out.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm sure they're perfectly safe. After all, they've been invented by some of the brightest minds in the world.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Let's not forget that we know at least one has exploded.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... I'm sure... I'm sure there are other ways to fly!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Here's the scorching on the ground that you mentioned.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, and there's what's left of the green balloon's envelope. All clear evidence of the balloon that exploded on the day of the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Poor Professor Harebrayne. I do feel sorry for him that his dreams have been shattered like this...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Someone's well and truly burst his bubble, as it were! Ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ouch. I'm a bad person...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Gina... ...we were actually hoping that we could investigate the scene again...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, alright. If it's around 'ere, ya can do wot ya like.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! That's alright, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I'm gonna be playin' wiv me new friend 'ere.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ah yes, Toby...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Toby">Woof!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The machine that exploded must be at the top of those stairs, I presume? I haven't actually seen it yet, so if you don't mind...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Sorry, ya can't go up there, Sooze.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">It's like I told 'Oddo yesterday. Even I ain't allowed near that wreck. Wot's it called again? The reason we ain't s'posed to touch it... The Special...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The Special Dispensation for Scientific Equipment Act? Is that what you were thinking of?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">That's the one! That's why only them lot are allowed to investigate it. Wot are they called again? The Friend Sick somefin'...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The Forensic Investigation Team? Is that what you were thinking of?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">That's the one, yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But isn't it the case that the special dispensation has been lifted?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I think so... I don't really get it, to be truthful wiv ya. Yer still s'posed to get permission from some bigwig or other as far as I know. Wot was 'is name again? Um, Lord Strange-somefin'...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm not sure that's quite right, Gina. I think you mean Lord Stronghart perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">That's the one, yeah! Apparently 'e's always watchin' the time or somefin'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So without Lord Stronghart's express permission, we can't investigate on the stage...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Gina... ...we were actually hoping that we could investigate the scene again...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, alright. If it's around 'ere, ya can do wot ya like.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! That's alright, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I'm gonna be playin' wiv me new friend 'ere.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ah yes, Toby...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Toby">Woof!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The machine that exploded must be at the top of those stairs, I presume? I haven't actually seen it yet, so if you don't mind...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Sorry, ya can't go up there, Sooze.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">It's like I told 'Oddo yesterday. Even I ain't allowed near that wreck. Wot's it called again? The reason we ain't s'posed to touch it... The Special...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The Special Dispensation for Scientific Equipment Act? Is that what you were thinking of?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">That's the one! That's why only them lot are allowed to investigate it. Wot are they called again? The Friend Sick somefin'...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The Forensic Investigation Team? Is that what you were thinking of?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">That's the one, yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But isn't it the case that the special dispensation has been lifted?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I think so... I don't really get it, to be truthful wiv ya. Yer still s'posed to get permission from some bigwig or other as far as I know. Wot was 'is name again? Um, Lord Strange-somefin'...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm not sure that's quite right, Gina. I think you mean Lord Stronghart perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">That's the one, yeah! Apparently 'e's always watchin' the time or somefin'!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Actually, we've just recently been to see Lord Stronghart!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Eh?! You wot? You've met 'im?! Last time the boss was called to go an' see 'im... ...'e waited for three hours at the cove's office an' came back snivellin'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Tragic...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, Lord Stronghart has given us permission to examine the scene, as long as we touch nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Oh yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Honestly.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">......... Alright then, go ahead. But if it turns out yer lyin'... ...it'll be the boss who gets it. He'll never eat another chip again in 'is life. So...yer still sayin' all this is above board, are ya?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm, I'm sure everything will be fine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That really would be tragic.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Alright then, them's the stairs. Off ya go.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, thank you, Gina!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">It was great, weren't it? I 'ad a right laugh. It was a new one on me, that. Ya know, bein' in court an' not spendin' the whole time worryin' I'm about to be found out!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...You did keep an awful lot of secrets in all your previous court appearances, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, and 'Oddo's made things 'ard for me every single time an' all!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Just doing my job, Gina.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">But watchin' someone else get it in the neck is a lot o' fun, actually. It was amazin' when you showed that dodgy professor's dodgy experiment was a total fix!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...The 'dodgy' professor as you put it, Gina, is Mr Naruhodo's client.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. I'm starting to wish he wasn't, though...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">It's the boss I feel sorry for. Sent off to do the impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">'E's supposed to arrest that other cove, ain't 'e? An' in time for tomorrow an' all! Ya know, the dodgy engineer. Wot's 'is name again?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Drebber, you mean? Enoch Drebber.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">That's the one, yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So the police are looking for this mysterious man with the black monocle... I guessed they would be.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">It's puttin' too much on the boss if you ask me. 'E says it's givin' 'im gut ache.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Oh dear. But I do wonder if that isn't actually from all the fried food.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So Scotland Yard are trying to track down Mr Enoch Drebber. I wonder if they've had any luck...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">'E's really funny lookin'. Got two eyes wot don't match. Stole a glimpse of a picture of 'im earlier. I mean, I didn't actually pinch it or nuffin'. The old devil's got it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry? Who?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Ya know. That scowlin' Reaper wot's always gluggin' down glasses o' that blood-red plonk.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, Lord van Zieks.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">'E's always 'ad it in for me, that cove. Dunno wot 'e's always scowlin' about, mind. Prob'ly would've been a pretty good boss, as it goes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>She'd rather be the Reaper's apprentice than a detective's trainee?</thought> The way I see it... ...if the choice is between a chip-guzzling detective and a chalice-glugging demigod... ...you're equally badly off with both.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">...I s'pose yer right. I 'adn't thought of it like that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Glad we've put that one to bed...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Anyway, the point is, everyone at the Yard's dead set on findin' the fishy engineer... ...but there don't seem to be no clues to go on. So they're stuck.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>There's nothing that can lead us to Drebber at all...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Where did you find that little mutt then, Gina?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Oi! Don't be so flamin' rude, 'Oddo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Slight overreaction, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">'E ain't no mutt, alright? Toby's...'ow did they put it...? ...Oh, yeah! A 'bone-fide' detective!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I've given 'im a proper title an' everyfin'. It's Chief Inspector Toby to you!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>More senior than Inspector Gregson, is he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ooh, so he's a police dog, is he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The police recruit dogs now?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I've heard that they're already being used officially in Germany as part of their city policing. They're used for chasing criminals and suchlike! They have a wonderful sense of smell, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I have a fairly good sense of smell myself, as it happens. I can tell undergarments that have been freshly laundered from undergarments that...haven't.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Haaah... That's nuffin' compared to this little fella, 'Oddo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh really?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Accordin' to wot the boss said... ...once Toby 'ere's got a good whiff of yer drawers... ...'e could chase that scent to the other side o' the world!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">WHAT?! To, to the other side of the world? You mean... ...he can swim?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo... ...I think you may have missed the point...by rather a wide margin.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I just can't believe this little dog has such an incredible skill...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I'm tellin' ya, 'Oddo, there's gonna be more an' more dogs doin' their bit for the police in future.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! I agree!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Right! One o' these days, they'll be barkin' orders at us lot, not the other way round!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... Sorry, Gina, I don't think I agree with your vision quite that much...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Well anyway. Wotever ya think about that, Toby 'ere is Britain's first police dog! I found 'im down the East End the other day. Someone 'ad just chucked 'im out on the street.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>There you go. I knew she'd lifted him from somewhere...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh Gina, you're such a kind-hearted soul, aren't you? To children and to animals!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">There were a bunch of reporters at the trial today, eh? One of 'em got a sketch of me in the witness stand!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh really?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, I looked pretty good, right? An' that testimony o' mine was spot on!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm not sure that 'spot on' is quite the right description...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">And look, it was in the special edition an' all! I bought a copy.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, that's a lovely picture of you, Gina!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But I thought you couldn't read?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Wot d'ya take me for? I'm crammin' every day!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I started at 'A'...an' I've already got all the way to 'E'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...It could be a long journey for you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gina, have a look at this photograph...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">It's amazin' lookin' down on everyfin' from up there. I love 'igh places, me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? If I'm honest, I can't stand looking down at the ground when I'm high up. I always have to look up.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Shame, I wanted to show ya wot it's like. But there ain't no point now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">If all yer gonna do is look up at the sky, I ain't gonna be able to look down on ya- Wiv ya, sorry. I mean, I don't look down on ya or nuffin'. If ya don't wanna do it, it's your choice.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I didn't think I'd ever go up in a balloon, to be honest. Not in my whole life. But now I'm starting to think I might like to...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">About this, Gina...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">...Yeah, I'm...still learnin' me letters at the moment. I only know 'A' to 'E'! So if it ain't too much bleedin' trouble?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, actually, Gina, it's the back of the card that's important.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Eh? 'Ow come? There's just a dirty old smudge on the back, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It turns out that this is very high-quality French machine oil. It has a very particular scent, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">You don't say! Let's 'ave a whiff then... ......... You sure? I don't smell nuffin'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no, we didn't mean that YOU should smell it!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Oh, right! Ya mean Toby!</line>
<line speaker="Toby">Woof!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">His sense of smell is so good, he can track people over the oceans, can't he?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Professor Harebrayne informs us that this oil is unique to Mr Drebber's workshop.</line>
<line speaker="Toby">*Sniff sniff sniff* *Sniff sniff sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I think he's picked up a scent...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">So ya mean, if 'e follows the scent o' this oil... ...Toby could lead us to that dodgy cove's workshop?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's right! That's exactly what we were hoping.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Alright then, we'll give it a go! I'll just borrow that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...? Wait, when did you...? <thought>Once a pickpocket...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">If I can lead everyone to that Drebber's workshop... ...I'll be the boss's boss before next week!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes, Gina! I'm sure you'll be promoted!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Poor, poor Gregson...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">We're gonna get goin' after that dodgy engineer cove right this minute. Oh, but 'ang on... Someone's s'posed to be on guard duty 'ere all the time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm afraid we can't help. We need to get on with our investigation as well, Gina.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Oh...right. Oh well, never mind. It ain't gonna be me wot gets it in the neck. It'll be the boss.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Poor, poor Gregson again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Ready Toby? Got that oil scent, 'ave ya? Come on then, boy! See ya later!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I do hope the scent of that oil leads them to that swindler's workshop.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I hope so too. Ideally before the dog swims across the Channel to France.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! So this is the machine... ...that was used to deceive people into thinking instantaneous kinesis had taken place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's right. Or rather it WAS the machine. It's a little worse for wear at the moment...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What extraordinary lengths Professor Harebrayne went to in order to obtain the research grant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no no! The professor was tricked as well. He didn't know anything about it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, of course. ...It is amazing, though, isn't it? The scale of the whole affair is so very British.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're right about that. You'd never see such a grand deception in Japan, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh look...is that... ...Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... ...So, I think we're more or less done here, aren't we? Shall we, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Already?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He IS the Reaper, remember. We'd do well to keep our distance, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But we have permission to be here! From the top! We're perfectly well allowed to investigate this machine... as long as we don't touch anything.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">From the top? Do you mean Lord Stronghart?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Exactly. So we can stay here and stare at this wreckage for as long as we like!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>She could have been at the centre of the explosion here and it wouldn't have bent her steel will...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>Ugh... 'Least Approachable Man in the World' winner, ten years in a row...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Be strong, Mr Naruhodo! Your country and your assistant stand firm behind you!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...Lord van Zieks...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm...well... Beautiful weather we're having, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... I thought I was making it quite clear that I didn't want to be disturbed. Apparently you Nipponese are unequipped to read the signs.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Oh, I read them...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">So? What are you doing here? Entry to this area is prohibited.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...well, the thing is...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Lord Chief Justice Stronghart granted us permission to investigate. On the condition that we didn't disturb anything.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...And yet you've managed to disturb me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Never mind. State your business, then.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Come to think of it... ...there are quite a few things I'd like to ask Lord van Zieks about. Not least of which is that awful case, even though it's nothing to do with this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ask away, Mr Naruhodo! You won't know unless you try!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...Klint...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...was the name of your older brother, I understand, Lord van Zieks.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">You Nipponese... I always have to be on guard whenever you're around. So, you've been investigating me, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! No no, it's not like that. <thought>Well alright, it is a bit like that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... My older brother was also a prosecutor. He was the pride of the van Zieks family. But tragically...a vicious killer took him from us.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The Professor, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Heh heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is, is something funny?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">That's the extent of what you've discovered, is it? I shouldn't be surprised.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry? <thought>There's more to it, then?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Lacklustre work is very much your trademark, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... You're too kind. Are you going to tar all 'Nipponese' with the same brush next?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">So tell me...what's your interest in that historic incident?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">As it happens, Lord van Zieks, there's a rather curious case that's come to our attention.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Are you aware of the Madame Tusspells Museum of Waxwork, by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I am, naturally. I believe that since last month, I feature in one of the displays there. For public scorn.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Of course the infamous Reaper of the Bailey would have to be exhibited, wouldn't he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, a particular waxwork has been stolen from the place...and held for ransom.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">A particular waxwork? Which- Wait! You mean...?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. It's the Professor. Mr Sholmes is investigating the case as we speak.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... I...was unaware of that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He's turned as white as a sheet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Are the police trying to locate the engineer, Mr Drebber, already?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Surely that goes without saying.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We're very keen to see him found as well. The trouble is, we don't have much to go on aside from the description of the man we heard in court earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Which, according to Professor Harebrayne... ...was of a tall, thin gentleman who has straight, white hair and wears a black monocle.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...I was just wondering... I mean, I realise it's probably not possible, but...erm...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We'd very much appreciate any more clues you can give us!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Wow. Susato-san...really knows how to take the bull by the horns...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Fine. Why not? I have a photograph of the man here from an investigation ten years ago. Though it appears he already had that black monocle at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...no, nothing. I, I was just surprised that you shared that with us.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">We all need the man's testimony in court tomorrow. Which means we have to do everything we possibly can to track him down in the short time available. ...So why wouldn't I show you the photograph?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>What is it about Lord van Zieks? Sometimes I just can't work him out at all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Are the police trying to locate the engineer, Mr Drebber, already?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Surely that goes without saying.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We're very keen to see him found as well. The trouble is, we don't have much to go on aside from the description of the man we heard in court earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Which, according to Professor Harebrayne... ...was of a tall, thin gentleman who has straight, white hair and wears a black monocle.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...I was just wondering... I mean, I realise it's probably not possible, but...erm...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We'd very much appreciate any more clues you can give us!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Wow. Susato-san...really knows how to take the bull by the horns...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Fine. Why not? I have a photograph of the man here from an investigation ten years ago. Though it appears he already had that black monocle at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...no, nothing. I, I was just surprised that you shared that with us.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">We all need the man's testimony in court tomorrow. Which means we have to do everything we possibly can to track him down in the short time available. ...So why wouldn't I show you the photograph?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>What is it about Lord van Zieks? Sometimes I just can't work him out at all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What a terrible explosion it must have been... Even the steel girders have buckled and twisted in the blast.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And what they call the 'birdcage' was right in the middle of it all, just here.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But look, Mr Naruhodo. That metal grille on the floor... ...looks as though it's designed to open.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It does...doesn't it? <thought>If the floor had opened at the precise moment the explosion occurred... ...the birdcage could have dropped through and disappeared from sight.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I don't think there's any doubt that this was a very elaborate hoax, is there?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This...wasn't here yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Really? But if I'm not mistaken... ...it's the cage in which the victim was standing before he was apparently 'beamed' through the air.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right. The birdcage. According to what Professor Harebrayne said in court, it's made of wood.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Or more precisely...Japanese cypress, I think. And despite having been in an explosion and then falling from a great height, it's relatively unharmed. What wonderfully durable construction, wouldn't you say, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'd understood that the Forensic Investigation Team had taken it away yesterday to examine it. I suppose they must have brought it back here when they'd finished their work...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But sadly not with the body inside it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...No, that's right. <thought>I know we were given strict instructions not to touch anything, but still... ...this is too important a piece of evidence to overlook. We might need it for the trial!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This...wasn't here yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Really? But if I'm not mistaken... ...it's the cage in which the victim was standing before he was apparently 'beamed' through the air.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right. The birdcage. According to what Professor Harebrayne said in court, it's made of wood.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Or more precisely...Japanese cypress, I think. And despite having been in an explosion and then falling from a great height, it's relatively unharmed. What wonderfully durable construction, wouldn't you say, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'd understood that the Forensic Investigation Team had taken it away yesterday to examine it. I suppose they must have brought it back here when they'd finished their work...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But sadly not with the body inside it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...No, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, isn't it exhilarating? All this different architecture from all corners of the world!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It does make you feel a bit like an explorer, doesn't it? I know it's all subjective, but the onion-shaped roofs have rather caught my attention, personally.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...It IS very subjective, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Japanese buildings, with their wood and paper construction, have excellent ventilation. And I've realised that British buildings, being made from brick and stone, are very strong and long-lasting. The more you know about how things are done in other countries, the more you understand your own, I feel.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes, I do agree with you there!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But I can't help wondering what an onion does for the roof of a building... I mean, I suppose it's playing on my mind because I don't like the taste of onions.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...You really oughtn't let your taste in vegetables dictate your taste in roofs, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I hear that a ride on the Ferris wheel is a favourite romantic outing among young London couples.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think the romance would be slightly spoilt by the abject terror, personally. But then I'm not a Londoner.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Are you a little scared of heights, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's not that I'm scared, not at all! It's just that staying on the ground seems so much safer.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, perhaps I shall have to ask Iris and Mr Sholmes to accompany me on it, in that case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... When you put it like that, part of me does want to give it a try...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... It is complicated for you, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Look at that horn-shaped transmitting device. Isn't it amazing?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's exactly what I thought when I first saw it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It makes you think, doesn't it? If only it had just been a normal horn, none of this would have happened.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's almost exactly what I thought as well! I bet I can predict what you're going to say next in that case. You're about to say 'nothing ever goes to plan', aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no. I would never say something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">However much I look at them, I just can't come to terms with those temari handballs floating in the sky.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You've been glaring at them constantly since we came up here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry. The feelings of wanting to ride in one and wanting never to set foot in one are fighting it out inside me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But if you don't look where you're walking, you might fall from the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't think I'd notice. That's how fiercely the battle inside me is raging.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I think you should make peace with riding in one, Mr Naruhodo. It really would be much safer that way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Look here, Miss Susato...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes, the wood's cracked and broken a little. I suppose because it fell from such a height?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, from the height at which the balloon was flying, down into the Crystal Tower below. A fall of about thirty feet. ...Or nine metres.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Leaving the man inside tragically dead.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Look here, Miss Susato...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes, the wood's cracked and broken a little. I suppose because it fell from such a height?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, from the height at which the balloon was flying, down into the Crystal Tower below. A fall of about thirty feet. ...Or nine metres.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Leaving the man inside tragically dead.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...Ah, the file I requested for the trial tomorrow. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Are you alright?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Who, who is this man, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord van Zieks's apprentice, apparently. <thought>So I'm not the only one. Susato-san can see it too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Um...Lord van Zieks... ...may we speak with your apprentice for a moment?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">With him? ...Why?</line>
<line speaker="Apprentice">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Kazuma-sama!</line>
<line speaker="Apprentice">......... ...Kazu...ma...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>I don't believe it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Your, your posture... Your presence... It can only be... It's you...isn't it, Kazuma-sama?!</line>
<line speaker="Apprentice">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I felt something strange the very first time I encountered this cloaked figure. As if I knew him somehow... Can it...? Can it really be you, Kazuma?</thought> W-W-Wait! <thought>Too late...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What's going on here?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What is your interest in my apprentice exactly? You act as if you know the man or something.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, um...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Since when has he been in your care?! I don't recall you having an apprentice before I left Britain six months ago.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Lord Stronghart introduced him to me about three months ago now. With instructions to mentor him as a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But he didn't tell you why, did he?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... The man appears to be suffering from amnesia. He's forgotten every last detail about himself.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">He has amnesia?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Tomorrow he will appear in court at my side.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">He's to serve as my judicial assistant. On Lord Stronghart's orders.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He'll...be in court with us...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Now then, unless I'm much mistaken, I believe this conversation has run its course...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh... Yes, um, thank you. <thought>I definitely saw a reaction there... When Susato-san called out like that, it really seemed to hit a nerve... When she called out 'Kazuma-sama'...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. Yesterday, in fact. At Lord van Zieks's office.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I see... ......... And if...if Kazuma-sama really is still alive... ...it means that Mr Sholmes lied to us.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I know. <thought>We're going to need to speak to him about that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">You're going to have to leave now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The Forensic Investigation Team are due to arrive shortly. If they find you here, it will...cause problems.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What sort of problems?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Foreign affairs problems.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Well we could do without that.</thought> Alright, we'll be on our way. Let's go, Miss Susato.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We'd better not try going up those stairs to the stage area now. If we were to bump into the Forensics Investigation Team, it sounds like it could make trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Gina... ...we were actually hoping that we could investigate the scene again...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, alright. If it's around 'ere, ya can do wot ya like.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! That's alright, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I'm gonna be playin' wiv me new friend 'ere.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ah yes, Toby...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Toby">Woof!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Apparently we can't look around on the stage now because the Forensic Investigation Team are at work. Can't you do anything, Gina? In your capacity as Inspector Lestrade?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Look, I'd like to 'elp you out. But I'm just a trainee, ain't I? Ain't nuffin' I can do.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>When it suits you, yes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm sure Gina and little Toby won't let us down! Now then... ...do you think we ought to try to speak with Mr Sholmes at this point? We have things to discuss and I'm dying to meet him again after all these months.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, it's quite possible he might know something useful, you're right. We ought to find him at Madame Tusspells. He's supposed to be working there as a temporary waxwork exhibit.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! Iris told me all about his latest unusual venture!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! No wonder it's called the House of Horrors... I'd like to turn on my heels and go straight home. Via the confectionery.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Being scared makes you crave sweets? I can understand that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I was looking forward to a reunion after six months away, but... ...there's no sign of Mr Sholmes anywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's strange. He should be here investigating the abduction of the waxwork... Oh well. I suppose we'll just have to come back again later.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! No wonder it's called the House of Horrors... I'd like to turn on my heels and go straight home. Via the confectionery.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Being scared makes you crave sweets? I can understand that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">But you know, there's something about that waxwork over there... It looks exactly like Mr Sholmes down to the very last detail!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Aha!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, sorry. I think you'll find... <thought>...that's the temporary waxwork himself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Ah, the friend of my dedicated employee...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, yes, hello again. It's Ryunosuke. Ryunosuke Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">I must say, I am quite spellbound by the great detective. He is a marvel. My precious waxwork is already back where it belongs.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You, you don't mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">But yes! The mystery is solved already.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Wow. Mr Sholmes can really engage his brain when he's hungry enough...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">So as you can see, he has returned to his...habitual duties.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">His...habitual duties...?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Alors...do not disturb, uh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Poor Susato-san. She looks very perplexed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Here we are again at the House of Horrors. I'm afraid I haven't got used to the place yet. I'd still like to turn on my heels and go straight home. Via the confectionery, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Susato-san really is after something sweet today, isn't she?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Look, Mr Naruhodo! Look at that waxwork! ...I'm quite sure it wasn't there before... It looks exactly like Mr Sholmes down to the very last detail!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Aha!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, sorry. I think you'll find... <thought>...that's the temporary waxwork himself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Ah, the friend of my dedicated employee...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, yes, hello again. It's Ryunosuke. Ryunosuke Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">I must say, I am quite spellbound by the great detective. He is a marvel. My precious waxwork is already back where it belongs.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You, you don't mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">But yes! The mystery is solved already.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Wow. Mr Sholmes can really engage his brain when he's hungry enough...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">So as you can see, he has returned to his...habitual duties.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">His...habitual duties...?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Alors...do not disturb, uh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Poor Susato-san. She looks very perplexed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, what a horrifying scene! A murderer caught in the grisly act!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know. And in case you were wondering, it's the one with the big knife that's supposed to be the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I...don't think anybody would be in any doubt about that, surely?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And did you know that according to the description, the bathtub at the back has no particular significance.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What?! Really? I would have thought it was meant to show that the killer also worked in a bathhouse peddling criminal wares.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Aha! We have a new theory...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah yes, the heavy curtains in the middle of the House of Horrors... Whatever's on the other side of them, you just know it's going to be terrifying, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The sign says it's the Madame Tusspells Special Exhibit. It seems you have to pay extra to go inside.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know! Can you believe that?! Pay more money, as if we haven't been scared enough already!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...It's not my doing, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That old policeman isn't here now, obviously. I still can't believe he just happened to be on the jury, though.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'd understood that London has a population of six million people. And yet... ...you do seem to run into the same people disproportionately often, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, there's a stepladder there, look.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh... Yes... A stepladder...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think perhaps we should let the proprietress know that someone's left it out. The stepladder, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Why do I feel as though I just managed to sidestep an argument...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... This one's posture reveals his weakness.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The killer's stance leaves him wide open to attack. I'm quite sure I could see him off... ...with a Susato Takedown, then a Susato Squash and finally a Susato Smash.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">R-Right...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And if that doesn't render the culprit unconscious, a Susato Slam should finish him.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A, a Susato Slam?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! I'm sorry, it's...rather hard to explain. Leave yourself open slightly, and I'll demonstrate...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Absolutely not.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We really do need to speak with Mr Sholmes, and I am longing to say hello again... ...but where is he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I think you might find...that he's quite nearby, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! What, what do you...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed, my dear fellows...it is I! The world-famous great detective and waxwork... Herlock Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Susato-san! Susato-saaaaaan!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My most humble apologies...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I thought I'd died and gone to eternal paradise for a moment...via London.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear madam...allow me to make amends by offering you a tasty free deduction at some point.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...As long as it's not of questionable street food quality.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I don't understand. Why are you working as a waxwork here, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Merely a secret identity, you understand. Though the case is largely solved now.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Largely solved?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We're talking about the waxwork abduction, I presume?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed we are, my good fellow. As I predicted, it was as easy as proverbial pie. Though I confess...I'm yet to partake of a pie, proverbial or otherwise. Or any food so far today for that matter.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That stomach rumble echoed around the whole museum...</thought> So how did you manage to solve it so quickly?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, well, do remember I said it was largely solved. Anyway, I simply negotiated with the culprit. Are you familiar with the so-called 'telephone'?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes! It's a most modern invention, allowing you to hold a conversation with people far away. In Japan, only the imperial capital and a handful of other cities are connected as yet.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">This morning, a telephone call was received here from the perpetrator of the abduction. As such, I was able to negotiate terms, and in the end, the waxwork was returned.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's amazing!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Just between you and I... ...it would appear the culprit had always intended to return the stolen waxwork in any event.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! But...I thought whoever was responsible had demanded a ransom, no?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes. I think perhaps... ...the ransom demand was necessary to avoid unwanted suspicion regarding the true motive.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But...does that not mean... ...your negotiating was entirely unnecessary?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... A fact that I must ask you to keep from Madame Tusspells at all costs! A hungry young Iris awaits my return to Baker Street, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Poor Iris...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Now then, do I sense that you have some business with this great waxwork?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We're in the process of trying to track somebody down.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, a man by the name of Enoch Drebber. He's the swindler who duped Professor Harebrayne, and the engineer who built the kinesis machine.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">A swindler and an engineer? Quite the modern man.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He also seems to be a conjuror of sorts, too, with considerable knowledge of stage magic. We really need to locate him before the trial resumes tomorrow morning. But we have so few clues to go on, that's the trouble. ...Do you have any good ideas?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I have no data yet. It is a capital mistake to have good ideas before one has data. If I knew something of the man's appearance, at least, I may be in a better position to help.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, Drebber's appearance...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Fortunately for you, however, presently I have little to occupy myself and little to fill my stomach. As soon as you find any clue - no matter how small - I should gladly give you my thoughts on it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes...did you lie to us?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear Mr Naruhodo...stay that piercing stare. What is this about?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Last winter, when we were first on our way to Britain aboard the steamship... ...your words were very clear:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">'So then...let us unravel this mystery... ...and discover what events led to this curious murder.'</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You told us that it was murder. And you examined Kazuma-sama's body.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed. And wherein lies the problem?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We met him earlier today. The 'victim', Kazuma Asogi.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... You're quite sure?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">He...was wearing some sort of mask, and was apparently suffering from amnesia. But yes, I'm quite sure. It was Kazuma-sama.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You must have known at the time, Mr Sholmes. That he...wasn't actually dead.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Well, I can only assume I was swept up in the murderous atmosphere of the moment. But the fellow wasn't dead at all? Ah ha ha ha ha hah! Priceless! ...I don't suppose that performance would pass muster, would it, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I could believe that the crewmen present at the time made a mistake. But not you...Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... I will now tell you something of the first importance, my dear fellow: Great detectives are wont to lie. ...It will serve you well to remember that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Please, Mr Sholmes...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Tomorrow in court, you will find yourself on the threshold of a very great mystery. For now, I'm afraid that is all I can say.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Odie Asman... Yes, a fearsome adversary.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? You, you mean you've fought him?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I once infiltrated his criminal organisation in order to investigate the man and his activities. But he saw through my disguise instantly. I still remember what the man said to me now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...What was it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">'Whoever saw such a tall old lady?'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Old lady?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed! But my special disguise hasn't seen the light of day again since that humiliation. Mrs Minicle is retired!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Mrs Minicle? I would give my right arm to see that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes, would you cast your eyes over this photographic print?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's of Mr Enoch Drebber... The face of the engineer we seek.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, all Englishmen look broadly the same, of course. So looking at the photograph won't...be particularly...... instructive.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Are you alright, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Ah. Yes, forgive me. Very interesting, this. Very interesting, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What's wrong, Mr Sholmes? You've turned quite pale all of a sudden...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Well...what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As I explained to you when you arrived, the missing waxwork has been returned. And I personally reinstalled it in the exhibit from which it was taken...behind those thick curtains.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, yes... The 'Professor' exhibit, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Would you like to see it? For a mere five shillings? ...That's a special, one-time-only price, you understand.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The opportunity won't come again, I might add. Wouldn't you like to see the fruits of my labour?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Well, we do have a rather pressing investigation to carry out. Perhaps we could postpone...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The price is a very reasonable five shilling. I think you'll find it's well worth it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Are you...? Are you being quite serious, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Surely you need only look at my expression to ascertain if this is seriousness or silliness?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I can never tell with you, that's the point.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Very well, it couldn't hurt. Here's your five shillings.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Gratefully received. So, the special exhibit awaits behind the curtain. I invite you to peruse it at your leisure.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, the money's been spent, so... Let's go and see the special exhibit!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Hm, through those heavy curtains at last...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Five shillings we've had to pay... It doesn't seem right somehow that Mr Sholmes slipped the money into his own pocket, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No... Ah! We could ask Gina to retrieve it for us. Using her special skills.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Pickpocketing police officers and diddling detectives... Is this what makes Britain 'Great'? Not to mention demigod prosecutors taking the law into their own hands or chip-loving inspectors.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Inspector Gregson comes off rather well in that list, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He's gone back to his wax 'work'...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes! Mr Sholmes is renowned as being a master of disguise, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Does pretending to be a waxwork count as a disguise?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... I, I felt a shiver run down my spine as soon as we walked in here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Susato! I say we turn on our heels and go straight home...via a really big confectionery!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We...we certainly can't do that. We've paid five shillings already!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...True. Actually, now I'm looking a little more closely... ...we've paid good money to see an exhibit that's clearly incomplete...! The nerve of the great diddling detective is far more terrifying than anything else in this place!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">This must be what Mr Sholmes meant when he said the case was 'largely solved'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Be that as it may... ...Mr Sholmes heavily implied there'd be a clue about the engineer in here, didn't he? But where...?</thought> Since we've paid five shillings, let's do five shillings' worth of investigation, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, we, we will get what we paid for!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Is that fear or frustration...that's making Susato-san's voice tremble?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">This part of the exhibit is just as disturbing as the rest. It looks so real...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It seems to be a young man in a white overcoat.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And he has a large shovel in his hand, too, look.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Perhaps we should investigate in a little more detail...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't see his face very well, can you? Perhaps if I just... </line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Do, do you think you should be manhandling the exhibits, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'll put it back exactly as it was, don't worry.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's this here?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, this would appear to be a lens in the middle, so... ...I believe it's probably a camera.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A, a camera! But it's so small! British technology is incredible, isn't it? I mean, what about Mr Sholmes's skin prints?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I think perhaps you should treat Mr Sholmes's inventions as...exceptions to the rule. But anyway, why would the man be in a graveyard at night with a camera?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I wonder... Perhaps he was trying to capture the moment a dead body came back as a ghost on film!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... We'll just borrow this for a little while, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">By looking at the photographic plate inside the camera, we can see what picture was taken.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's a photographic plate?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's a piece of glass coated in a special emulsion that reacts to the light coming in through the lens. If we open the cover at the back of the camera, we should find it. Let's have a look!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>You should see yourself, Susato-san. Your eyes are shining. You really do like machinery, don't you?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's this here?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, this would appear to be a lens in the middle, so... ...I believe it's probably a camera.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A, a camera! But it's so small! British technology is incredible, isn't it? I mean, what about Mr Sholmes's skin prints?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I think perhaps you should treat Mr Sholmes's inventions as...exceptions to the rule. But anyway, why would the man be in a graveyard at night with a camera?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I wonder... Perhaps he was trying to capture the moment a dead body came back as a ghost on film!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... We'll just borrow this for a little while, I think. By looking at the photographic plate inside the camera, we can see what picture was taken.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's a photographic plate?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's a piece of glass coated in a special emulsion that reacts to the light coming in through the lens. If we open the cover at the back of the camera, we should find it. Let's have a look!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>You should see yourself, Susato-san. Your eyes are shining. You really do like machinery, don't you?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">What a large shovel... He's holding it rather ominously, isn't he? What on earth was the man doing with a shovel in a graveyard in the middle of the night?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...Miss Susato...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's...a spade, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... No, it's a shovel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no, shovels are for digging. That's for scooping up loose material. It's a spade.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We've been through this, Mr Naruhodo. It's a shovel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no no. Although...we haven't considered trowels...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... We've allowed ourselves to be distracted, I feel. Perhaps we should concentrate on what the man was doing with the implement.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So we're going to bury the hatchet?</thought> You're right, though... What was the man doing in the graveyard in the first place, that's the real question.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's quite a large lamp the man's carrying. Or is it a lantern? It's not unlike a Japanese chochin paper lantern actually, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Lamp, lantern, chochin... The point is it casts very little light. To be walking alone in a graveyard at night with only this... Well, I certainly couldn't do it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm not sure I could visit a graveyard at all, even in broad daylight, to be honest.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It doesn't matter if they're here in Britain or Japan, graveyards are scary.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Now I come to think of it, this is the first time I've seen a British grave. According to what I've read, the custom in Britain is to bury the dead as they are, without cremation.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Whaaat?! But, but if you do that... ...you might accidentally bury people while they're still alive!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm not sure that would be worse than accidentally incinerating people while they're still alive.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I think we can both agree that it's best not to be still alive when our time comes, then.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...And what am I to say to that?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">This must be the killer! The fiend known as the Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I think so. According to what Madame Tusspells said... ...he killed five victims, all of noble or royal blood.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The waxwork is so lifelike, isn't it? Like all the models in this place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know. It looks like it could start moving at any moment, doesn't it? ...If only it had a head, that is. <thought>Perhaps we should examine it in a little more detail...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">So this is the condemned man...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. The so-called 'Professor'.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Then, then perhaps... ...his head was ch-chopped off by a guillotine! But, but unable to find peace, he, he emerged from his grave as a headless g-g-ghost!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Do, do we have to entertain such terrifying ideas, Miss Susato? Anyway, I'm sure the model had a head once. There's a metal fitting for it, see?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Then...perhaps Mr Sholmes absent-mindedly forgot to reattach it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's an extremely absent-minded detective you're describing, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Or perhaps... ...the thief absent-mindedly forgot to include the head when he or she returned it to the museum?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And that would be an extremely absent-minded thief. <thought>Could there have been some reason why only the head wasn't returned?</thought> Well, whatever the reason... ...it means we don't know what the face of the infamous Professor looked liked, do we? ......... Oh... There's something caught just inside the convict's jacket here... It...looks like a piece of broken glass. <thought>And quite a big piece, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's very thick, isn't it? About five times thicker than normal window glazing, I'd say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Where could such a thick piece of glass have come from, I wonder...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I suppose it must have been made thick to increase its strength?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But why?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, perhaps... ...because the glass had to span a particularly wide area. Such as in a big building, for example.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...well we've seen a large glass building recently, haven't we? And some of the glass was broken, too.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You don't mean...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Exactly. The Crystal Tower at the Great Exhibition.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But why would glass from the Crystal Tower be lodged inside this waxwork's jacket?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It makes you think, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Earlier in court we established that the kinesis experiment was a trick. And now we discover this fragment of glass here in this waxwork. ...Is it just a coincidence?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">So this is the condemned man...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. The so-called 'Professor'.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Then, then perhaps... ...his head was ch-chopped off by a guillotine! But, but unable to find peace, he, he emerged from his grave as a headless g-g-ghost!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Do, do we have to entertain such terrifying ideas, Miss Susato? Anyway, I'm sure the model had a head once. There's a metal fitting for it, see?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Then...perhaps Mr Sholmes absent-mindedly forgot to reattach it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's an extremely absent-minded detective you're describing, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Or perhaps... ...the thief absent-mindedly forgot to include the head when he or she returned it to the museum?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And that would be an extremely absent-minded thief. <thought>Could there have been some reason why only the head wasn't returned?</thought> Well, whatever the reason... ...it means we don't know what the face of the infamous Professor looked liked, do we?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This piece of glass is almost as thick as it is wide.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I've never seen anything like it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you were to compare it to a human, only Mr Sholmes has such thick skin.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">There's really no need for such a comparison, Mr Naruhodo, as you well know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Anyway, it can only be from the Crystal Tower, surely?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I think so, too. It was probably made especially to meet the demands of that great structure.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What a wonderful machine!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You really love contraptions like this, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes! Anything mechanical I find absolutely irresistible.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Almost irresistible, surely?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, whenever I see a pocket watch, for example, I can't help myself. I simply have to take it apart.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's...worrying.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, Father tells the time by the rumblings of his stomach now. He's given up having a watch.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Poor Professor Mikotoba...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Look, Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">On the bellows just here...there seem to be some very dark red stains.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, you're right... <thought>It looks like blood actually...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Oh, oh my...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm, I'm sure it's not what you're thinking! Ha ha ha...ha.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Look, Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">On the bellows just here...there seem to be some very dark red stains.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, you're right... <thought>It looks like blood actually...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Oh, oh my...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm, I'm sure it's not what you're thinking! Ha ha ha...ha.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh look! The cover came open!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, now...there should be a glass plate inside. You have to change the plate with each new photograph you want to take, you see. .........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">There is no plate. It's been removed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, what a pity. But I suppose if you think about it... ...this wouldn't be the actual camera that was used at the time, just like the waxwork isn't the actual person. So we'd never have found a photographic print of the executed convict coming back to life anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh... Yes, you're quite right of course...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Poor Susato-san. She looks devastated.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Wh-What on earth...? How can...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I, I don't believe it! A black monocle!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! Is, is it possible that this man is...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes... It's Enoch Drebber!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The colour of his hair is different, but...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...It's unmistakably him!</line>
<line speaker="???">Indeed it is.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">This man is the subject of your present hunt, I believe?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's...that's right. Just who is this man? Why is he here in this exhibit?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And why does the convict behind him have no head?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...The head was missing when the model was returned by the thief who stole it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What a surprise.</thought> So then the case isn't yet solved, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Did I not say so myself? 'Largely solved' were my words, I believe. But I must locate the missing head 'tout de suite' as Madame would say, or I'll be in grave trouble. A very hungry Iris still awaits my return to Baker Street... preferably with rations!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Aaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Do you know, though... Something about this room is strange!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Strange? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, the displays in the House of Horrors are supposed to depict real events, are they not?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed they are, Miss Susato. Do go on...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And, as terrifying as they are, the scenes in the other exhibits are believable. But this one... This surely couldn't ever really have happened, could it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... I think it's time I educated you a little... ...about the nature of the incidents involving the Professor ten years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't see his face very well, can you? Perhaps if I just... </line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Do, do you think you should be manhandling the exhibits, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'll put it back exactly as it was, don't worry. So this...is Enoch Drebber...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What an extraordinary coincidence, coming across a model of the very man we're looking for.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If only this waxwork was a living model like Mr Sholmes. Then we'd have found our man.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And I would certainly have fainted again.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I believe I told you a little about the Professor yesterday, did I not? He took the lives of five victims...every one being either a member of the aristocracy or royalty. All were attacked by an enormous hunting hound and had their throats ripped from their bodies.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh gosh! An enormous hound? How awful...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">After taking the life of his fifth victim, the killer was apprehended. It was a case of unprecedented magnitude in Britain, you understand. Accordingly... ...the Professor was tried in a closed court. No members of the public were permitted.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A closed court? So you mean that the Professor's identity...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As you've surmised, my dear fellow. His identity was never made public. Naturally, he was found guilty, and was summarily sentenced to death by hanging. He was buried in a grave at Lowgate Cemetery, which adjoins the rear of the prison where he had been held. However...that was not the end of the affair.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The very night that he was buried, the convicted man... came back to life.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! C-Came back to life?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">He clawed his way out of the ground, and emerged into the moonlit graveyard. The exhibit here depicts that very scene, as described by the sole witness to those chilling events.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There was a witness?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But of course, my dear fellow. It was none other than...the young man in the white overcoat.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Enoch Drebber... He saw it happen?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So this is a waxwork model of Enoch Drebber...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ten years ago... ...the convicted Professor, having been gibbetted and buried, emerged from his grave in the dead of night. The sole witness to that unimaginable scene...was this young man. From appearances, I would say he was about twenty years old.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's so horrifying...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Scared out of his wits, the young Drebber ran to a nearby police station to report the incident. And the sheer terror of what he'd seen is said to have turned his hair white overnight.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, as shown in the photograph we have of him. His hair is completely white.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">For the following few days, the story of what he'd seen was on every front page in the capital. The public was frantic for every last detail about the killer who'd come back to life. As you've seen, an exhibit was even created here at Madame Tusspells.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I can quite understand why the man's hair turned white, certainly. But what I don't understand... ...is what Mr Drebber was doing in the first place... ...in a lonely graveyard, in the middle of the night.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, what...was he up to?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The Professor's acts of terror threw London's upper classes into complete panic ten years ago. It was a great scandal, one might say...at the very highest levels of society. And since the killer's identity was never made public, rumours abounded. After all, no killer had ever before systematically employed a dog as a weapon of murder.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I can imagine the impact the case must have had.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But in time, of course, the rumours abated. So too did talk of the shocking witness account of the convict who came back to life. It was forgotten. Dismissed as a dubious ghost story. As a preposterous parlour tale.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But...but why did people stop believing it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Why, simply because there was no resurrection to speak of. As was established in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What, what do you mean by 'no resurrection'?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The police investigated the grave in Lowgate Cemetery and published their findings. The convict's body was found to be buried exactly where it had been following the execution.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No! But that would mean Mr Drebber... ...must have lied to the police and the newspapers!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...That would appear to be the only logical explanation, yes. The young man subsequently vanished from society and nothing has been heard of him since. It's rather striking, then, that he should resurface now... don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Of course the convicted murderer couldn't really have come back to life. That's not possible. But Drebber's hair is unusually white, and if that really did happen overnight as a result of shock... ...it's hard to believe the incident was an out-and-out lie...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes, could you look at this photograph again?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... I see. So that's it...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? Have you worked something out?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">There is indeed one deduction to be made from this photograph, yes. Each time you show it to me, it will cost you five shillings. Otherwise...I have nothing to add.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Wonderful. And nothing for me to take away either.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">W-W-Wot the bleedin' Nora, 'Oddo?! Wot 'ave you gone an' done?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gina! What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I, I asked Iris, and she said this is where ya'd be, so... SO!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">G-Gina! Not so loud in the museum!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Madame Tusspells will have you take a position as a waxwork if you're not careful.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think there might be a more pressing concern!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I, I still 'ad some flash powder left from six months ago, so... SO!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Alright, Gina, we understand! But please...put down the gun!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Sorry, I...I got scared.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>You should try being the one on the other end of the barrel.</thought> So...what brings you here, Gina?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Wot brings me 'ere? Wot d'ya think?! We found it! We found that dodgy cove's workshop!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! You found Drebber's workshop?!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yup! Toby's nose took me straight there! The boss an' the others are headin' over there now in a drag. So come on! Here's the address. I got the boss to write it out.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, thank you, Gina! We'll make our way there at once.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Alright then! See ya there!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...You go. Don't mind me. I'll just stay here...being still.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I know my place...in the exhibit over there...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear, someone is feeling sorry for himself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Let's go, Mr Sholmes! You're coming!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Your words hearten me, I must say. But if I were to shirk my duties here... ...Madame would have me pay monetary recompense and Iris's dinner plate would be empty once more.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Forget that! I'll pay for everything!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Then there's not a moment to lose, my dear fellow! I shall hail a carriage at once!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>No offer to share the cost from Mr Sholmes, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I shall gladly pay half, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you, Miss Susato. Right, let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That looks like...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! It's another super-high-voltage instantaneous kinesis machine!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed it would appear so. Though only a prototype, naturally.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Ah, so ya got 'ere, then?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gina! Well done for finding this place! And in such little time... You've really worked miracles!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">It's Toby 'ere who's the miracle worker.</line>
<line speaker="Toby">Woof!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Ah...I thought you lot would show up before long.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hello, Inspector. <thought>That's one knitted brow... He looks like he's eating a lemon, not a bag of fish and chips...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">So, Inspector...is there any sign of the engineer?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Sadly not. We didn't find a soul in here.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...what a shame.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, thank you for letting us know about this place and giving us the chance to investigate.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Accordin' to what Gina tells me, we only found it thanks to a clue that you lot turned up. I wouldn't wanna, say, go to Paris with a debt of gratitude unpaid now, would I?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Anyway, if you're hopin' to snoop around in here, I'd get crackin'. Lord van Zieks and the Forensic Investigation Team are on their way here as we speak.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Them again...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I imagine you've got the picture by now. They don't take too kindly to lawyer types.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So then, my dear fellow! Let's turn this place upside-down whilst we have the chance!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">And you, Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">They take even less kindly to 'great detectives' than they do to lawyers.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah ha ha ha ha ha ha ha hah! Very droll, Gregson, very droll. But you may consider me nothing more than an inconspicuous waxwork model!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Right then...let's see what we can find in here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah...this appears to be most interesting. Yes, most interesting indeed, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's an impressive-looking back massager, that's for sure. I've no doubt that if you hit your shoulders a few times with that, your aches and pains would soon go away.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... It's a Royal Society trophy for excellence in science. A young scientist could wish for no higher honour.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Would you like a massage?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no! No, I'm fine, thank you! <thought>I had no idea it was such a grand thing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think it's becoming increasingly clear... ...that there's much more to this Mr Enoch Drebber than conjuring tricks.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...I couldn't agree more, my dear madam. And how about you, Mr Naruhodo? Wouldn't you like to take it with you? For your tired shoulders, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He's not going to let that go, is he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's curious though, isn't it? You would expect such an important trophy to be proudly on display somewhere, not haphazardly cast aside. English gentlemen can be quite a mystery at times...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah...this appears to be most interesting. Yes, most interesting indeed, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's an impressive-looking back massager, that's for sure. I've no doubt that if you hit your shoulders a few times with that, your aches and pains would soon go away.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... It's a Royal Society trophy for excellence in science. A young scientist could wish for no higher honour.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Would you like a massage?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no! No, I'm fine, thank you! <thought>I had no idea it was such a grand thing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think it's becoming increasingly clear... ...that there's much more to this Mr Enoch Drebber than conjuring tricks.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...I couldn't agree more, my dear madam. And how about you, Mr Naruhodo? Wouldn't you like to take it with you? For your tired shoulders, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He's not going to let that go, is he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's curious though, isn't it? You would expect such an important trophy to be proudly on display somewhere, not haphazardly cast aside. English gentlemen can be quite a mystery at times...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What on earth is this?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">An 'aeroplane', Mr Naruhodo. One day, scientists believe it will allow humans to fly freely in the skies.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Is that how the trick will be described, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, it's actually suspended by a thin, but very strong cable, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Well...this model is, yes. But a real aeroplane would actually fly high in the sky.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...While suspended from somewhere even higher in the sky, of course. Because large metal objects obviously can't really stay in mid-air unsupported!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...So to you the solution is...ever taller towers?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm sorry, Mr Naruhodo. That machine is covered by the Special Dispensation for Scientific Equipment Act. There would be serious repercussions if you were to examine it! From the Crown and the government.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">.........</line>
<line speaker="Gina">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well those two don't seem to be holding back.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It's quite hollow inside. No working parts or devices of deception to be seen, my dear fellow.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">No loose change dropped on the floor or nuffin'. Not even a bone for Toby 'ere...my dear fella.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">British people are very much ruled by their own ideals, aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I think that's just these two, Miss Susato.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This door...doesn't want to open.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, looks like it's got a pretty hefty lock on it.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">There's a specialist locksmith on his way over from the Yard. So hands off till he gets here!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">With permission, Inspector, I could have that lock open in less than a minute.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Well you don't have permission. An' no one's givin' it to you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Gregson looked as though he really enjoyed that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, there's no sound of anybody on the other side.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No. Drebber must have fled at the first sign of danger.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This... This is... It's a European-style quiver of arrows! With steel bolts inside!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Do you suppose...?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Crossbow bolts, these. And just the right size for the bow you lot turned up at the exhibition grounds.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In other words...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yup. That's more evidence to support your theory. It all goes to show that Drebber was the one pullin' the strings behind the scenes of the whole scam.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This... This is... It's a European-style quiver of arrows! With steel bolts inside!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Do you suppose...?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Crossbow bolts, these. And just the right size for the bow you lot turned up at the exhibition grounds.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In other words...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yup. That's more evidence to support your theory. It all goes to show that Drebber was the one pullin' the strings behind the scenes of the whole scam.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's a little metal plaque here, look. 'Fostering burgeoning talent for the future of scientific discovery'.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...It seems rather ironic, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But clearly Mr Drebber really was a very talented scientist.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is something wrong, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well...I thought I heard a noise. From the far side of that door. Well, Gina? Did you hear it too?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Y-Yeah, I 'eard it an' all. Wot d'ya reckon, Toby?</line>
<line speaker="Toby">Woof, woof!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Right, mind the grease!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Whoever's in there, open up! This is Scotland Yard!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my... Someone IS in there!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Argh! This rotten, bleedin' lock!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear Gregson, as I said only minutes ago... ...if only it were countenanced, I could unlock that door in less than a minute.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">...! ......... Fine. I'll take the rap for it. Just get us through that blasted door!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">There! You may enter at will.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>You've confused minutes with seconds, I think...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Time is of the essence, I feel. What are we waiting for?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Nothin' for it, I suppose. This is an emergency.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">There's a strong possibility that beyond that door...is the engineer you all seek. Be prepared for action, my dear fellow!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What...? What's happened in here? <thought>Why is everything upside-down?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Rats! There ain't no one in 'ere after all!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But, but there must be! It was only moments ago that we heard those noises.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Maybe that was the sound of Drebber running away.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But there's only one door into this room!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And no windows that could afford an escape route. Those skylights are too high.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...? What's that up there? Are they footprints...on the ceiling?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Blow me! What have we here, then? Looks like someone was tryin' to burn somethin' in a hurry.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, that looks like a set of blueprints!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">To what?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">To that Professor Harebrayne's barmy machine, is it? Blimey! If we'd had these, there'd have been no need to muck about tryin' to investigate all that scrap metal!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">There is something of great interest here, too. This rope was lying on the floor at the foot of that pillar.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A rope? What's significant about that?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Never mind. You see, but you do not observe, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We must investigate the entire room thoroughly! And before the Forensic Investigation Team arrive, too!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Almost every piece of furniture is upside-down!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Even Mr Sholmes's suite isn't ever in this much of a mess.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You're in no position to comment on mess, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...But I suppose it's not quite the same thing, is it? I mean, it's not messy in here per se. It's that everything is literally upside-down.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But why...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's no denying it, is there? They're footprints.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, it would appear so. And I simply can't imagine how they came to be there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Isn't there a Susato Shoot-Up or something? Like a Susato Takedown, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I'm no wonder woman, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That would make her almost superhuman, I suppose...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's a really lovely model. It looks just like a real flying balloon!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I think it's probably staying aloft on the same principle as a full-sized balloon, using gas.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...A green flying balloon... It does have the hallmarks of that amazing deception at the Great Exhibition, doesn't it? <thought>Could it be... ...that the whole thing was planned here in this very workshop?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's a very large safe. I don't suppose even Mr Sholmes could open that lock. Although if you were a thief, you could just steal the entire thing, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's bolted to the floor to prevent exactly that sort of underhand trick, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well then...you could just steal the floor as well, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm sorry, but you really aren't making any sense at all... Anyway, I think we can agree that whatever is inside must be very important.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...Mr Sholmes? Have you found something?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, Mr Naruhodo. Yes, in point of fact, something rather fascinating. What do you make...of this?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm, let's see... <thought>I've never seen anything like it before.</thought> It looks like a bundle of thick cigars wrapped up in a large watch to me, but-</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Susato! What's the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That, that, that, that... That's a... Surely that's a time bomb...isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">WHAAAAAAAAT?! Did you say...?!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">A...time bomb...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...sorry, but... ...what is a 'time bomb' exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah ha ha ha ha hah! You truly are one of a kind, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I won't take that as a compliment...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Hah! Ya don't know nuffin', do ya, 'Oddo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You haven't got a clue what it is, either, have you, Gina?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I invite you to consult a dictionary later, Mr Naruhodo. But this particular specimen is no time bomb. Though I confess it has a very similar appearance.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Oh, well, thank goodness! But then...what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... I see... So that's it...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Goodness! Mr Sholmes... Have you seen to the heart of the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">There are times when I consider my lot most unfair. For I'm fated never to know how it feels to flounder as you do when a puzzle presents itself. But...I have learnt to accept the hardships that come with being a great detective, Miss Susato.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Here we go. I feel a great deduction coming...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Once again, I can draw two conclusions from the scene we see before us. The first... ...is that the inverted nature of the furniture in this room is the work of Drebber himself.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! But how could you...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And the second conclusion... ...is that the small device on the floor there is without question completely genuine.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Please, Mr Sholmes! You must explain everything!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...It would be a pleasure. After all, it is a great detective's civic duty to teach Scotland Yard the finer points of the trade.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well, Inspector Gregson seems delighted with the idea, anyway.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah ha ha ha ha hah!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, you deflected the inspector's glare with such fortitude there, Mr Sholmes! Well done!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You're too kind, my dear madam. I hereby dedicate this great deduction to you. Kindly stand just there, Miss Susato.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...yes. I'd be delighted!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So...shall we begin? Once again, Herlock Sholmes is proud to present...his 'Logic and Reasoning Spectacular'!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It's plain to see that this room is in complete disarray. The bed, the table and chairs, the lamp... Everything is upside-down. Almost as if every item in the room had, until recently, been happily positioned on the ceiling... ...before falling straight down onto the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Every item in the room was on the ceiling... Are, are you suggesting that...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed. The key here... ...is gravity. It would appear that technology has at last succeeded in freeing us from the great pull of the earth. For the gravity in this room was reversed, and then... suddenly restored to normality!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Goodness!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The inverted furniture clearly reveals the truth about the part gravity played in this whole business. I quite understand your scepticism, Miss Susato. I, too, was incredulous at first. However, my conviction in my analysis was cemented when I observed...this. An anti-gravity device...almost identical to one that featured in a dream of mine only the other day, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But, but then why does it have a clock on it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">A most relevant question, indeed. That is a timing device that controls when the gravity direction will switch. There was clearly a requirement for the engineer to be able to restore normal gravity automatically. And the commotion we heard earlier from the other side of the door was the moment that restoration occurred. Yes, the reason why everything in here has been turned upside-down is because of the anti-gravity device! So you see, we need look no further to explain the state in which we now find this room. The direction in which gravity acts in here was reversed by Mr Drebber... ...before being restored to normality in an automatic fashion some time later by the timer device! I have witnessed precisely this scene in a dream I once had when I fell out of bed.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Now, let us consider the next conundrum: What was our engineer friend's aim? Indubitably, the greatest clue we have to explain his actions...is above our heads.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, how is it possible that there are footprints all the way up there on the ceiling?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">A question whose answer will lead us neatly to the truth, my dear madam. The reason there are footprints on the ceiling...is because of the nearby skylight! Of course, Drebber's aim was singular: to escape. However, there is but one way into this room. ...Excepting the skylight, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">By inverting the gravity in here, Drebber was able to 'fall' conveniently to the ceiling... ...and make his escape via the otherwise inaccessible skylight, leaving those footprints behind on the way.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But the ceiling in here is very high, Mr Sholmes. If the gravity reversal was sudden, wouldn't Mr Drebber have fallen up to the ceiling rather violently?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm, 'falling up' is both scientifically and philosophically a rather interesting concept, I feel. But the man was cornered with nowhere to run, so escape through the skylight was his only option. You may recall that I found this in the room earlier, which I believe offers a solution.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! The rope...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">To reach the intended destination, what better tool than this rope? By anchoring one end to the wall, the man was able to 'lower' himself safely to the ceiling. Which explains how Drebber was able to escape this room before our arrival. He reversed the pull of gravity and fled via the skylight! And personally, I should very much like to reverse the pull of gravity again now...just for fun.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Thus concludes Herlock Sholmes's great deduction...of this topsy-turvy puzzle!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">.........</line>
<line speaker="Gina">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>She's completely spellbound...</thought> Um, Mr Sholmes...there is just one thing that troubles me.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I would expect nothing less. You're destined to be troubled by 'just one thing' for the rest of your life.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The thing is... Is such a thing actually possible? An anti-gravity device, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...I would say that with man's current scientific knowledge at the turn of the twentieth century... ...it's no more possible than instantaneous kinesis!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... But your whole deduction hinges on it!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, but my dear fellow... ...when you have eliminated the impossible, whatever remains must be the truth... ...however improbable it may seem.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It's a marvellous line, wouldn't you agree? One of my more enduring pearls of wisdom. I had Iris come up with the exact phrasing. My original was...clumsy.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes, I have a feeling I've read it in something that Miss Susato lent me once.</line>
<line speaker="Susato"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Actually...there IS one other thing, Mr Sholmes...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ah, the spell's broken at last.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">The rope you found was on the floor, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed it was. In lonely coils near the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But...if Mr Drebber had used it to escape in the way you described... ...wouldn't it still be tied to the wall?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Mysteries inevitably unravel in the end. As, I think you'll find, do ropes. And as evidence of such, you need only look at the mystery we faced in this room, now skilfully unravelled.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That argument is as circular as the coils of rope...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think perhaps we might need to give Mr Sholmes the usual little helping hand. I'm sure with some minor corrections, the great detective's great deduction will lead us to the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, you're right. And we must do it quickly, before Enoch Drebber gets too far away!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">If you're ready, then let us resume... ...Herlock Sholmes's 'Logic and Reasoning Spectacular'!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It's plain to see that this room is in complete disarray. The bed, the table and chairs, the lamp... Everything is upside-down. Almost as if every item in the room had, until recently, been happily positioned on the ceiling... ...before falling straight down onto the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Every item in the room was on the ceiling... Are, are you suggesting that...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed. The key here... ...is gravity. It would appear that technology has at last succeeded in freeing us from the great pull of the earth. For the gravity in this room was reversed, and then... suddenly restored to normality!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Goodness!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The inverted furniture clearly reveals the truth about the part gravity played in this whole business.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">To think gravity could have been reversed in this very room! I find the whole idea utterly enthralling! Only Mr Sholmes could conceive of such an explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But the man himself admitted it was a scientific impossibility, so...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, you're quite right. We must completely discount the idea at once.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ooh, that's unusually merciless of you, Miss Susato.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">'When you have eliminated the impossible, whatever remains must be the truth.' The great detective himself said so, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">While refusing to part with his dreams of anti-gravity devices...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Yes, I suppose so.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, let's see if examining this topsy-turvy scene a little more closely... ...reveals some proof that shows exactly what the gravity in this room was or wasn't doing!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">All the furniture in here is very conspicuously upside-down, certainly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. It does immediately put you in mind of some strange quirk of gravity, I admit.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah! Could it be that a mini whirlwind passed through here, do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'm not sure that's much more plausible than Mr Sholmes's explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear. Saying the first thing that comes into your head isn't the way forward here, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well well! I wasn't expecting to find a pretty bunch of flowers in here, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah! Look at that!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know. That slender little vase looks like it's about to topple at any moment, but the flowers are thriving. Somehow it makes you think of the fragility of life, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... To be honest, Mr Naruhodo... ...something else about it made a rather deeper impression on me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Look, Miss Susato! When everything seems to be upside-down in here... ...this safe is conspicuously the right way up! Have you noticed?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's true. But look more closely at the safe's feet.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ah. That's a lot of very large bolts fixing it to the floor...</thought> ......... Think before you speak, that's what you wanted to say, isn't it? I really put my foot in my mouth there.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I certainly didn't say that...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo, with that answer you haven't righted my reasoning in any way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As a logician, you will never surpass me. The science of deduction and analysis requires long and patient study. I'm several steps ahead of you. And your attempts to correct me serve only to highlight your deficiencies.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...this is what you get for agreeing with someone? <thought>(I need to reconsider my answer, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo, I implore you to observe more closely. As you can see, the safe's feet is firmly bolted to the floor, saving it from any effects of gravity.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! So it is...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But there is one thing we can learn from your misguided conclusion: A good deduction is no mean 'feet'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... Can we at least make jokes at my expense funny?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">If the reversal of gravity is scientifically impossible, perhaps we can prove it didn't occur?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, to prove a hypothesis is wrong...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...The easiest way is just to find an obvious exception.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Let's have another good look around...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The upright vase clearly reveals the truth about the part gravity played in this whole business.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Upon my word, Mr Naruhodo, you've surpassed yourself. By completely turning my argument on its head! Trying to impress your assistant here, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...No one is trying to steal your spotlight here, Mr Sholmes. Trust me.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As you rightly say, though it appears at first glance that all the furniture in the room is upside-down... ...this unassuming, slender vase is standing keenly to attention. And unlike the large safe, there is nothing affixing it to the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And it's the exception that breaks the rule.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In short, much as it pains me... ...the gravity in this room was never inverted at all!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...My, my deepest sympathies for your loss.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, poor Mr Sholmes...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But the show must go on! So...let us continue with our deductions. Now that we know this contrivance is not in fact an anti-gravity device, there remains but one other possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You don't say.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Someone deliberately turned over every piece of furniture in here!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Which might sound obvious, but leaves one mystery very much unsolved. Namely, why would anyone choose to do that?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Quite! And naturally, there is an explanation. Yes, the reason why everything in here has been turned upside-down is because of the anti-gravity device!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He's absolutely determined that this device must have something to do with it, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm afraid the lure of an exciting scientific explanation is too strong.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...there's no doubt that somebody did this. Somebody turned all this furniture over. So whoever it was must have had a reason.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm afraid nothing comes to mind at all, though.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, let's look around and see if the answer presents itself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We've already established that gravity wasn't actually reversed in here, haven't we? In other words, this isn't an anti-gravity device at all.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Which makes me very curious to know what sort of device it is. But I think for now it's clear that we're looking for an answer elsewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's a coal-burning heater, I think, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, it is, but it's not just for heating, you know. You can grill on it, bake in it, boil and steam things with it... It serves all sorts of purposes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That seems like having your cake and eating it, too. Not unlike a heated kotatsu table with a nabe hotpot, a mikan orange, a cat AND an elderly relative.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...you mean it seems too much? I suppose perhaps it does. But you realise only some of those things on your list are edible...don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look, there's something written on the underside of this armchair!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes. 'Safe: 432582'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Safe'? As in 'safe and secure'?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">As in 'secure lockable box', I think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Admittedly more likely.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, there is a large safe bolted to the floor on the other side of the room, so...yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you mean, this number would let us open it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I wonder why it's written here, though?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo, with that answer you haven't righted my reasoning in any way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As a logician, you will never surpass me. The science of deduction and analysis requires long and patient study. I'm several steps ahead of you. And your attempts to correct me serve only to highlight your deficiencies.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...this is what you get for agreeing with someone? <thought>(I need to reconsider my answer, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In other words, it would automatically flip a fried egg? But I make a point of frying eggs on one side only. It's quite the proper way!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... he really scrambled that idea.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Now we've shown it was nothing to do with gravity, we know somebody must have done this to the furniture. But who? And why?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, those are the questions we really need to answer!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well we at least need to resolve one of them here!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, the reason why everything in here has been turned upside-down is because of the safe combination!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Precisely! I believe, Mr Naruhodo... ...that you had a very similar experience once, did you not?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes! Last year... ...when I bought a lottery ticket and noted the ticket number down on the inside cover of a book just in case!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">That's it! For people are forgetful souls at heart, and always make a written note of important information.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Just keeping the ticket itself safe would be more sensible, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And what, pray, happened next, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When the day of the draw came round... ...I'd forgotten which book I'd written the number in and had to turn my room upside-down to find it!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">That's it! For people are forgetful souls at heart, and always forget where they've noted things down!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Not if you always note things in the same place...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I actually won the second prize, you know. But I couldn't remember which magazine I'd slipped the ticket into, so I had to turn my room upside-</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Thank you, Mr Naruhodo, but I believe I've proved my point now. Which is that a very similar scenario has clearly unfolded in this room.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Finding himself requiring access to the safe, the occupant of this room needed the combination code. He remembered that he'd written it on the underside of a piece of furniture, but forgot which one.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Leading to the state in which we now find the room. Yes, Mr Drebber overturned all the furniture in here... ...in a desperate hurry to locate the combination code that would unlock the safe!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Now, let us consider the next conundrum: What was our engineer friend's aim? Indubitably, the greatest clue we have to explain his actions...is above our heads.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, how is it possible that there are footprints all the way up there on the ceiling?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">A question whose answer will lead us neatly to the truth, my dear madam. The reason there are footprints on the ceiling...is because of the nearby skylight!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, if a change in the direction of gravity can't explain it, then how did those footprints get there?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I feel as though that particular mystery has just become even harder to solve.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I can't think of any other way to explain it at all. Ooh... Life was so much simpler in those halcyon days when gravity could be reversed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It was minutes ago. And those 'halcyon days' never existed in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, I suppose we must simply put our faith in Mr Sholmes and observe the area in more detail.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Putting our faith in Mr Sholmes is what gets us into these situations in the first place...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It looks like these are the only windows in the room. In other words, if you wanted to escape without using the door, these skylights would be the only way.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's true. But even so...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And right next to the only escape route, we notice some telltale footprints...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Nevertheless, as we've said many times now, gravity can't explain how they got there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... But powerful springs in the soles of the man's shoes could.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Have you been having strange dreams as well, like Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is a gas balloon, isn't it? It's tiny, but it does seem to be a real balloon.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I think you're right. I think it's helium that's keeping it up.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A green gas balloon... <thought>Why does that seem to ring a bell with me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">If you can see, there are footprints on this balloon, too, look.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes... Surely that's a clue, isn't it? ...Though what it tells us, I'm not sure.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's hard to believe, but... ...there's a shoe up there, look!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes! And there are more footprints on this little balloon, too. Perhaps the shoe was thrown up there and became lodged, do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If so, then judging from the number of footprints, it must have been thrown up several times. Why would anyone be throwing shoes up at the ceiling, though?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... That's beyond me, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo, with that answer you haven't righted my reasoning in any way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As a logician, you will never surpass me. The science of deduction and analysis requires long and patient study. I'm several steps ahead of you. And your attempts to correct me serve only to highlight your deficiencies.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...this is what you get for agreeing with someone? <thought>(I need to reconsider my answer, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I take no pleasure in delivering bad news, but the undeniable truth is... ...it's clearly too small.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...?! I KNEW you were going to say that!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow, then you are twice the fool. If people could fly in such small balloons, why would anybody ever manufacture larger ones? I despair of your lack of common sense at times, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...that really hurts...coming from you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Those footprints up there on the ceiling really are a puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And as they're so close to the skylight... ...it really is very hard to believe the two are unrelated.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But perhaps we need to approach this from a different angle...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The reason there are footprints on the ceiling...is because of the nearby shoe!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And on closer inspection, there are clearly footprints all over the balloon as well. In other words, the aim was never the skylight at all, but the balloon.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But...for what purpose?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">A green balloon... Hmmm, that seems somewhat familiar data.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was a piece of a green balloon's envelope that Mr Naruhodo and Iris found at the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And inside the green balloon that Master Gotts claims he saw above the stage when the incident occurred... ...was the second birdcage. The crux of the whole instantaneous kinesis deception...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You, you mean to say...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">If we assume the balloon in here is a model of the one used on the day... ...there is a strong possibility something may be concealed inside it. Something our absconder was desperate to retrieve before making a hasty getaway.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but the balloon's out of reach!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hence why he resorted to a projectile. Namely...the shoe.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Most probably, Drebber intended to tear a hole in the envelope by assailing it with the shoe. However, his efforts were thwarted when the shoe itself became a prisoner of those lofty heights.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, dear... We desperately need to examine that balloon. If only there were some way we could see inside...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You may recall that I found this in the room earlier, which I believe offers a solution.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! The rope...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">To reach the intended destination, what better tool than this rope?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Mr Sholmes has managed to bring the deduction back to the rope!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright, I have to admit...that was clever. So we just throw the rope up to the balloon and then pull it down to us on the ground?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Which is much easier said than done, I feel. And could take us a very long time as well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">True. Perhaps we need a more surefire method. In fact, we already have one of course, don't we?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sholmes:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, it's gone over your head, Mr Sholmes? Obviously, I was thinking of using it to examine the balloon.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">On the contrary, nothing has gone over my head but this rope. For it is clearly the superior idea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Really? Throwing the rope to catch the balloon and tug it back down? But there's a far more reliable method that I can think of. Even if it is a little heavy-handed...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, look! The hotheaded Mr Sholmes is trying to lasso the balloon!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It would be wonderful if he succeeded. Then we could pull it down to us. But it would be even more wonderful if there were some better way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And we need to think of it fast, before Mr Sholmes starts tiring of being a cowboy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">To reach the intended destination, what better tool than this crossbow?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That was found at the scene, in fact!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And in all likelihood, belongs to Mr Drebber.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">If the man had only brought it away with him that day... ...he could have avoided losing a shoe at such a critical time as this.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So...shall we? Your curiosity is deeply stirred no doubt, my dear fellows. What is it that Enoch Drebber has hidden inside that balloon...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Aaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">W-What the...? A, a waxwork?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed it is. A waxwork head inside a metal mask. A mask that is shut tight and fastened with a strong and quite impenetrable lock.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So we can't see the face inside, that means.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Just a moment... This...this is the head of a waxwork model? Does that mean...? Oh goodness!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I see you've joined the dots, Miss Susato. Excellent.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! <thought>Of course! A headless waxwork model!</thought> The case of the abducted Madame Tusspells model that you'd 'largely' solved... It was only the head of the killer that was still missing!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed it was. But I believe Madame Tusspells will now have to settle her sizeable account with me. This, as you have now surmised, is the head of the infamous Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But why is it here?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...This conclusively confirms my suspicions. The man responsible for stealing the Professor from Madame Tusspells... ...and returning it - sans tte - earlier today...was none other than Enoch Drebber!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This is incredible. Professor Harebrayne's case and the waxwork abduction are... They're inextricably linked! By Enoch Drebber's workshop!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This lock does look very strong, doesn't it? There's definitely no way you could remove the mask yourself if it was put on you.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What a terrible way to treat someone, even a convicted criminal.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know. It's starting to make me livid, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo, please...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I mean, just think about it! Imagine if you had an itch on your cheek all of a sudden! You'd be utterly helpless!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Well, yes, that's true. But I'm not sure...that warrants quite so much anger.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...right... Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well...it appears our logical pleasure cruise has come to an end, my dear fellows. All that remains is... Yes, to speak with the architect of this adventure.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The architect?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean...Mr Drebber?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As it seems quite impossible that he escaped via one of the skylights... ...obviously the man must still be here in the room.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And his location should be abundantly clear... ...if you simply reflect on the journey we've made together during this deduction.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Enoch Drebber is right here, somewhere in this room?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So, Mr Naruhodo, will you do the honours?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes, of course. Mr Drebber's hiding place must be the...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">This looks to be a cupboard for cups and saucers and the like.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah... An ingenious hiding place!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, when you say 'cupboard' you automatically think of cups and saucers, don't you? And the clever engineer knows that, so he knows you'd never look for him in there, because he's not crockery!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Though sadly it does seem to be full of...only crockery.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Personally, I still think he might have escaped via one of those skylights.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But you heard what Mr Sholmes said: 'The man must still be here in the room.' I'm afraid your opinion might put you at loggerheads with the great detective.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Susato... ...sometimes a man must stand up for what he believes in and fight.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! ...Well in that case, I'll leave you to it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you need to hide, there's no better place than a wardrobe. I stand firmly by that.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, yes... You had some experience of that yourself a year ago, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We'll find him in there, mark my words! He'll be curled up in a ball, trembling and hungry. In fact, my own hand is trembling just thinking about making the discovery!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Never mind, Mr Naruhodo. He could be hiding somewhere else, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at all that mess in front of the safe.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, plans and accounting ledgers...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Almost as if somebody was in a hurry to empty the contents of the safe, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow, he wouldn't be in there. It's a cupboard after all. For cups and saucers.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Unless the Drebber you seek is a piece of fine bone china?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You delight in my mistakes, don't you, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Gracious no, Mr Naruhodo! You're quite mistaken! Ah ha ha ha ha hah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm afraid you shall have to learn to help your feelings, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">We've already reached the conclusion that escape via a skylight was quite impossible. I'm sorry to say your only recourse is to follow the logic again from the very beginning!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'll...swallow my pride.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Not there, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but I don't understand...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You could always climb inside yourself? Please, don't mind us. Do go ahead. I know how fond you are of wardrobes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'll think of something else, thank you very much!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Where could Mr Drebber be hiding? I'm sure that we've already come across a clue that reveals the answer, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, it was when we deduced why all the furniture in here was upside-down, wasn't it? That gave us the answer, I'm sure.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">We're very close now, Mr Naruhodo! I can sense it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Before we gained access to this back room, we heard noises from in here.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Which tells us that the engineer was still in the building at that point in time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He was in fact searching for the combination to his safe.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And pressed for time, made no attempt to right the furniture that he overturned in the process. From which we can deduce that his search for the combination happened very recently indeed. In summary...Mr Enoch Drebber... ...is, at this very moment, inside the safe! Thus concludes Herlock Sholmes's great deduction...of this topsy-turvy puzzle!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So...Mr Naruhodo. I think perhaps it's time we ended this game of hide-and-seek, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">By opening the safe, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What else?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Let's see... The combination was one...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Four three two five eight two.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I knew that! <thought>Alright then. Here goes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Right then, sir... Mr Enoch Drebber, I presume?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Correct.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You'd better start talking! You tricked Professor Harebrayne with that bogus machine you built!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And you shall have to explain the theft of the waxwork from Madame Tusspells as well!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Whilst I would be delighted to answer your many questions... ...personally, I would advise that you deactivate my little parcel first.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Deactivate...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Your parcel...?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">I refer of course... ...to the time bomb. I left it in a most prominent position.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Ha-ha-ha. I see. Stunned silence. You're all gearing up to die with me then?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Nooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes! With only seven seconds to spare!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That was too close for comfort! I've got one foot in the grave already!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Are you tryin' to help us get a killer, or get us killed?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes's deductions can be...completely life-altering, can't they?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, my dear fellows, that was a close shave. The resemblance to an anti-gravity device is really quite startling, I must say.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Anti-gravity devices don't exist!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Whew, I wouldn't push it, Mr Sholmes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I still can't believe we were nearly blown up...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What was that sideways glance in aid of, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I thought that deducing meaning from the movement of people's eyes was your specialty, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Never mind that now. Let's see what Mr Drebber has to say for himself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What on earth happened in here?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">You've found me, haven't you? No need to screw me down any further. Everything in here...is precisely what it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yeah, well we'll be givin' it a thorough goin' over, don't you worry, Drebber.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">......... What fails to click with me... ...is how you were able to locate my workshop. That I was not expecting. When I heard whistling from the other room, I knew it was time to bolt.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Whistling?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah. That would have been me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">For some reason, I woke in fine fettle today!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>No words...just tightly squeezed chips...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Clearly I must have a screw loose, though, as I couldn't remember the combination for the safe. And another one loose, as I couldn't remember on which piece of furniture I'd written it down.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We also found a rope over by the wall...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Yes, I had hoped to exit through the skylight, but sadly the rope was too short. So...I then set about searching for the combination code to open the safe.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And burning the incriminating blueprints, don't forget. Regrettably, though, you failed to retrieve the head from the balloon among the rafters.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And after that you hid yourself inside the safe? Having first set this 'parcel' ticking.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Well...I had no intention of being nailed by the police.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Got a death wish, have ya? Hidin' right beside a tickin' time bomb.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Please... Why do you suppose I chose to hide inside the safe? It's no ordinary safe. It's specially designed. A dynamite explosion wouldn't leave a scratch on it.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So in fact, the safe was the only 'safe' place.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Precisely.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But once you'd climbed inside, you wouldn't have been able to get out again...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">I invite you to look more closely. The safe is fitted with a handle on the inside, to allow the door to be unlocked from within.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! So it is...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">I had always intended to blow this place to smithers in any case. I just wasn't expecting uninvited guests to come along and screw up my plans.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Do you...do you mean to say...you were plannin' to blow us all up?!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">No. No. That was unforeseen.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Most people run, you see. When they see a ticking time bomb at their feet.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">I calculated the time required for retreat to a safe distance, and set the device accordingly. But your seemingly endless discourse in here threw a spanner in the works.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Is something wrong, Gregson? Do I have something on my face...besides the usual eyes, ears, nose and mouth?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It might surprise you to learn that I'm actually a lawyer from the Empire of Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">...I detest lawyers. They wield so-called 'special powers' in an attempt to grind down our freedoms. Yes, let me be quite clear: I detest lawyers very much.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Any chance two negatives make a positive...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Drebber, look at this, please.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you, um...have anything to say about it?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Are these strange mechanical movements supposed to be some sort of answer...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Professor Harebrayne's instantaneous kinesis experiment at the Great Exhibition... ...and the waxwork model you stole, which this head belongs to.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">That's no ordinary head, you know. That's the head...of the Professor. Clad in a mask with a lock so strong, I'm unable to open it safely to reveal the killer's identity. I've been considering carrying it around as...protection. After all-</line>
<line speaker="???">That's enough!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">What's going on here, Gregson? I'm sure you're aware that I have sole jurisdiction to investigate here.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Ah, um... Yes, well...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Dr Sithe again. So the Forensic Investigation Team are here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sithe">And you know full well this engineer is a key witness. Why are you allowing this lawyer access to him? If Lord Stronghart knew of this, you'd be finished.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">You lot. Leave at once.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear madam, there's no need for such a threatening tone, I assure you. After all, that's no way to greet an old acquaintance, is it, Dr Sithe?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Hello...Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Mr Sholmes knows Dr Sithe?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">If it's protecting the machine next door that's causing such a sour expression on your face, you are quite misguided. It's really nothing more than a shell, you-</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Get out!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But of course. We'll show ourselves the door. ...I see you haven't softened at all. Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It would appear that our delightfully entertaining investigations have run their course for today.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but Mr Sholmes...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Let us leave this place in the doctor's capable hands.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">I said get out! Now! All of you! Your presence here is not required either, Gregson.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">......... Understood. But I'll just say one thing before I head off: If it wasn't for this lawyer an' his companions... ...we'd never have found this place. And the whole workshop would've been blown to bits. There was a time bomb set in here that this lot disarmed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Inspector...</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">.........</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Kuh kuh kuh...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">...! Somethin' given you a chuckle, has it, Drebber?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Ah, so sorry. Didn't mean to offend. You're quite right of course. You did disarm the time bomb, didn't you? Yes... You did disarm that one.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Eh? Wot are you...? 'That' one? Ya, ya mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Kuh kuh kuh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes managed to open that door in almost no time at all. It was incredible!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Thanks to one of his great deductions, no doubt! About the shape of the lock set into the door!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I think maybe you're putting too much stock in his deductive abilities. Aaanyway, what's waiting for us on the other side, that's the question, isn't it? <thought>And there's no point trying to deduce that. Let's just go and see!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't find anything out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Nothing particular of note...</thought></line>
</xml>