<xml>
<title>The Last Inquisitor</title>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now once again in session. However... I must say, I am quite surprised at this recent turn of events... To see Miss Kira at the witness stand once again... Frankly, I cannot believe my eyes! You...were most certainly sent to the flames as a witch!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Enough. A witch must be in possession of a Talea Magica in order to use magic. I hate to disappoint you all, but do you see such a thing on her person? ...I think not!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-but... She must have... That girl must have used Dimere. Surely you can see that, High Inquisitor.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Dimere is a spell able to make someone disappear from sight. It cannot make one vanish entirely. And besides... an investigation conducted by the Knights of the Inquisition has concluded that this girl is not capable of using magic.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Listen well, Miss Kira. Your existence alone jeopardizes the very peace of Labyrinthia. Yet, given the current situation... it is now imperative that you testify to this court regarding what you saw. Immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what...?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">This girl has already been convicted and tried as a witch in a previous trial. What good could come of her testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">High Inquisitor Darklaw... I'm afraid your objection is overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ You wish to proceed then? Very well. ...Let us see just how much of her "story" this girl is willing to tell the court, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's no doubt about it. Ms Kira must have escaped through the passage leading under the Chamber of Fire. Although... from the looks of it, the judge doesn't have a clue that escape route even exists.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wish he'd hurry up and get the hint! I'm dying to take this helmet off already. The top of my head REALLY itches...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, Maya. Take that thing off now, and we're as good as done. Just hang in there a little while longer.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aaawww...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Witness... You may begin your testimony. Explain to the court how you are standing here in court today... And why you were hiding at the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I am not familiar with this "Kira" you keep talking about... I came from the Eldwitch Woods...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-you came here to...KILL the Storyteller?!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Yes. That was my task.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ ...Hmph...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I must admit, I too am extremely interested in hearing what this witness has to say. ...Defender! You may begin your interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I am not familiar with this "Kira" you keep talking about... I came from the Eldwitch Woods...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Yes. I've never heard it before.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-but...I say! That is your name, young lady! Honestly, what witchery is this?!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ I have no name. ...I am simply a resident of the Eldwitch Woods. Nothing more.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Eldwitch Woods...? The very same woods said to house the souls of the witches sent to the flames? Are you telling me they really exist?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No matter how you look at her, the Kira up on that witness stand doesn't look like much of a soul to me.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The girl has lost all memory of ever being a flower seller... That is all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If that's the case... then I wonder if she even remembers our run-in back at the marketplace...</thought> ...Um. Say, Ms Kira, do you happen to remember me at all?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ ...No. I do not know you. I first saw you just now at the bell tower.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I came to this town...to summon forth the fire dragon and kill the Storyteller.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Yes. It was all a part of my orders. I was told to come here this evening and wait for the right moment when the Storyteller would appear before the people... Only then was I supposed to shout out the incantation as loudly as possible. ...Oh great beast from the inferno... ...Heed my call...Granwyrm...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...I believe this bears repeating: the girl does not possess a sceptre. It is impossible for her to summon any sort of magical dragon!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...A-ah. Yes! Quite right, High Inquisitor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Then why are you hiding underneath the bench, Your Honour?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem... Hmm... Yes, well... It is as I thought, then. She could not have cast the spell.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...I believe I have made it perfectly clear. This girl is not the Great Witch Bezella. Naturally, the Great Witch is... that girl there, Espella Cantabella. There can be no other.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Kira">As it rained...I waited near the bell tower, next to the Vigilantes, for my chance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Yes, that's right. My orders at that time were to-</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...The girl is a witch.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Therefore, something as simple as vanishing from sight is child's play. ...Isn't that right, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ Yes. That is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah ha! I remember now! Just a few days ago, this girl... used that very vanishing spell! Dimere, if memory serves!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Well, what are you gawking at, witness? Continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What was that just now...? I could've sworn I just saw Kira's face turn even paler than normal...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Yes, that's right. My orders at that time were to-</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...The girl is a witch.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Therefore, something as simple as vanishing from sight is child's play. ...Isn't that right, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ Yes. That is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah ha! I remember now! Just a few days ago, this girl... used that very vanishing spell! Dimere, if memory serves!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Well, what are you gawking at, witness? Continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What was that just now...? I could've sworn I just saw Kira's face turn even paler than normal... Wait a second...there's something not right about this testimony. It's just a hunch, but... What should I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ms Kira! I have one simple question for you. You stated earlier in your testimony that you snuck past the Vigilantes guarding the bell tower and went right inside... Tell me, did you use the spell Dimere to get by them?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-that must certainly be the case. Had she not, she would surely have been spotted.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Therefore, if that's true... then you, Ms Kira, would not have been able to use Dimere at all!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ ...I...am not a witch...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...And I...cannot use magic...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-so then... exactly HOW were you able to ascend the bell tower without being noticed? Witness! Amend your testimony this instant!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Okay...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-what's going on...? There's got to be another way she got into that bell tower unseen... But other than magic, I have no idea what that could be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not 100 per cent sure there's anything funny here. Is there something I'm missing?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I dunno... Even I noticed something a little weird in there. There's...definitely something funny about what she just said. I say you press first and ask questions later, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She might actually be right... Maybe I should try doing a little less thinking and a little more questioning...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kira">I was wearing the robe of invisibility...so no one was able to see me there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Yes. That is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A robe...of invisibility...? S-surely you don't mean... a robe that can make one vanish from sight when worn?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Yes. That is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ms Kira! Do you have that robe on you right now?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I...don't have it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">That is...I dropped it... Back at the bell tower...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>...What the heck was that? Why was Kira...looking over at Darklaw when she spoke just now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Are you listening to this farce, Milord? Surely you do not give any credence to this witness' testimony. Especially to this preposterous notion of a "robe of invisibility"!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...indeed. I must say, witness, that is quite an unbelievable story.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If something like magic can exist, the chances of a robe of invisibility being real are pretty high, wouldn't you say?!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-prove it...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Hmm. What say you, defender? Can you prove to the court that the robe of invisibility does, in fact, exist?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes, Your Honour. The defence believes it has evidence to prove the robe's existence.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Why am I not surprised? A ridiculous defender only begets ridiculous arguments.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've gotta admit...an invisible robe does sound pretty far-fetched, even for Labyrinthia... But... If there's even the slightest possibility this evidence is right... then I've got to try it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Defender, please show the court this evidence. Show us the piece of evidence that proves the existence of this robe!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I am far more inclined to believe in the existence of this fantastical robe...than in your ability to properly perform in court!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaarrrrrrgh! <thought>Two against one... Yeah, that's real fair.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">We will continue with the interrogation. Defender, I recommend you take this time to really think about what you've learned just now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honour...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defence...cannot prove that just yet, Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I must say, defender. Given your penchant for the absurd, I find this rather sensible decision quite surprising.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! A-are you just going to let her sit there and stump us?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it IS a "robe of invisibility", Maya... I mean... how exactly am I supposed to prove the existence of something that's invisible? It's impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Impossible, huh...? Well...there is one thing you could try. Just say... "Your Honour! The fact you can't see this evidence PROVES beyond a shadow of a doubt that it's really an invisible robe!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait...what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Now see here, you two. I will not have you presenting imaginary evidence in MY courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Of course, Your Honour! <thought>Looks like I've got to try again with some REAL evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I...was only there to carry out my orders. I don't know anything else...outside of that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ I cannot say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...And why is that?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I am not to disclose the identity of the one who has given me my orders. ...That, in itself, is an order.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How convenient...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kira">I am only supposed to carry out my orders. Nothing more. I do not know anything else. And besides... There is nothing more that I can really do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Nothing more" she can do...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But, hold on just a minute! Surely you are capable of using magic... You ARE a witch, are you not?!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ ...I...am not a witch...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...! What did you just say?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ I...cannot use magic...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She...can't use magic?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">This girl is a witch... Every person in this courtroom knows that as a matter of fact. There can be nary a doubt.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm...doesn't look like there's much to work with...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Even though she just finished explaining everything, I still don't fully understand. Oh man, Nick... You don't think this Kira is actually some sort of crazy magical zombie, do you?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Maya. You went through the same thing as Kira. Did you become a "magical zombie"?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh yeah... I guess not, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Luke and I couldn't believe it was Kira when we ran into her in the marketplace... I mean, we thought for sure she was a goner back at the trial.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't think I'm far off, though. This Kira is way different than the old Kira. It looks like she doesn't remember a thing. She's almost like another person entirely.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... What if that's just it, Maya? What if the Kira right here, right now, is the real Kira and the "old" Kira wasn't?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The real Kira, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, and that's why... I think I'm bound to find something useful in her testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">We can do this, Nick! I hope you're ready to slam on some desks, because we're gonna do some serious pressing here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was, in fact, a robe dropped and left at the crime scene tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A robe...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Kira... That robe of invisibility that you mentioned earlier wouldn't happen to be... this one right here, would it?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaarrrgh! <thought>Well...she's kinda got a point there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, hey! What if the robe...actually disappears when you wear it?! Give it here, Nick! Watch in wonder as Maya the Magnificent disappears before your very eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...So? Are you amazed yet?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ ...Yeah, I'm amazed. At how totally ridiculous you look in that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! What gives?! This thing must be busted or something! ...I didn't disappear at all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm...well, that's not it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...No...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Tonight...at the bell tower...I was wearing that robe.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh... What did you saaaaaaaay?! ...Order! I said order! B-but how is that possible? The robe did not disappear at all just now...</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ That's because of the white powder on it... It's usually not that dirty...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... Y-you mean...these spots here? <thought>Please, don't tell me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh yeah! Patty totally unloaded an entire bag of flour on to those knights, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not to mention it was still raining when we were up there. The flour must have gotten nice and wet, so it's stained the robe. Say, what if... we try washing the flour off...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah! There is a small water fountain at the edge of the square. Head there right now and wash the robe so that we can get to the bottom of this. Quickly now!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All right, this shouldn't be too hard. Take notes, Nick. THIS is how you do the laundry! See, all you have to do is throw the robe into the water, like so...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Wait, what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So? Do you see anything, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Th-that's just it... I don't see a thing... It's disappeared...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Defender. What is the meaning of this?! How could you have lost such a vital piece of evidence?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Your Honour, it wasn't on purpose! Trust me, I wish I knew how it happened... <thought>I can't believe it... The robe actually disappeared from sight...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I don't quite know what you're talking about. I can...still see the robe just fine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Look. It's right here, see?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no Ms Kira... I really DON'T see... <thought>...Because there's nothing TO see!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...So, is that how it works? Putting the robe on makes you disappear completely from sight... But from the looks of it, only Kira is able to actually see the robe itself...</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...It is not just me. It's all inhabitants of the Eldwitch Woods. All of us can see the robe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Eldwitch Woods...</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Our village lies deep within the recesses of the forest...in a world much different from this one. That's where I live. As long as we obey the "law" of the land, we are allowed to live there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I knew it. There's definitely something different about Kira compared to the rest of the townspeople here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">For the time being... seeing as only the witness can see the robe, we will cover it in flour again for the sake of visibility.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... There's still one tiny thing bothering me. Ms Kira, your robe was found on the middle floor of the bell tower, the same floor where we found my client. However...you were hiding on the uppermost level of the bell tower.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You testified a little while ago that you dropped your robe, but... I have to wonder... What exactly were you doing there on that top floor?!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Hmm. It would seem...there is still much we must ask this witness. What say you, High Inquisitor Darklaw?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ 'Tis the inquisition's duty to follow Milord's decision on such matters. ...I have no objections.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Witness, you are hereby ordered to continue with your testimony. Tell us what happened between your sneaking up to the top floor of the bell tower and tonight's most terrible crime!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Yes, okay.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I was waiting on the middle floor of the tower. I started to turn around, but I was too late...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-witness, are you saying... someone attacked you while you were in the bell tower?!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Yes... That is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But...who?!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I...don't know. Th-they attacked me from behind, so I couldn't see who it was...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So you were unconscious the entire time after that?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">That's why...I was unable to complete my mission... But even if I hadn't been unconscious, I couldn't have done anything trapped high up in the belfry like that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I wonder if that weird contraption we found there was used to move Kira up to the belfry... At least, I can't see any other way she could have got up there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">You heard the witness. She was locked up in the belfry of the tower. ...In other words, she couldn't have had anything to do with tonight's events. Therefore, there is no need for this utterly useless interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender, are you implying...that this attacker could have been Bezella?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I cannot say for certain, Your Honour. Regardless, the defence requests we be allowed to cross-examine this witness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Request granted. Now then, defender, you may begin your interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And here's where the "fun" begins... Let's see if we can coax this "mysterious" second witch out of hiding!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kira">I was waiting on the middle floor of the tower. I started to turn around, but I was too late...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Y-yes, that's right... Not even a teeny bit. They attacked me from behind, after all...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Did I just hear correctly? It sounds like she hesitated in answering...</thought> By the way... may I ask why you turned around, Ms Kira?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Wh-what? What do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it's just that you said you suddenly tried to turn around. Something must have really grabbed your attention to make you try to turn around so suddenly.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ ...I don't remember.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I-I do think... I heard a sound come from behind me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're saying that you heard something and that's what made you turn around?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Y-yes... But... I don't have any recollection of what exactly that was...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I heard the incantation for Fainfol and before I could even turn around...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Yes... There is no mistaking it.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The attacker used magic to vanish from sight, went up the stairs and then rendered the witness unconscious, also with magic... Clearly this must be the work of none other than the Great Witch Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is no mere coincidence that the attacker was able to use such spells. This is certainly no ordinary witch...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Afterwards, the witness' [sic] attacker carried her off. Naturally, that would require the use of both hands, one would think.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-both hands...High Inquisitor?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">In other words, the witch would not have been able to hold a Talea Magica...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right...and the only witch that doesn't need a sceptre like that is...Bezella.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...I see you have somehow managed to get that through your thick skull, defender. Very well. Continue, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">They attacked me from behind. There was nothing I could do. My arm was restrained, and the attacker covered my mouth...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I-I... I don't remember much. ...But I do know the person easily overpowered me. I remember they grabbed my left wrist... I tried to scream, but they quickly covered my mouth before I had a chance... I desperately tried to break their hold...but it was no good. ............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It sounds like the attacker managed to restrict her movements from behind...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I-I... I don't remember much. ...But I do know the person easily overpowered me. I remember they grabbed my left wrist... I tried to scream, but they quickly covered my mouth before I had a chance... I desperately tried to break their hold...but it was no good. ............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It sounds like the attacker managed to restrict her movements from behind... Still, saying that... There's definitely something not right here. Something about her testimony just doesn't add up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm...yeah. Something about it is a tiny bit different from what we've heard so far. I think it'd be a good idea to check the Court Record again, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You stated that you were attacked from behind and that the attacker grabbed you by the wrist, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Y-yes. That's right...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Assuming that was, in fact, the case...then I'd say no matter how much you struggled... there's no way you would have been able to yank off this pendant, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The strap on this pendant is too short! There's no way you could have reached behind you and managed to pull it off!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-that is a good point!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ms Kira. The only way you would have been able to yank this pendant off of your attacker... is if they were standing directly in front of you!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Nooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order, I say! Witness, is this true?!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I-I...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Well now, defender. I see you are as pathetically short-sighted as ever. Your argument is only valid assuming that this girl here actually saw her attacker.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">If she was not able to see this person... Well, I'd say it'd make no difference where they were standing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-then...that means... The attacker was also wearing one of these robes?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">That is impossible, Milord. As the witness already stated earlier... only residents of the Eldwitch Woods are able to see these robes. In short... The attacker must have been a witch and must have disappeared from sight with the use of magic.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You must mean...the Great Witch Bezella...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">There is one more thing proving the attacker to be a witch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And just what might that be?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The witness has stated that she lost consciousness. If you take a look in the Grand Grimoire... you will notice a spell called Fainfol. ...Witness. Allow me to ask you... did you hear the incantation of this spell?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ N-now that you mention it... I do remember...hearing something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-say whaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-ah! Here it is! Fainfol: "Causes those who hear the incantation to lose all consciousness"!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">We must not forget...the Great Witch can use any and all magic at will.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! Amend your testimony to reflect this important piece of information!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Yes, right away.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, boy... I can't believe she managed to get out of that one... But still, I'm not about to give up just yet. I'll keep on going until we finally get to the bottom of who this attacker REALLY is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then! Let us continue with the interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I was suddenly attacked. There was nothing I could do. My arm was restrained, and the attacker covered my mouth...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Th-that's right... They grabbed me by my right wrist... I think that's when I reached out and pulled the pendant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So basically, the attacker was in front of you the entire time... And yet somehow...you never managed to see their face?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Y-yes... I didn't see them at all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>Something doesn't add up here. If the attacker was so easily able to hide their presence... they why did they have to attack and knock her out to begin with?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Kira">As I struggled to get away...I think I managed to pull something off of my attacker...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I was still really dazed at the time...so I can't remember it very well. But... when I flung my hand up...I felt myself grab a small, round object... I must have pulled it off without thinking... I felt whatever it was snap right off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So...from what you're saying, it sounds like this could have been something that was on your attacker's person...</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I think...so. I can still feel it...even now. It felt like I'd just snapped a piece of rope or something. I really wonder what that could have been... I think I would recognise the shape if I saw it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She'd...recognise the shape if she saw it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">If only we had something that could trigger her memory. Then all we'd have to do is present it and we'd be in business!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, tell me about it. <thought>You know, that might not be such a bad idea, Maya...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Oh... Th-that's it! I recognise that shape. That was the object I grabbed!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What did you say?! B-but, that's... the accused's pendant, is it not?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Not quite, Your Honour. There are actually two pendants like this. ...The one you see here is the counterpart to Ms Cantabella's pendant.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ Now that you mention it... I remember... The necklace was actually very tough. It really didn't rip right off so easily. So...I struggled against it, tugging and pulling at it for a bit, and I must have scratched their neck in the process...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-wait a second... You mean...you scratched your attacker's neck?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I think so, but I don't know for sure...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! I-in that case... that means the dark stuff on the necklace could be...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... <thought>It could be the attacker's blood!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As the court can clearly see...there are still traces of blood left on the necklace itself... However! Take one good look at my client, and you'll notice there are no visible scars or cuts of any kind around her neck! Ergo, there is no way Ms Cantabella could be Ms Kira's attacker!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Have you already forgotten what I told you? The Great Witch can use any spell in existence. She could have easily healed any such wound in the blink of an eye.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Grrr... <thought>I can't believe I'm saying this...but I already miss Inquisitor Barnham...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Man...we really can't catch a break on this one, huh, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let us resume the interrogation. Witness, continue with your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Yes. I think that's the one...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's definitely a trace of blood on this necklace. Blood that must have come from Kira's attacker, when she yanked this pendant from their neck...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Remember, defender. We are talking about the Great Witch here... It is more than possible she used magic to heal any wound that may have appeared on her person. Therefore, I suggest you abandon the idea that this somehow removes all suspicion from the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sheesh...we could really use some more decisive ammo right about now, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think so... This pendant is all the decisive ammo we need. We just have to think... <thought>There has to be something about this pendant that I can present as evidence...</thought> Kira is still definitely hiding something... But I'm pretty sure we can get her to spill the beans with the right piece of evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All right! C'mon, Nick! Get out there and spill them beans!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">That's when I lost consciousness... I woke up to find myself next to the bell on the top floor of the tower.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Y-yes. In fact... It actually felt a lot like magic... It was the first time I had ever experienced a magic spell quite like that...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">As I thought, there was magic at play here. Must I remind you... that the Great Witch Bezella can use any and all magic with the snap of her fingers.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed... Such a spell does, in fact, exist... It was...err... Oh blast it, what was it called again?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't sweat it, Your Honour! Just leave it to me and my trusty ol' Grand Grimoire!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder...could Kira's attacker have actually been a witch?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... It really doesn't look like magic was used to knock her out, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anyway... It looks like Kira is telling the truth. Still... <thought>She's definitely avoiding eye contact... Not to mention, she seems extremely hesitant. There's no doubt about it. She's trying to keep something big from getting out!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">In that case, Nick... Let's give it all we've got and get to the bottom of this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... It really feels like there's a lot riding on this one, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ms Kira. I have watched you at that witness stand this entire trial... desperately trying to keep something hidden from the rest of the court.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder if you're familiar with the saying: "A lie begets more lies"... It means...multiple lies are bound to unravel and leave your story with more holes than Swiss cheese.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Get...to...the point, defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to the Grand Grimoire, Fainfol causes a person to lose all consciousness. It's written here in black and white: "Its effect takes hold the second the incantation is heard."</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Kira... You testified as follows... You heard the incantation for Fainfol and immediately became aware of the presence of your attacker. You then put up a fight... But! If you really did hear that incantation... there's no way you would've been able to yank that pendant from your assailant!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Uh... AAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Orderrr! What...is the meaning of this?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The meaning is that Ms Kira didn't actually hear the incantation like she claims she did!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-but then, why... Why on earth was this girl unconscious?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Kira was definitely knocked out by whoever attacked her... and when she woke up, she found herself up on the top floor of the bell tower.</thought> It's possible Ms Kira was rendered unconscious by...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think it's possible...that another kind of sleeping spell could have been used here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Another...sleeping spell?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...like, a really DEEP sleeping spell, or something...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Stop fooling around and get serious! It's not exactly a picnic having to lug this oversized paperweight out every time I need to fact-check your crazy claims...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not a paperweight, Maya... And I'll have you know my claims are not crazy.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Moving on. The only other sleeping spell I am aware of...is the crazy nonsense coming out of your mouth, defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honour... The defence humbly requests another shot...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well...what if I told you there was ANOTHER witch present?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ ...And? Do explain to the court this brilliant theory of yours, defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?! U-uh... To be honest with you, I was kinda hoping everyone would sorta help me fill in the blanks...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ I will not allow you to drag the rest of this court in to the depths of stupidity with you. Defender! This ridiculous excuse for an argument is yours and yours alone, do you understand me?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, ma'am! <thought>Boy, I really ticked her off...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Don't be such a crybaby! Put on your big-boy pants and try again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The answer here is obvious. Something other than magic must have knocked her out.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Wh-what?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Kira's claim that she heard someone say the incantation is completely false. Even so... that wouldn't be too much of a problem if she actually had heard an incantation.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-that... That's right...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However... Going by her testimony, that can't have been the case. The only spell capable of making someone lose consciousness is Fainfol. Isn't that right, High Inquisitor Darklaw?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">D-defender! Are you claiming there is another way, beside magic, that could have been used to render Miss Kira unconscious?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's only one other thing that crossed my mind... I'm speaking, of course, about sleeping medicine.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Sleeping medicine?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you remember, Ms Kira stated that the attacker covered her mouth before she could scream. In doing that...the attacker was able to administer a potent sleep medicine, thus putting Ms Kira out like a light.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">H-hmm... Indeed. That does make sense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Therefore, Your Honour! The attacker did not necessarily have to be Bezella. ...I mean, why would an all-powerful being, capable of commanding any and all magic, need to resort to drugging someone?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-the robe of invisibility...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, despite all that...there's still one glaring problem. ...Ms Kira.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Y-yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You admitted to the court earlier that you were attacked from the front, correct? If that's the case...then there's only one possible conclusion we can draw. You, Ms Kira...were entirely capable of seeing your attacker's face!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Wh-wh-why is that?! I didn't...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It's simple. You even said it yourself. Only residents of the Eldwitch Woods are able to see this robe. That means, Ms Kira...there is a piece of this puzzle only you could possibly know! Only you can tell us the identity of the person who entered the bell tower and attacked you tonight!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ ...I can't tell you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...No matter what happens... ...I just can't tell you, no matter what...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You see, everyone... This witness has been covering up for someone from the very start of this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But luckily for us...we won't be needing any more of Ms Kira's testimony. Because the answer is staring us right in the face. I'm speaking, of course, about the true identity of Ms Kira's attacker... All the clues so far point to this one person!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Defender. I take it you are prepared to prove such a serious accusation?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I am. <thought>All right...it looks like it all comes down to this. Now we'll finally see who's been pulling the strings this whole time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Defender, tell the court... Who was the one responsible for attacking the witness and locking her up on the top floor of the bell tower?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?! U-um... How can I explain it? You could say I just kinda...had a hunch.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Again, I must be honest with you. I do not agree with this "hunch" of yours.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Milord, I have a little "hunch" of my own... I think perhaps this defender could benefit from a bit of fresh air out in the pillories.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah yes, now that I can agree with. ...That would give you plenty of time to get all those absurd "hunches" out of your system.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no thanks! I'm good! Please, just...let me give it another shot! <thought>Okay, Phoenix, think! Who would be capable of intimidating Kira into covering up for them?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The answer is obvious, Your Honour. It was you! ...High inquisitor Darklaw!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wha... WHAAAAAAAAT?! Order! Order! Order in the court! I-inconceivable... There's no way...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I must say, defender... Your courage is impressive, however reckless you may be. Accusing a High Inquisitor is no small feat, I assure you... However... With serious accusations come serious consequences. One small misstep... and I will personally see that you never set foot in this courtroom ever again. ...Mark my words, defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Hmph. My, how confident. Let us see if that confidence of yours... is well justified!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Kira's attacker drugged her with sleep medicine. It likely took no more than a few seconds for her to lose consciousness. The medicine must've been very potent...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...true. After all, its effects appear somewhat similar to magic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's only...one person I can think of in all of Labyrinthia who could supply you with that kind of medicine. ...Sir Newton Belduke.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's a fact I'm well aware of, believe me. While he was still alive, Sir Belduke provided the citizens of this town with a variety of medicines for whatever ailed them... But it wasn't all just medicine. He also created some very dangerous concoctions. That's why, after he passed away...all of his medicines and creations were confiscated.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">C-confiscated?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Inquisitor Barnham said as much in the last witch trial.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The victim was an alchemist, after all. We were hoping the items confiscated from his study could provide some clues. Besides, such things must not fall into the wrong hands. It may not be standard practice, but it was deemed necessary. The confiscated goods are stored in our secret vault. The only person with access to them is the High Inquisitor, Lady Darklaw.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Unfortunately for you...I would hardly call that "proof". You said it yourself... Sir Belduke concocted a plethora of dangerous medicines in his efforts to assist the people of the town... He was well known for this fact... A fact that he no doubt was none too pleased with. As such, it is highly likely that those same dangerous substances are still scattered throughout the town!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">And therefore, defender...it is entirely possible that the culprit was able to get their hands on such dangerous medicine.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Indeed. Long has Sir Belduke's medicine played an active part in maintaining the health of this town's citizens... There is plenty of reason to believe some of his more dangerous medicines still remain within Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Hmph... A piece of advice, defender: the next time you speak in court... I recommend you try procuring some real evidence before spouting such idiotic accusations. If you fail to do so...your next words will be uttered to the flames.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Figures... I knew she wouldn't take that argument sitting down.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Both High Inquisitor Darklaw and Inquisitor Barnham are the very harbingers of justice within Labyrinthia. Raising such an accusation against either one of them without valid reason will result in the most severe of punishments.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-what does he mean by the "most severe of punishments"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think the judge is saying that if I don't start making a case...we're gonna be paying Sir Belduke a visit real soon. <thought>I need to present some decisive evidence and fast... I'm pretty sure I should be able to do that much... High Inquisitor Darklaw is the attacker, and the one thing that proves it is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Your Honour. The defence has decisive evidence linking the High Inquisitor with tonight's crime!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Evidence, you say? ...You seem rather certain, defender. Very well... Here's your chance to present this so-called evidence. Show the court the piece of evidence that connects High Inquisitor Darklaw to tonight's crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's right, Your Honour. But more than that...this pendant has left us a pretty important clue. High Inquisitor! This pendant is connected to another clue still present somewhere on your person!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The only thing this evidence proves... is how decisively daft your argument is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaaarrrgggh!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you doing, Nick?! They're gonna throw us in the fire if you don't get this right...for REAL this time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's gotta be a clue proving that Darklaw was at the scene of the crime... All right. Back to the drawing board!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...The proof is in the pudding, Your Honour. Or in this case, the Profiles. The defence believes there is someone in particular who can prove Darklaw was the attacker!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">D-did you say "someone", defender? Hmm...indeed. Very well... Here's your chance to present this evidence. Show the court the piece of evidence that connects High Inquisitor Darklaw to tonight's crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?! Oh, well y'see... I, uh...thought they looked kinda suspicious...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Since you seem to be in the mood to point out "suspicious" people... Instead of wasting the court's time, why not start with the oddly dressed person standing right next to you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Thanks a lot, Nick! Now people think I dress funny! This is all your fault!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trust me, Maya... Everyone thought you dressed funny before I ever even opened my mouth. <thought>There's gotta be a clue proving that Darklaw was at the scene of the crime... All right. Back to the drawing board!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...The defence believes there is one clue here linking High Inquisitor Darklaw to the crime... High Inquisitor! That clue is actually still on you right now!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">O-on...me?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I must admit I do not know where you are going with this defender, but...please point out this clue to the court. Show us this clue, supposedly still on the High Inquisitor's person!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Defender, I recommend you get rid of that smug look and take that pointing finger out of my face...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">That is... unless you'd rather I REMOVE it for you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaaaarrrrrrgggggh! <thought>*gulp* Well, that was wrong...and scary...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hang in there, Nick! We're so close I can taste it! Just relax your finger, take a deep breath... and have another look in the Court Record!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Taking the pendant must have left some sort of mark behind... The question is: where...? All right. Back to the drawing board!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-the... The High Inquisitor's...neck? You don't mean...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ms Kira yanked this pendant off of her attacker's neck. Take a look at the necklace...it still has a bit of blood left on it.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to her earlier testimony, when Ms Kira pulled at the necklace... she supposedly felt herself scratch the attacker's neck. Is that correct, Ms Kira?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Y-yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Therefore! The attacker should still have a mark on their neck from having been scratched.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Would you mind letting the court take a look at your neck, High Inquisitor Darklaw? I'm pretty sure that underneath that high collar, we'll find exactly the mark we're looking for! ...Unless, of course, you were able to get rid of it with magic!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...... ......... ............ Hmph...most impressive.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I have to say, defender... You've managed to finally hone that dull blade of yours into something of use. You are correct. There is, in fact, a mark on my neck that I did receive tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wha... WHAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">........................ Ah, err...oh! ...Y-yes! I see you're still here, defender!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Your Honour...I know you're shocked and everything, but c'mon...work with me here.</thought> Your Honour, the defence... would like to call High Inquisitor Darklaw to the witness stand!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what did you just say?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's quite clear that the High Inquisitor has some connection to what transpired tonight! And what's more... There is a chance that she used her position of authority as High Inquisitor to frame my client as the Great Witch!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-but, never in all my years as judge of this court has an inquisitor been asked to take the stand in the middle of a trial!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well, we're going to have to make some history here if we're finally going to find the truth, Your Honour!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">E-even so... This trial cannot continue any further without an inquisitor!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Um, in that case...how about you get Inquisitor Barn-</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Inquisitor Barnham remains incarcerated in the underground dungeons, for the crime of treason against the Storyteller. ...I don't think he will be able to make it to this party.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-no way!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Most regrettable, defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This whole thing is hopeless... Unless High Inquisitor Darklaw takes to the witness stand... Espella will be done for... and the truth along with her! But on the other hand...without an inquisitor on the other side... the trial can't continue and the outcome would end up the same... What should I do...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Anime cutscene</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I believe I can fill that role.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Professor, wait...what are you saying?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I can prove conclusively... that Espella Cantabella, is in fact the Great Witch Bezella! Now, Mr Wright. The time has come at last, to settle this once and for all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Professor... But...what are you doing?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What am I doing, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! You were supposed to show up with some decisive evidence and save the day, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...I'm afraid my only concern here is the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The truth...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The truth behind the real identity of the Great Witch...Espella Cantabella. If seeking the truth requires us to stand on opposite sides of the courtroom... then so be it. I expect you to defend Miss Cantabella with everything you've got, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now back in session. Are you prepared, High Inquisitor?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">So long as I remain on the witness stand, I am no longer High Inquisitor. Simply "Darklaw", will suffice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Darklaw... I'd like to just confirm something. A moment ago, we established... that you were, in fact, present at the bell tower during the time of the incident. That makes a total of three people at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...It would appear that was the case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However, you managed to stay hidden from ten different guards... with the help of this right here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The robe of invisibility...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In other words, there is every reason to be suspicious of your actions tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Lady Darklaw... While I cannot believe you would deceive us in such a way... I ask that you tell the court what happened at the time of the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The town square was to be the parade's final stop. I patrolled the perimeter to ensure nothing was amiss.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You apprehended the intruder...?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">While I hold the position of High Inquisitor... there are often times when I must partake in various secret tasks, unbeknownst to the citizens of Labyrinthia. One of those tasks being...ensuring the security of the Storyteller.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Security?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...As such, there is nothing odd nor suspicious about my actions tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I see. Defender, you may now begin your interrogation.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The town square was to be the parade's final stop. I patrolled the perimeter to ensure nothing was amiss.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Now you tell me, defender. Surely you remember the final part of the Story.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She must mean the part about the Storyteller's death...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">There is little possibility of changing the outcome of what has already been written in the Story. However there are still those...who would challenge the Story and make an attempt at changing the inevitable.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...That is what I, too, think.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's up, Maya? Did you notice something?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... You could say that. It's just...look at Kira. She's been looking down in the dumps since the start.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, right...Kira. I honestly forgot she was still here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Not only that...she looks sorta scared, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're right... We can't afford to forget about her. <thought>...I wonder if Kira has anything else she could tell us. I've got to remember to question her the second I see an opening...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">As I passed by the bell tower, a pair of small footprints leading inside caught my eye. I went inside to investigate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Indeed. The ground outside was quite muddy after the rain, so her footprints were easily visible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. According to the Vigilantes' testimony... They thought the footprints looked like Foxy's, but it turned out they weren't hers...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...That's right. Her footprint would have contained a mark where her stiletto had been. But...the footprints I saw at the bell tower contained no heel mark at all.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And you stepped inside those footprints on your way up the stairs so as not to leave your own and risk being detected, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Exactly. At that time, my main task was to ensure the safety of the town square... In doing so, it was of the utmost importance that no one knew of my presence there.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Had the townspeople noticed your presence there, it would undoubtedly have raised some suspicion...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Indeed. So naturally, that is why I did not wish to be noticed by the Vigilantes. Therefore, it was imperative that I mask any traces of my being there, even if it meant utilising another's footprints.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...I see. A clever tactic worthy of the High Inquisitor herself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is there anything off about her testimony just now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I can't let the professor catch me off guard. If I'm going to press an issue, I'd better be sure I know what I'm talking about.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">...A wise decision, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Boy, Nick... He can totally read you like a book.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay, seriously...is my face THAT easy to read, or is everyone just psychic?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ms Darklaw. I just noticed something in your testimony... that's very relevant to the case! The defence requests you amend your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Hmph... You just can't help letting that ridiculous imagination of yours run wild, can you...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The inquisition...has no objections.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. The witness will amend her testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Indeed. The ground outside was quite muddy after the rain, so her footprints were easily visible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. According to the Vigilantes' testimony... They thought the footprints looked like Foxy's, but it turned out they weren't hers...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...That's right. Her footprint would have contained a mark where her stiletto had been. But...the footprints I saw at the bell tower contained no heel mark at all.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And you stepped inside those footprints on your way up the stairs so as not to leave your own and risk being detected, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Exactly. At that time, my main task was to ensure the safety of the town square... In doing so, it was of the utmost importance that no one knew of my presence there.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Had the townspeople noticed your presence there, it would undoubtedly have raised some suspicion...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Indeed. So naturally, that is why I did not wish to be noticed by the Vigilantes. Therefore, it was imperative that I mask any traces of my being there, even if it meant utilising another's footprints.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...I see. A clever tactic worthy of the High Inquisitor herself.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">There was no heel on the footprints, so as I ascended the stairs, I was careful to match my footsteps to them, as far as possible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">It is as I said earlier. I was in the town square to make sure the area was secure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, but...surely you had some inkling that Bezella might've been lurking around there somewhere, right? Wouldn't it have been a lot better if you went into the bell tower with some backup from the Vigilantes?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Defender, you witnessed the summoning of the fire dragon with your own eyes, did you not? Ten more people at my side against a power such as that would only mean ten more lives lost.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's got a point there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">And besides...even if those ten had been with me... Their combined strength is nary that of even Barnham's annoying mutt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No objections here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Say, Nick. About Darklaw's testimony... I think I noticed something kinda fishy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, me too. <thought>It'd probably be a good idea to give the Court Record another check, just in case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">It would appear so. I would never mean to offend the hard work of Labyrinthia's Vigilantes, but...tonight's task was mine and mine alone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, okay. When you put it that way... I can't help but notice a contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What...did you say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Darklaw, you stated the following: When you climbed the stairs, the footprints had no heel, so you tried to match your footsteps to them as far as possible. However, if you look at the actual footprints that were left behind... You can clearly see that not only is the heel present, but so is the entire foot. If you were trying so hard to step on the footprints already there, then the footprints in this sketch shouldn't have heel marks.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...that is very true. Although I do not think such a small detail is of much importance in the long run.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I agree, it's a small detail, Your Honour. But that's not all I noticed... There was something very telling about Ms Darklaw's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Telling, you say...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She stated that she stepped on to the footprints that were already at the scene, in order to disguise her presence. Now, there's something strange there. Specifically... Why were these footprints left at the crime scene in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Tell me, can you show the court why this seemingly minor detail is odd?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I... I can't exactly do that at the moment...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Who can say whether or not these footprints are indeed worthy of concern? And if it is an issue, then what exactly are the implications? That, above all, is what you must answer, Mr Wright. I do not believe you can assert that this is a blatant "contradiction" at this time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Urk! <thought>There he goes again, flexing that amazing brain of his...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Umm... ............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what is it, Ms Kira?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ O-oh... It's nothing. Really.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...What the heck was that about...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It looked like Kira definitely had something she wanted to say just now.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It would appear the witness has nothing to add. Lady Darklaw...will you please continue with your testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Anyway... Darklaw shouldn't be able to explain her way out of trouble much longer. There's got to be something more to those footprints...but what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">It would appear so. I would never mean to offend the hard work of Labyrinthia's Vigilantes, but...tonight's task was mine and mine alone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, okay. When you put it that way... I can't help but notice a contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What...did you say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Darklaw, you stated the following: When you climbed the stairs, the footprints had no heel, so you tried to match your footsteps to them as far as possible. However, if you look at the actual footprints that were left behind... You can clearly see that not only is the heel present, but so is the entire foot. If you were trying so hard to step on the footprints already there, then the footprints in this sketch shouldn't have heel marks.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...that is very true. Although I do not think such a small detail is of much importance in the long run.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I agree, it's a small detail, Your Honour. But that's not all I noticed... There was something very telling about Ms Darklaw's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Telling, you say...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She stated that she stepped on to the footprints that were already at the scene, in order to disguise her presence. Now, there's something strange there. Specifically... Why were these footprints left at the crime scene in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Tell me, can you show the court why this seemingly minor detail is odd?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I... I can't exactly do that at the moment...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Who can say whether or not these footprints are indeed worthy of concern? And if it is an issue, then what exactly are the implications? That, above all, is what you must answer, Mr Wright. I do not believe you can assert that this is a blatant "contradiction" at this time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Urk! <thought>There he goes again, flexing that amazing brain of his...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I had my own reasons for not allowing any one of those Vigilantes to see me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">They relate to protecting the Storyteller... It was something I was to carry out at that particular time.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Did it perhaps have something to do with what was already decided upon in the Story?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The Storyteller's word is absolute. Therefore... Any and all those who make an attempt to alter his will must be dealt with immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Ms Kira?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Witness!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Ah! Y-yes...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Figures... She really doesn't remember her own name...</thought> You seem to be deep in thought about something... Did you remember anything regarding the High Inquisitor's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...No, I'm sorry. ...Nothing in particular... It's just... I'm a little disappointed in myself...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Disappointed...?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I travelled all the way here to Labyrinthia in order to fulfil my mission, but... all I managed to do was fail and end up being captured...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Regardless of your own failure, Miss Kira, the Storyteller did die as was foretold, did he not...?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Tonight...as the rain came pouring down over the town...I arrived at my designated location. Naturally, the bell tower was surrounded by guards on patrol. Ten, to be exact... I was very nervous.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She must be talking about the Vigilantes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kira">"Just relax. You'll be fine so long as you're wearing this robe," I kept telling myself... Little did I know, I was wrong. But...none of this would have happened if I was just a little bit more careful...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Enough. I would be thinking more about atoning for your past crimes and less about what could have been, if I were you.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is there anything wrong with Kira's testimony?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No, looks like Kira's testimony is a one-way road to nowhere...</thought> ...All right. No further questions, Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Understood. Lady Darklaw, please continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Hold on one second. About your testimony, Ms Kira... You were thinking to yourself that so long as you had your robe on, you would be fine...</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Y-yes. That's right, I was...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So basically, you were wearing the robe the whole time you were on the top floor of the bell tower, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Y-yes. I had it on the entire time. That is...until I was attacked... Then my robe was ripped off by the wind...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Kira, this is the first time we've heard any mention of this information.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I-is that so? I think I must have just forgotten...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Your Honour, perhaps we should update this piece of evidence in the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Right you are.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Lady Darklaw, please continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Ms Kira?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Witness!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Ah! Y-yes...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Figures... She really doesn't remember her own name...</thought> You seem to be deep in thought about something... Did you remember anything regarding the High Inquisitor's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...No, I'm sorry. ...Nothing in particular... It's just... I'm a little disappointed in myself...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Disappointed...?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I travelled all the way here to Labyrinthia in order to fulfil my mission, but... all I managed to do was fail and end up being captured...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Regardless of your own failure, Miss Kira, the Storyteller did die as was foretold, did he not...?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Tonight...as the rain came pouring down over the town...I arrived at my designated location. Naturally, the bell tower was surrounded by guards on patrol. Ten, to be exact... I was very nervous.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She must be talking about the Vigilantes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kira">"Just relax. You'll be fine so long as you're wearing this robe," I kept telling myself... Little did I know, I was wrong. But...none of this would have happened if I was just a little bit more careful...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Enough. I would be thinking more about atoning for your past crimes and less about what could have been, if I were you.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, there's absolutely no way you would have been able to disappear from sight! Not unless...you either used magic or were wearing this robe.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The night is still young, defender. You ought to save the theatrics for later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">There was indeed a very simple way that I was able to sneak into the bell tower.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A...simple way? Like what?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Come now. Must I really spell it out for you? I used this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-that's...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">This is the whistle used by the guardsmen to warn of danger. The second any guard hears this whistle, they immediately head out to investigate the trouble...Vigilantes included. With a simple blow of this whistle... those guards took off from their post.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And then, the second they were distracted, you crept into the bell tower undetected.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">All I needed was a small break in their perimeter to sneak in. It was so easy, even a person of your calibre could do it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I see. Then surely, there was absolutely no need for this robe, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Indeed, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I climbed the stairs up the bell tower and saw an intruder inside with their back turned. I proceeded to apprehend them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ While I hate to admit this... I allowed myself to act rashly without first considering the circumstances.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">So, the second I noticed their presence, I took action. Never did I imagine the intruder would have as much strength as they did... Perhaps I should have gathered more forces to accompany me... However, at the time... I was not thinking straight. ...I assumed any additional help would not be necessary.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-but, Lady Darklaw...through your quick thinking and judgement... you still managed to successfully catch the suspect!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Unfortunately, Milord...'twas nothing more than pure luck. Exceptional results can only be obtained through exceptional thinking. ...Don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Umm. Why are you looking at me when you say that...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What are you talking about, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Kira... Err, or should I say, the witness... stated that while she was waiting on the upper floor of the tower... she was wearing her invisibility robe. ...Therefore! There's no way Ms Darklaw would have been able to see the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Oh! Y-you're quite right! Anyone wearing this robe becomes invisible!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right, but...there is just one particular group that CAN see anyone dressed in this robe.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-and who is that, exactly...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Only residents of the Eldwitch Woods are able to see the robe. If you're from the Eldwitch Woods, then you'll have absolutely no problem seeing this thing!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's right, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh- What is THIIIIIIS?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A most impressive display, Mr Wright. However... there is one detail that you appear to have overlooked.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-something I overlooked...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You say Miss Darklaw saw something she should not have been able to see... However, the truth is...that there is one other possibility as to what occurred tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>Did he just say what I think he said?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">...It's rather easy to work out. Quite simply, the witness was not wearing the robe in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what are you talking about, Inquisitor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This witness has proven her memory of tonight's events to be quite unreliable. I believe that by the time she climbed the bell tower, she had, in fact, already removed her robe...</line>
<line speaker="Kira">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...'Tis as you say, Inquisitor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">As you can see, defender...your assertion is mere speculation, at best. Your little witness here has been lying to the court the entire time. It's as simple as that.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ ...I'm not sure...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I mean, my...my memory is a little fuzzy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no way!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It would appear there is nothing more to be gained from this line of questioning.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Your Honour, I suggest we return to the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A fine idea, Inquisitor. Well then...Lady Darklaw. Will you please continue with your testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...As you wish.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No matter how you slice it, Kira looks like she's definitely hiding something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... If only there was some way of getting her to talk, huh, Nick? No matter what Kira says, Darklaw just stays cool and brushes it off...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah. This isn't going to be easy, that's for sure. That's why... we really need to set our sights on Darklaw. If we keep doing that... then sooner or later, Kira is bound to speak up and say something.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa, Nick... That's your most dastardly devious plan yet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All right, I know there's still a clue or two in this testimony somewhere... And I'm gonna find it! I should go back and double-check her previous testimony. There have to be some more contradictions...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What are you talking about, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Kira... Err, or should I say, the witness... stated that while she was waiting on the upper floor of the tower... she was wearing her invisibility robe. ...Therefore! There's no way Ms Darklaw would have been able to see the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Oh! Y-you're quite right! Anyone wearing this robe becomes invisible!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right, but...there is just one particular group that CAN see anyone dressed in this robe.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-and who is that, exactly...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Only residents of the Eldwitch Woods are able to see the robe. If you're from the Eldwitch Woods, then you'll have absolutely no problem seeing this thing!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's right, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh- What is THIIIIIIS?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A most impressive display, Mr Wright. However... there is one detail that you appear to have overlooked.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-something I overlooked...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You say Miss Darklaw saw something she should not have been able to see... However, the truth is...that there is one other possibility as to what occurred tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>Did he just say what I think he said?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">...It's rather easy to work out. Quite simply, the witness was not wearing the robe in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what are you talking about, Inquisitor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This witness has proven her memory of tonight's events to be quite unreliable. I believe that by the time she climbed the bell tower, she had, in fact, already removed her robe...</line>
<line speaker="Kira">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...'Tis as you say, Inquisitor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">As you can see, defender...your assertion is mere speculation, at best. Your little witness here has been lying to the court the entire time. It's as simple as that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like that's all we're getting out of her for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y'know, if Darklaw was just going into the bell tower to arrest some intruder... then I wonder why she didn't just come out and say that to begin with?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Simple... That information was on a strictly need-to-know basis.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Need-to-know basis, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That sort of secrecy is pretty common, but usually they've got to have a reason for not disclosing the information to begin with. <thought>Darklaw was hiding this information for a reason. That's why we need to find out exactly what she was doing in that tower... I've got to get her to tell us!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick. Is it me, or do you feel like we're being...watched?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, tell me about it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder what's up with the professor? Something MUST have happened! There's no way he'd turn on us like this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The professor has been very quiet so far... But surely... He must've noticed there's something that just doesn't add up with Darklaw's testimony...</thought> ...Anyway, there's bound to be something in this testimony that we can use. We just have to make sure we comb this thing from top to bottom for any contradictions.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...That's right!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ ...That's enough...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Ms Kira...?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Lady Darklaw... How? How could you... How could you simply abandon us? How could you...betray us?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Betray"...? W-witness, what is the meaning of this?!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Lady Darklaw, you are...you are the mistress of the Eldwitch Woods. You are the one responsible for handing us our "tasks"...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-whaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...This wretched girl is nothing more than a detestable spawn of magic. Her words cannot be taken seriously. People of Labyrinthia, I ask you! What am I, if not a loyal daughter of this fair town?!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">No! You're lying, Lady Darklaw! When I was waiting up there at the top of the bell tower, I was most certainly wearing that robe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Lady Darklaw...you... You were also wearing a similar robe, were you not? Don't you remember?!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Hmph... What nonsense. I haven't a clue what you're babbling about. I simply managed to sneak right by those makeshift guards... 'Twas not the most demanding of tasks for someone like me.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Yes, you're right... That would be true... if you'd been sneaking around by yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"By yourself"...? Witness, explain yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Enough. Listen to me and listen well. Continue as you are...and I will see to it that this court be the last place in which you ever set foot.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">It matters not... The end is already nigh. After the events of today, I shouldn't even be here right now...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Kira... You're saying that Ms Darklaw was not by herself at the time of the incident tonight?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...That's right. Lady Darklaw was wearing the invisibility robe. And underneath that robe... was a young girl, passed out on her back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A girl...? Could that be...</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Yes. It was...the very same girl imprisoned inside that cage up there.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-you mean... Espella Cantabella?! Order! Orderrr! S-so the accused was carried up the bell tower...?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Milord, there is nothing left for me to say. 'Tis the word of the High Inquisitor versus that of a witch. Tell me, who would you sooner believe?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The only thing that carries any meaning here within the courtroom is evidence. Don't you agree, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes. Absolutely, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Well, now...things are beginning to heat up a little, are they not? Fine. Tell me, defender...have you the means to prove this assertion? Do you actually think you can prove that I, the High Inquisitor of Labyrinthia, carried the accused into the bell tower?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>From the looks of it, Ms Kira was supposed to keep quiet about Darklaw's little secret... But she couldn't deal with all of Darklaw's denials and finally found the guts to chime in. I can't let Kira's effort go to waste... I don't care what stands in my way... I'm going to find the truth!</thought> ...Your Honour, the defence wishes to present evidence proving that Ms Darklaw did, in fact, carry my client up the tower!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, defender. You may present your evidence. Show us the evidence that proves Lady Darklaw carried the accused up the bell tower!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Say what?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright, it pains me to say this, but it seems I may have overestimated you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come again?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Hmph...you are not worthy to stand behind that bench. Take that strange lackey of yours and leave this courtroom NOW!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaarrrrgggh!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............ Wait a second... "Strange lackey"...? Say, you don't think she means...me, do you, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...I'm pretty sure she did, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">NICK! You're just gonna sit there and let her get away with trash-talking me like that?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I sure am. Welcome to my world, Maya...</thought> A-anyway! The defence wishes to try again!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Please endeavour to make your point more clearly this time, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was something in your testimony just now that I'm not buying... ...And that's the footprints that were left at the bell tower.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Did I not just finish admitting that those were my footprints?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Darklaw, you stated the following: "There was no heel on the footprints, so as I ascended the stairs, I was careful to match my footsteps to them as far as possible"... However, the reality is... the footprints pictured in the sketch actually do contain a heel. That means...something must have prevented you from being able to tiptoe along the footprints that were already there.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Prevented"...? Ah! Y-you mean...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's right, Your Honour. Ms Darklaw, when you climbed up the bell tower tonight... you must have been carrying Ms Cantabella on your back. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you remember, it rained quite heavily tonight. That means the stairs must have been quite slippery. With your two hands occupied carrying my client, there would be no safe way for you to tiptoe up the stairs without falling... That right there is the truth behind the footprints on the staircase!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">L-Lady Darklaw... Y-you...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ ...Fine. I admit it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">It is as you say... I donned the robe and made my way up the tower. But I was not alone. I carried both Espella Cantabella and her little "friend" up the tower with me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Little friend"...?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">That black-furred creature of hers. The thing is nary ever a second from her side.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! She must mean Eve!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">When I arrived at the top of the tower... I saw this girl already there and called out to her.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...I was very shocked to see the mistress show up in person like that.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The girl's presence was an inconvenience... So I immediately put her to sleep. Believe it or not, it's just like you said, defender. I used what remained of Belduke's medicine to put the girl out of the picture.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's when... Ms Kira put up a fight and pulled this pendant right off your neck, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I cannot fathom it. That would mean... This pendant actually belongs to you, Lady Darklaw?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ ...I just have one question, Ms Darklaw. Why? Why take Espella up the bell tower? Why render her unconscious? ...And why go through the trouble of sneaking past the guards? What exactly was your aim in all of this?!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...I am in no way obliged to answer that question, defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! Wh-what makes you say that?!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Simple. None of this has any relevance to the case at hand. That is why.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Professor... What are you saying?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would seem the defence has forgotten a very important point. Namely, the point of this, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The aim of this trial is to find the identity of the Great Witch Bezella. Whether or not Miss Darklaw locked the witness at the top of the bell tower... is hardly relevant to the purpose of this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-but...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...There is one thing that is very clear. Neither Miss Darklaw nor this witness could possibly be Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If either one of the two were Bezella, then there would be no need for them to have used this robe of invisibility. They cannot use any magic... Therefore, it is inconceivable that either of them could be the Great Witch.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...A rather straightforward argument if there ever was one.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">At the time of the incident, there were three people present. Of those three, two used the robe of invisibility to vanish from sight. Leaving only one person. Indeed... Miss Cantabella.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urgh!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...With this in mind, the larger question is: who is Bezella?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Is that not obvious? The accused, Espella Cantabella, is the only possible answer. Besides, the accused's voice was heard by all the townspeople, chanting the spell Granwyrm.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Only to discover that they are not, in fact, the Great Witch Bezella...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'm saying there's a possibility that these two are somehow related to Bezella!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...The court will now announce its thoughts on the matter. I must say, what Inquisitor Layton has stated certainly does ring true. However, Lady Darklaw... I have one question I must ask you. What exactly were you hoping to accomplish here tonight?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ I assure you...'twas not my intent to deceive the good citizens of Labyrinthia. However... I must now reveal the truth to you all...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Lady Darklaw... Are you saying that you're...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Hmph... That's right, Milord. I am a Shade.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A Shade...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Lady Darklaw. Will you please tell the court exactly what you mean when you say "Shade"?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Yes...of course. I grow weary of standing behind this bench. I will tell you all I can.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What the heck is she trying to pull...? Why testify about something that could potentially undermine your credibility?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Shades live outside the realm of those who dwell within Labyrinthia. To them, I am known as "the Great Witch".</line>
<line speaker="Kira">We exist to carry out tasks given to us by our mistress, the Great Witch herself...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what on earth?! High Inquisitor Darklaw... do you mean to say that not only are you a witch... but that you're the GREAT Witch?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...I do hope you have not forgotten what we established only moments ago. It is not possible for Miss Darklaw to be Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-but, Inquisitor Layton! Surely the testimony just now proves it...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I am afraid that in the heat of such "revelations", you have all misheard the information.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...'Tis pointless. This is the extent of what the people of this town will believe.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I believe the truth will become clear during our cross-examination. Don't you agree, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender, you may begin your interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Shades live outside the realm of those who dwell within Labyrinthia. To them, I am known as "the Great Witch".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Yes, that's right. However...I am not Bezella. The mistress to those who dwell in the Eldwitch Woods is dubbed "the Great Witch". Even if I wanted to be Bezella, I couldn't. As the ever so charming inquisitor stated earlier: I cannot use magic.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Miss Darklaw, I have one question. What do you mean by..."live outside the realm"?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I mean just that, Inquisitor. We truly do live in a realm separate from this town. Now, surely one as intelligent as yourself has worked out the answer by now, no?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps... That remains to be seen, Miss Darklaw.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Regardless...'tis something we cannot discuss with anyone. ...But it is something that the defence should be able to prove.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>That almost sounds like a challenge...</thought> By the way, Ms Darklaw... Since you're not actually a witch... why do you continue to be called that?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">To answer that... I must first discuss the true identity of the Shades.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What is it...Inquisitor Layton?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Through your testimony just now, we have all come to understand the process of how one becomes a Shade. However, I was hoping you could perhaps elaborate on one additional point. Namely, what exactly is the purpose behind the Shades?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ If you wish to know our purpose, there are certain other things you must first understand. Once you've done that...the answer should be quite clear. Isn't that right, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>The purpose behind the Shades?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Rest assured, you will not get the answer from me. As the saying goes, "the witch is in YOUR court", defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like...Darklaw's challenging me to figure this out... ...Challenge accepted!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Those that are put to the flames in the witch trials become Shades, who live their lives in the woods.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Indeed, defender. The girl has no recollection of her life prior to living in those woods.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what manner of witchery is this? Why... this girl, err...Kira the flower seller, was cast straight to the flames before our very eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right, Your Honour. But as you can see, she didn't die. You see...there's actually a trick to the incineration device in the Witches' Court.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-a trick...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Once the verdict has been delivered, the court attendants move the steel cage into position, after which it seals shut. Then...the cage is dropped down into a pit of fire. The bottom of the cage then opens, allowing the witch inside to escape unharmed into an underground passage.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-if what you're saying is true, defender... th-then... what of this town's witch-purging history? What has been the purpose of all of this...?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">You and the knights have indeed been ridding Labyrinthia of witches. However... Nary a single life has been taken in the process. That is the reality...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-but... you cannot truly expect me to believe such a ridiculous notion...</line>
<line speaker="???">Your Honour! It's TRUE!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Take a good hard look! It doesn't get any more alive than this!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah! I-it's you... ...Aya Mey!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well...it's actually "Maya Fey", Your Forgetfulness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what the heck are you doing?! Everyone's gonna recognise you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, but...seeing is believing, Nick! Now they HAVE to believe you!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Do you see? Are you satisfied? All those found guilty in the witch trials lose their names, magic and memory. They are then sent to spend their lives as Shades in the Eldwitch Woods. And the mistress of those Shades is the Great Witch... As you can see...this girl, too, has become a Shade.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I-I have no more words to express my utter disbelief at this situation...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...That's enough. Shall we return to the testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I have the feeling things are going to get a LOT worse...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What is it...Inquisitor Layton?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Through your testimony just now, we have all come to understand the process of how one becomes a Shade. However, I was hoping you could perhaps elaborate on one additional point. Namely, what exactly is the purpose behind the Shades?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ If you wish to know our purpose, there are certain other things you must first understand. Once you've done that...the answer should be quite clear. Isn't that right, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>The purpose behind the Shades?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Rest assured, you will not get the answer from me. As the saying goes, "the witch is in YOUR court", defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like...Darklaw's challenging me to figure this out... ...Challenge accepted!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Indeed, defender. The girl has no recollection of her life prior to living in those woods.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... There is no doubt that this young lady did not perish after that previous trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's all thanks to this door on the bottom of the cage.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Right. So in reality, the witch escaped the cage just in time to avoid the flames... To think such trickery was being used right under my beard... I truly had no idea.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Boy, even the judge was clueless about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">My sincerest apologies, Milord. The only ones privy to this information were the Storyteller, myself and a handful of the Shades. It was imperative this be kept a secret from the citizens of this town.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ If I may be frank... I must say, I am a little relieved to hear this.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I feel I carried out my role as judge of these witch trials to the best of my ability... For that, I have no regrets. However... If this means that lives were actually being saved this entire time... then I do believe the secrets and deception were worth it.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ Indeed, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Miss Darklaw, you are saying that these chambers of fire have been nothing more than mere trickery, are you not?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...That is correct. All those found guilty within the Witches' Court lose their name, their grasp of magic and their memory. They are then sent to spend their lives as Shades in the Eldwitch Woods. And the mistress of those Shades is the Great Witch... As you can see...this girl, too, has become a Shade.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I-I still cannot wrap my head around this whole situation...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Now, if you don't mind, shall we get back to my testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Figures... The judge is having one heck of a time coming to grips with all this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kira">We exist to carry out tasks given to us by our mistress, the Great Witch herself...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Yes. I was told to come here and become Bezella...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-wait just a moment, witness... Did you just say become Bezella?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Or-order! ORDER!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I'm sorry... I don't know why I was given such a task... All I can do...is follow the orders I am given. If I can do that...then I can return.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what do you mean "you can return"...?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Such is the nature of the Shades. Neither human nor witch... Theirs is an existence spent in the shadows. Each of the Shades is given specific tasks. Then...upon successfully completing such tasks... they are allowed to return to Labyrinthia as brand new people...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-but, Lady Darklaw! How can they return as brand new citizens... when we already know who they were? For instance, we all recognise the former flower seller standing before us...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Now that, Milord, remains a secret. But a secret you will come to understand sooner rather than later.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-simply baffling...</line>
<line speaker="Kira">The one who gives us our tasks is the Great Witch. That would be you, Lady Darklaw... Um, I mean...oh magnificent one...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">While this explanation is wrought with much I cannot comprehend...I request the witnesses add it to their testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Okay.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Lady Darklaw...was our venerable mistress. She assigned us our tasks. She was the Great Witch...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ A Shade's tasks must never be discussed with others...no matter what.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She says that even though she just finished telling us all about her "secret" task...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Incidentally, do you perhaps remember... when you arrived back in town to carry out your orders?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Well...not really. My memory is still...a little fuzzy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Say...didn't Kira only just recently become one of those Shade thingies?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Still...I...I failed in my task tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come to think of it, when Luke and I had our little "run-in" with Kira... I remember being blown clear across the marketplace. But, I never saw any explosives or gunpowder...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Maybe... Kira was given the task of blowing you to smithereens, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaaand we're done. Getting back to this testimony... <thought>I'm sure there's something here that just doesn't add up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What is it...Inquisitor Layton?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Through your testimony just now, we have all come to understand the process of how one becomes a Shade. However, I was hoping you could perhaps elaborate on one additional point. Namely, what exactly is the purpose behind the Shades?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ If you wish to know our purpose, there are certain other things you must first understand. Once you've done that...the answer should be quite clear. Isn't that right, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>The purpose behind the Shades?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Rest assured, you will not get the answer from me. As the saying goes, "the witch is in YOUR court", defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like...Darklaw's challenging me to figure this out... ...Challenge accepted!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kira">I am not a witch, nor am I a wandering spirit...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I...I don't.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">When a witch becomes a Shade, they lose all memory of their past life.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-they lose their memories? But...why?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...And yet, you still have some grasp of the concept of magic, do you not, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Let me spell it out for you: magic does not exist in the Eldwitch Woods.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Oh, but... There are actually lots of things back in the forest that I have not seen in this town...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are...things there you haven't seen here?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Like...really huge machines, that sort of thing. There's one that spits out fire with such amazing speed, and then it expels these huge plumes of grey smoke...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-a machine that spits fire...? Never have I heard of such a thing! Are you certain that these "machines" of which you speak are not simply magic...?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">You know...now that you mention it... I don't think anyone from this town... can actually see those of us from the forest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-they can't see you? <thought>Could it be something like that robe...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... How can such a thing even be possible without magic...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What is it...Inquisitor Layton?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Through your testimony just now, we have all come to understand the process of how one becomes a Shade. However, I was hoping you could perhaps elaborate on one additional point. Namely, what exactly is the purpose behind the Shades?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ If you wish to know our purpose, there are certain other things you must first understand. Once you've done that...the answer should be quite clear. Isn't that right, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>The purpose behind the Shades?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Rest assured, you will not get the answer from me. As the saying goes, "the witch is in YOUR court", defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like...Darklaw's challenging me to figure this out... ...Challenge accepted!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">There is...but one true purpose for the Shades that dwell within the Eldwitch Woods.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">As mistress to the Shades... I cannot disclose the purpose of their existence.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Well then. Since Miss Darklaw is unable to tell us herself, it seems we must rely on evidence instead.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Evidence, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I do believe the Shades could have something to do with... that which exists in this town, but ought not to.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>Something that exists...but shouldn't?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Well, defender? Are you prepared to present evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was born ready, Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something that exists in this town, but shouldn't... I think I know what you're getting at, Professor!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender, please present your evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes, Your Honour. The purpose of the Shades could be to make sure this particular thing exists in Labyrinthia!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ Defender, just the other day you found yourself caught up in a nasty little explosion in the marketplace, did you not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y...yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Well then, the Shades' goal should be rather simple to work out. It was to rid Labyrinthia of useless, time-wasting defenders in ridiculous blue outfits!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaaaarrrrgh! <thought>Boy...that was cold-blooded...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">There is but one thing these Shades must ensure exists in this world, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There are many potential answers of which any will do. Show the court one of those answers. And perhaps it would be in your best interest not to anger the witness with an irrelevant answer for a second time, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Could the defence please have another chance to think this through, Your Honour?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Lady Darklaw, please give your testimony to the court one more time!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Of course, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh...well...actually...the defence is not quite ready yet, Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Come now, defender... Surely you, of all people, are aware of just how important it is to know your product before you try and sell it, no?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">You are a baker trying to sell yourself as a defender, and right now, I'm not buying it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That was forever ago.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Lady Darklaw, please testify to the court one more time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Get that objection finger ready, and really nail 'em with some evidence, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's it for her testimony, I guess...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whatcha thinking, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm thinking there's something really weird going on with Darklaw.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? Do tell!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I mean, just listen to her testimony. She's more than willing to elaborate on some potentially incriminating information.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm...I see your point.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The one REALLY trying to put an end to the Story... could be Darklaw herself.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess... But still...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Remember, Nick, we're here to save Espella. So let's squeeze every last bit of information we can out of Darklaw and clear Espella's name!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Y'know, you could be on to something. <thought>I'd better gather as much information as possible, for the time being.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>Something that doesn't exist ...? I have a feeling no one is going to like the answer I'm about to give, and it'll probably end up shaking this town to its core... But...I've got to tell them. The truth has to come out!</thought> ...Since I arrived here in Labyrinthia, there's been no shortage of really strange events. Ignaize, Dimere, Godoor, Goldor... and now Granwyrm.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The mere command of magic is in itself a crime, is it not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In this town, witches are arrested and made to participate in witch trials. They are then sentenced to death by fire. ...But none of those witches actually died! That supposed "death by fire" wasn't real! And... neither is magic. ...It doesn't really exist.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what are you saying, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Eldwitch Woods apparently contain some rather large machines unlike anything that exists within Labyrinthia. Machines that emit fire and produce large plumes of smoke. To top it all off, the citizens of Labyrinthia are not able to see said machines...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It sounds like nothing more than magic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... That's exactly it, Your Honour. Ms Darklaw.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Magic doesn't really exist in this town. That's the answer, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-magic does not... What utter nonsense!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ It seems we have finally arrived at the stunning conclusion... ...The secret behind Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wha............ WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?! Order! Order! ORDER, I say! Wh...wh-what is the meaning of this?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It means...that all of the magic you've seen in this town... was nothing more than an illusion created and put into motion by the Shades!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But, defender! The witches...we have clearly seen them use magic!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ Hmm... Let us take a moment to think carefully about the systems employed by the Shades.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-systems...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What is essential in order for a witch to use magic?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witch must possess a Talea Magica and must say an incantation in order to cast a spell.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...And the spells able to be cast are determined by the sceptre's magic gems. Now, what do you think is the purpose of placing such requirements on the use of magic?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what do you mean..."purpose"?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">These requirements are not there to allow the user to cast magic. Rather, the reality is they are there to inform the Shades of who should be using magic.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is possible...that witches were always being closely observed by Shades. That's why they donned these robes... To appear hidden until they were needed to create magic.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Create"...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Indeed. There are all kinds of spells within this tome. It would be quite troublesome if they were simply allowed to use any spell at will.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...it would make the Shades' job that much more difficult, for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Precisely so. That is why it was imperative that a certain restriction be placed on the use of magic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... You're referring to the Talea Magica, right, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Of course... No wonder the sceptre could contain only two magic gems!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Then there's the incantation... What would happen if a witch could simply whisper the incantation quietly to herself, or not even say it at all?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Boy, that'd be so cool... I'd be casting spells all day long, and no one would ever see it coming!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, we spent an entire trial proving that you WEREN'T a witch, remember? If the witches didn't give some sort of signal... then there would be no way for the Shades to know when to "cast" the spell!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Right you are, Mr Wright. The incantations were a way of telling the Shades when the witch was ready to use magic.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what on earth...? Never did I think these requirements could have such a purpose!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Now, let's think back to the previous events, leading up to today, that have involved magic. Our first encounter with "magic" was the use of the spell Ignaize a few nights ago. A "spell" like this... was nothing more than a flame spewed from a machine being used by the Shades.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-then that means...Dimere...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A spell that makes the caster disappear? No doubt about it... It must have been this robe.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Next is the incident with Goldor, the spell that "transmuted" me into a gold statue. While I understand this may sound a bit absurd, I can only surmise... that the Shades created a gold statue in my image, took me and left it in my place the instant the incantation was uttered.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Professor...it's no more absurd than anything else that's happened so far...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">...We can therefore conclude that all of the "magic" in Labyrinthia was created in a similar vein. What do you say to that, Miss Darklaw?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ ...I'd expect nothing less from you, Inquisitor Layton.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">At any given time, there were between five and ten witches in town. All of the witches were accompanied by Shades at all times. It was easier than you would think. You see, the Shades living in the Eldwitch Woods total in the hundreds. It was simply a matter of having each of the Shades operate in shifts, in order to watch over each of the witches within the town.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I must say, Lady Darklaw... That is quite a number of Shades...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">'Twas not only those who fell victim to the flames that were turned into Shades, but their victims too were made permanent residents of the Eldwitch Woods.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...! Th-then... those two shady thieves from before were... turned into Shades...?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Ah, yes. You mean Robbs and Muggs. Despite their dubious appearance, those two were a couple of my best Shades.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Shady thieves turned into Shades. This stuff writes itself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I cannot believe what I have heard...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...However, there is still one thing I do not understand just yet.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...And what would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">As has just been explained...we have established that there is no possibility of magic being real. But...replacing me with a gold statue to give the illusion of transmutation, for example... While it sounds simple enough... I myself, and presumably also Miss Fey, have no recollection of this replacement actually taking place.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-hey, that's right! The professor got all bling-blingy before I could even bat an eye!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It begs the question: how and when was that statue created, let alone used to replace me...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-that is true...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The same goes for Godoor. It's supposed to create a portal between two green-coloured walls.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps...that is exactly why the spell can only work on green walls, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Still...it'd be impossible for the Shades to get those "portals" ready so quickly.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I agree. If we take a moment to think... we can see that all of these spells have one strange thing in common.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A thing in common?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, indeed. Almost as if some time between the start and end of the incident was unaccounted for... Furthermore, any memory I might have had regarding the incident seems to have simply disappeared in the process.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-I've got it! Nick... it's just like what happened to Kira. She's got absolutely NO memory of her life in Labyrinthia before the trial, right?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Y-yes. I do not remember this "Kira" you speak of...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And... Oh yeah! When you really think about it... doesn't it seem super weird how the Shades are able to return to town if they complete their tasks?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're right, Maya. I mean...the townsfolk are bound to remember some things about them, right? ...Like how Ms Kira here threw a major hissy fit in court and was barbecued for being a witch...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Eloquently put, Mr Wright. Hence we cannot yet conclude that this entire illusion was primarily accomplished through the use of machinery. Simply put... there must have been some way of affecting the memories of all those within the confines of this town.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ Missing time and lost memories? Now that IS interesting, Inquisitor... You are correct. There is, in fact, a secret that lies within the depths of the Eldwitch Woods. Something that the people of this town cannot see... Something that can rob people of their time and memories... 'Tis the very thing that connects all of what you have heard tonight... 'Tis a secret of monumental proportions...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And... Let me guess... 'Tis a secret that cannot be revealed by the mistress of the Eldwitch Woods... Is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Yes. An excellent deduction, defender.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Witches' souls wander astray within the Eldwitch Woods"... Until tonight, I thought this nothing but a mere fairy tale told to children... But it has become clear that a seemingly large organisation lies within that forest!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The Witches' Court is the border between "this world" and the "other world".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then...that means... In "this world", you're Labyrinthia's High Inquisitor...while also being mistress to the Shades in the "other world". <thought>Otherwise known as the Great Witch...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ May I intervene for just a moment,  Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-sure!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">In all honesty...there is still something that sticks out as a little odd. ...Particularly in Miss Darklaw's previous testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-did you say the...previous testimony? <thought>Argh...I'd already pushed that out of my head...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">...There was one vital truth that we managed to take away from that testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You mean that magic does not truly exist in Labyrinthia... Indeed, quite the vital, albeit shocking, truth.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">However... There is one more truth hidden within that same testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>There's something else in that testimony? I must've checked the Court Record more times than I count, but...I didn't find a single other contradiction.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Have you forgotten already, Mr Wright? Where there is no evidence left... we have but one more weapon at our disposal with which to uncover the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...hey! I've got it, Nick! Remember, in a witch trial you can cross-examine two witnesses at the same time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-hey, that's right! I completely forgot! Being able to have a look at two testimonies side-by-side is bound to turn up a contradiction somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And that contradiction...should provide us with a much-needed clue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>I'm not entirely sure where the professor is going with this, but... I believe in his judgment. Besides, if we're going to blow this case wide open, it's got to be worth a shot!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. We will now take a closer look at Lady Darklaw's previous testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This is it...Miss Darklaw's previous testimony. There is a glaring contradiction between this piece of testimony and the others... Ready yourself, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Shades live outside the realm of those who dwell within Labyrinthia. To them, I am known as "the Great Witch".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix/Layton">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix/Layton">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Layton">M-Mr Wright, please wait a moment. Perhaps...you would be better served not leaving this up to chance, would you not agree?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-but, Professor! I could've sworn that was it...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well... If anything is going to contradict Ms Darklaw's testimony, you'd think it'd HAVE to come from Kira. She only has two statements. If it's not one, it's got to be the other. The technical term is "process of elimination", Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gee, thanks for the "pro-tip", Maya...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright. Please...take a moment to think this through carefully and try again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">G-got it, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honour, there's obviously a huge discrepancy between these two pieces of testimony. Ms Darklaw stated that she is known as the Great Witch... However, according to Ms Kira's testimony... Ms Darklaw WAS her "venerable mistress" - the Great Witch.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That is correct. She was the Great Witch... Note Miss Kira's use of the past tense.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Past tense"...? I am afraid my grammar is not quite what it used to be... May I ask what you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's simple. Ms Darklaw WAS mistress to the Shades...or as they also called her, "the Great Witch". Therefore... She...is no longer the Great Witch!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">She is...NOT the Great Witch?! W-witness, is this true?!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Huh?! Uhh...I-I... ............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...It is as you have heard, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I relinquished my position as Great Witch in order to fulfil the objective of this task.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What would that objective be again...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That would be the assassination of the Storyteller, Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Witness! At the beginning of this trial, you stated... that you came to town in order to complete your task, didn't you? What's more... You said that you were going to summon the fire dragon to do it. Now, this task...it wasn't Ms Darklaw here that gave it to you, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...N-no, it wasn't...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">So then...the most pressing question is: who was it that gave you that task? Who told you to come to Labyrinthia and assassinate the Storyteller?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ I...I cannot tell you. ...No matter what...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All right. So Darklaw isn't the "Great Witch" any more... Which must mean...the mastermind behind this entire thing is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hm... It would seem the defence has worked it out as well. Mr Wright, you know who really gave Miss Kira her task tonight, do you not?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender, I ask that you enlighten the court. Show us who really gave this witness her task to assassinate the Storyteller!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Defender! Pray this mysterious mastermind gets their hands on you before I do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaarrrrrgh! <thought>Boy, she REALLY doesn't like me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">It pains me to say this, but it seems as if I might have overestimated you. Now then, please endeavour to make your point clearly this time, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-sure thing, Professor... <thought>Could you not just, oh I don't know...give me the answer?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y'know... whoever replaced Darklaw has to be someone pretty high up on the food chain, don't you think, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Someone...high up, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The St-Storyteller...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We're talking about someone with the authority and power to replace the Great Witch. Someone who calls the shots. I can't think of anyone else that meets those criteria, except for the Storyteller himself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">P-preposterous! Then that would mean...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Exactly, Your Honour. It means that the Storyteller gave this final task to Kira himself. He was, in short, responsible for his own assassination.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?! Order! Order! Order in the court! ...But, for what purpose?! Why would he plan his own assassination?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That I cannot say, Your Honour. However... The final chapter of the Story does tell of his inevitable death. While he assigned this task to Kira himself, it is perfectly natural that he would do so. However, what is not natural... is your behaviour tonight, Miss Darklaw.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what was unnatural about the High Inquisitor's behaviour?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You were once the head of all the Shades... and yet, tonight you tried to interfere with the Storyteller's plan. You rendered Miss Kira unconscious and locked her away in the belfry of the bell tower. That, to me, seems like the activity of someone aiming to put a stop to his plan altogether.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-indeed... Lady Darklaw, what would be the reason for such behaviour?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I leave that to you, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Based on what we've seen in this trial, the defence believes Ms Darklaw's reason for covering up her actions tonight... can only be attributed to one thing. <thought>This plan was handed down by the Storyteller himself... and Ms Darklaw was definitely aiming to put a wrench in it...but why?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's one possible reason I can think of for why Ms Darklaw had to hide her actions tonight... She wanted to sabotage his plan!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Sabotage?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I mean, think about it. Her boss forced her to give up her position as the Great Witch. I'd say sabotaging your boss' plan for the sake of revenge is a perfectly plausible reason!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It worries me GREATLY that you should say that with such a huge smile on your face, defender.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...It would be my honour to wipe that smirk from his face myself, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Remember, Mr Wright. In the end, the plan was not stopped. The Storyteller was, in fact, killed tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ That's true.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is my belief... that this was an act of betrayal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Betrayal, of course! I should've seen that one a mile away...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's one possible reason I can think of as to why Ms Darklaw had to hide her actions tonight... She was aiming to betray the Storyteller!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-betray the Storyteller...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I agree, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could it have been that she was trying to protect the Storyteller?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Protect...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. That explains why she locked up Ms Kira - the big, bad, scary witch - in the belfry!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Following that, the Storyteller perished. I do not believe anything about her actions tonight indicate an intention to "protect".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ That's true.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is my belief... that this was an act of betrayal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Betrayal, of course! I should've seen that one a mile away...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">The Storyteller used the Great Witch Bezella to take his own life. Instructions to carry out the plan were given to Miss Kira. However... Miss Darklaw planned to intervene and change the scenario at the very last minute.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She planned to do so by changing the identity of the Great Witch from Ms Kira to Ms Cantabella.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Thus bringing us to our current situation: Miss Cantabella on trial for the murder of her father at the hands of Bezella. You, Miss Darklaw, seem to harbour a rather strong hatred for the Storyteller, if I am not mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ ...Heh heh heh... A "hatred", you say? Yes...I suppose you could call it that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">That's right. Behold...my revenge.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">D-did you say...revenge?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Miss Darklaw, will you please tell the court of your plan for revenge?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ If you insist.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Indeed. What we witnessed tonight... was the cowardly act of a man looking for an easy way to end that which he could not properly finish! He cared for no one but himself... Hence this sudden sham of an ending! And for that...I will never forgive him.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What do you mean by "sham of an ending"?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The Great Witch Bezella is to summon a dragon of fire and end the life of the Creator... She will then be put on trial and judged, thus heralding a period of peace and prosperity for all of Labyrinthia... Such is the ending written for this town and its people. 'Tis not an ending I oppose in principle. Who would not wish a happy ending for their own people? However, the problem lies...in Bezella's identity.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Bezella's identity?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">As you know, he... assigned the role of the Great Witch to this girl beside me.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">But you're saying that was a falsehood... Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...I knew Bezella's true identity. 'Tis not something I could ever forget. That is why...I went to the bell tower. And it is why I took the accused there. I did it...to ensure the true witch, foretold in the Story, was given the judgement she was due!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The true witch... Y-you don't mean...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Yes! I speak of none other than Espella Cantabella!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">And what would that be...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's supposedly common knowledge that Bezella is capable of using all magic. However! That is FAR from the truth! "Magic" does not actually exist in this town! It was all one giant illusion created by the Shades! Therefore... the Great Witch Bezella cannot exist either!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="???">...Heh heh heh... ...You fool...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Defender... you really don't have a clue, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-but, wait just a minute now! Is the defender not correct? If magic does not exist, then it goes without saying that witches do not exist either. And that would include the Great Witch, would it not?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I have but one simple question. What, exactly, is Bezella?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?! Well...err, she's...supposed to be the head of all witches...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Allow me to reword the question. The Great Witch Bezella is the root of all disaster within Labyrinthia. Knowing that...what specific "disaster" might she have been the root of?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-that would be... Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I just thought of something... We've been hearing Bezella's name left and right since we got here, but not once has the real Bezella shown up in person...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Indeed, Miss Fey. Bezella herself has been virtually absent from the Story thus far.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But, Inquisitor! Did she not claim the life of the Storyteller tonight?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would appear so, Your Honour. However, there is just one more thing... Consider this... Which particular "story" is every citizen of Labyrinthia most familiar with?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well...that would have to be... The Legendary Fire...right?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Precisely.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-surely you're not serious. As the name implies, that is but a mere legend. No one knows for certain if it occurred...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">So they say... But the reality is, there are still traces of that terrible fire within the town today.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The professor's right! We've even seen some of it up close and personal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey, yeah... At the Great Archive...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You are indeed correct, Inquisitor. Littered throughout the town are burnt remnants of a fire most fierce. However...no one can say for certain what transpired back then. You see, not a soul saw what actually happened.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let me see if I have this straight...there's an entire town full of people and NO ONE saw what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Correct. Except for one particular person.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There is one person who saw everything. I am speaking, of course, of the one responsible for the fire itself...the Great Witch Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="???">...Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I...remember it. All of it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Espella, what are you saying?!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...When I close my eyes, I can picture it so vividly... ...The awful sight of the flames engulfing everything they touched... ...The scorching heat on my skin. ...The smell of burning cinder all around me. ...The large plumes of black smoke. ...The warm tears streaming down my face. I...remember it all...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What you are recalling now...is the moment the Great Witch Bezella destroyed our town. Well, it appears my role here is finished. As for the rest... I leave it in your capable hands, Inquisitor.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?! <thought>Darklaw... She...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">...She's right. These memories... ...are proof that I am Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But, Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Remember, if you will, what I said at the beginning of this trial. I came here to prove that Espella Cantabella is, in reality, the Great Witch Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There is still one more thing I wish to present to the court. I would now like to call the final witness to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-the final witness...?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't see anything out of the ordinary.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah...really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Let that be a lesson, defender. I recommend the defence take more care in raising objections henceforth...or else.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something tells me the judge's gavel has something to do with that "or else"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Are you saying that piece of evidence is somehow relevant to this statement?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It isn't, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is not. But this penalty is certainly relevant to your performance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I really think...the judge enjoys handing down penalties.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence's objection is overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-why?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">We have gathered here to deliver the final judgement on the Great Witch. This trial is strict and its results irrevocable. You should at least have the good sense to notice when you make a mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaargh! This trial does feel different to the other ones...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I have no idea how... And here's your penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arrghhhhhhhh! P-Professor...I could really use a hand!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Regrettably, Mr Wright, I cannot oblige your request.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why not...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A gentleman must play the game fair and square, would you not agree?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ughhh... Apparently gentlemen make for pretty cold-hearted prosecutors.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">I am, after all, a gentleman.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Ms Darklaw...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you like to comment on the testimony we've just heard?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seemed like something in it attracted your attention...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess whatever I say, she'll just stand there going "..." with her eyes closed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Darklaw doesn't make a great witness, does she?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't you "..." me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, witness, continue testifying!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is something wrong, Ms Kira?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Witness!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Oh... Y-yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She really doesn't remember her name...</thought> You looked like you wanted to say something... Did something in High Inquisitor Darklaw's testimony strike you as odd?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">No, I'm sorry... I...wasn't really listening...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... She seems pretty scared. She must be intimidated by Darklaw.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Lady Darklaw, please continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There is no need to continue this trial. The accused's true identity has been proven beyond doubt. The court shall now issue the final verdict for Espella Cantabella!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is a crime to be a witch. We must do everything to erase magic from the world. Despicable witch! Into the flames with you!</line>
</xml>