<xml>
<title>The Final Witch Trial</title>
<line speaker="Maya">It's finally starting... The last witch trial...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Witches' Court will no longer serve any purpose, once the Great Witch Bezella is burned...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But... Espella isn't Bezella! I'm not buying it one bit! I mean, the Storyteller is her father! I don't know what happened between them, but a father would never do that to his child!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ I think you're right, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...But no one else does. They're all throwing accusations at her... I just feel so sorry for Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It feels like this whole case is under some kind of bad spell.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...A spell?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. We just can't see it yet... That's why it's so vital that we expose the real "witch" behind all this. And we've got to do it during this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...I believe in you, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, by the way...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm? Yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you going to do during this trial? I mean, if you were thinking about watching...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaaaaaaaat?! You mean you don't want me to be by your side? I didn't take you for such a cold-hearted guy, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's not what I mean! Let me finish before you start jumping to conclusions... What I was going to say is that you can't let people see you. You're supposed to be, you know...dead. You were "cast into the flames", remember?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Ohhh, right. THAT. You mean, after I was on trial for the murder of "Sir Top Hat"... Heh heh heh. Don't underestimate me, "Sir Blue Knight"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I've already got it covered. Check it out. I brought this with me. With this masterful disguise, I shall be transformed into Maya the Ironclad! I found it in Barnham's room and figured I'd take...uhh, "borrow" it for a while.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't tell me you're going to the trial... wearing that helmet?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I sure am. Can't be Maya the Ironclad without being clad in some iron.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's just hope Barnham doesn't flip out if he sees you wearing his trusty head gear.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Anyway, I'm going to do what I can to help! We've got to save Espella, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ We will. Come on, let's get going. It's time to break whatever bad spell Espella's under and put an end to these witch trials once and for all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're okay with that, aren't you, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's a ton of people out there, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's do this. Come on.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, as scheduled... The trial of Espella Cantabella shall commence forthwith. Knights of the Court. Are you ready now to cross your swords of justice?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ The Knights of the Inquisition have spent countless years trying to track down the elusive Great Witch... The secret of her identity shall finally be brought to light in this very court. All those present, pay attention, so that the truth may be burned into your memory! Today, the legend of the Great Witch shall become a closed chapter in the history of Labyrinthia!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You could cut the atmosphere with a knife. It's so loaded but at the same time oddly subdued.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">And now... the whole truth shall be revealed to all. The moon, eye of the night, shall bear witness to that. Don't you agree, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Your Honour, the defence is ready.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">How regrettable. I see you won't allow yourself to be provoked.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You may now begin your opening statement, High Inquisitor Darklaw.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Thank you. People of Labyrinthia, the Story has ended. Its end has been sealed through the Storyteller's death. The one who put an end to the life of the Storyteller, and to the Story which governed our lives, was the Great Witch Bezella. A foul embodiment of evil who has long been lurking among us, concealed deep within the consciousness of a certain girl. I'm sure you are all aware of her name. I refer, of course... to Espella Cantabella! Today, at dusk...a tragedy unfolded right in front of us all. A giant fire dragon descended into the town square, devouring the Storyteller. 'Twas a nightmarish vision that we shall never be able to forget. That fearsome fire beast, of which we had only heard tell through legend, returned at the hand of the Great Witch.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed, it was just as in the illustrations of the Legendary Fire...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...And the girl, within whose heart lies the Great Witch herself, has committed her final, and most heinous, crime. ...The crime of patricide!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">May this trial serve as an offering... An offering to the Storyteller, who can be with us no longer.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, High Inquisitor. The inquisition may now begin proceedings.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">As I have said... this unthinkable crime took place in the town square, within plain sight of all Labyrinthians. ...Everyone is a witness. Surely there can be no need for a formal interrogation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You...you can't say that!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I suggest you mind your temper, defender. In a few moments, you will have no option but to accept the truth... once we hear it from the very mouth of the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">From Espella...?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The inquisition hereby demands... that the accused, Espella Cantabella, testify about her crime. Or rather...that she confess to it.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The inquisition's dema- ...request shall be granted. Bring Espella Cantabella down to the witness stand!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is it...the last trial. In all likelihood, Espella will admit to the charges... I have only one chance to break whatever spell she's under. When she testifies...there are bound to be some clues to the truth in there!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Now that you're here, witness. State your name. And tell us your real name, as well.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">My name is...Espella Cantabella. But I have...another name, too... Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-order! Order! Order in the court! Then, you really do admit...that you are the Great Witch?! You openly concede that you are Bezella herself...the cause of all evil and destruction?!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The inquisition was right... The accused herself has spoken. It would seem there is no need for an interrogation.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I assure you, there is none. The only possible verdict has been clear to everyone from the very beginning!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maya:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... What I would like to know is this... Just who in the world are you, young knight?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...me?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...How to put it? I feel as if we've met somewhere before... It was... Hmmm... Where was it, again...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh, we haven't! It's just your imagination, Your Honour! I mean, er, Milord! As for who I am... I'm with Sir Blue Knight. Not...in a romantic way, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is this a friend of yours, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, yes! And, um... Don't comment on the helmet, please... She really wouldn't, err...like to have her face seen. How can I put this gently... It's not something you'd want to look at.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you talking about?! You make it sound like there's a problem with my face!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I can assure you, we have no interest in your face, miss. ...Although I do wonder where you acquired that particular helm.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-why's that?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">A helm of that ilk is not something you can simply purchase from a street stall.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Weeeeeell... I...I found it. In the forest. Finders keepers, y'know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you doing, Maya?! You promised me you wouldn't draw any attention!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ughhh... Sorry, Nick. I lost it a bit...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, anyway! The defence's opinion is as follows... We should hear the defendant's testimony before coming to a verdict! There may be some things even she isn't aware of.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...How amusing. As this is to be the last witch trial ever held, perhaps it is only fitting that we cross swords before you accept your defeat.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I agree. Thus, the accused herself will now testify. Miss Cantabella, tell the court of your involvement in this incident!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I finally realised that Bezella has been lying dormant within me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That was a very unusual testimony. When you used magic against your father... were you doing so as Espella Cantabella, or as the Great Witch Bezella?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">A most fascinating query. However... it matters not!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The inquisition has ingeniously solved the query by disregarding it.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What matters is that Bezella exists within this girl! Being a witch is a crime. Such a fundamental rule will always hold. And this girl here is not just any witch. ...She is the Great Witch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Espella has admitted the charges, just as I suspected... I just have to hope I can find some contradictions in her testimony. If I don't, we can kiss this trial goodbye!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence may begin the interrogation.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Defender, steady your sword of justice. Should I see it waver, or point in the wrong direction, I will not hesitate to cut down your arguments and end this interrogation. You had better keep that in mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I finally realised that Bezella has been lying dormant within me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes... I've always had a feeling, but... my memory is rather hazy. I've always felt as though I'm not who I think I am...and that I've forgotten something very important.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have a question for you, Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eve!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Just what on earth are you doing, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? I...I was just... Eve is Espella's friend, so I was wondering if she might want to have some input...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm... Whether or not this furry little witness can contribute to the testimony... seems to be obvious at a glance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is...that so...? <thought>I guess questioning a cat wasn't the best idea... Where's Luke when you need him?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you wish to say something, High Inquisitor Darklaw?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I just remembered a line from a fairy tale that I heard when I was little. A fairy tale about Bezella: "The Great Witch Bezella is always accompanied by a black cat." ...Or so it claimed. It would seem there was a grain of truth in that fairy tale after all.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That's true... Eve always follows me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Always...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! Nick, that means... they must have been together when the incident happened, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that she mentions it... I think I saw a black cat at the bell tower when it happened.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, yes. Eve was with me in the bell tower.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honour!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defence requests that Ms Cantabella's comment be added to the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Request granted. Witness... Add what you just said about that cat to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Incidentally, when did you become aware of Bezella's presence within you?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...It was when I went to the Great Archive with Mr Layton and Luke. Ever since I saw the mural depicting Bezella, I started having strange flashbacks... I saw things from the distant past. Memories...of the Legendary Fire.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The Legendary Fire...?!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I saw it. I was there when it happened... I saw the town consumed by flames.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You couldn't have! That's...impossible! The Legendary Fire occurred over a hundred years ago! And there were no survivors!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, I know that. But it's true. I remember it happening. ...Because I'm Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhm, Nick? Have you noticed how weird Espella is acting today?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I sure have. It's almost like... <thought>she's a puppet...but who's pulling the strings?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...Meow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Eve...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Look! Check it out! It's Eve! She must be here to root for Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think a cat's emotional support is going to help us all that much...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, this is an unexpected intrusion... But as we're in the middle of an interrogation, I will ask the witness to carry on with her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Yes, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Once evening fell and the rain ceased... I climbed up the wooden stairs of that bell tower and awaited the parade.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm not sure... When I came to, I was in the town... It was pouring, so I wanted to go to Aunt Patty's bakery and wait for it to stop. But...I couldn't face her, so I just went to the forest instead.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have a question for you, Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eve!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Just what on earth are you doing, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? I...I was just... Eve is Espella's friend, so I was wondering if she might want to have some input...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm... Whether or not this furry little witness can contribute to the testimony... seems to be obvious at a glance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is...that so...? <thought>I guess questioning a cat wasn't the best idea... Where's Luke when you need him?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you wish to say something, High Inquisitor Darklaw?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I just remembered a line from a fairy tale that I heard when I was little. A fairy tale about Bezella: "The Great Witch Bezella is always accompanied by a black cat." ...Or so it claimed. It would seem there was a grain of truth in that fairy tale after all.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That's true... Eve always follows me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Always...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! Nick, that means... they must have been together when the incident happened, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that she mentions it... I think I saw a black cat at the bell tower when it happened.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, yes. Eve was with me in the bell tower.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honour!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defence requests that Ms Cantabella's comment be added to the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Request granted. Witness... Add what you just said about that cat to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you were in the forest until the incident? <thought>We couldn't find you, though...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">The rain finally stopped and the time came. I made my way over to the town square. I was feeling strange, as if I wasn't myself. ............ Then...I noticed I was up in the bell tower, looking down at the square.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Espella's not a witch. And that means... there's got to be something strange about this statement.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Is that...the Vigilantes' report?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. And according to this... the Vigilantes have been constantly guarding the entrance to the bell tower, ever since it appeared.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However! There is nothing about Espella going up the tower in their report!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Yes. I used an invisibility spell to enter the tower unnoticed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me...?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Did you honestly think the difference between a regular witch and the Great Witch was in name alone? The Great Witch, unlike other witches... can command any magic she desires without the use of a witch's sceptre!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Every Labyrinthian should know about that...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">A witch's sceptre can hold only two magic gems at once. Whoever heard of a Great Witch that could only use two spells?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">In any case, this should convince you that the accused entered the tower.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-this is... a sketch showing footprints?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">It was raining before the parade reached the town square. Obviously, if you walk through muddy streets before climbing up a staircase, you will inevitably leave footprints on the steps. This sketch shows that there were indeed muddy footprints present on the bell tower stairs... And since you'd no doubt be quick to ask, I can tell you that they match the sole of the accused's shoes. It's certain that the accused climbed up the bell tower after the rain had fallen!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court accepts this sketch as evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I almost pity you, defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The evidence you threw in our faces with such verve was, sadly, useless.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed... It would seem there were no problems with that testimony after all. Let us not waste time. If you could carry on with the interrogation...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">That is, if the defender hasn't run out of ideas yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The judge seems ready to announce the verdict any second now. I've got to find a flaw in her testimony, and fast! I need a solid lead in this case!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Yes, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have a question for you, Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eve!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Just what on earth are you doing, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? I...I was just... Eve is Espella's friend, so I was wondering if she might want to have some input...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm... Whether or not this furry little witness can contribute to the testimony... seems to be obvious at a glance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is...that so...? <thought>I guess questioning a cat wasn't the best idea... Where's Luke when you need him?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you wish to say something, High Inquisitor Darklaw?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I just remembered a line from a fairy tale that I heard when I was little. A fairy tale about Bezella: "The Great Witch Bezella is always accompanied by a black cat." ...Or so it claimed. It would seem there was a grain of truth in that fairy tale after all.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That's true... Eve always follows me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Always...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! Nick, that means... they must have been together when the incident happened, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that she mentions it... I think I saw a black cat at the bell tower when it happened.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, yes. Eve was with me in the bell tower.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honour!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defence requests that Ms Cantabella's comment be added to the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Request granted. Witness... Add what you just said about that cat to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella, do you have a clear recollection of using such a spell?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ I don't... But I left footprints on the stairs...so I think it's pretty clear that I must have.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What's clear is the evidence. There can be no room for doubt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Really, Darklaw? I'd say it's pretty clear that we don't have all the facts yet... Anyway, I'd better try a different approach.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">My cat, Eve, followed me...as always.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Well, not necessarily always... But when I'm especially sad or happy, like when something out of the ordinary happens, she's always there with me. I can't remember since when... but Eve has long been my dear friend.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">...Meow.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is something amiss, High Inquisitor Darklaw?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...No, it's nothing. It just made me think of that little dog that follows Barnham around.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You mean Constantine? That little puffball is so cute, too! I bet Barnham cuddles him all the time when no one's looking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When you climbed up the bell tower, your cat was with you, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes. She was quietly following me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Espella looks so happy when she talks about that cat...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I waited for my father's speech to end. ...And then, I summoned the fire dragon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes...that's the one. Although I won't say it now... I'm sure something terrible would happen if I did.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have a question for you, Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eve!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Just what on earth are you doing, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? I...I was just... Eve is Espella's friend, so I was wondering if she might want to have some input...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm... Whether or not this furry little witness can contribute to the testimony... seems to be obvious at a glance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is...that so...? <thought>I guess questioning a cat wasn't the best idea... Where's Luke when you need him?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you wish to say something, High Inquisitor Darklaw?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I just remembered a line from a fairy tale that I heard when I was little. A fairy tale about Bezella: "The Great Witch Bezella is always accompanied by a black cat." ...Or so it claimed. It would seem there was a grain of truth in that fairy tale after all.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That's true... Eve always follows me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Always...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! Nick, that means... they must have been together when the incident happened, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that she mentions it... I think I saw a black cat at the bell tower when it happened.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, yes. Eve was with me in the bell tower.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honour!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defence requests that Ms Cantabella's comment be added to the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Request granted. Witness... Add what you just said about that cat to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's fine, absolutely fine! No need to prove that statement! In fact, the court forbids you to prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Hee hee hee, of course I won't say it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come on...THIS is supposed to be the "Great Witch"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look at her...there's no way Espella is a witch! It must be like you said, Nick. Someone's cast an evil spell on her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something in this testimony keeps nagging at me, that's for sure... I just need to figure out what...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's something strange about this statement... And I think I know exactly what was bothering me about it. She used that dragon-summoning spell but didn't have a witch's sceptre...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">The Great Witch can use all spells without using a sceptre, right? I mean... That's a little TOO overpowered, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh, that's probably what makes the Great Witch, well..."great". She'd be a pretty sorry Great Witch if she could only use two spells.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh-huh. Yeah, I guess so.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhm, Nick? Have you noticed how weird Espella is acting today?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I sure have. It's almost like... <thought>she's a puppet...but who's pulling the strings?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...Meow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Eve...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Look! Check it out! It's Eve! She must be here to root for Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think a cat's emotional support is going to help us all that much...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, this is an unexpected intrusion... But as we're in the middle of an interrogation, I will ask the witness to carry on with her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Yes, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I...I don't know why I killed my father.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...It was me. I summoned the fire dragon... I...I killed him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have a question for you, Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eve!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Just what on earth are you doing, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? I...I was just... Eve is Espella's friend, so I was wondering if she might want to have some input...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm... Whether or not this furry little witness can contribute to the testimony... seems to be obvious at a glance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is...that so...? <thought>I guess questioning a cat wasn't the best idea... Where's Luke when you need him?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you wish to say something, High Inquisitor Darklaw?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I just remembered a line from a fairy tale that I heard when I was little. A fairy tale about Bezella: "The Great Witch Bezella is always accompanied by a black cat." ...Or so it claimed. It would seem there was a grain of truth in that fairy tale after all.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That's true... Eve always follows me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Always...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! Nick, that means... they must have been together when the incident happened, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that she mentions it... I think I saw a black cat at the bell tower when it happened.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, yes. Eve was with me in the bell tower.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honour!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defence requests that Ms Cantabella's comment be added to the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Request granted. Witness... Add what you just said about that cat to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The Storyteller chose his own death... That is a fact that cannot be changed. 'Tis common knowledge that all things written in the Story will become a reality... and Bezella's appearance has been written into the Story's final chapter. ...She has no choice but to act out the role that has been written for her.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... In other words, everything happens in accordance with the Storyteller's Story.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhm, Nick? Have you noticed how weird Espella is acting today?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I sure have. It's almost like... <thought>she's a puppet...but who's pulling the strings?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...Meow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Eve...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Look! Check it out! It's Eve! She must be here to root for Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think a cat's emotional support is going to help us all that much...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, this is an unexpected intrusion... But as we're in the middle of an interrogation, I will ask the witness to carry on with her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Yes, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I've gotta find those contradictions and fast...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">If the cross-examination ends now, what will happen to Espella...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She'll be pronounced guilty and sentenced as the Great Witch Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Talk about drastic measures... Hurry up and find something to object to, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Haste makes waste, Maya... I need to gather more info first!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">The professor's bound to show up soon and bring us that awesome evidence we need! ...We can't let the trial end before then!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I've gotta find those contradictions and fast...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, we can't let it end yet! Look, even Eve showed up to root for us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eve? Oh, right...that black cat. <thought>The Great Witch Bezella always has a black cat by her side, huh.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... But you know, if Bezella is always accompanied by a cat... then she should've had it with her when the incident happened, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that she mentions it... I think I saw a black cat at the bell tower when it happened.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... You think I might be on to something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A witch with a trusty black cat, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, so that's it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We've got pretty much all the info we need now... We just have to find a decisive contradiction to go with it. <thought>Revealing a contradiction will be the first step towards getting a "not guilty" verdict.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">All righty! Then how about... we go through the Court Record again?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, that's not a bad call. <thought>When in doubt, get the Court Record out. There's got to be something in there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, Espella... but there's a problem with that statement.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...A problem?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You went up the bell tower in the evening, after it stopped raining, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Y-yes. I think so. After all... there's proof of that. My footprints were left on the stairs...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right... There were footprints on the steps. However, there's something missing in this sketch.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Missing? What do you mean, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are no paw prints...of Espella's cat, Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You said Eve was following you, right? In which case, naturally... there would have to be cat paw prints on the stairs as well!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Ahhhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Y...yes. Eve was on my shoulders. I think. She dislikes dirt, so when it's muddy, she tends to climb up on to my shoulders.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...I...It's...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What...what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">For a while now, Espella hasn't been testifying in her own words. All the vital parts of her testimony... have come from High Inquisitor Darklaw! She made Espella say those things!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, if that's not the case... then there's one more possibility. Namely, that the witness, Ms Cantabella, has no clear recollection of what happened this evening.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what?! Are you saying the witness has no memory of the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Espella. Do you actually remember what happened? Do you remember entering the bell tower and summoning the fire dragon?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You say you also remember the Legendary Fire, which burned this town to the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes... Yes, I do. Even though it was a long time ago...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...And you remember tonight's events just as clearly? Do you truly remember summoning that terrifying fire dragon and killing your own father?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I-I... I don't know... I don't know what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm Bezella...am I not? I can remember it...the Legendary Fire... So then, why... Why can't I remember anything about what happened tonight...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honour! The defendant is confused and cannot remember what happened! Therefore... her confession that she is the Great Witch is not credible!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ I... I am more than one person... Who is the other one within me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A brief summary of the accused's current situation... Espella Cantabella became extremely agitated during the interrogation and proceeded to lose consciousness. She remains unconscious, although her life is not in danger...until the verdict, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well that's a relief! She had me pretty worried there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, I don't mean to sound insensitive or anything...but this is just what we needed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure I follow...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The professor is out looking for clues to help us out, right? That means all we've gotta do is buy some more time until he returns with his findings!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya's right... That's just what we're going to do!</thought> ...Your Honour. It's impossible to continue the trial while the defendant isn't present. And also...it's possible that someone at the crime scene was manipulating the defendant. The defence proposes an intermission in order to carry out further investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... What is your opinion on this, High Inquisitor Darklaw?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...My opinion is that the defender is just playing for time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She saw right through my plan!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">However, I shall allow it. As long, of course, as the townsfolk who have gathered here have no objections.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, then. So be it. The court shall be adjourned until tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="???">Vigilante* Boistrum:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilantes">What he said! What he said!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">You can't squirm your way out of this!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilantes">What he said! What he said!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">'Cos we know everything!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilantes">What he said! What he said!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">We will reveal your wrongdoings to everyone gathered here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Orderrr!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">If anyone here should be silenced, it is not us, but that defender over there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uhm... And...who are you?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">You ask who we are?! We are the ones who watch the bell tower, guard the bell tower and take cover from rain in the bell tower! We are the bell tower guards, known as the Vigilantes! And I am their captain!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, right... That guy showed up at the crime scene when we were trying to investigate it.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">You there! You...defender!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y...yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">What was it you said earlier...while taking advantage of all the confusion, like the rascal you are?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhm...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">You said someone at the crime scene may have been manipulating the accused! We Vigilantes were at the crime scene! Are you suggesting we were manipulating that witch?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, no! That's totally not what I-</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Don't think you can silence us like that! We shall have our say now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>They sure will...no matter what anyone else has to say about it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">We are the Vigilantes, dutiful and righteous! Superior, happy, fulfilled on the job...our passion is burning and our blood is red! If you fail to let us speak out, we will have no choice but to turn to violence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I disapprove of violence... The burning of witches being a necessary exception, naturally.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...In which case, it's best to just let them have their say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">You may not know this, but it's not unusual for the accused to fall unconscious in this court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No...kidding...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Let us lend our ears to these brave knights. ...We shall hear what they witnessed!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Very well. These knights will be accepted as witnesses. They may testify.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">People of Labyrinthia! Did you hear the word of the judge? Today's trial is not over yet. In fact, it is just beginning!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Now, Vigilante Captain Boistrum! You may testify to your heart's content!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Lady Darklaw! Thank you for this honour! I will talk to my heart's content, you can be sure of that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, joy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ughhh... So much for buying some time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">We Vigilantes despise injustice and inequality! We shall remain united, friendly, confident and self-reliant!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">We have come to do away with this fiendish defender trying to protect the witch!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">We shall fight! And we shall protect our town from this villainous defender!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, whatever. Did I just hear something crash on to the floor?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Honourable Vigilantes, let us first hear your proud names.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">I am Vigilante number one, the captain of this unit. My name is Boistrum!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">I'm Vigilante number two! My name...is Lottalance!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">And I am Vigilante number three! My name's Balmung. They say dogs that bark don't bite...but I assure you, I do bite!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Vigilante number four. Name's Lyewood.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">I... I'm...V-Vigilante number f-five. M-m-my n-name is...Sh-Shakey...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">And I, Vigilante number six, am no more than a hopeless slave to love. My humble name is Servius.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">I'm the steel angel gracing the Vigilantes with my sweet presence. My name's Foxy. Don't you dare forget it.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">I am but a man who wants nothing more than to feel Foxy's steel heels on his back. You can call me Treddon.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Vigilante number nayn! Ah go by th' name Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">As for me, I am the tenth Vigilante. Nothing more, nothing less. Just that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... It's no use...I cannot remember that many new names and faces at once. Well, anyway... Honourable witnesses, you may testify about this evening's incident. Tell us about everything you saw on this dreadful night!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">We have been guarding the bell tower ever since it appeared! No one's ever said a bad word about us!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">The defender tried to hide decisive proof that the girl is the Great Witch! But he couldn't fool us!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">Before the rain, after the rain... At no point did a single suspicious person approach the bell tower!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">But then, suddenly, footprints appeared on the bell tower stairs. When I saw them, I thought "it's that witch"!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">M...m...my eyes...went h-hazy... It...it... made me sh-shake and I...got d-dizzy...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">The rain stopped and a beautiful butterfly appeared at our side.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">Rain is so loathsome. My steel stilettos get dirty from the mud, and my lovely hair loses its texture.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">You have no idea how delightful it is when Foxy steps on us in her dirty stilettos, imprinting the mud on our backs...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Ah didne rin awa'! Ah did mah duty when Ah doscovered th' intruder, Ah teel ye!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">I have been mulling over this incident... and just now, the realisation dawned on me. I...remember nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ Well, I suppose that can be summed up by saying... you all did the best you could.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The Vigilantes have been taking turns guarding the bell tower since its appearance. Only a witch could have gone past them unnoticed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes, that would seem to be true. However, I must say that something caught my attention in that testimony... Defender...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honour?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Have you been...concealing important evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh? Wh-why would I do that?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">Don't think you'll get off the hook by claiming you forgot about it! Right, Captain Boistrum?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Of course he won't! Defender, you and your companion tampered with the crime scene... and tried to sneak away with a very important piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...We did? <thought>Wait, is he talking about the pendant?</thought> B-but! In the end we gave it to you guys. We weren't trying to steal it or anything.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">That's absurd! We saw you putting it in your pocket!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right...that.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">The evidence we retrieved from you has been passed on to the Inquisition. We have done our citizenly duty! Isn't that so, Lady High Inquisitor Darklaw?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ Hmm. This thing, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! That's... the pendant that Espella Cantabella is always wearing, is it not?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. This pendant will be accepted as evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ Well...the accused was caught in the act, so this pendant doesn't change the situation much. Although it should at least clear any doubts as to whether or not she was at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww, man! If they'd appeared just five seconds later, they wouldn't have seen us swiping that thing... Right, Nick? Uhm, are you okay? You're spacing out...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, uh...yeah, I'm fine. <thought>Was it just me... or did Darklaw look mighty uncomfortable just now? What's more, on closer inspection... that pendant seems to have some blackish stains on the strap.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender, you may begin your interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">We have been guarding the bell tower ever since it appeared! No one's ever said a bad word about us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">As you might know, that bell tower suddenly appeared, out of nowhere, about three months ago! It has an overwhelming presence, and it looks as if it's been here forever. "It's a bad omen." "It's the Great Witch's doing." Simply put, the townspeople are scared of it. That is why, defender. The Vigilantes were compelled to step in and keep an eye on that tower, in order to ease the minds of the townsfolk!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">That bell tower is in fact tied to two dreadful incidents.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Two...?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">You shouldn't have to ask... The alchemist committed suicide a few days after its appearance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ah, right... She's talking about Belduke.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">And now, this most heinous crime... The murder of the Storyteller!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The bell tower is cursed. 'Tis the curse of the Great Witch.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Next witness, continue the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">The defender tried to hide decisive proof that the girl is the Great Witch! But he couldn't fool us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">Yes, that's it! That's the pendant the accused is always wearing! It's proof she was at the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The strap on this thing has been torn.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">Of course it has! Otherwise, she wouldn't have dropped it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right, but...there must be a reason why it's torn. It wouldn't just snap on its own.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">Ugh... Uh... Yes, that's right...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">You there, you rascal! I mean, defender!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y...yes?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">You no-good, good-for-nothing, useless swine! You're doing it again, huh?! You're insulting the Vigilantes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Someone tore the pendant from the girl's neck, huh? And you have the temerity to suggest it was us! That's what you wanted to say, isn't it?! That we did it?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, no, that's not what-</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">When this trial is over, we will hold our own trial in which you'll be the accused!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>One more reason to prolong this trial as long as I can...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">Before the rain, after the rain... At no point did a single suspicious person approach the bell tower!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">Sure I'm sure! And anyway, I'll be honest with you... Ever since I started guarding the tower a few months ago... not a single person, suspicious or not, has come near it. No one but us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">No one even approaches us for a chat when we're on duty. People almost treat us like we're not even there... It gets so very lonely out on the job! So...cheerless!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">What he said! Cheerless! Lonely!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">You have no idea how sad it can get guarding that tower!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">It's very sad, oh, it is! You'd think people would be interested in a highly suspicious bell tower like that! But no! I mean, what's that about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Isn't their job to keep people AWAY from the bell tower anyway?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">And so, it goes without saying: the Vigilantes haven't seen anyone enter the bell tower. And you know what that means...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>But footprints appeared on the steps...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">But then, suddenly, footprints appeared on the bell tower stairs. When I saw them, I thought "it's that witch"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Yes. Muddy footprints left by one person, from the entrance all the way up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The footprints you saw... are they the ones shown in this sketch?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">If these are the footprints from the bell tower, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And when did you notice those footprints?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">After the rain...but still quite some time before the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">W-wait a second, Lyewood. I don't remember you reporting this to me!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">............ Yeah, that's right...I didn't report it.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">...Lyewood! Why not?! I thought you were serious about your duty! At least compared to the others! Why did you neglect to report that?!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">You're right, Captain...it was out of character. I'm sure there was a good reason why I didn't report it to you... ............ It's no use. I've forgotten. I think I'd remember if someone could give me a clue...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Grrr... That guy! It's like he's teasing us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We can only hope he remembers what it was... <thought>But his testimony did give us some new info to go on... The culprit entered the bell tower soon after the rain stopped.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Yes. Muddy footprints left by one person, from the entrance all the way up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The footprints you saw... are they the ones shown in this sketch?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">If these are the footprints from the bell tower, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And when did you notice those footprints?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">After the rain...but still quite some time before the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">W-wait a second, Lyewood. I don't remember you reporting this to me!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">............ Yeah, that's right...I didn't report it.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">...Lyewood! Why not?! I thought you were serious about your duty! At least compared to the others! Why did you neglect to report that?!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">You're right, Captain...it was out of character. I'm sure there was a good reason why I didn't report it to you... Ah! Now I remember!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Yes, I saw them! I saw the muddy footprints in the bell tower. But I didn't report it to the chief. And now...I remember why I didn't report it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that is the case, you will add it to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Yes, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">When I saw those muddy footprints, at first I figured they were Foxy's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Yeah. She's always doing whatever she likes, causing us nothing but trouble. I was sure she'd entered the bell tower to take shelter from the rain, leaving those footprints.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">Excuse me, boy! How could you think that? That place is off limits, isn't it?! I take orders seriously. And I value obedience...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius/Treddon">Foxy, give us any orders you wish! We will obey you, whatever you require of us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However, you told us a different story before, Mr Lyewood. You previously stated that when you saw the footprints, you thought they were those of a witch. Did you think that Ms Foxy was a witch?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Well, I didn't mean it literally. It's just that... Foxy can be such a bother, you can't help but call her a witch sometimes. You can understand that, right? You can see what kind of a person she is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If that's the case, then the footprints you saw in the bell tower... must have looked like they were left by stilettos?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Yeah, those stilettos. She likes to dig them into the other men's backs. There are men in this world who enjoy that sort of thing, too... Well, it's best not to think too much about it. We'd never mistake those footprints... Foxy's footprints are unique.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Lyewood thought they were just Foxy's footprints...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So that's why he didn't report his findings...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">In case you want to know, they weren't mine. I didn't leave those muddy footprints in the bell tower.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>Now that's weird...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">M...m...my eyes...went h-hazy... It...it... made me sh-shake and I...got d-dizzy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">Y...y...yes... Sh-Sh-Shakey's the name.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you...feeling okay?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">Y-yes...I'm...p-p-perfectly...peachy. L-looks can be d...deceiving.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you see anything around the time of the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">I...I've...told you... My...eyes...were hazy... I was dizzy... A-and the r...ringing in my ears... L-l-like the c...crying of a g-girl...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's okay, that's all I wanted to know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But what I'd like to know... is how Mr Shakey got into the Vigilantes in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, maybe it's better not to ask.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">The rain stopped and a beautiful butterfly appeared at our side.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">Yes, a butterfly! Happily fluttering around, watching us from above. When I saw it, I thought: "Maybe my goddess has turned into this butterfly!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you talking about...?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">Gracefully moving from one flower to the next...like my goddess of love... the divine Foxy.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">I'm the steel angel gracing the Vigilantes with my sweet presence. My name's Foxy. Don't you dare forget it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhm...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, about that butterfly... I think that must've been a witch using a transformation spell...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Seriously? You think a witch turned into a butterfly and flew up the bell tower?</thought> By the way, what happened to that butterfly?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">Ah, well... It carelessly flew straight into the fire torch and burned.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">I felt enlightened by that sight... The butterfly cannot resist its dangerous attraction to the flame, even if it results in death.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Perfect, thank you. That was quite the... exhaustive reply.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">Rain is so loathsome. My steel stilettos get dirty from the mud, and my lovely hair loses its texture.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">Yes, boy. See? Foxy's heels are always polished to sparkle.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! I can see myself in the reflection! They're like mirrors!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you notice anything suspicious during the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">Hmm... Not really. I was busy having some tea at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were...having tea?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">I made it for her! Tea with milk is just the thing for rainy afternoons.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But...weren't you supposed to be guarding the bell tower?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">I couldn't possibly walk around in the rain. My stilettos would get dirty.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">Ahhhh... These lovely stilettos, their tips as sharp as Inquisitor Barnham's sword. And when they grind against my armour with such force and passion...I am the happiest man on earth.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">Would you like me to squish you under my stilettos? Just say the word.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No...I'm fine, thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's not every day someone offers to tread on you. Maybe it's a Labyrinthian custom?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I get walked all over in court often enough as it is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">Yes, boy. See? Foxy's heels are always polished to sparkle.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! I can see myself in the reflection! They're like mirrors!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you notice anything suspicious during the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">Hmm... Not really. I was busy having some tea at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were...having tea?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">I made it for her! Tea with milk is just the thing for rainy afternoons.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But...weren't you supposed to be guarding the bell tower?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">I couldn't possibly walk around in the rain. My stilettos would get dirty.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">Ahhhh... These lovely stilettos, their tips as sharp as Inquisitor Barnham's sword. And when they grind against my armour with such force and passion...I am the happiest man on earth.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">Would you like me to squish you under my stilettos? Just say the word.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No...I'm fine, thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's not every day someone offers to tread on you. Maybe it's a Labyrinthian custom?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I get walked all over in court often enough as it is.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Ah! Now I remember!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Yes, I saw them! I saw the muddy footprints in the bell tower. But I didn't report it to the chief. And now...I remember why I didn't report it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that is the case, you will add it to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Yes, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">You have no idea how delightful it is when Foxy steps on us in her dirty stilettos, imprinting the mud on our backs...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">You are such a hopeless man. Actually, all men are. Don't you also dream of feeling that beautiful, pointed tip of her shoe brutally digging into your back?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Do you, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">NO. Anyway, you mentioned "us". Are there more...uhm...fans of Foxy's?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">Yeah, sure there are. Servius is one of us, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah...I suspected he meant that guy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">Oh ho, that look! You're not averse to that sort of thing either, eh, defender? In that case, have a look at this! This is the mark left by Foxy's stiletto!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Wow. Isn't that amazing...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I must say, you've been quite beautifully trodden on there.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">See how it exquisitely tapers to a point? This deserves to be called art.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">Oh! I'm so jealous, Servius! Such charming beauty, born from dirty mud...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About that muddy footprint... Why didn't you wash it off?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">What?! Don't be silly!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">Have you ever exchanged a handshake with a beautiful singer? It's just like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Aaaaaanyway... Foxy was wearing high heels that whole time. That's an important point... I think.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">You are such a hopeless man. Actually, all men are. Don't you also dream of feeling that beautiful, pointed tip of her shoe brutally digging into your back?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Do you, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">NO. Anyway, you mentioned "us". Are there more...uhm...fans of Foxy's?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">Yeah, sure there are. Servius is one of us, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah...I suspected he meant that guy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">Oh ho, that look! You're not averse to that sort of thing either, eh, defender? In that case, have a look at this! This is the mark left by Foxy's stiletto!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Wow. Isn't that amazing...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I must say, you've been quite beautifully trodden on there.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">See how it exquisitely tapers to a point? This deserves to be called art.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">Oh! I'm so jealous, Servius! Such charming beauty, born from dirty mud...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About that muddy footprint... Why didn't you wash it off?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">What?! Don't be silly!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">Have you ever exchanged a handshake with a beautiful singer? It's just like that.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Ah! Now I remember!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Yes, I saw them! I saw the muddy footprints in the bell tower. But I didn't report it to the chief. And now...I remember why I didn't report it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that is the case, you will add it to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Yes, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Ah didne rin awa'! Ah did mah duty when Ah doscovered th' intruder, Ah teel ye!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">...It's Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">If ye want tae ask me somethin', address me by mah name! Make fin ay me coz Aam a bairn an' Ah'll make ye regret it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, er...okay. Dzibilchun...chuck...mil?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Cannae gie it reit, can ye?! Aam not talkin' tae ye onie mair!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gahhhhh! <thought>Oh...c'mon!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhm...Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil. Can you please tell us about what you know? This evening, during the incident...what did you see?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Sure! Ah saw the witch's footprints, that's whit Ah saw!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Good job, Maya! But...how? Hmm... Dzibilchaltun...sounds kind of..."Mayan"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil, do you mean... these footprints, drawn in this sketch?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Aye! Aye, those'r th' ones!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And then...? What did you do after discovering the intruder?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Th' chief tauld me tae report onie intruder Ah saw, right? Sae Ah went tae report it. They aw treat me lake a bairn, e'en thocht Ah can tak' oan onie witch, Ah tael ye!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Mr Boistrum?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">............ Oh... Ooooooh! What's this, out of the blue?! Have some respect for the Vigilantes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is there anything you'd like to comment on from Dzibi...from Number Nine's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">...Comment? Ah, well, certainly. I remembered about his report!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Strange footprints appeared on the bell tower staircase... Why didn't you investigate as soon as it was reported to you?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">We are the fast-footed Vigilantes, the most dutiful of knights, giving our all for the utmost sense of accomplishment. It is unthinkable that we would not launch an investigation after a report like that!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...And yet, I don't recall any such report being passed on to the Inquisition.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">That's right! I had my hands full with assigning tasks to each of the Vigilantes, myself. So I got hold of a reliable Vigilante and gave him the following order: "Investigate the suspicious footprints that appeared on the staircase. Immediately!" ...That's what I said to him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who was that "reliable Vigilante"?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Huh?! Hmm. It...it was... Well...I'm having a bit of trouble remembering just who it was. But I'm sure it was a young and high-spirited Vigilante! Hmmm... But who was it, again...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can I ask you something, Mr Shakey?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, don't! You can't expose that poor guy to your ruthless questioning! Just look at him...he may not be able to take it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ughhh... How am I supposed to talk to him then? Let's try this again. Please excuse me, Mr Shakey... The person the captain asked to investigate the suspicious footprints... Was that you, by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">............ ............ ...Y-yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?! It was him?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I feel compelled to say this, but... although Mr Shakey may be young, very few would describe him as high-spirited.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Huh? What? That may be so, but... Well, what of it?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh...</thought> Mr Shakey, did you not follow your orders? Didn't you investigate the footprints?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">I...I investigated them...of c-course. O-orders...are orders. Ev...everyone looked t-to be v-very busy... and no one...would l-listen t-to me... N-now...s-someone finally asked me a-about it! V-Vigilante Shakey, r-ready to r-report...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ That was a very convoluted testimony. But at least now we know that this young man's report didn't reach anyone, because his seniors were too busy to listen.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Yeah! People treat me like a bairn! Did mah report go tae waste?!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...What's that? The fourth Vigilante, Lyewood, seems kinda lost in thought...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, let's find out more about the footprints!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup, let's do it. <thought>I can only hope this is all leading somewhere...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let us go back to the interrogation. Witnesses, continue testifying!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can I ask you something, Mr Shakey?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, don't! You can't expose that poor guy to your ruthless questioning! Just look at him...he may not be able to take it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ughhh... How am I supposed to talk to him then? Let's try this again. Please excuse me, Mr Shakey... The person the captain asked to investigate the suspicious footprints... Was that you, by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">............ ............ ...Y-yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?! It was him?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I feel compelled to say this, but... although Mr Shakey may be young, very few would describe him as high-spirited.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Huh? What? That may be so, but... Well, what of it?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh...</thought> Mr Shakey, did you not follow your orders? Didn't you investigate the footprints?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">I...I investigated them...of c-course. O-orders...are orders. Ev...everyone looked t-to be v-very busy... and no one...would l-listen t-to me... N-now...s-someone finally asked me a-about it! V-Vigilante Shakey, r-ready to r-report...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ That was a very convoluted testimony. But at least now we know that this young man's report didn't reach anyone, because his seniors were too busy to listen.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Yeah! People treat me like a bairn! Did mah report go tae waste?!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Ah! Now I remember!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Yes, I saw them! I saw the muddy footprints in the bell tower. But I didn't report it to the chief. And now...I remember why I didn't report it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that is the case, you will add it to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Yes, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Young and high-spirited, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... That's still pretty weird.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What is?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why won't that person step forward and say it was them? Since their captain can't seem to remember...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, yeah...that is pretty weird. <thought>Hmm... Whoever it was, it looks like they don't want us to know it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe if we observe everyone closely, we'll be able to tell who it was!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They shouldn't be treating you like a kid. You're so brave, Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Ah've got tae dae whit th' chief says like a guid loon, ur he willnae gie me onie mair pocket money.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The kid reported to the chief, huh... We haven't heard about that before.</thought> Can you tell us more about the report you made?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Say mah name.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Sybilchoonchook...mille...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Drop dead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess I'll just ask the captain instead...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">This might be important! We've got to follow up on this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhm...Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil. Can you please tell us about what you know? This evening, during the incident...what did you see?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Sure! Ah saw the witch's footprints, that's whit Ah saw!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Good job, Maya! But...how? Hmm... Dzibilchaltun...sounds kind of..."Mayan"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil, do you mean... these footprints, drawn in this sketch?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Aye! Aye, those'r th' ones!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And then...? What did you do after discovering the intruder?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Th' chief tauld me tae report onie intruder Ah saw, right? Sae Ah went tae report it. They aw treat me lake a bairn, e'en thocht Ah can tak' oan onie witch, Ah tael ye!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Mr Boistrum?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">............ Oh... Ooooooh! What's this, out of the blue?! Have some respect for the Vigilantes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is there anything you'd like to comment on from Dzibi...from Number Nine's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">...Comment? Ah, well, certainly. I remembered about his report!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Strange footprints appeared on the bell tower staircase... Why didn't you investigate as soon as it was reported to you?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">We are the fast-footed Vigilantes, the most dutiful of knights, giving our all for the utmost sense of accomplishment. It is unthinkable that we would not launch an investigation after a report like that!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...And yet, I don't recall any such report being passed on to the Inquisition.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">That's right! I had my hands full with assigning tasks to each of the Vigilantes, myself. So I got hold of a reliable Vigilante and gave him the following order: "Investigate the suspicious footprints that appeared on the staircase. Immediately!" ...That's what I said to him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who was that "reliable Vigilante"?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Huh?! Hmm. It...it was... Well...I'm having a bit of trouble remembering just who it was. But I'm sure it was a young and high-spirited Vigilante! Hmmm... But who was it, again...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can I ask you something, Mr Shakey?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, don't! You can't expose that poor guy to your ruthless questioning! Just look at him...he may not be able to take it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ughhh... How am I supposed to talk to him then? Let's try this again. Please excuse me, Mr Shakey... The person the captain asked to investigate the suspicious footprints... Was that you, by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">............ ............ ...Y-yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?! It was him?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I feel compelled to say this, but... although Mr Shakey may be young, very few would describe him as high-spirited.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Huh? What? That may be so, but... Well, what of it?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh...</thought> Mr Shakey, did you not follow your orders? Didn't you investigate the footprints?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">I...I investigated them...of c-course. O-orders...are orders. Ev...everyone looked t-to be v-very busy... and no one...would l-listen t-to me... N-now...s-someone finally asked me a-about it! V-Vigilante Shakey, r-ready to r-report...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ That was a very convoluted testimony. But at least now we know that this young man's report didn't reach anyone, because his seniors were too busy to listen.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Yeah! People treat me like a bairn! Did mah report go tae waste?!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...What's that? The fourth Vigilante, Lyewood, seems kinda lost in thought...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, let's find out more about the footprints!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup, let's do it. <thought>I can only hope this is all leading somewhere...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let us go back to the interrogation. Witnesses, continue testifying!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can I ask you something, Mr Shakey?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, don't! You can't expose that poor guy to your ruthless questioning! Just look at him...he may not be able to take it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ughhh... How am I supposed to talk to him then? Let's try this again. Please excuse me, Mr Shakey... The person the captain asked to investigate the suspicious footprints... Was that you, by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">............ ............ ...Y-yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?! It was him?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I feel compelled to say this, but... although Mr Shakey may be young, very few would describe him as high-spirited.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Huh? What? That may be so, but... Well, what of it?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh...</thought> Mr Shakey, did you not follow your orders? Didn't you investigate the footprints?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">I...I investigated them...of c-course. O-orders...are orders. Ev...everyone looked t-to be v-very busy... and no one...would l-listen t-to me... N-now...s-someone finally asked me a-about it! V-Vigilante Shakey, r-ready to r-report...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ That was a very convoluted testimony. But at least now we know that this young man's report didn't reach anyone, because his seniors were too busy to listen.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Yeah! People treat me like a bairn! Did mah report go tae waste?!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Ah! Now I remember!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Yes, I saw them! I saw the muddy footprints in the bell tower. But I didn't report it to the chief. And now...I remember why I didn't report it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that is the case, you will add it to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Yes, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Young and high-spirited, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... That's still pretty weird.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What is?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why won't that person step forward and say it was them? Since their captain can't seem to remember...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, yeah...that is pretty weird. <thought>Hmm... Whoever it was, it looks like they don't want us to know it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe if we observe everyone closely, we'll be able to tell who it was!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They shouldn't be treating you like a kid. You're so brave, Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Ah've got tae dae whit th' chief says like a guid loon, ur he willnae gie me onie mair pocket money.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The kid reported to the chief, huh... We haven't heard about that before.</thought> Can you tell us more about the report you made?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Say mah name.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Sybilchoonchook...mille...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Drop dead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess I'll just ask the captain instead...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">This might be important! We've got to follow up on this!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">I have been mulling over this incident... and just now, the realisation dawned on me. I...remember nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me... I'm pretty sure we've met before... Mr Wordsmith, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">Wordsmith? I must disappoint you, young one. I am not familiar with that unusually unusual name. Wordsmith? A smith of words? Would that not be the Storyteller?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean you don't remember?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">I do not. From where did this Wordsmith come? To where did he head? At where will he next arrive? I know not... Regardless...such questions are of no concern to any of us. I am...on a green field, sky-clad, watching petals dancing in the wind... Allow me to indulge in my dream for a while longer, young one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You're not fooling anyone, grandpa!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">An awful lot must've happened to him since that other trial...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe. But just what the heck is the matter with all these Vigilantes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All right. Now that I've heard their testimony, it's time to get thinking. But there are just too many of them! I've never handled this many witnesses at once!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's gonna be one humongous undertaking squeezing information out of this wacky bunch...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In any case, the footprints left on the bell tower stairs are our best lead for now... Some of the witnesses saw them too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So...let's focus on that and press 'em hard until they cough up some more useful info!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, that's the plan. <thought>If I can't refute the witnesses' testimony, it'll be the end for Espella! I need to fish out a decisive contradiction in their statements!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You seem pretty sure that the footprints in the bell tower were Ms Foxy's. In other words, the footprints you saw... were stiletto footprints, with pointy tips.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Yeah, pointy. They were hers, for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And yet...we have a sketch of the footprints as they were found after the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oooh! Those footprints... They have rounded tips!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you see, Mr Lyewood... Your testimony contradicts the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">N-no way!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">That sketch was drawn by the Court Illustrator, based on how we found the crime scene immediately after the incident... I can guarantee that the sketch is accurate!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Well, I saw what I saw. There's no way I was wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How can you say that?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">The reason is pretty simple... If I'd seen footprints like those in the sketch, it wouldn't have occurred to me that they might be Foxy's!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">Exactly! Those are nothing like Foxy's! Sweet Foxy's footprints look like this!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is quite puzzling... Perhaps the defence can explain this contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Only one trail of footprints was found in the bell tower. One of the witnesses claims the footprints had pointy tips... But the Court Illustrator's sketch of the crime scene shows they were rounded.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is the witness' [sic] account correct? Or is it the sketch that shows the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness has to be right! The footprints were pointy!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... That's because...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Because if the footprints were as shown in the sketch, the accused would be found guilty? That's not your reason, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh...she can read people's minds... Isn't that witchcraft?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I know that look! She hit the bullseye, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why don't you keep such observations to yourself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Heh heh. Sorry, Nick, but you're like an open book to me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's easy to see which version of events is correct. The footprints were round, as shown in the sketch!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Hmph... So you admit it, then? That it was the accused, Espella Cantabella, who entered the bell tower, using invisibility magic?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, wait...what?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's what you just implied, Nick! There was only one trail of footprints, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Your Honour! Please hold on! The defence would like to reconsider its answer!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I will hold on this time, but your next explanation had better hold up in court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ughhh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Both the witness and the sketch are correct, Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Two different types of footprint were observed in the bell tower. Now, if neither party is mistaken... it means that two trails of footprints were left on the stairs!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Psh! And how would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's organise this evening's events on a timeline. Mr Lyewood discovered the footprints soon after the rain stopped. Which means that at that point, someone had already entered the bell tower.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes...that would be the case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The footprints that were observed then had pointy tips. And then, sometime later...another person went up those stairs. But that person left different footprints... Footprints that had rounded tips.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh...oh! I think I can see where this is going!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm glad you follow, Your Honour. You see, the second person... walked on the footprints that had already been left, perfectly covering them up as they went!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This explains why only one trail of footprints was left!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What makes you say that?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Even WE can tell you that much!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">There's no way there were two intruders!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">It's a big stretch, honey.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">E'en if a body ay them was a witch 'at was invisible...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">We would have seen the other one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What you're saying makes sense... but it's a fact that none of you noticed the second intruder. And the only explanation for that... is that the second intruder was also a witch, who had also made herself invisible when she entered the bell tower!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Wh-wha... WHAAAAAAT the heck?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Orderrrrr! Th-there were two witches...?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It may seem ludicrous to you, but you can't say it's not a possibility!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">It's easy to bat around "possibilities", but your theory alone doesn't change anything. Or perhaps you have some proof to support your little story?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Because we do have proof that Espella Cantabella was, in fact, in the bell tower at the time of the crime. Not only was she seen by many people... but this was found at the crime scene afterwards, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Espella's pendant, huh.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">If you think there was one more person in the bell tower... then prove it, defender!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well then. The defence shall present evidence. Do you have proof that someone other than the accused was in the bell tower?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Huh" is not an explanation. Well, what do you make of it, High Inquisitor Darklaw?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">If there's one thing I can say about this evidence... it's that it certainly proves a point. Just not the one the defence was arguing. You were supposed to prove that a second witch left muddy footprints... but your argument was as clear as mud. And now your name is mud, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uwaaaaaah! <thought>She's so unforgiving. Cut me some slack... anyone can make a mistake, right?</thought> The defence apologises for the mistake and would like to have another chance, Your Honour...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! That's a...uhm, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This robe was found at the top floor of the bell tower. As you can see, it's way too big for Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes, indeed. It would seem to belong to a much taller person.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Vigilantes, I'd like you all to confirm something for me. You have been guarding the bell tower ever since it appeared, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Indeed we have, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Had anyone ever gone up the bell tower before the incident this evening?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">Of course not! What would be our purpose if we freely allowed people inside?!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">Suspicious or not, sadly no one ever approaches our bell tower!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see. But then... how did this robe get up there?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Uhm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Do you get it now? There must have been a second witch in the bell tower!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Orderrrr! So there were two witches inside that tower?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly, Your Honour. It's true that the defendant was seen in the bell tower at the time of the crime... But if another witch was present too, it's impossible to say for sure that it was Ms Cantabella who summoned the fire dragon!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilantes">Vigilante* Boistrum:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">We must not let this defender confuddle our understanding of the situation!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">It was the Great Witch Bezella that summoned the fire dragon.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Aam gonnae expose 'er fur whit she is!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">We've braved fierce rapids, scaled high mountains and crossed vast plains to testify in this court and expose the Great Witch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhm... What are they talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...You'll know soon.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">High Inquisitor Darklaw! Permit us to testify again!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ You believe you can reveal the truth about the accused?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Yes, Lady Darklaw! We may be just a bunch of commoners, but we shall offer you our testimony with passion, purpose...and plausibility. Let us speak now...for the sake of Labyrinthia!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh man. For the sake of my sanity, please DON'T speak...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Permission granted. May your words be as sharp as swords... and cut through all lies and fallacies straight to the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">The Storyteller finished speaking to the crowds at the town square in the evening. That's when the Great Witch appeared.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">I still cannot forget the sound of that terrible incantation! It was undoubtedly that girl's voice!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">We ran towards the tower as soon as we saw her, keeping our eyes on her to make sure she didn't escape!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">We split into two groups at the entrance... One group to guard it, the other to chase down the witch. I was in the first group.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">I...I was...one of the p-pursuers. I ran into the t-tower...and caught the w-witch.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">There was no one but us at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">We captured the girl. There was nowhere for anyone to hide there.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">There was no other witch. I'm sure of it.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Ah was guardin' th' entrance. Ah hud th' duir locked!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">That's right, young one. The fateful bell tower. The fateful incident. We saw them with our own fateful eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ Well, I suppose that can again be summed up by saying... you all did the best you could.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The Vigilantes were the first to arrive at the crime scene. Their testimony is credible.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It does seem so. And if what they say is indeed true... it would be decisive proof of the accused's guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Our opponent is a witch. The Great Witch, to be exact. Things probably aren't as simple as they seem.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Heh. If you think so, feel free to look for any cracks in their testimony. ...If there are any. And if you're up to it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender, you may begin the interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">The Storyteller finished speaking to the crowds at the town square in the evening. That's when the Great Witch appeared.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">...ALL the people were in the square. You read the contents of the Story, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The town's grand finale was kind of a big deal, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">It happened only several hours ago... a sight we'll never forget! The Storyteller noticed the Great Witch first. She appeared at the bell tower...and she conjured a flame above her finger. The Storyteller fixed his gaze on that flame. ...But it was already too late! The Great Witch uttered the incantation.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">"Granwyrm"...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">I still cannot forget the sound of that terrible incantation! It was undoubtedly that girl's voice!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">What a question! I mean Espella Cantabella! Who else?! She took her father's life with that fearsome word!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Yeah! No doubt about it! That voice belonged to Espella Cantabella!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">That fiendish voice! It even made me shudder. A little.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">Oh yes! She shouted that dreadful incantation! "Ignaize!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wrong trial, grandpa. That wasn't even the same witch...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It looks like they all remember her voice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, to be honest, I also think it was Espella's voice...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhm, maybe it's better not to dig too deep into this topic.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">We ran towards the tower as soon as we saw her, keeping our eyes on her to make sure she didn't escape!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">Of course! I was worried the Great Witch may escape us... so I never took my eyes off her until I reached that bell tower!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You didn't lose sight of her even once?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">No! Even when I tripped on a pebble and fell down, I kept my eyes fixed on her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You fell down?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's dangerous to run without paying attention to where you're stepping.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">I saw my fellow Vigilantes capture the Great Witch. That's when I tripped and fell...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">It was impossible for someone else to have traded places with the person who summoned that fire dragon. Therefore, the Great Witch Bezella can be none other than Espella Cantabella.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">We split into two groups at the entrance... One group to guard it, the other to chase down the witch. I was in the first group.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">It was me and Lottalance. The rest went after the witch. Right, Lottalance?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">Yeah. I think that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Ah, yes. Now that I think about it, it was quite a scene.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Quite a scene?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">If you want to know more, why don't you ask the kid?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ahem...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">I'm fairly certain that I, too, was there. Guarding the entrance. ...Well, wherever I may have been, the winds that blow over plains will have blown just the same.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>These guys aren't the best when it comes to teamwork...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">I...I was...one of the p-pursuers. I ran into the t-tower...and caught the w-witch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">Sh-she was as if in a d...daze. I...I, too, was in a daze... Th-then I seemed to...f-fall un... unconscious. When I c-came to, it seemed that I'd...captured her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That means...you climbed the tower before anyone else?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">Y-yesss... That's...that's c-correct.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Lemme tell you, that guy's the fastest among us! Runs at breakneck speed!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">Number Five is very light. I'm quite jealous of his feathery build!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>I just...don't know what to say.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">There was no one but us at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">Very sure. There were only two people on the top floor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Wait a second! You said "two"?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">Yes, two. It was me and my sweet Foxy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">I am in love. All my attention is directed at Foxy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a weak excuse... There were several other Vigilantes at the crime scene too, weren't there?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">Yeah, probably. But that means nothing to me! To me, there is only Foxy! That's my romantic interpretation of events.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wish you would testify about what you've actually witnessed.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">We captured the girl. There was nowhere for anyone to hide there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">The whole city was watching the tower at that time. If the witch tried to climb down using a ladder or something, she'd have been seen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, that's a fair point.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">But, we're talking about Bezella here. She could've become invisible and flown out of the bell tower, you know. It'd be child's play for Bezella, since she can use any spells [sic] she wants.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right. The Great Witch Bezella could have escaped with ease. And yet, Espella was caught at the crime scene...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hear that, Nick? That's further proof there's NO WAY Espella is Bezella, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's hardly conclusive... I mean, if that was enough to convince everyone, we wouldn't be having this trial. <thought>But there's something in Foxy's testimony that keeps nagging at me. Was there really no place to hide? Can any evidence in the Court Record confirm that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That's the sketch of the bell tower, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Most fascinating. Well, defender... how about you show us? Enlighten us as to where exactly the witch could have hidden!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">If you were a true Knight of the Court... you'd show us evidence rather than trying to justify your vague theories with "the use of magic"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaarghhhhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She kinda has a point, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How else could someone get to the top of the bell tower? There has to be a way... Was it magic?  Or something a little more... plausible? Whatever it was, I need proof.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's getting late. I can see no point in dwelling on this. Defender, you may continue the interrogation.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... I can't say I see exactly what you're pointing at.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, Your Honour. My finger slipped and I pointed to the wrong spot...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">What a silly slip-up, defender boy. Are you giving in to the stress? Want me to massage your back with my stilettos to help you get back into shape?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">It would do you good! Try it! Become one of us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gaaaah! <thought>Somebody save me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, I think I see a good hiding place in that sketch. Give it another try, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Got to get it this time... I don't think I can take any more of Foxy's, err...teasing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">There was no other witch. I'm sure of it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">Sorry to disappoint you, but no one used any magic at that time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What makes you so sure?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">To cast a spell, a witch needs to say that spell's incantation. And we heard no incantations. Nor any other suspicious noises.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr Shakey...? I...didn't mean to startle you. Do you have anything to add to Mr Treddon's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">Ah... Ah...y-yesss... I...I...think there w-was...s-s-something. A s-strange...noise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! You actually... heard something at the crime scene?! And you say it was a strange noise?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">............ ...Y-yes... </line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look what you did, Nick! That's just cruel!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What, I didn't DO anything!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can't remember if I heard anything odd when we were in the bell tower...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Mr Shakey?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It looks like we're temporarily one witness down.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's give him a break. Maybe someone else also heard that noise. <thought>Number Eight said he didn't hear anything unusual... And it wasn't only Shakey that seemed to have a different opinion on that matter.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's question the other witnesses, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Number Six?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">Yeah? I'm sort of busy thinking about something right now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think about Mr Treddon's statement? Is there anything you'd like to share with us?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">Well, kind of. Just a thought I had... Treddon's saying that since he didn't hear the incantation, the witch didn't use magic, right?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">Yeah! She didn't, so she couldn't have turned invisible, see?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">That's some surprisingly good reasoning, especially coming from you. But couldn't she have simply cast the spell earlier?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">If she was invisible from the start, of course we wouldn't have heard that incantation.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">............</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">Mmm. My, aren't you the smart one, Servius. You took the words right out of my mouth! I was thinking the same.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">Out of...Foxy's mouth? Oh dear! I feel like I'm melting inside. Watch me bask in Foxy's love, Treddon!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">Grrrr! The envy, the jealousy, the chagrin! You make me suffer so, Foxy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It was a...noteworthy testimony. But this witness wasn't the only one that seemed to have something to say about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, let's question some more people!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Foxy?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">What? Would you like to ask Foxy a question, defender boy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd like to know what you think about Mr Treddon's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">Uhm. I have this little pet theory, you know. He's saying that since he didn't hear the incantation, the witch didn't cast a spell, no?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">Yeah! She didn't, so she couldn't turn invisible, see?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">Well, that would make sense... But couldn't she have simply cast the spell earlier?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">If she was invisible from the start, of course we didn't hear that incantation.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">............</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">So I think you've made a fool of yourself, sweetie.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">I...I have! It's just as you say! Oh, the public humiliation... Walk over me more! Let me be your doormat!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It looks like the testimony went kinda off the rails there...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me about it... Just leave them to themselves. And don't make eye contact... <thought>But, you know... It wasn't just Foxy that seemed to be thinking about something during Treddon's testimony.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, let's question some more people!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Mr Wordsmith...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">I do not know anyone by that name.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh, yeeeeeeah... Anyway, would you like to comment on Mr Treddon's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">............ ............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see you have nothing to say. <thought>He's in "green field" mode again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">Do not rush to conclusions, young one. I am...on a green field, sky-clad, watching petals dancing in the wind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup, I knew you'd say that.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">And yet...a single shaft of light has shone through the dark abyss of my memory. I heard something in the bell tower, when we went to apprehend the witch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! What did you hear? Was it an incantation?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">No, it wasn't an incantation. Nevertheless, it sounded like a woman's voice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr Wordsmith! This is extremely important information! Please add this to your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">Yes, I shall do that. It's best that I tell you about it now, before I forget again.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As the defender requested, you will now testify about the sound you heard!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When you say "suspicious"...what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">If a witch cast a spell of invisibility, we wouldn't see anything. But... we would've heard the incantation! You shouldn't be asking us what we've seen, but rather what we heard!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">What do you think, my gorgeous Foxy? Didn't that sound cool? Wasn't I kinda awesome just then?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">Uh-huh. Maybe...somewhat.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">Woohoo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Noises heard at the crime scene...it may be worth keeping that in the back of my mind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Next witness, continue the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Ah was guardin' th' entrance. Ah hud th' duir locked!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Aye! Ah wasnae gonnae lit anyain escape. Sae Ah turned th' key in th' lock!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh... You did a great job, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">His intentions weren't bad, but it did more harm than good.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">The little boy swallowed the key... And there were no spares. He successfully locked in everyone who'd entered the bell tower.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He...swallowed the key?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's right. We couldn't get down from the bell tower for some time afterwards.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">This incident has led us to coin a new word for getting helplessly trapped. It's to be "Dzibilchaltunchunchucmilled". It's getting quite popular.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Dornt go aroond attachin' strange meanings tae people's names!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So...you could say we got ourselves kinda Dzibilchaltunchunchucmilled in Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at you, a budding expert on Labyrinthian slang.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">That's right, young one. The fateful bell tower. The fateful incident. We saw them with our own fateful eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">I can indeed...since you're asking. The delicious scent of mid-evening dinner permeated through the air. Then, a soft light shone faintly in the distance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes...right. So, what time was it, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">Dinner time. When else would the scent of dinner be in the air, if not dinner time? ...Do you see?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh... You still haven't answered my question.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">At any rate, I heard it then. That ominous incantation. It made my beard hairs stand on end! "Ignaize", she cried!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ I, um, think you're getting things mixed up with a previous case.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">............ I am...on a green field, sky-clad, watching petals dancing in the wind... Allow me to indulge in my dream for a while longer, young one.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">I recall...hearing a woman's voice. A faint, delicate sobbing, no less.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">Yes. Sobbing, or perhaps wailing... EEEE! EEE EEK! EEEE! ...She sounded a bit like hinges in need of some grease.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Boy, his falsetto packs a serious punch.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">And there was another noise, too. CLACK, CLACK, CLACK, CLACK. ...It was a pleasant sound, rather like that of wooden cogs in motion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">And another sound... A CLINK-CLANK of chains creaking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We've come a long way from the sound of a woman crying...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Owww... Aaah...aaaaah...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">Aaah... I remember now! A w...wo...woman's...s-s-scream. It...it was likely the c-contraption's...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">On second thought, I heard it too. I remember a certain wailing, creaking noise flowing through the air!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...And when did you hear it?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">Hmm... We ran to the bell tower...and I think it was when we arrived at the entrance.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">Indeed. Only the quickest of us got there in time to hear it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mr Wordsmith is a fast runner? Gotta be honest, Nick, I never saw that coming...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think it might speak more for the slowness of the other Vigilantes... <thought>Anyway, we've got a new piece of info... The Vigilantes heard some noises resembling machinery in the tower.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder what was making all those eeks and clinks and clacks...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Was there any machinery up in that bell tower...? Now's the perfect time to present something that may have some connection to those noises.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">That reminds me... there was some contraption up there unlike anything I'd seen before.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">That's right, chief! We never touched it, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How about we try operating that contraption to see what it does? We might just be able to reproduce the sound that Mr Lottalance heard at the crime scene...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">Right! You might be on to something!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">But it was I who testified about it before that young man...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">I...t-talked about it, too...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, you've got my curiosity. Let's see you set that contraption in motion.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Milord! Just leave it to me!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Get ready, everyone! Prick up your ears!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As you've all seen...or rather, "heard"... It's clear that device was operating shortly after the incident!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... High Inquisitor Darklaw has a point.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's not like I don't have an idea what that machinery was used for... But how should I go about proving it to the court? Guess I should confront "Madam Butterfly" over there about her testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems we've wasted a lot of time over nothing. Defence, you may continue the interrogation.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">That reminds me... there was some contraption up there unlike anything I'd seen before.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">That's right, chief! We never touched it, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How about we try operating that contraption to see what it does? We might just be able to reproduce the sound that Mr Lottalance heard at the crime scene...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">Right! You might be on to something!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">But it was I who testified about it before that young man...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">I...t-talked about it, too...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, you've got my curiosity. Let's see you set that contraption in motion.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Milord! Just leave it to me!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Get ready, everyone! Prick up your ears!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As you've all seen...or rather, "heard"... It's clear that device was operating shortly after the incident!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">Yes, it was. The world is full of strange devices. But I shan't be but another cog in the wheel.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">As for devices, I wish to be left to my own. I shall pursue my own dreams, as a fallen leaf pursues a warm breeze. Whirling, semi-transparent cogwheels. There are more and more of them...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think his train of thought got derailed. Anyway, we know that the contraption was in use shortly after the incident.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can't stop thinking about what this contraption is for...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd have to prove her testimony wrong to find the answer to that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like they're all saying pretty much the same thing... But there was another witch in the bell tower. If only it was easier to prove...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">If the other witch used the invisibility spell, that would explain why no one saw her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No kidding, Maya. That's the whole point of invisibility, after all. ...But just knowing that doesn't help me. I need more information to go on.</thought> I'm sure there was one more person... another witch, in the bell tower at the time of the incident. And I'm going to find a way to prove it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right! Let's keep our eyes peeled for any witnesses acting suspiciously!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Remember our demonstration a little while ago?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Demonstration? Are you referring to that silly contraption?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?! Is that what it is?! Order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Another witch was in the bell tower when the incident happened... And the reason she wasn't discovered... is because she used that contraption to reach the belfry and hide up there!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I'm talking about your little "demonstration" earlier. Yes, the device was set in motion and made some strange noises... And yet... that's all it did!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">That's right...nothing else happened. If it was a device for accessing the top of the tower... then why didn't it take us there?!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Ergo, that contraption is of no relevance to this case. ...Which brings us back to my erstwhile conclusion that there was no other witch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">And why is that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, our demonstration didn't show it... but maybe the device didn't work because it wasn't used correctly!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What? Why do you think so?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My reasoning is simple. Let's just say it would be troublesome if just anyone could go up and sound that bell. So it's reasonable to assume that access to the belfry would be restricted... In other words, that a special key would be needed.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...A key?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And I think I know just what that key is!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Before I ask you to present evidence, I'd like to summarise your theory. You believe that there was another witch in the bell tower at the time of the incident. And that this witch used a contraption within the tower to make her way up to the belfry and hide there.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Your whole theory rests solely upon that contraption. If it doesn't allow access to the belfry, then your reasoning is completely wrong. I'm sure you know what that would mean for Espella. ...Your mistake would seal her fate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... I'm aware of that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right then. The defence shall prove its theory. Show us this "key" needed to operate the contraption in the bell tower!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">You're no longer new to these witch trials, and yet you still do not seem to understand. The life of the accused depends on your actions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She didn't even let me get a word in...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! At this rate, Espella will be...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honour, let me start again! I accidentally picked the wrong evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Very well... But before you do, perhaps a penalty will encourage you to be more careful.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ughhhhh! <thought>The key to this theory... has to rest within that contraption!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's not over yet... Let's check that device in the Court Record. A closer look might shed some light on how to use it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The key to the contraption is... this pendant.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That belongs to the accused, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. We found it at the crime scene. Now, if we take a look at the bottom part of this contraption... there's a depression here about the exact same size of the pendant.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Oh, yes. I remember it. A hole in the shape of that pendant! Hmm... But I don't get it... Why would that pendant be the key to the bell tower?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know either. At least not for now... But the point is, it definitely is. With this pendant, we should be able to operate the contraption and access the belfry!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, the court will grant the defence a chance to prove its assertion. ...However, you shall be given one chance only.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Are you ready, defender? Make sure you are prepared for the consequences of a mistake. This will be your only chance. If it doesn't work, that will be the end of it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes...I'm ready! <thought>I've got to be right about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Good.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>To be honest, this looks like a puzzle... I wish the professor was [sic] here... This is totally his field of expertise.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Are you ready, Nick? Should we give it a try?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... It's got to work!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">N/A* <thought>listed as 70 picarats, but not able to be solved at this time</thought></line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">Before starting puzzle:</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, Nick! Let's give this thing a shot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Whoa! A beam of light... <thought>Of course. This must be the key...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">That light is just begging to be pointed at one of those red gems!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're right. Still... It looks like there's some kinda trick to the whole thing...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A trick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, think about it. There are two gems. I bet we have to light them both simultaneously. Looks like we're gonna have to do it with only this single beam of light, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wha...?! A-are you sure we can pull that off?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have no clue, but... We've got no choice but to try. <thought>All we have to do is move the gears and bounce the light off those blue gems!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">All right! No time for the jitters, Nick! We've gotta make this work! For Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Did you see that?! It lit up for, like, a second!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, it did. But... <thought>That was only one gem...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">............ What gives? Nothing's happening.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What exactly did you expect?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The gems must be lit "simultaneously".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But! There's only one light. It's impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Indeed. Now then, I believe we have our answer. It is, as you say, "impossible".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-wait a second! Let me try just one more time!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">That will not be necessary. Your time is up. Or have you already forgotten? You were given only one chance to back up your claim.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No way!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In the end...the defence has failed to prove its theory. The contraption cannot be operated with the pendant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But the pendant fit right into the mechanism... There's no way that's a coincidence! But still... no matter how much I try, it seems impossible to direct the light at both gems simultaneously!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">It seems your foolish experiment wasn't too much of a waste of time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">While you were tinkering with that contraption... the accused regained consciousness.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is she okay?!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Well... Despite seeming a bit confused, she's in better shape now. Although... I wouldn't describe her situation as "okay". Quite the opposite, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Don't tell me you've forgotten your agreement with the judge. You failed to prove your theory... and so, the accused's fate has been decided!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Arghhh... There's nothing I can say to that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Attendants! Bring in the accused!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Accused, the trial has reached its conclusion in your absence. The court shall now announce its verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">The verdict...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">You are the Great Witch. And your true name is Bezella. This evening, a terrible crime took place. You killed your father, the Storyteller, using the spell Granwyrm. Does the accused have anything to say?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ Yes...I am Bezella. The one that brought calamity upon this town.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">And my memories are proof of this. I remember the Legendary Fire, in which this town was burned to the ground. And this day, several hours ago... I summoned a fire dragon and took my own father's life. There is no doubt that the Great Witch is a part of me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Fool.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what?!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">You've been fighting a battle in this court. You have come here with your logic, finding contradictions to astound everyone. It was your battle, not hers!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">So how can you be telling her not to give up, when you have already dropped your sword? If you are a true Knight of the Court, you will fight your battle to the end!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>Why is she telling me this...? It almost sounds like she's encouraging me... Is she...waiting for something?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">No, it's okay, Mr Wright. Ever since I was little, I can only remember being all alone. But that's not really true. There were people who were dear to me and memories that I cherished. At least, I think there were. But...I've already lost all that. They were taken from me the moment I became Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Poor Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Since then, I started working at Aunt Patty's bakery. I met Mr Wright, Maya, Mr Layton and Luke. The four of you did all you could to help me. I am truly happy to have met you. But blame for the Great Witch's crimes rests solely on my shoulders.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Espella">So let's put an end to this now... Bezella must not remain in this town. Thank you, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then... It's time for the final verdict!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Think, Phoenix, think! Isn't there anything I can do?! I just need something... anything that could offer even a single glimmer of hope in this darkness of despair. There's gotta be something...right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't have any solid evidence...and if I make another mistake now, that could be it. Maybe something will pop into my head if I wait a bit and see how it goes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">No! What are you doing, Nick?! You want to wait and see how it goes? I'll tell you how it's gonna go if you wait... BADLY! You've got to do something now! C'mon! You always find a solution when trials are at their most hopeless! That's your thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I guess it sort of is. It's not great for my heart, though. Still... I've got to pick up my sword of justice and fight!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honour, please hold off with the verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's that, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's too early to pass the final judgement on Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What? Explain yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You said earlier that the trial has reached its conclusion. But... there's something we have yet to examine!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what are you suggesting?!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Do you mean to say...you have some new evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-but surely there can't possibly be any new evidence at this late stage...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Very well, defender. We shall play along with you just one more time. Now, show us this evidence that we haven't yet seen!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The new, crucial piece of evidence is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It is, without doubt, at the crime scene, inside the bell tower!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Really, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, are you feeling okay? Do you realise what you just said?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, there's nothing new in the Court Record... So that's one possibility down. If there's anything else we can use, it's got to be at the crime scene, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, come on! The bell tower has been searched loads of times already!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Er...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Think about it... We're not going to find anything new there now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Your Honour, please hold on! The defence would like to reconsider its answer!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">You're so frustrating to watch, defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ughhhh... <thought>Being me can be even more frustrating, trust me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Think about your answer harder next time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It has to be in the Court Record!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">In the Court Record? Why, that's an answer I didn't expect, even from you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick? Did you really just say that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But...where's evidence gonna be if not in the Court Record?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We need NEW evidence here, Nick! Not something that's already in the Court Record!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We've already looked at everything in there, and none of it is what we need here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Your Honour, please hold on! The defence would like to reconsider its answer!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">You're so frustrating to watch, defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ughhhh... <thought>Being me can be even more frustrating, trust me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Think about your answer harder next time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's only one place where it can be... It's in Espella's possession.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I...I have it?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I saw it for a second. Something there that she shouldn't have... An item that contradicts what we've heard. My gut feeling tells me that item is the key to this whole case!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Most interesting. I shall enjoy watching you hopelessly struggle through this, like a fish caught in a net.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, defender... show us this new evidence that the accused supposedly has in her possession!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Don't look to me for answers. Maybe the defender, who's sweating profusely for some reason, can explain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...? Espella...at least you know what evidence I meant, right?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I...I'm very sorry, Mr Wright... I don't know. I was unconscious until just now, so I'm a little bit lost...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, at least you understand me...right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I... I'm sorry, Nick. I'm kinda lost too... Guess I must've spaced out for a bit myself.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">It would seem the one who's truly lost here is you, defender. Not to mention your case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh! <thought>Looks like I messed that one up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't be so hopeless, Nick! Something Espella has on her right now caught your attention, remember? ...So open your eyes and look for it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something Espella is wearing contradicts the evidence as we know it... In other words, she has something that she shouldn't have...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella... Can I see the bracelet on your left hand?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Uhm, yes, certainly. If you'd like. It's actually a pendant, you know. But the strap got torn somehow when I was up in the bell tower... That's why I've had it around my wrist since...well, just before this trial started.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...! But...this pendant... It looks exactly the same as the one we already have here!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">W-wait a minute! What's all this?!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">We confiscated her pendant at the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">Why...why is she wearing it now?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">I don't get it... It's giving me a headache!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So I was right!</thought> I have another question about this pendant. Espella, do you remember when exactly the strap broke?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm trying to remember, but...no, I can't. I know it was still fine when we parted ways, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>In other words, she has no memory of it... She doesn't remember when it broke or when she tied it to her wrist!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's certainly bizarre, I must say! Your pendant has already been submitted as evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">R-really?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Y-yeah! She was caught red-handed by us, the Vigilantes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...This pendant proves something crucial to this case.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">It can't be more "crucial" than us catching her at the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The second pendant wasn't dropped by Espella. So, as the defence already suggested... one more person was at the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Whaaaaaa... Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Accused! Submit your pendant as evidence, this instant!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, Milord...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhm, Nick! If we have two pendants to work with... maybe we can see if that strange contraption will work this time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! ...Now it makes sense! That must be why it didn't work before! Your Honour! The defence would like to try operating the mechanism in the bell tower one more time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What? Why now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The contraption didn't work before, because we only had one pendant. ...But both pendants are needed to operate it properly!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Foolishness! Try as many times as you like. It's no use! High Inquisitor Darklaw! You know this is a waste of time!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">If it's not going to work anyway... Why not let the defender see for himself.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Defender, if you think you can operate the contraption with two pendants... then I suggest you go ahead and try it. Unless it has already dawned upon you that such a plan is futile.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence shall be given one more chance to verify its theory about the aforementioned contraption. Let us now make our way to the bell tower.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">This is going to be your last try.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I know.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Are you not terrified? The life of the accused rests in your shaky hands... We won't be having any more let-me-try-again-please-Your-Honours. Besides, you must be aware that this puzzle may well be unsolvable.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ I wouldn't have been able to solve a puzzle like this before arriving here in Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But now...I'm sure I can take on any puzzle. <thought>And it's all thanks to you, Professor. You taught me that every puzzle has a solution. I have everything I need now.</thought> What do you say, Maya? Should we hurry up and get started?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sure thing! It's puzzle-bustin' time!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">70</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>I'm sure I did it right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhm. Nothing's happening... ...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This...this sound!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">This...this is...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">What an astounding contraption!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">Hmm, what do we have here? It's still no comparison to the incomparable astoundingness of Mother Nature.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">Ooh! I'd like to climb up those stairs! I like being on the top!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius / Vigilante* Treddon">We shall escort you!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Aam gonnae tay!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">.........!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, Nick! Let's go see what's upstairs!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... Isn't this bell...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. I think you're right. That's the bell that was taken from underground... The Bell of Ruin. <thought>The bell that must not be sounded...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">......!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! There's someone hiding behind the bell!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... It's you... <thought>Now that's the last person I expected to find here.</thought> Ms Kira...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's so quiet in here... There's not a sound to be heard.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Let's be very careful though, Luke. The puzzle we just dealt with is not necessarily the only one in place here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Let's proceed with caution...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Interesting. I wonder how this lift is controlled?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Blimey, Professor... I can't believe this cage can make it ALL the way to the top of the tower!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It appears the chain is connected to the upper section. I gather it must be of considerable strength.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I wonder just how much this chain is capable of pulling?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I don't quite understand what good it does to have a tower this high...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Without this lift, it appears as if reaching the very top would be quite impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Is this what I think it is? It looks like...a lift!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed it does... It looks a lot like the kind of lift with which we are well acquainted.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But...we haven't seen anything else like this since we arrived in Labyrinthia!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, quite... In truth, I didn't think machinery of this sort existed here. I wonder what it's using as a source of power...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, since there seems to be no other way up...does that mean we get to ride it?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. That would seem the most logical course of action. I must say, I find the presence of such a device most intriguing. But we can't stand around pondering such things now. There will be time for that later. Onwards and upwards, my boy!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right then, let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I know I keep saying this, Luke, but bear in mind that we must proceed with caution.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm with you on that one, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, we've stopped! Wh-wh-what's going on here?! Are we trapped?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...No, I don't believe so, Luke. Although I do get the feeling that something is about to happen.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Something, Professor? What do you mean by "something"?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Luke, stand close to me.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">O-okay!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Whoa! We've started moving again!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would seem this entire lift is, in itself, another puzzle put in place to protect whatever secrets lie ahead. I don't believe we're in the clear just yet... This may take a while.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We've stopped again! Another stage of the puzzle?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... Indeed, that would appear to be the case.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'll take on this one, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">All right, but don't overexert yourself. We'll need to work together to solve the rest of this puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Roger that!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">40</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I did it, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You certainly did. Well done, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But...we're still not there yet, are we? Just how far is this lift going to take us...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, judging by all the stages thus far, whoever put this puzzle in place is certainly keen that we don't reach the top easily. We still can't afford to let our guard down.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah... We've stopped again!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well then...allow me to take on this one.</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">50</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That was an exceedingly difficult puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The next stop must be our destination!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I think you're probably right, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, this is it, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It seems we have arrived at last.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow! This is certainly different! There are flowers and plants everywhere. I can even see a water wheel over there.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is a beautiful place.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Brrr...this evening breeze is a little chilly. So...is this the Storyteller's garden then?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I think that's probably a safe assumption, Luke. Judging by the abundance of water and rose bushes, it's being well taken care of. I'd be inclined to say the tower seems more akin to a castle.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Who'd have imagined we'd end up in a beautiful place like this?! Let's investigate!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I don't think Labyrinthia will have to worry about water shortages any time soon, that's for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I imagine it must have been quite important to develop a technique for drawing water up to such a height.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Amazingly, it appears the structure was recently adorned with flowers and kept in rather good repair.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I bet Espella sure must have had quite the comfortable life back when she used to live here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This must be where the water that surrounds the tower is turned into mist, right, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I wonder if this is what is creating a veil of mist over the garden.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This building is really something else... I guess this part must be the Storyteller's house. Espella must have lived here when she was younger...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, indeed. This must have been her family home.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............ Her family... I wonder if she had any plans to ever come back here...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">No matter where she goes or what she does, family is family. This will always be her home. I'd say it's highly likely that she would wish to come back here someday.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I suppose so...even if her family was only the two of them.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The relationship between Espella and her father may well prove to be an important clue.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yes, I was thinking the same thing... ...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What's the matter, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's nothing... I'm probably seeing things... But for a moment there, I thought I saw something moving at the top of the tower. Sorry...it must have just been my imagination! Let's go inside, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...? This appears to be...a child's room.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It certainly looks that way! From its condition, I'd say it hasn't been used for some time... Presumably it was used by Espella as a child.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right... So this is where Espella grew up... Something pretty big must've happened to make her leave home so young. I wonder how Espella and the Storyteller used to get on together.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Espella is a young lady of strong conviction and a kind heart. I'm certain that's because she grew up within a fine home environment. In other words, I'm sure she and her father must have spent some quality time here together.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yeah... I have a feeling you're right about that. For Espella, this place must be full of precious memories. I almost feel we're intruding, coming in here like this...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">But, Luke, we have no choice if we wish to save Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yes...I suppose that's true. When you put it like that, I guess she wouldn't mind even if she knew!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey, look at all those stuffed animals and toys!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Whoever made these stuffed animals appears to have put quite their heart and soul into the craftsmanship.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The paintings on the wall certainly give this room a rather charming feel.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This painting sure does make you feel all warm and fuzzy inside, doesn't it, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This wall is filled with artwork from top to bottom. And not a speck of dust in sight.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It looks as if the room is just the way Espella left it back when she left home.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Look, Professor! That door over there looks like the way forward!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. But first of all, let's investigate this room a little, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Crikey! P-P-Professor! Behind that curtain... There's...someone...there!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ The mysterious figure turned out to be...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Just a doll... Whew, that's a relief! My heart was in my mouth!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Espella must have played with this doll as a child.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Eh? What's this? Look, Professor. There's a child's picture book here. The title is..."The First Story".</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would appear to be a handmade children's picture book.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I wonder if it was written especially for Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...It may well have been. Evidently, a great deal of loving care has been put into the writing and illustrations.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Who'd have thought there would be a fairy tale about Bezella? She's a mysterious character, all right...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Tell me, Luke. Why do you think the author chose to write about Bezella in a children's picture book?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? Well, maybe...to make their child behave? Something like: "If you don't do as you're told, Bezella will come and get you!"</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, indeed. That is a possibility. Still, I have to wonder... why is it that some lowly witch was caught, and not the great Bezella herself?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hmm... Well, I suppose it is a bit strange... If Bezella herself had been caught, the story could have been brought to a more conclusive ending. Do you think there's some other reason?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's certainly a possibility. I don't suppose there are any other handmade picture books in the room apart from this one...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Handmade picture books... Hmm... ...I don't see any. I guess that must be the only one.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Which would imply this book has some special significance.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I guess so. After all, it is handmade... I bet she really treasured it. Do you think it was the Storyteller who wrote this book?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The handwriting does seem very similar to that of the Story. This book appears to have been written with a touch more care and attention, but I imagine it was the Storyteller who wrote it.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">He must've written it as a gift from father to daughter... That actually seems really thoughtful... even if the story itself is a little scary. I'd like to take this book to Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes...let's do just that, Luke. We must take good care of it.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I believe we've seen all there is to see here. Let's press on, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What do you make of this room, Professor? It's not very tidy...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This appears to be the very top room of the tower. ...? The parchment lying on the floor here seems very similar to the type on which the Storyteller writes his Stories. I think we can say with some certainty that this is the Storyteller's room.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Huh? This is...the Storyteller's room?! I was imagining something a bit grander, like a throne room with all kinds of posh decorations.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">While I agree that it's a little eccentric, it's unmistakably the study of an author. He probably spent all his time in here, continuously writing those Stories.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The Stories... I wonder what Espella thought of it all... Her father writing Stories for all the townsfolk, I mean. I wonder if she looked forward to seeing the new Stories completed... Or if she...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The Stories were probably a little too mature in content for a young child. I don't imagine the Storyteller would have shown Espella many of them.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But in that case, surely she can't have had many opportunities to even talk to her father, given how busy he was. I guess that means she was pretty lonely... It must have been hard for her, even knowing how important those Stories are for the people of the town. But...I don't think it's right. No child should be unable to talk with their father.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I absolutely agree, Luke. I believe it will be important in the upcoming trial to have an understanding of Espella's feelings towards her father.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Knowing you, Luke, I'm sure you must have a lot of things on your mind at the moment. So if there is anything at all that you want to talk about, you will tell me, won't you?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Of course I will, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm always ready to listen, Luke. Now then, shall we start investigating this room?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow. There sure is quite a bit of light coming through that stained glass window, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm. I wonder if this is actually the topmost part of the tower?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm. Papers are strewn about the floor. Strange. It doesn't appear as if they've been written on.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I know it sounds a bit silly, but let's try not to trample all over these papers, okay, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">From the looks of this room, it appears the Storyteller is quite the talented artist.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Something about this room really makes it feel a lot like the professor's study.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Look, Professor! A photograph! Wait...I didn't think they even had photographs in this town.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, it's not the kind of thing one would have expected to find here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Too right! I certainly haven't seen any cameras about since we got here. There's no doubt that this is a photo, though. What could that mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This may be in some way related to the tower being so closely protected. What do you see in the photograph, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There are two children, both young girls.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The photo looks quite old, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I wonder who they are...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... Well, one of them is surely Espella. There can be little doubt about that.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Hey, you're right! And look at that pendant! It's the same one Espella always wears!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The fact that she's continued to wear it ever since shows just how important that pendant must be to her.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What about this other girl? Do you think she's a friend of Espella's?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. I'd wager the two of them were rather close friends, at that.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They do look pretty chummy, all right. See, they even have the same pendant!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A glimpse into Espella's past... This may well prove to be an important clue. I would like to ask her about it face-to-face. Let's borrow it for the time being.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I wonder if there are any other clues knocking around...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, I'd say the "something" that you thought you saw moving earlier is a point worth pursuing.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But isn't this the last room in the tower? I must have just been imagining things...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Not necessarily, Luke. If I'm not mistaken, there should be a way of getting beyond even this room. Let's look around more closely.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah! This is...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What is it, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This letter on top of the piano... This was evidence during that trial!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">"That trial", my boy...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yes! The trial about Sir Belduke's death. The trial when you were...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah, you mean when I was turned to gold? In which case, this letter is the one that... the Storyteller's owl, Hoot, gave us after we last paid him a visit.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well...yes, it is. But...that letter was completely blank, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Indeed it was.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That was meant to be Sir Belduke's suicide note, which he'd addressed to the Storyteller.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">His suicide note, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But Sir Belduke's butler swapped the letter for some plain sheets of parchment before it got delivered... And those blank sheets were given to us by Mr Hoot, who knew something was strange about them.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I see... I certainly missed out on some intriguing developments during my absence.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The real suicide note was revealed at the trial. But...how has it ended up here?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well... I imagine that's quite simple, Luke. It's likely that after the trial finished, the letter was returned to its rightful owner. It was addressed to the Storyteller, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right... I guess that does make sense! I suppose the Storyteller finally had a chance to actually read it, then...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm, yes... In fact, it would be reasonable to assume... that he most likely did so very recently. Perhaps even today, while sitting at the piano. ...What on earth was going through his mind here before that final parade? There's something we're not seeing here... We need to investigate this closely, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What could it be...? Surely this is not a trap of some kind...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's unlikely that a trap would be so obvious. Just a moment... There's some kind of puzzle in this piano...</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">50</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Look, Professor! A stairway just appeared! Could there be another room above this one?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I have a feeling that the rooftop we saw from the garden continues above here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh! I can see what you mean, Professor. It's really dark in here, but moonlight seems to be coming in from up above.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, there's no turning back now. The answer to the biggest mystery of all is surely waiting for us ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I think so too, Professor! I wonder what on earth it could be...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The next step in the Storyteller's Story, if I'm not mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The next step? But the Story has already finished, hasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Not yet, Luke. It's still a little too soon for the ending.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I had a feeling that you, of all people, would make it this far.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's you!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I thought so - you are still alive.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Professor Layton. I've had enough of your running around, flagrantly contravening the flow of my Story. As such...I can no longer ignore your meddling!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor! Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Thank you, my boy!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">70</line>
<line speaker="Notes">A failure at any stage restarts the stage without penalty</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">Before starting puzzle:</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I'm afraid your role in the Story ends here, Professor. Now, allow me to write the tale of your demise.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Well played, Professor... But how will you fare in this tragic tale?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Think you worked it out, do you? Let us see if you can predict the ending of this final chapter.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, behind you! Professor! Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well now, that was close.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Storyteller! I'm afraid that the power of your pen is no longer absolute!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">You never fail to impress me, Professor Layton. Just tell me one thing...what exactly are you trying to achieve?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You could say...I'm trying to lift the veil that hangs over the town.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">If that is indeed the case, the answer lies in the "Final Story". This very evening, the Great Witch Bezella will be tried, and all stories will end. You should take your place in the gallery and observe the final trial.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Permit me, if I may, to ask you a question, Mr Storyteller... Why is it that you are here?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You, too, should be watching in the gallery. Watching as your twisted Story unfolds...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">My "twisted Story"...? What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You must surely be aware that your Story has already become twisted. Take our arrival in this town, for instance. Not to mention our being here at this very moment. Neither of these things could have happened in the Story you wrote. In other words, what I am saying is that you are no longer the weaver of the tale.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">........................</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Hmm... It is as you say... The Story I crafted has indeed been twisted out of proportion by someone else's actions. I'm not surprised that you realised... It seems nothing passes by those sharp eyes unnoticed.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">That is exactly why I decided to write the grand finale. ...To prevent any further distortion.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Do you mean to suggest that by ending the Story, you could return this town to its original state?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">To its original state, you say? I'm afraid that is not the case. The entire "truth" behind Labyrinthia is sealed by a single spell. That's right...the final spell.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...The final spell, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">When that spell is invoked, Labyrinthia's true form will become clear to all.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wh-what kind of spell is that?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">It is...a spell that has always been hidden within plain view.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Essentially... The final spell is concealed at the start.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">"The final spell is concealed at the start"? What on earth are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Bah... I thought you two took it upon yourselves to unravel mysteries, do you not? ...Do what you will with it.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Very well. Now then, I believe there's just one thing that you may wish to hear from me...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">...And what would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Firstly, what would you say if I told you that this "twisting" of your Story... is leading towards a grand finale quite different to the one you had planned?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ This evening, you supposedly gave up your life to the Great Witch Bezella, did you not? ...As a result, the person thought to be Bezella is being tried in court at this very moment. Now, if you'll permit me to ask... Do you happen to know the name of the accused?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">...Naturally. I wrote the name myself. There can be no question. Of course, the name of the accused is...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Espella Cantabella.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............ Wh-what are you saying?! Y-you mean my Espella is...?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, the accused at this evening's trial is none other than Espella Cantabella.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">That...can't...be! That's preposterous! This is your doing! What have you done, Layton?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You ask me what I've done, Mr Storyteller... I am but a solver of puzzles and mysteries. I do not concern myself with scheming.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">My Espella! Why... How is she the accused?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps you ought to go and see for yourself, Mr Storyteller. Do you think it's a good idea to just stand here lamenting your daughter's fate?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">...! What's...to be done?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Well, Mr Storyteller, I will be returning to the court. I'd like to witness this grand finale with my own eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah, yes. Before I leave, there is just one thing I'd like to make clear... I do not intend to simply take my place in the gallery and observe the trial. Naturally, there is only one place for me to stand in order to unravel all of these mysteries.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">You...you mean to say... that you will stand as the defender?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ha ha ha... Unfortunately, the defender's position is already taken. Moreover, Mr Storyteller, I am the one who knows the truth... The true identity of the Great Witch Bezella, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">How...how can you know...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There is only one place at which I should stand in order to assert such a fact... And that is not on the side of the defence.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">S-surely you can't mean...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I anticipate seeing you again soon, Mr Storyteller.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence's objection is overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-why?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">We have gathered here to deliver the final judgement on the Great Witch. This trial is strict and its results irrevocable. You should at least have the good sense to notice when you make a mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaargh! This trial does feel different to the other ones...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't see anything out of the ordinary.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah...really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Let that be a lesson, defender. I recommend the defence take more care in raising objections henceforth...or else.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something tells me the judge's gavel has something to do with that "or else"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Are you saying that piece of evidence is somehow relevant to this statement?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It isn't, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is not. But this penalty is certainly relevant to your performance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I really think...the judge enjoys handing down penalties.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, hello? Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh! Yes? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Regarding the testimony we've just heard... Is there anything you'd like to say about it?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ I'm sorry, Mr Wright. I'm not sure about anything at all...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something's blocking out her memories... Maybe trying to force them back all at once isn't the best thing for her... I've got no choice now but to trust the professor and keep on going.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, let's carry on. Witness, continue testifying!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">May I ask you something, Eve?</line>
<line speaker="Eve">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eve?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Just what are you doing, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Well, I just... Eve is Espella's friend, so I was wondering if she might have some input...</line>
<line speaker="Eve">............</line>
<line speaker="Espella">By the way, Eve doesn't always react to her name... So to coax her, I call her Little Miss Eve. You should try it, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh, seriously...? ............ ............ <thought>Ughh... Somehow, I just can't call a cat that. "Little Miss Eve, can you comment on that testimony?" It's just too embarrassing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What a welcome silence from your incessant whining... Witness, continue testifying.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Certainly...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's rather hopeless. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's...hopeless?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, defender. Hopeless. That which lacks hope. Much like the accused's fate. And here is the punishment to match such a performance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I could've done without the definition... or the insult, for that matter...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your objection clearly contradicts the facts. And for that, you shall receive a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uwaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Maybe Barnham would let your silly objections pass... but I'm not so kind-hearted.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I don't think Inquisitor Barnham would be having any of this either.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...These guys are just mean.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Mr Boistrum...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">What do you want, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You seemed to be thinking very intensely about something...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">............ We're the Vigilantes! Our love and devotion to Labyrinthia is unmatched! Labyrinthia is our town, so it's up to us to protect it. That's our...raisin de... something!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Raison d'tre. Yes, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">But I was thinking... It's all well and good that we protect the town and all... But who will protect us?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Maybe the true meaning of being a Vigilante... is that you're vigilant against threats to your own life and health...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I didn't take him for such a thinker...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Continue with the testimony. Next witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Number Two...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">You want to ask me something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You looked lost in thought, so I was wondering what you were thinking so hard about.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">............ I've been thinking about my life a lot lately. I've just been going with the flow, trying not to stand out... But...was it really what I wanted to do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, maybe...?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">This is a big day for me. It's my brief moment of fame...but I lack the sparkle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I...see... <thought>His "big day", huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lottalance">If you don't leave an impression, people will just forget all about you... Maybe I should try shaking like a leaf on a windy day, or changing my name to something unpronounceable!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not so sure that would be the right way to go about it... <thought>Great... So he wasn't even listening to what the other guys were saying.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mister... Um, Number Three...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">Huh? What's up?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looked like you were thinking about something...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">Yes, yes. We've been guarding the bell tower for a few months now, right? And no one ever approaches it... Not just suspicious types...no one at all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Doesn't that make your job easier?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">But...it gets so lonely there! It's so dreary, you know?! So, I've been thinking...about what we could do to make it more appealing to the townsfolk. Like selling bell tower postcards! Or opening up some little beverage stalls nearby!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Balmung">We could really liven up the place... Heck, we could make it a town landmark!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... You might be on to something there. <thought>Honestly, I really couldn't care less...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Next witness, continue the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Number Four...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looked like you were thinking about something...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">Well, yeah. It keeps bothering me. I saw footprints on the stairs. But...I didn't report that to the captain. Why didn't I do it? I didn't even know myself...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh...okay?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">But now I've come up with a possible explanation. Maybe, all this time...I've just been unconsciously... trying to undermine Boistrum's authority and take over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">When I think that I may be acting out such a devious plan as that...it makes me feel afraid of myself.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">Y-you ungrateful backstabber! You seriously mean to say that's what you were thinking about?!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Lyewood">I'm sorry, Chief. I think it's possible... The subconscious is a terrifying thing.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Boistrum">To be scheming behind my back! I've had enough! Draw your sword, Lyewood!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Guys, can you sort out your differences after the trial?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Mr Shakey...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you like to comment on your fellow Vigilante's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Shakey">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, don't worry about it... <thought>I'd better avoid speaking to him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Continue with the testimony. Next witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Number Six, may I have your attention?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">My attention is focused on something else. Can you be quiet and let me think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is a trial and I'm an attorney! You can't just silence me like that. ...What are you thinking about?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">............ I think, at some point...I will have to make a choice. A choice between the bell tower and my sweet Foxy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you talking about...?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Servius">When that time comes...I know what choice I'll make. It'll be my lovely Foxy! I'd like to avoid it, but no one can escape their fate... Scary, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Very, um, insightful... But I'm not sure I quite follow.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's leave it at that. Now then, I suggest we carry on with the interrogation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Ms Foxy...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">Hmmm? You want something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhm, I'd just...like to know what you were thinking about, if you don't mind sharing.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">I can feel everyone's eyes on me... It's giving me this tingly feeling. I'm such a naughty girl... I guess people just can't help wanting to look at me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhm, I'm not sure that's quite it. I think everyone's watching you because you're sitting on top of the witness stand...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If the stares make you uncomfortable, perhaps you could get down and stand with the others...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Foxy">No, no, no. You probably wouldn't know this, old man... but attention only makes a woman's beauty shine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh boy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhm, Number Eight...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">Yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you noticed anything you'd like to tell us about?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">If anything, I've got a question. Have YOU noticed it yet? That all people can be divided into two groups.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">There are those who trample and those who get trampled.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what...?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Treddon">The joys of treading and the joys of being trodden on... The most important thing in life is to discover happiness. Defender... I'd recommend you, too, lie down and submit yourself to Foxy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is this guy...still talking about being stepped on?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">You can get trampled all you want...AFTER the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, uhm, Number Nine...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Hoo mony times dae Ah hae tae teel ye, mah name's Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil! Ye hink ye can disrespect me, coz Aam a bairn?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, I didn't mean to offend you...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Mah faither was an airheid, but one day he took me tae th' side an' said: "Son, yer name comes frae a stoatin warriur. Ah hiner yoo'll become a stoatin warriur, tay, an' protect thes toon."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-is that right...?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Sae Aam daein' mah best tae become strang!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Silly child.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">Whit?!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">You think you were named after a great warrior? Don't make me laugh...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">But... But! Mah normally thooghtless faither...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Was just as thoughtless as usual when he made up such a random and ridiculous name. Do not attempt to see a reason where there is none.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">............ Ah see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Boy, Darklaw didn't just shatter his dreams, she OBLITERATED them...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ Listen well, child. It won't be any time soon... but perhaps one day your own deeds will bring a positive meaning upon your name.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Dzibilchaltunchunchucmil">............ Ah... Ah will... Ah will dae 'at fur sure!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow. She has a motivational side, too! That was impressive!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think she just realised she went too far and wanted to make up for it somehow...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Continue with the testimony. Next witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Mr Wordsmith...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">I do not know any Wordsmiths.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Mr Wordsmith...what do you think about the testimony we've just heard?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">Believe it or not, there was a time when I would struggle to remember... what, if anything, I had eaten the previous day. But now, I need no longer comb through my memory in vain. The answer is clear as the water on a crystal-clear lake. It was spaghetti!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh...what...?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">From where does this confidence stem? And to where does it periodically vanish? The answer to that question is simple and definitive. I have decided to eat only spaghetti. Spaghetti yesterday, spaghetti today and spaghetti tomorrow. Is that not the perfect solution? The days when I would fight a battle with my memory, nearly losing to it, weak as it is...are over. And so now I am on a green field, sky-clad, watching petals dancing in the wind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ So...you have serious memory problems. Do you remember anything?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante* Wordsmith">I do remember something. I can answer one question with utmost confidence. What did I have for dinner last night? ...Spaghetti.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I think it's safe to assume he can take on one more question. "What am I going to eat today?"</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There is no need to continue this trial. The accused's true identity has been proven beyond doubt. The court shall now issue the final verdict for Espella Cantabella!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is a crime to be a witch. We must do everything to erase magic from the world. Despicable witch! Into the flames with you!</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Are there any other puzzles you'd like to give a go?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">That was splendid!</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Any time you wish to try your hand at some puzzles, be sure to come and see me.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, that didn't go quite as I'd anticipated.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But if the puzzle is in this room, then it really must be something worth solving! Please try again, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Fear not, Luke. I'm not about to give up just yet.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Why would such a puzzle be necessary within his own room?</line>
</xml>