
<xml>
<title>The Rite of Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Warden">Wakey, wakey, 201. We've got some more questions.</line>
<line speaker="Rebel 1">Well, you know, with Datz back on the streets, things'll be on the up and up for us.</line>
<line speaker="Rebel 2">Keep your voice down! You WANT that rebel hunter to find us or something?</line>
<line speaker="Rebel 1">Come on. We're small fries compared to--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ahh... Another fine day in the Kingdom of Khura'in. ..................... It's so peaceful here... <thought>I can't believe it's been two weeks already, but... ...this place is really starting to grow on me. Still...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It sure was a rough start. Now, to do what I came here to do: To see Maya! Her long ascetic training is finally coming to an end. But before it does, she said something about one last rite she has to perform today.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Hap'piraki!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Ahlbi. Hap'piraki.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Oh, you've mastered the traditional greeting of Khura'in!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I don't know about that... <thought>But I guess all that practicing is paying off!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Have you gotten used to life at the temple?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm grateful they're letting me stay here, but the mornings start a little too early for me.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Ha ha ha! Yes, well, morning prayers do begin at dawn! After all, you can never pray too much! Daily devotion is very important here in Khura'in!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hats off to you guys. I don't know how you do it.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">And today's a special day, full of even more prayer than usual! There's nothing better in this world than being able to pray to your heart's content!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I... can think of a few things I'd rather do...</thought> So, what makes today so special anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">You mean you don't know?! Today's the Purification Rite! It's only performed once a year!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's what Maya must've been talking about on the phone yesterday. I wonder what her role in it is...</thought> ...So, what exactly is Maya going to be doing for this "Purification Rite"?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">What?! Didn't she tell you?! She's playing the role of Lady Kee'ra! It's only the most important part of the entire rite! It's unprecedented to have a foreigner play such a key role!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow, that's really something.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">It really is! Helping out such an amazing person... ...has been the greatest honor of this humble tour guide's life!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, who is this "Lady Kee'ra" you mentioned?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Allow me to explain! Once upon a time, hundreds upon hundreds of years ago... ...there lived a female warrior who fought valiantly to establish the Kingdom of Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let me stop you right there!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">...Is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, it's just... I get the feeling I'm in for a really long story.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Yeah... I'd say it normally takes around two hours to tell.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whew, dodged a bullet there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">...Oh, right! You're supposed to finally see Miss Maya today! The story can wait, then. In the meantime, you can read up on the rite with this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An English guidebook? Where did you dig this up from?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I found it just lying there in the temple library. I figured no one's using it, so I borrowed it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm? Hey! This book belongs to Maya. See, there's her name on the back. Guess there's no harm in keeping this for a while, then.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Miss Maya should already be at the site where the rite is to take place. Let's go! ...To the Plaza of Devotion!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if Maya's matured any since I last saw her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">It's on a mountaintop, so it might get a little cold, though!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think I can handle it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should offer a prayer now and then since they're letting me stay here. Hmm, let's see... May there be a slightly softer futon tonight. And may tomorrow's breakfast be a little bigger.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I'm impressed by your prayerful heart! Prayer is at the heart of Khura'inism, after all. May the Holy Mother's blessings be upon you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, uh... <thought>Now I feel kinda bad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are those buildings over there?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Those are training halls. Monks continuously undergo rigorous training there, day in and day out.  ...You could try it out for a day if you'd like. They do really interesting stuff -- like meditating while standing on their heads!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That's REALLY okay, Ahlbi! Thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is a really gorgeous spring.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">You have an excellent eye for beauty, sir! This is the Guiding Waters -- the centerpiece of our temple tour! It's a sacred pathway for people's mitamah, so don't ever wade into it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why? What would happen if I did?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I-I don't think we should even be talking about this. Just don't go in it, okay?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's the worst that could happen...? (B-But we're okay for now, right...? As long as we stay out of the water?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">There have been a lot more tourists this year than last.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then your tour guide business must be booming.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">It is! But I have more important things to do right now! Namely... helping you, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Let's head over to where the Purification Rite will be held.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What sort of rite is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Umm... We'd wind up missing a whole day of the rite if I were to explain it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In that case, I think I'll just go see it for myself...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Wooow! What a beautiful badge!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the attorney's badge we use in my country.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">It kind of looks like a sunflower to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yep, and I'm pretty sure there's even a reason for it.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Please do explain, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maybe next time. <thought>I should've known he'd ask me to explain...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Is this... some sort of new tourist souvenir?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but no.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry to be such a disappointment...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Brrr... I-I-It's s-s-so c-c-cold... <thought>It's like the air itself is made of ice.</thought> But look at all these people...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Well, this IS the day we come to offer prayers to Lady Kee'ra, the protector of our land. It's amazing to see how devoted everyone is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Devoted... Right... But couldn't they just as easily do all this praying someplace warmer?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">This, too, is a part of our religious training! It helps us build strength of spirit and willpower! Further up, at the end of those stairs, is the Inner Sanctum.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... Everyone I've met so far seems deeply religious.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Of course we are! After all, Khura'in is also known as the Land of Prayer. It's said that we Khura'inese spend an average of fifteen hours a day in prayer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! F-Fifteen...?!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">From the moment we wake, to the moment we fall asleep, our hearts are always in prayer. You see all the square flags around here? They're known as prayer flags. They contain the prayers of our people!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, he's talking about these colorful strips of cloth. There's something written on each one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Such piety is the glory of our people, and...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm afraid that story's going to have to wait for another time, Ahlbi... Maya should be here any minute now.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">...Oh, yeah, you're right! I can't wait to see Miss Maya again.</line>
<line speaker="???">...Pardon me, O noble traveler.</line>
<line speaker="???">How do you fare, Mr. Wright? It's been many a day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-And, uh, who might you be? M-Maya?!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Miss Maya! Hap'piraki!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hap'piraki, Ahlbi. And you, Mr. Wright... May the Holy Mother guide you on your journey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.........Oh, um, thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Hee hee! Long time no see, Nick! Well? Well? Did I surprise you with my act?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, you can say that again. <thought>This is Maya Fey. She's a spirit medium from Kurain Village back home. She was also my assistant for quite some time. ...But that was many years ago. Her ability to channel spirits saved me more times than I can count.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I sure miss those days. It was a ton of fun being the REAL boss of Wright &amp; Co. Law Offices!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now she's here, training to be the leader of Kurain Village and the master of her craft. Apparently, to become the master of the Kurain Channeling Technique... ...you have to train here in Khura'in, since this is where the technique originated.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Didn't I sound just like a pious nun when you saw me just now?! Too bad that's about all I learned from all the training I did.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha. You haven't changed a bit, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? And what's THAT supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She may look a little more mature on the outside, but inside, she's the same old Maya. ...I'm actually kind of glad for that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ahlbi said these are called prayer flags. And the prayers written on them are carried throughout the kingdom by the wind. Now, if I were to pray for something... ...it would be for me to not get dragged into any more trouble than I already have been.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What a magnificent gate. You can tell it leads to someplace sacred like the Inner Sanctum.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sadly,  only holy people are allowed through there. And here I am, hoping to show you just how amazing I've become during the rite today. All of that spiritual power I built up during my training is going to rush out like a raging river!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah... Just try not to overdo it, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow... No one's moved a muscle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Two days straight?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Glad I'm not them! AND that I get to be Lady Kee'ra!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>M-Maya...! Don't be rude!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You just hang in there, Nick. It's only two days, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't recall signing up for this part of the tour...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know what they say: "When in Rome"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now I understand the saying, "There's no place like home."</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I heard what happened, Nick! You ended up in court almost as soon as you got off the plane, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah well, it's kind of a long story.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I was the accused! But you should've seen Mr. Wright in action! He was amazing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha ha ha ha...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... I bet it was another one of your famous seat- of-your-pants, come-from-behind wins, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">W-Well... I WAS almost found guilty any number of times.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay, so it wasn't my finest hour. So sue me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You haven't changed a bit, either, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ouch. It definitely stings more when it's coming from her...</thought> So, I guess you've finished the bulk of the training needed to become the master, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, you mean the "Special Meditation Course for Increasing Spiritual Power"? Yep! I've completed the full two years! I can finally go home once I perform the Purification Rite today!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, I was wondering why they're having a foreigner conduct one of their sacred rites.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, the high priest's wife usually conducts it each year... ...but with her baby on the way, it's just more than she could handle. So the high priest practically begged me to stand in for her this year.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, you may not know all of their customs, but with your training, I'm sure you'll do great.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You bet! Just you watch, Nick! I'm going to be the best Lady Kee'ra: Guardian Diety ever!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd better throw in a few prayers for things to not end in a flaming disaster, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So about that guardian deity you'll be portraying today... What exactly are we talking about here?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, first of all, Lady Kee'ra isn't really a deity in the way we think of them back home. She's a real person who fought to establish the Kingdom of Khura'in a long, long time ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, so she actually existed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">And now the kingdom's people worship her as a guardian deity. They believe she appears to protect the kingdom whenever it's in danger. Cloaked in a sacred robe, she's a champion of justice who defeats the kingdom's enemies!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That sounds like something you'd be into.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I know, right?! Who wouldn't want to be a kick-butt warrior who takes on evil with a wicked dagger?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Right... Whatever floats your boat. Still, Lady Kee'ra must really be a popular deity if all these people are here for her.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yep. But there's more to it than just her popularity this year!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's more?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, why's this rite attracting such a large crowd this year?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Because there's been actual sightings. You know, of the real deal.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Allow me to explain! A mysterious figure clad in Lady Kee'ra's robes appeared, just like in the legends. And she began capturing members of the Defiant Dragons right and left!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You're kidding, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">They say it's only a matter of time till she gets their leader, the revolutionary Dhurke, too! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So Lady Kee'ra's a rebel hunter  now, huh...</thought> It's a bit hard to swallow though. I mean, even if they are trying to disrupt the peace... ...I doubt the actions of a band of rebels can bring a legendary figure back to life.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I didn't believe it at first, either. But there's a real picture of her on the front page of today's newspaper! Sightings of her go back about two years... ...but this is the first actual picture of her to ever be taken!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't believe someone was able to actually capture her on film...</thought> But couldn't this just be some Lady Kee'ra fan? You know, like you, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You mean like a cosplayer? Those rebels are no joke, Nick! They're trained in hand-to-hand combat and stuff! You think some regular cosplayer can take on people like that dressed in a costume, alone? That's why she HAS to be the real deal! It gives me chills just thinking about it! I bet Lady Kee'ra's spirit possessed the sacred robe or something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A spirit possessing a piece of clothing...? Umm... Maybe you should cut back on all those action-superhero shows, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't know who you're talking about, but that's definitely not me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">*sigh* You've really lost your edge since I last saw you. Those spikes of yours have grown really dull... and there's even one that's drooping!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Can we leave my hair out of this?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Anyway! I swear that the Lady Kee'ra people have been spotting is the REAL DEAL! Besides, it's just so much more fun to believe it's true, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't believe you really buy all that...  <thought>Although... I wonder who's under that robe.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">But, Mr. Wright! She's the talk of the town! She even gave me this great new food idea! It's gonna be like a soul bun, but based on Lady Kee'ra! I'm calling it the "Kee'ra Bun"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">T-Talk about a "Kee'ra" business strategy... Come on, Maya. Just admit it's you running around dressed as Lady Kee'ra already.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">! .................. Hee hee hee hee hee hee. I guess the jig is up!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">What?! I-Is it really true, Miss Maya?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Indeed! It is I... Lady Kee'ra! After hundreds of years, I have returned in this lovely young lady's body!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Whaaaaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Only a minion of the Defiant Dragons could see through my disguise! Now... feel my wrath, foul lawyer! Hi-yah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OWWW!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">M-Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Just kidding! I mean, come on. I may be dressing up as Lady Kee'ra for the rite today... ...but there's no way I could ever beat up one of those rebel-types!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't know... That was a pretty solid left hook she just threw.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">O-Oh! You were just trying to be funny! You really had me going there for a second!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No one can be THAT naïve, right...?</thought> Well, I hope you enjoy playing superhero at the rite today.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh, when you put it that way! I'm even more hyped about it now than I was already!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, hey! Congrats on getting your badge back, Nick! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now you can go back to a life of bold-facedly bluffing the day away, everyday!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's...  not exactly why I returned to the courtroom, you know...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! That's mine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it was just sitting there in the temple's library, so Ahlbi sorta checked it out for me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hope it comes in handy, then! Oh, and by the way... the Maya Library of Guidebooks has a $2-a-day "donation" policy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I hear the sound of the high priest's footsteps. I'd better get going.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His footsteps?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">During the rite, he wears these really big bells on his ankles. That way I know he's coming. Pretty handy, right? Well, see you later!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I doubt they're actually meant to be a "stop slacking" warning system for you, Maya...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Miss Maya is always so bright and cheerful!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I'm glad to see she hasn't changed. <thought>As in, at all... I wonder if this means her training's been all for naught... I hope not.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Ah, it's Acolyte Zeh'lot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Acolyte Zeh'lot...?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Look, he's the one praying in the red and saffron robe. He's a disciple of the high priest, Abbot Inmee, and lives and trains at his house. See how he prays in the cold without moving a muscle? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, I could never do that...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Ah, it's Abbot Inmee! The Purification Rite is about to begin! </line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Please, sir,  it's not a good idea to stare like that. You could be struck blind!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just give me a few more seconds. I mean, this isn't something you see every day... ...Oh, those bells on the high priest's ankles... they're a lot bigger than I thought they'd be.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Mr. Wright! It's time to enter the prayer pose like everyone else. Those who don't will suffer the wrath of the Holy Mother!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, let's see... First, I kneel down and cross my ankles, and then I bow forward... Youch! Great... Now all I can see is the ground, and my back is killing me!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">You really should have trained for this, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait a sec... How long are we supposed to stay like this, Ahlbi?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">The rite requires that we stay like this... until the day after tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That's two whole days! Nngh... I don't feel so...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">M-Mr. Wright! Are you okay, sir?! S-Somebody, heeelp!</line>
<line speaker="???">...ster... Wri... Mist... ...ight? Mister Wright! Please, you have to get up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh... Ouch, my aching...! ...Hm? Where are we?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">The high priest's house at the foot of the Plaza of Devotion!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I passed out from that back pain. They must've carried me all the way here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Something terrible's happened! It's Miss Maya! She's... She's... Ooh, justfollow me to the Plaza of Devotion!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something must've happened while I was passed out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*huff* *puff* <thought>Where's Maya?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Just take it easy, all right!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-But I'm telling you! I-I... I haven't done anything wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Hmph. You can talk all you want back at the station.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">L-Let me go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! I didn't kill him! I swear I didn't!</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Quiet, you! Come along peacefully or suffer the consequences!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-W-Wait a second! What on earth is going on?!</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">I don't know who you are, but if you don't get out of my way--!</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey! Back off, officer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Ema? Ema Skye?! <thought>What's she doing in Khura'in?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm so sorry, Mr. Wright... but we're placing Maya under arrest. All right, take her down to the station! But with respect -- got it?!</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Yes, ma'am!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Niiiiiiiiiiiiiick!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what are you doing in Khura'in, Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's a long story. Anyway, what are YOU doing in Khura'in, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Same here -- it's a long story. But we can get caught up later. Right now, I need to know what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Maya's... well... under arrest for the murder of the high priest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, the high priest was... murdered?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a befitting gate for the path to the Inner Sanctum.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's apparently considered a sacred object to the people of Khura'in. I wasn't even allowed to dust it for prints.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, even applying a little fingerprint dust to it would be sacrilegious, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I guess so... But I applied some luminol on it instead when no one was looking!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sounds like an invitation for the Holy Mother to strike you down later, Ema.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow... Even with the murder, all these people are still here, praying.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">They're so into it, they wouldn't notice anything you did to them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean like... taking their fingerprints?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh?! Oh, um, who would ever do something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ema... You didn't...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Acolyte Zeh'lot is really in the zone.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, you mean that monk who's been living at the victim's home? Yeah, he hasn't moved a muscle, even though his teacher has been murdered.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess he's so deep in prayer, he's not aware of what's going on around him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What happened, Ema? Please,  tell me everything you can.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, basically, here was a murder during the rite as it was being performed last night. The victim is Tahrust Inmee, the high priest who was presiding over the rite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, hold on! "Last night"...? You mean to tell me, an entire day's passed since the Purification Rite?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">That's right, sir. You passed out for a whole day from your back pain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I never knew my back's like a ticking time bomb... I'd better take better care of it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">The murder took place at the Inner Sanctum where the rite was being held.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Inner Sanctum...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">It's the place where the spirit of Lady Kee'ra is enshrined! It's through that gate over there and up at the top of the mountain stairs just beyond!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, so that's why everyone is offering their prayers in that direction...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Abbot Inmee and Miss Maya went up to the Inner Sanctum to begin the rite... ...just after they finished the prayer you fainted in the middle of.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, who do you think killed the high priest?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Unfortunately, Maya is our sole suspect right now. During the rite, the Inner Sanctum was off-limits to the general public.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So then, only the high priest and Maya could have been there when the murder occurred?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Right. Plus, the Inner Sanctum is on the side of a very steep mountain. The only way up there is the stairway that starts here at the Plaza of Devotion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's why she's been arrested.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Also, the crime scene was only discovered after Maya came down alone. She's the one who told the worshippers in the plaza that the high priest was dead. ...And she made a police statement to that </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So she was the first one to discover the body... Well, that definitely doesn't help. That makes it even less likely that someone else was there at the crime scene.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Mr. Wright, sir... Are you going to defend Miss Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, of course. There's no way she killed anyone.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Y-Yeah! I don't believe it, either! She's been framed! But this is really something else, huh, Mr. Wright? I mean, who'd have thought you'd have to take on that horrible court again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Tell me about it. I never thought I'd have to go through another trial... ...where the Divination Séance determines all, and defense lawyers are unwelcome.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what brings you here, Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Back in the U.S., I was working a case with an international prosecutor from Khura'in. He told me this is where I could see the latest techniques in international forensic science. I can't believe I fell for it! I mean, just look at this place. It's like we've gone back in time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, I can't say I've been impressed with the police work I've seen so far...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Ema">Still, he said he takes on cases from around the world... ...so maybe next time, he'll have one in a major city somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sounds like this prosecutor has taken a liking to you, Ema. After all, it's not every day a prosecutor takes a detective with them overseas.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I wonder... He's calm, and kind, and almost always has a smile on his face... ...but it's hard to tell what he's really thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This international prosecutor...  Is he the one who handled Trucy's case?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes, he is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I take it he'll be the prosecutor on this one, too?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi's already been assigned...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">P-Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?! Pohlkunkaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know him, Ahlbi?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Of course! Everyone in Khura'in does. He's a highly revered individual, both as a prosecutor and a monk! If you go up against Prosecutor Sahdmadhi... you'll incur the Holy Mother's wrath!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But it's my job to, as a lawyer...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Oh, right! Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just great... A prosecutor who's also a revered monk in a deeply religious country...</thought>  <thought>This trial's shaping up to be even more uniquely Khura'inese than the last one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm not sure I should be saying this, but he's a formidable opponent.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I heard Apollo had a really tough time, so I'd better give it everything I've got. Anyway, I'm glad you're here, Ema. hey treat lawyers like criminals here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? Are you sure you aren't going to get in trouble for helping "the enemy"...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">*gulp* He did come down on me pretty hard when I tried to help Trucy in that last trial... .................. Let's just say... I'll help where I can!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-Thanks. But don't go getting yourself in trouble on my account, okay? <thought>Prosecutor Sahdmadhi sounds pretty strict.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, first things first. Let's start with this. Hot off the press, it's the high priest's autopsy report!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The victim bled to death from a deep stab wound to the abdomen. The murder weapon is believed to be Lady Kee'ra's Warbaa'd Dagger. It's used during the rite, however, the dagger has yet to be found.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lady Kee'ra's dagger, huh... <thought>I think Maya mentioned something about a dagger...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Maya">Who wouldn't want to be a kick-butt warrior who takes on evil with a wicked dagger?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Right... Whatever floats your boat.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... And isn't that rebel hunter posing as Lady Kee'ra also armed with a dagger? Of course, hers must be a replica, right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Congrats on your return to the legal world! I wanted to congratulate you sooner, but I never had the chance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Ema. And congratulations to you, too, on becoming a forensic investigator.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Heh heh, thanks. Oh, I know! Let's celebrate by dusting your attorney's badge for fingerprints! Or how about we do a luminol test on it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think I'll pass on both, but thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The victim's name was Tahrust Inmee. He bled to death from a stab wound in the abdomen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the killer?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">At the moment, our only suspect is the person who was with the victim at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In other words, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's been ages since you've presented evidence to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Remember when we worked that one case together? I seem to recall a thin layer of fingerprint powder on every piece of evidence then...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">W-Well...! I guess they get that way from time to time now, too...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As enthusiastic as ever, huh, Ema.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would it be okay for me to go take a look at the crime scene, Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The police have already wrapped up their investigation... ...but the location itself is off-limits to the general public, so I'm not sure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ema, please! I'm begging you! Just like the police, I need access if I'm to mount a viable defense.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...All right, then. Leave it to me! I'll explain the situation to Prosecutor Sahdmadhi and the police later. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Ema!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You have quite a climb ahead of you, so be sure to watch your step!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Wait, you're not coming with me?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">O-Oh, no, I'm not climbing up there again. No way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-Is it really that bad? I wonder if my back can handle it...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">You get to go to the Inner Sanctum?! Oh, you're so lucky, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why don't you join me, Ahlbi?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Th-Th-That's crazy talk, sir! If a commoner like myself were to set foot in there, I'd surely be cursed for all eternity!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because the Inner Sanctum is off-limits for you, huh... Oh, well... Guess I'll just have to face this all by my lonesome. By the way, what about all the people still praying here? Aren't they going to go home?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The customs of this rite require that they not move from this spot until tomorrow afternoon. It doesn't faze them to have police milling about. Some of them are even off-duty cops.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not a Khura'inist, but maybe if I prayed with all my might... ...the Holy Mother will help me... Who am I kidding? I have to figure out how to solve this case myself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can hear the monks' prayers all the way over here. Maybe the Holy Mother would answer mine if I slipped it in with theirs. Here goes... "Please let me save Maya Fey!"</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I look a little haggard in my reflection. It's like the water's showing me how I feel on the inside... ...Wait, what am I doing?! I have to stay strong, especially for Maya.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I still can't believe there was a murder during the Purification Rite... Could it have been an act of divine justice by Lady Kee'ra?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Divine justice, huh... <thought>We wouldn't need a trial if that's what it was.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Oh, no! Maybe I'm next for coming up with my "Kee'ra Buns"! P-Please, Lady Kee'ra! I meant no disrespect!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, I don't think that's a terrible enough of a crime to be divinely punished for, Ahlbi...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">We don't have time for chit-chat, Mr. Wright! We have to prove Miss Maya's innocence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. Let's hurry back to the Plaza of Devotion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like Maya is still being questioned. I'll just have to come back again later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a bell here. I wonder if it's for calling the guard.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Don't do that unless you need something, you lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry! <thought>I didn't even get to say anything!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why does that guard keep eyeballing me? I can't let him get to me... I can't let him get to me... Ack! He's doing it again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Brrrr... I-It's really high up, and really, really c-c-cold. What did I do to deserve this? At least I made it. I'd better get started while I can still feel my fingers. <thought>...Hm? Who's that? It kind of looks like...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>.........Hmm. I should probably at least say hi to her before I start my investigation... Not that I want to, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Ah! It's you...! Do you even know where you are, Barbed Head?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course, I do. May I ask why you're here, Your Benevolence?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I came to pray for the high priest's soul. But what are YOU doing here? This is one of the most sacred spots in Khura'inism! Unscrupulous lawyers such as you have no business being here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I'm not "unscrupulous"...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Quiet! You dared to find fault with my Insights at every turn the other day!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's STILL sore about that trial...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hm? Why do you keep looking away?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was thinking about investigating the crime scene...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Well, you can do so later! You are speaking with me right now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>As you wish, princess... I guess the investigation will have to wait until she's done talking at me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As you know, Your Benevolence, a murder has occurred, and I need to investigate--</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">But we know the killer is one of your own!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In my country, suspects are innocent until proven guilty. Plus, she is a serious student of spirit channeling who came here to study. So, can't you at least give her a chance to explain what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">All practitioners from overseas are big... big... phony baloneys! And her wish to train in the homeland of spirit channeling is but a bid for prestige.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh. It seems like nothing I say will convince her otherwise, thanks to that last trial. Tweedledum and Tweedledee really did a number on her impression of foreigners.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As the defense attorney on this case... ...I really need to investigate this crime scene -- and I need to do it now. I've even been authorized by the police, so...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...What's this?! Y-You intend to make a mockery of our sacred Hall of Justice once more?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, I simply want to defend my client.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Which means, you have come to forge evidence, then! I knew all lawyers were criminals! I must now redouble my vigilance!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ouch, that's unfair. Who taught you to demonize a whole group of people anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">My mother and father! Do you have an issue with their parental guidance?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No... I would never dare criticize the royal couple... <thought>I still can't imagine what the lawyers here must've done to garner such hatred...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmmmmm ............... Oh, ho! Heh heh heh. I just had the most wonderful idea, Barbed Head.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I have a bad feeling about that glint in her eye?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... what's this most wonderful idea of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">If you are to investigate this murder... ...then I shall oversee your every move, so as to prevent any misdeeds, naturally. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! You want to follow me around the entire time?!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Of course. Not that I want to, mind you. And I will not tolerate any objections, understood?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sh-She can't do this to me...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What was that, Barbed Head?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, n-no! It's nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Very well, then. Let us get this investigation over with. We mustn't stay here in the Inner Sanctum a moment longer than necessary.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Please don't rush me.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It is not without reason that I insist on a speedy investigation, Barbed Head. I am a direct descendant of the Holy Mother, you see, who guides the people of Khura'in. As such, I must not sully myself with the blood of battle that Lady Kee'ra bears.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The blood of battle...?</thought> If it's that big of a problem, why don't you head on down now? I won't do anything, I promise.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">No. Lawyers are never to be trusted! Now, make haste, so that we may leave here soon! ...Oh, and one more thing!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Your victory the other day was but a stroke of fortune! But this time, my Insights shall reveal the absolute truth! So brace yourself for a defeat most bitter, lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I will. Now can I get on with my investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">As long as you know where we stand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sigh* I'd better hurry up and poke around for clues before she changes her mind...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hm?! What is that badge you bear?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a sunflower pin. They're quite popular in my country.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmm... It IS rather cute, I must say. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, it's just my attorney's badge.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Oh? So you mean it would have actually been worth more as a cheap accessory?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-My profession is worth more than $1.20, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That is a book from your land, is it not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, it's a guidebook about Khura'in that was written by people back home.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Oh? So there are people in your land who know of our fair kingdom. Then I imagine it must say something about me in there, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, yes. It says the Dance of Devotion is performed by an adorable little princess...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">H-How dare they write of me as though I were a child!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, I'm just reading what it says... <thought>Though, she does seem secretly pleased...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What a dreadful way to die...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you know the high priest, Your Benevolence?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, he was a pious priest of Khura'inism. As such, he had the trust of the entire kingdom.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The entire kingdom...? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes. But what do you know of faith and trust? You, who can never hope to match his virtue. It is like comparing the moon to a pebble, or the sea to a puddle!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How did this suddenly become a game of "Pin the Diss on the Lawyer"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A dahma for your thought?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Ugh! Get that thing away from me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, I'll just put it away, then.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Who told you to put it away? How am I to inspect it if you do that?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Keep it out, put it away -- I wish she'd make up her mind...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I turn back now, I'll have to climb all the way back up here again later... *sigh* Guess I'll have to make Princess Rayfa see things my way somehow...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What an amazing wall painting! So this is Lady Kee'ra...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Do you see that red mark upon her brow? That is the character for death in Khura'inese. It is a mark of resolve to fight to the end. There are many different marks we make on our bodies, each with a different meaning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, interesting... Come to think of it, Your Benevolence has marks on your face. So did the high priest.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The high priest's marks are those of a monk, while mine are of a royal priestess. All members of the Khura'inist clergy have such marks upon them. The shape and location of the marks vary in accordance to conditions like status and age. And all records about them are kept at Tehm'pul Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So it's kind of like a national ID registry, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that a weapon in her hand?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, it is Lady Kee'ra's dagger -- the very same one used in the rite. It is made to resemble a warbaa'd, the bird Lady Kee'ra fashioned herself after.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that dagger is the weapon that took the high priest's life...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">If you wish to know more about Lady Kee'ra, you need but ask.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I get the feeling she's going to be super relevant to this case... I should definitely ask the princess for more details later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This wall painting really is amazing, no matter how many times I look at it.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Do you see that red mark upon her brow? That is the character for death in Khura'inese. It is a mark of resolve to fight to the end.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, interesting... Come to think of it, Your Benevolence has marks on your face. So did the high priest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So it's kind of like a national ID registry, huh. Is that a weapon in her hand?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, it is Lady Kee'ra's dagger -- the very same one used in the rite. It is made to resemble a warbaa'd, the bird Lady Kee'ra fashioned herself after.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that dagger was the murder weapon, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This mountain face is like a towering wall. There are characters carved into it,  but I have no idea what they mean.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">There is a prison at the apex of this mountain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A prison? Way up there?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It is said that Lady Kee'ra laid those she defeated to rest atop this mountain... ...so that their souls would not spawn evil spirits.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm feeling queasy just thinking about being all the way up there... <thought>And the fact that it's a prison just makes it worse.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">During the rite, the Inner Sanctum was fully enclosed by this ritual curtain... ...making this case something of a locked-room mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The Purification Rite is akin to a bathing ritual for Lady Kee'ra. Therefore, it must be closed off from the outside world.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, so the Inner Sanctum is like her private bathroom.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Indeed. So see to it that you keep it clean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This flap in the center acts as the ritual curtain's door, but that's about it.</thought> Eek! </line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">And what was that shrill scream for just now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-It's just... I'm afraid of heights. <thought>I didn't notice it as I was climbing up, but now that I can see all the way down... *gulp*</thought> I guess that flight of stairs from the Plaza of Devotion really is the only way up or down...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's take a closer look, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa! <thought>Th-This is blood!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">.........This is a statue of a warbaa'd, the bird on which Lady Kee'ra based her appearance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And all of this blood is from the high priest, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">He no doubt embraced the statue in the hope that Lady Kee'ra would save him from death. May his soul rest in peace.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Considering the amount of blood, he must've been stabbed with considerable force. But there's no way Maya would be strong enough to deliver such a blow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's been stained red by the high priest's blood.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">"The spring shall run red upon Lady Kee'ra's return."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's that from?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...An old legend.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait. Does that mean... ...that the rebel-hunting Lady Kee'ra in the newspaper is the real deal? ...Nah. That's crazy talk.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, isn't this Lady Kee'ra's robe?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">O Holy Mother! Lady Kee'ra's robe is...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know how you feel, but we should leave it as is to preserve the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You imbecile! This is the actual robe Lady Kee'ra once wore!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-It is?! What the heck is it made of? I mean, nothing should look this good after a few hundred years!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...............Enough! If I say it's the actual robe, it IS the actual robe! That foul murderer shall not get away with this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It is tough to see a piece of history sloppily tossed on the ground like this, though... It even looks like it's been mended a number of times.</thought> ...Hm? This robe kinda smells...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">How dare you insult such a sacred piece of clothing like that?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, I meant that it smells like incense.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Oh, I see. The scent you detected is from the sacred incense used to purify Lady Kee'ra's robe. Whenever a rite is to be performed, the robe is first scented with sacred incense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If this still smells like incense now... ...the scent must have been much stronger last night when the victim was killed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A bloodstained scrap of paper... Looks like some kind of note or letter, perhaps? But it's written in Khura'inese, so I can't read a lick.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Let me see that. ".........once the flame is lit, then......... ...........................will be..." This is simply impossible to read! ...Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it?!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">This stamp in the lower right! It's the mark of those insurgents -- Defiant Dragons!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's it doing here? Is there some kind of a connection between the high priest and the rebels?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a statue of a bird... I should take a closer look later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, the bird's missing its eye. I feel sorry for the poor fella.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Are you the one who took it?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course not!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. This statue has been here for ages. I suppose some damage is to be expected. I shall ask my mother to have it repaired.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No wonder there are no lawyers left. I'd leave, too, if I was always treated like this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think I'd better go take a closer look.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no snow here. Maybe it was removed because it would interfere with the rite?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The day before the rite, the temperature in this area plunged below freezing. Even the Plaza of Devotion was covered in a layer of white frost.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Must be the elevation. It wasn't all that cold back in town, as I recall.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This lantern is damaged. <thought>The wind guard is completely broken.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Damaged? Was this your doing?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-N-No! I didn't even touch it!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph! Then perhaps a falling rock struck it. I will request that it be repaired when we are finished here. Of course, I doubt you will live long enough to see it restored.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'll be back to take a look! You'll see!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a lantern. ...Hm? And it's still lit.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Of course it is. The sacred flames in the four lanterns here have burned for centuries. Anyone who extinguishes even one of them would be put to death immediately.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's why they're outfitted with glass wind guards. Still, I'd better keep my distance... Just in case.</thought> So the moon and these lanterns were the only sources of light up here that night?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The rite is performed by the light of the full moon because moonlight is a purifying force.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">No touching!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I wasn't going to!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This rock must've fallen from higher up on the mountain. It's like the perfect perch for taking a peek over that curtain... Well, up I go! Wow, what an incredible view! It almost... boggles the mind...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Get down from there this instant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Right! Sorry! I'll be right down. <thought>It looks like the Inner Sanctum is just slightly higher up than the top of that mountain.</thought> ...I guess that confirms that the stairs from the Plaza of Devotion is the only way up here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm? There's something hanging off of the ritual curtain there... These look like those prayer flags down at the Plaza of Devotion.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Except, they are arranged like no prayer flags I have ever seen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How so?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">All of these flags have been sewn together.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, you're right. It's like they're one big banner now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That lantern looks broken, but it's hard to make out the details from this angle. I'll take a closer look when I'm in a better spot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me about this place, Your Benevolence?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...I have nothing to say to you, lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that because you don't actually know much about it...?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You ill-mannered--! I am the crown princess of Khura'in! There is nothing I do not know! ...Nayna!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoa! Where'd she come from?!</thought> ...Hey! No cheating!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Silence, Barbed Head! Nayna's knowledge is my knowledge. End of discussion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is she, your pocket internet?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">This spring is where Lady Kee'ra came to cleanse her body of the blood of battle. And today's Purification Rite is a ceremony that traces its origins back to those days. Cleansing Lady Kee'ra's robe in this sacred water lends one courage for the next battle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I see. Thank you for that excellent explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Commoners are normally barred from here, except for the day of the rite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who normally controls the access to this place?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The high priest and his family are responsible for that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">high priest and his family, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me about the high priest and his family?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Abbot Inmee lived with his wife and his disciple, Acolyte Puhray Zeh'lot... ...a young man the couple took into their home upon finding him near our kingdom's border.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Speaking of his wife, isn't she the one who usually plays the role of Lady Kee'ra?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, but as she is with child, the role was appointed to someone else. The killer no doubt offered to stand in, as she saw it as a chance to slay the high priest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, you have it backwards. He was the one who asked Maya to stand in.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Then that braggart must have embellished her qualifications.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm really not sure how she could. Besides, why didn't you stand in for the high priest's wife, then?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Did I not tell you before? As a direct descendant of the Holy Mother, the role of Lady Kee'ra is forbidden to me. For those descended of Her Holiness must not defile their bodies with the blood of battle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, yeah... You did say that, didn't you? <thought>I should probably talk with the high priest's wife and Acolyte Zeh'lot later, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, so could you tell me more about this Lady Kee'ra?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">As an outsider I suppose your ignorance is all but unavoidable.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whatever happened to "you need but ask"?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Nayna! Lady Kee'ra was the Holy Mother's younger sister. But unlike her older sister, she lacked the ability to channel spirits. However, it is said that none could equal her skill with the dagger. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A dagger? Well, this became relevant fast.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The Holy Mother guides our souls, and Lady Kee'ra keeps the peace with her dagger. Lady Kee'ra was prepared to die for her people. She cloaked herself in a sacred battle robe, and concealed her face as her sister did.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, but who was she fighting against?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Throughout our history, we have been set upon by rebels... Now is no different. For our enemy now is the Defiant Dragons, led by that insurgent Dhurke.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So Lady Kee'ra played a role akin to the police, huh? So what's with the bird imagery?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Lady Kee'ra's robe is fashioned in the likeness of a warbaa'd. It is a fearsome bird that is unique to Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I have heard about her, but I have yet to ascertain the truth. However, I believe her to be a vigilante -- or more precisely, a patriot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The snow has obviously been cleared away here, and the lantern is broken. I still have that camera I brought to take pictures of my trip. I should snap one of this area here  just in case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That about does it for the Inner Sanctum... Hmm... I should probably head back to the Plaza of  Devotion, and let Ema know I'm done. After all, she's the one putting her neck on the line for me to investigate this place.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The guard will come over if I ring this, right?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. I have no need for such an implement. .........Guard!</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Yes, Your Benevolence?! It is my honor to be at your service!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Now, you try it, Barbed Head.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, uh... Okay.... Um, Mr. Guard? Could I please speak with you?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">.........Tsk!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It seems he will not respond to a lawyer's call.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Somehow, I saw that coming a mile away.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The killer must have been the one they call Maya Fey. There can be no other.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You never know. It's still pretty early in the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. She has spent time in the company of lawyers, so she must have a wicked soul.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Thanks for reminding me how much people like me are hated in this country...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It is only by the Holy Mother's mercy that you are allowed to investigate this sacred place. Remember that, and give thanks to Her Holiness for this great blessing at once!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, um... Thank you, Your... Holy Motherness! <thought>Er, that didn't come out right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That seemed a little insincere. Shall we halt this investigation immediately?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, wait! I'm grateful! Really!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmm, I wonder...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh... This is going to be worse than walking on holy eggshells.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Well? Are you going to conduct your investigation or not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I will! I-It's just... are you going to keep following me around like this?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Of course! Unless you intend to do something you feel the need to hide?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No! I do everything by the book!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Then get on with it. I am not doing this for fun, you know. I, too, have many duties I need to attend to.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Then why don't you go do them instead of hovering over me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hm? What is that look you are giving me? Am I perhaps, being bothersome?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, don't be absurd! <thought>You're being INCREDIBLY bothersome...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow... They're STILL praying!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The religious devotion of our people is the pride of our kingdom. Come what may, they will continue to pray until tomorrow afternoon.</line>
<line speaker="???">You there! Wait. I want to ask ya something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Okay...</line>
<line speaker="???">Do ya know me? And do I know you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, well... I-I'm Phoenix. Phoenix Wright. I'm a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="???">No, no...! I wanna know if ya know who I am!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Huh? How should I know? I've never even seen you before. <thought>This guy's acting really strange. I wonder if he has amnesia or something? I should talk to him a little more, just in case he's connected to this case somehow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, are you having trouble remembering who you are? Ack! I-I'm sorry if I offended you! <thought>Whew! I thought he was going to pull a weapon on me! But he's just pulling some snack out one after another.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">I'm trying to remember what I'm supposed to do. I know it's something important...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No! I just said I've never seen him before, didn't I?!</line>
<line speaker="???">...Are you Lady Kee'ra?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You know of Lady Kee'ra? Then you are Khura'inese, I take it?</line>
<line speaker="???">*chomp, chomp*... Maybe...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait... Are those LIZARDS he's eating?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">What? Ya want one?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No thanks! I, uh... I just ate!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, now I remember! Get a load of this! ...Well?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.........W-Well, what?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...I believe he suffers from a far more serious malady than mere memory loss.</line>
<line speaker="???">...No good, huh? Guess I'll try somebody else!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah! M-My head...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Are you okay? <thought>Did he remember something?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...My head... is so itchy! Har har har har har har!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is with this guy...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">So, who was that man, and what did he want, Barbed Head?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wish I knew.</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey! Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! What now?!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What's wrong? I didn't surprise you THAT badly, did I?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, no, it's nothing. Actually, I've been looking for you. I wanted to tell you I investigated the crime scene. I hope it wasn't too much trouble getting my investigation of the Inner Sanctum approved.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, it was fine. Prosecutor Sahdmadhi gave his okay straight away.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, he seems like a rather fair-minded prosecutor.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">He said that you would probably give up once you saw the crime scene for yourself. ...And that moving on before the trial began would be the smart thing to do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>.........He must be feeling really confident about his case.</thought> Well, just so you know, I have no intention of giving up.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I figured! That's why I've prepared a little gift for you! I thought it might help your investigation. Here, it's all yours! I wanted to bring you a bunch of other forensic tools... ...but they were confiscated at the airport.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Luminol testing fluid... This actually might come in handy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Also, I made a copy of the crime scene photo for you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks. All of this will definitely come in handy. <thought>So this is what the high priest's body looked like after the murder... I'll keep this along with the picture I took at the crime scene.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, yeah! They're done questioning Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? I should go pay her a visit, then! <thought>Poor Maya. She must be feeling pretty lonely. I should let her know that I'll be defending her, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, shoot! Look at the time! I have to get going.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You sure seem busy.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's because His Ephemeral Holiness is a real slave driver.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"His Ephemeral Holiness"...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Prosecutor Sahdmadhi. He's like the world's hardest riddle, wrapped in a flowy sash. I keep wondering if it's just a clash-of-cultures type of thing, you know? Like, he'll ask the most insane things of me without batting a single, long eyelash of his!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, this Prosecutor Sahdmadhi sounds like he's used to holding some serious clout...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Argh! Why do I have such bad luck with prosecutors! First it was the glimmerous fop. And now that I'm finally rid of that grating, bling-loving Europhile, I get this guy! Oh, no! Now I'm really going to be late! He'll probably make me listen to one of those really long sutras again. I'll see you later!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He makes her listen to sutras? Sounds like Ema's got it pretty rough, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">She does not appreciate Prosecutor Sahdmadhi's sutras? What ingratitude. It appears that she, too, is lacking in religious devotion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that's what the problem is here. Besides, Ema's not even a Khura'inist.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...To think I would witness a lawyer being allowed to pass through this sacred gate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, well, I wouldn't unless I had to. Those stairs were brutal to climb...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What's this?! Do you even know how many monks would give their lives to pass through that gate?! Be thankful for the great honor you have been afforded!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Benevolence!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It's called "their absolute devotion to Lady Kee'ra."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you don't have to pray to her, Your Benevolence?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Our customs dictate that I must never associate myself with Lady Kee'ra in any way. Instead, it is my duty to offer my prayers and dance to the Holy Mother every day. Why don't you try offering up a dance or two? I think you'll find it quite uplifting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No thanks! I'm good!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Acolyte Zeh'lot is still focused on his prayers.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Is not such devotion worthy of commendation? Still, he has not yet learned of the high priest's death. When I think of how he will learn of it once his prayers are over...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, it does seem cruel, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That man we just met... He seemed quite suspicious to me. Don't tell me he is an acquaintance of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not everyone who's suspicious is friends with a lawyer, or vice versa, you know. For example, I have many upstanding friends and acquaintances, like a chief prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Well, as long as your friends are free from the taint of corruption.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They are! <thought>And not everything is about good and evil!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Are you going to speak with that woman?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you mean Maya, then yes. There's something I need to talk to her about.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Something like... a jailbreak?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And how exactly could we do that with you and a guard watching us like hawks?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! I knew you'd come!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya... She sure looks tired.</thought> How are you holding up?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It wasn't me... But no one will believe me. Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have to admit, I'm still a bit in shock. Who'd have thought you'd get caught up in something like this? And so far from home? But I'm going to defend you, so hang in there. We can do this if we work together.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">.............................. Nngh... This is all my fault. I mean, you came to Khura'in just to visit me. We hadn't seen each other in ages, and then, this happens.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I haven't seen her this down in ages, either.</thought> Come on! Remember who you're talking to. Besides, I'd thought you'd be used to being the usual suspect by now!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">! Ha ha ha... I guess you're right. And you've saved me each and every time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup, so just tell me everything you can and let's go from there.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head! Stop stalling and go straight to the matter of true import! We know she is the murderer! Therefore, it is time for her confession!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-Your Benevolence... What brings the royal priestess to a place like this?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I am watching over this lawyer to keep him from tampering with anything in this case. Now, out with it! Confess to your crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Please, Your Benevolence. Could you please take it down a notch or three...?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, please tell me what you can. I know this must be difficult, but anything you can remember might help.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">S-Sure, okay...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I didn't kill the high priest. I wouldn't even dream of it... I mean, he always treated me so well. Abbot Inmee was an important figure with a ton of duties, including training acolytes. He was really kind, even to a foreigner like me. He even invited me over to his house whenever I was between training sessions. How could I ever kill someone like that?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He sounds like a really good person. <thought>I think I would've liked him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It was so much fun. I got to enjoy meals with his family and everything. And his wife was a master of Khura'inese cuisine! I've never eaten better in my life!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's like they were her family, and home away from home in this foreign land. They must've been a source of comfort, what with being here for training all alone.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">........................... But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But what?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...I can't completely deny the charge, either.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">As I suspected! The snake has shown her true colors at last!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Benevolence, please! I'm trying to figure out what really happened here.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Nngh... Hmph!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what do mean, you can't completely deny the charge?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-Well... during the Purification Rite... ...I suddenly got really, really sleepy. The next thing I knew, Abbot Inmee was... you know...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You suddenly got sleepy? So then, you didn't actually see the high priest get murdered?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No, I didn't, but... ...if I was possessed by some crazed spirit while I was asleep... then...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What an excuse. How dare you pin your crime on another person's soul?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. Be honest: What you call "training" is but an extended vacation in reality. And that "training" here is simply for prestige.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-No! It's not like that at all!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm training to become the master of the Kurain Channeling Technique.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. A neophyte practitioner such as you become a channeling master? I think not. The spiritual power required is beyond the means of an outsider like you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Rayfa seems to really hate fakers... ...but Maya does actually have the power to channel spirits. I should let Rayfa know.</thought> Your Benevolence. I wouldn't call Maya a neophyte, because... ...she can already cha--</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ahhh! Wait, wait, wait, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... Can I talk to you for a second?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why is she whispering all of a sudden?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I want to keep my spirit channeling ability a secret while I'm here, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'll, um... explain later. Just, keep it a secret for now, okay?! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you say so... <thought>What's that all about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What is all that whispering about over there?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, i-it's nothing, really. <thought>I'll have to ask about this later when Princess Rayfa's not around.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I almost forgot! Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">About Abbot Inmee's murder... There was something I noticed that I thought strange...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what was it you noticed?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well... ...you probably won't believe me, but....</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why don't you let me be the judge of that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay... So, you know that spring?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The spring? You mean the pool in front of the warbaa'd statue?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes, that! The water in there... was dark red!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And when I say "dark" red,  I mean "blood" red!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, that? Yeah, I saw it, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You did?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. The high priest's blood turned it red.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What? No, that's not what I meant! The spring was red before he was killed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What? Wait, so it was already red? Even before the high priest was killed?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! I noticed it during the the Purification Rite -- just before I passed out. It's just like the ancient legend says...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What "ancient legend"?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"The spring shall run red upon Lady Kee'ra's return." That's how it goes, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hold on! Yes, there is a legend about the Inner Sanctum that says just that. But the water runs red this time thanks to the murder. The police investigation confirmed it. Perhaps your eyes were deceived by the lantern light reflecting off of the water.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-I don't think that was it, though...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An ancient legend, huh...? I wonder if it's connected to this murder, somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">........................ Um, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So... Uhh... Actually, there's one more thing...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's up with Maya? She keeps looking over at Her Benevolence, like she's worried what Rayfa will think.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's... There's something I want to show you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I found this at the Inner Sanctum after I came to.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is this... a letter? <thought>It's in Khura'inese...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">See that stamp on the far left, at the end of the letter? Does it look familiar?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This red stamp here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's the mark of Lady Kee'ra.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">L-Lady Kee'ra, you say?! Let me see that! ............... Wh-Why, this is...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? What does it say?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Do not perform the rite. I know what you are planning. --Lady Kee'ra"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That sounds like a threat -- or a warning! Whoever's pretending to be Lady Kee'ra was pressuring the high priest to stop the rite!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, that's what it looks like to me, too. Nick, do you think...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait! First, there's that ancient legend.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"The spring shall run red upon Lady Kee'ra's return."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, there's also Lady Kee'ra's warning. Plus, with the Warbaa'd Dagger being eyed as the murder weapon... D-Don't tell me...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's why she HAS to be the real deal! It gives me chills just thinking about it! I bet Lady Kee'ra's spirit possessed the sacred robe or something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't tell me...  ...you actually believe that the real Lady Kee'ra returned to kill the high priest?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">..................... Don't be silly, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Historical figures don't come back to life. I mean, give me a break.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-B-But! You were saying only yesterday, how it was more fun to believe that she's the real deal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, YESTERDAY! I wish I could keep on entertaining that fantasy, too... ...but the fact is,  we're dealing with a murder here! Thus, my days of dreaming have come to an end.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">........................</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm going to keep it real from now on. And you should, too, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I thought you said I was the boring one because I was "keeping it real"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sorry, I guess I've outgrown that stepladder argument we always have...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think you mean "ladder," Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what do you mean by "keeping it real"?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, umm... So you know how someone is dressing up like Lady Kee'ra and capturing rebels, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, you mean the rebel-hunter Lady Kee'ra in the papers?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, that one. I think that's who probably sent this warning.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What nonsense is this?! You dare to suggest... ...that Abbot Inmee was slain by Lady Kee'ra?! You... Youuu... nincompoop!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The rebel hunter is sure to be a vigilante who loves this kingdom. And it is that patriotism that led them to cloak their identity in the guise of Lady Kee'ra. Such a patriot... would NEVER slay the high priest!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess it's only natural for Princess Rayfa to see it that way, but I can't let it go at that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Besides, why would such a vigilante want to stop the Purification Rite in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I haven't figured that one out yet.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I rest my case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Still, if this rebel hunter had a compelling enough reason... ...they might've killed the high priest after he ignored their warning.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Y-You... big dummy! You can't fool me! It was you who forged that warning letter! You are trying to shed your guilt onto our most sacred Lady Kee'ra! Admit it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-No! I'd never do such a thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, now, Your Benevolence. Let's try to remain rational about this...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Grrrrrrr...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, did you show that letter to the police?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... no. I was afraid that it would anger everybody needlessly. So I was waiting to show it to you, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And judging by Her Benevolence's reaction, I'd say Maya was right to be worried. ...Hm? Wait, what are... There are a number of places on this letter where there are three holes in a row. ...Are these supposed to be some sort of a message, too? Not that we'll be finding out any time soon, I suspect...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I didn't kill the high priest! I swear!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course you didn't.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">And why should I believe the words of an accused?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But I really didn't kill him! And if you don't believe me, then prepare to get an earful! ...From Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! Keep me out of this!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There you go, presenting things left and right again, as always! Sure takes me back to the good old days! Ooh, ooh! Present something else, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh,  if that's what you really want...? At least it seemed to cheer her up a bit.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guard">All right, accused. Wrap it up.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess they have more questions for me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... At least I have a better idea of what we're up against now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, Nick...? There's something I've been meaning to say. I... don't need a lawyer this time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What are you talking about?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's just, you know they have that Defense Culpability Act here in Khura'in, right? Well, if I'm found guilty... you'll be charged with abetting a criminal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya... Thanks for thinking of me, but...</thought> Don't worry, Maya. We'll pull through this together somehow. We always have, haven't we?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah... But we're not in Kansas anymore, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">True, but I've been through one trial here already. So I know what I'm getting myself into. We're going to win this one, no matter what. Because I believe in your innocence.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">! Yeah, I know... We've always won because of your faith in me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. So, it's "All Aboard the Phoenix Freedom Express!"</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Thank you, Nick. Well, I'll see you later.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Bravado will not save you tomorrow, and by then, it will be too late to ask for mercy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...We're going to beat this charge. You'll see.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. I don't care to understand every single word that was spoken... ...but I don't like the sound of that "Phoenix Freedom Express" one bit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait... Don't tell me you don't know what "Freedom Express" refers to?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Augh!  Of course I know! D-Do not presume to know what I do not know! ........................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm no closer to understanding why someone would want the high priest dead... ...but given the use of the Warbaa'd Dagger and the existence of the warning letter... ...I'd say the rebel hunter disguised as Lady Kee'ra  is the real prime suspect. It might help if I knew a little more about this modern-day Lady Kee'ra. I wonder if anyone has any info on them... Hmm... Maybe the first thing I should do is to go someplace where locals like to gather.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That woman you call Maya Fey is not to be trusted. I hear she is already twenty-eight, and yet, she is still as antsy as a maiden in her teens. Surely, she must be hiding something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Actually, that's... just Maya being Maya.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what next?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmm, let me think... Oh, I know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Dare I ask...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Admit the accused's guilt, so we can go straight to the inevitable guilty verdict! That will solve everything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did I even ask...? I think I'll just keep on investigating.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Why is that warning letter comprised of paper cutouts?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Probably because the author wanted to hide their identity. It's not a common technique these days, what with the spread of computers and printers.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">W-We have such modern conveniences here in Khura'in, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm sure you do. <thought>Not that I've ever actually seen any of them.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess the bazaar is as good a place to start as any. Now, who should I... ...Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmm, I see... So that is what a "Freedom Express" is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Consulting her pocket internet again, I see...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That sounds like...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Is Miss Maya okay? I believe her, Mr. Wright. I know she didn't do it!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Do you now, boy?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">P-Pohlkunkaaa! Y-Y-Your Benevolence!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You mustn't trust in lawyers, you... Hm? Are you not the accused from the last trial?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Oh, u-um...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's wrong, Ahlbi?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Y-Your... Your Benevolence speaks... with the... um...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You may speak in the vernacular, little monk. Now, what is your name?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Y-Yes, Your Benevolence! Ahlbi Ur'gaid, Your Benevolence!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Know this, Ahlbi: Your soul is only as clean or filthy as the company you keep.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wish she'd stop insinuating that all lawyers are trash.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">P-Please forgive me, Your Benevolence, but Mr. Wright is a very trustworthy man. A-And I... I trust him as a lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">.........What's this?!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I-I'm sorry! ...F-Forgive my insolence!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I-If a common boy such as he can place his trust in lawyers... ...it can only be because of my failure at the Hall of Justice the other day. Ooooooh...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Mr. Wright! Her Benevolence has sunken to the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She must really feel responsible for what happened in court that day... Let's give her some breathing room for now. I'm sure she'll be back on her feet in no time. In the meantime, do you mind if I ask you some questions?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Of course not! I'm always glad to help!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Allow me to explain! This bird is known as a warbaa'd. It's only found here in Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right -- the bird Lady Kee'ra based herself on. It's a really beautiful bird. Tourists must love it.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">They usually do. There's just one thing about it that's kind of hit or miss. Its unusual cry drives children to tears. It can even make some adults collapse in fear...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe they should keep such a fearsome creature in a less crowded area...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Ahlbi, what's this cow-like animal?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">It's a yak. They carry heavy loads and provide milk. They're indispensible partners in our daily lives.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Interesting... Hey, they're kind of cute up-close!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Oh, and they are also prized for their meat. You know -- the meat you enjoyed so much last night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... <thought>"Partner" must mean something else here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at all these vegetables...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Let's see... There's giah'pam, konuuro, and zabaas. And they're all freshly picked this morning!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've never heard of any of them. Maybe I'll buy some to see what they taste like. You want some, too, Ahlbi? My treat.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Really?! Thank you, sir! I'll take some of this, and this, oh, and this, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.........Um, Ahlbi? That's quite a lot you've got there already, don't you think...?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">But this is barely enough for a side dish!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I hope I brought enough money.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A manhole...? I guess they have a sewer system here in Khura'in. What am I thinking? Of course they do. That was ignorant of me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's a poster. It looks like some kind of Khura'inese superhero. Why do all superheroes look the same, regardless of where they come from?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">This is a really popular bun shop here in Khura'in!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ooh, they even sell magatah'man. Let's see... "1 magatah'man: 15 dahmas." ...Wait a second. Ahlbi, weren't you selling them for 20 dahmas apiece...?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">The extra 5 dahmas is the service fee!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's quite the shrewd businessman.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't read the sign, but this looks like a souvenir shop. It's too bad I don't have time to do some shopping right now... ...but I'll have to stop by here before I go back home. I'm sure everyone's expecting something... Especially Trucy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what have you heard about the rebel hunter that was in the newspaper?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Everyone's overjoyed at her appearance! They say she's the modern-day Lady Kee'ra!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So they're treating this rebel hunter like a mysterious protector of the people, huh.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">People have been on edge recently, what with that jailbreak and stuff. I sure hope they catch that escaped prisoner soon!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Escaped prisoner?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Yes, he was one of the vicious rebels that Lady Kee'ra had captured.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So there's a hardened criminal on the loose? That IS bad news.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Yes, but the modern-day Lady Kee'ra is also super amazing! I mean, she takes down big, scary rebels all by herself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. That's not exactly something just anyone can do. <thought>Someone that strong...</thought><thought>...could've easily overpowered and killed the high priest.</thought> Hmm... And what about that escaped prisoner, Ahlbi?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what's the escaped prisoner supposed to be like?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">They say he's a vicious fiend who serves as Dhurke's right-hand man.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Dhurke? As in the leader of that rebel group?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Yes! The escapee serves that dreadful master of the Defiant Dragons. They say the prisoner's a former soldier, and that he wields a big scary knife. Rumor has it, he's a cold-blooded killer to boot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He sounds like a really dangerous man.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">He is. But the police still can't find him, even after an exhaustive search!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Wait. <thought>I remember hearing about a prison...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">There is a prison at the apex of this mountain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A prison? Way up there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The prison is at the top of the Inner Sanctum's mountain, right? How did he even break out?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">No one really knows. He supposedly did it without any tools to speak of, too. Some say he must've fallen to his death. Personally, I'd like to believe he did... Otherwise, something like that terrible incident might happen again...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Terrible incident...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was that about a "terrible incident," Ahlbi?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">It happened before I was even born, but... ...Queen Amara -- the previous queen -- was assassinated. And it was the rebel leader Dhurke who did it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The previous queen was assassinated?! <thought>That's kind of unsettling...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Ooh... It was the terrible deed of a heinous sinner. I mean, to take the life of such a gentle queen?! Only someone with a dark, defiled soul could have done that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>They really take their queens seriously here. Like, god-worshipping level serious... It really would take someone pretty bold and blasphemous to assassinate one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Those Defiant Dragon rebels are not afraid to do anything to accomplish their goals! That's why, with that escaped prisoner on the loose... ...who knows who might be killed next!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's why the people of Khura'in are so afraid of that escapee. And why they want the rebel hunter to take him out, along with the other rebels.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Rayfa's still sitting slumped on the ground. I can't leave her here like this... ...so I guess I should keep talking to Ahlbi until she recovers.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, is there anything else you can tell me about the rebel hunter Lady Kee'ra, Ahlbi?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Umm, I was just thinking there was something else, but what was it...? Oh, yeah! Here!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Shah'do found it!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Why that's... the Warbaa'd Arrow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Feeling better now, Your Benevolence?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">This is no time to be feeling sorry for myself. For I am the crown princess of Khura'in! Now, let me see that, boy.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Y-Yes, Your Benevolence!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmm... It looks very much like one of the legendary weapons Lady Kee'ra once used in battle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A three-pronged arrow? <thought>I could swear I've seen something resembling that arrowhead recently...</thought> Where did Shah'do find it, Ahlbi?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Near Abbot Inmee's house.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Near the victim's house, huh... Something tells me I'd better look into this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ahlbi, can I ask you to take me to the high priest's house?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">...Y-Yes, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come to think of it, he was married, wasn't he? And his wife is the one who usually plays the part of Lady Kee'ra in the Purification Rite. I should probably talk to her, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, that bird over there is a warbaa'd, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Yes, but they're endangered now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I wonder how many of them were killed to make this arrow.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Oh... Would you like me to explain, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, that's okay.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That is the Warbaa'd Arrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't see the connection between this arrow and a warbaa'd, though.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The feathers of a warbaa'd were used in its fletching. And its design was also inspired by the official bird of Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow, you were able to explain all that without Nayna.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What did you just say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... N-Nothing! Never mind! <thought>Why can't I ever keep my big mouth shut?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So this is where the high priest lived. Wait a minute. This is where they brought me when my back gave out. And the woman in front of that altar... She must be the high priest's wife...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Rayfa is glaring at me with a piercing look in her eyes. Guess it'd be rude to start poking around before saying hi to the high priest's wife...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">...Yes? May I help you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was hoping to speak with the high priest's wife. Are you she?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Please forgive the intrusion, Lady Beh'leeb.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Oh, my... Y-Your Benevolence.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Please, be at ease. What a terrible time this must be for you. I owe much to your husband. You have my deepest sympathies for your tragic loss.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">You honor me with your kind words. Look dear, the royal priestess has come to visit us. Yes... Mm-hm. ...What's that? ...Oh, of course... hee hee.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sh- She's talking with his funeral picture!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">My husband, too, is delighted that the royal priestess has graced us with her presence.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Y-You can speak with Abbot Inmee?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">No, I don't possess the power to speak with the dead. But I can feel his presence. ...What's that? No, that can wait till later, dear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sh-She's definitely speaking with him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">...So, Your Benevolence. What is it that brings you to my humble abode?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">This lawyer is investigating your husband's death. And I am watching him to ensure he does not tamper with any of the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know this must be difficult, but could I ask you some questions? A good friend of mine has fallen under suspicion, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">A friend of yours...? So then, you must be Maya's friend from the States... correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">...I'm sorry, but I'm still grieving. ...Isn't that right, dear?...Yes, I know.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Abbot Inmee and his wife were one of the closest and most loving couples in Khura'in. If she is not ready to talk, I will not allow you to press her any further.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She did just lose the love of her life... It would be incredibly insensitive of me to force answers out of her right now. But I need to talk to her if I want to learn more about the high priest. Plus, there's the Warbaa'd Arrow that Ahlbi found near the house. There's too much I need to find out for me to leave just yet.</thought> Um... Would it be okay if I stayed here for a little while?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head! Have you not been listening to a word I said?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, Your Benevolence. I'm sorry for her loss, but I'm running out of time. So what I will do is promise to leave if she doesn't change her mind.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Please, let me talk to my husband about this. ...Yes. Mm-hm. I know... No, don't. Not in front of the royal priestess. Now, if you would excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh- What the heck were they even talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You have but poured salt on her wounds. This is precisely why you lawyers are so despised!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk! <thought>I was just trying to help Maya's case. I didn't mean to hurt Mrs. Inmee...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Could it be that you actually possess a conscience?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course I do! But I'm also desperate for information.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...So, what do you plan to do now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pass the time by looking around the room, I guess, and see if she changes her mind.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Just see that you do not touch anything you should not.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess I should watch what I touch, then. Just in case Princess Rayfa gets mad at me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What a magnificent altar.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Of course it is magnificent -- it is for the Holy Mother, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Holy Mother... Is she that faceless figure there?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Such insolence! How do you not know who Her Holiness is on sight?! Do you seek to cross over into the Twilight Realm right this instant?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry! It won't happen again!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Hmph, this is why lawyers are so despised. Now listen well: Depicting Her Holiness's face is the greatest taboo in all of Khura'inism. There are none alive today who know what her face really looks like. And that includes the members of the royal family.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow, now there's an unusual custom... <thought>It's gotta be one heck of a secret if even the royal family can't know what she looks like.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A poster... of the mountains? Oh, the Inner Sanctum mountain is featured against those other towering peaks.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Those beautiful mountains are known as the "Roof of Khura'in." Ah, and I see they have even included Mt. Poniponi in that poster.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mt. Poniponi? <thought>Is that the smaller peak to the left?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Known as the "Little Sanctum," it is just west of the Inner Sanctum. Is it not also beautiful? But I suppose a lawyer with a defiled soul such as you could not perceive such beauty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, that's not true! I think it's absolutely stunning!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is this... a piece of art of some sort?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What a beautiful orb. ...Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head, take one step back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Okay... Done. Did you spot something?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, your dismal reflection. It was ruining the orb's beauty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Did you have to put it like that, Your Benevolence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What show is this?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It is "The Plumed Punisher: Warrior of Neo Twilight Realm." It is based on Lady Kee'ra and is the number- one action-hero show in Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"The Plumed Punisher: Warrior of Neo Twilight Realm"?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, it is an entirely original show created right here in our kingdom.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not so sure about its "originality," given its overall look and that theme song...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Is something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it's just, we have an action-hero show back home that is really similar to this. <thought>I'm guessing this show's why Maya is so into Lady Kee'ra... Honestly, the theme song is exactly the same as the one for Maya's favorite show... ..."The Steel Samurai: Warrior of Neo Olde Tokyo." It's a popular action-hero series filmed right in LA. Set in a city known as Neo Olde Tokyo, it pits the Steel Samurai in mortal combat... ...against his nemesis, the Evil Magistrate.</thought>  <thought>Maya's collected DVDs and merchandise from that series as long as I've known her.</thought> The Plumed Punisher seems awfully similar to the Steel Samura--</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The Plumed Punisher originated HERE, in Khura'in. Is that clear, Barbed Head?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Benevolence! <thought>Note to self: Never suggest that again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This looks like a wastebasket... Hey, there's an envelope sticking out. <thought>Hmm... There are three holes in a row near the top. Now, where have I seen holes like these before?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Scrounging around in other people's garbage like some stray dog... You are a pitiful creature, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... What does it say here? <thought>Say what you will, but I've got a job to do!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It says, "To the high priest." Hmph... You cannot even read? You are even more pitiful than I had thought.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-Thanks. And I will keep your words of wisdom in mind, Your Benevolence. <thought>Guess I should've studied some Khura'inese before I came...</thought> So the envelope was addressed to the high priest, huh? ...But it's empty. Still, there's something about it... I'd better hang on to it.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head, it appears you are quite fond of rummaging through the garbage.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I just thought there might be some other important piece of evidence in here.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Oh, is that right? ..................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Look, I'm not doing this for fun! Really! <thought>Doesn't look like there's anything else of interest in there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What is this scary-looking spiky thing?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It is a floor cushion for heightening a practitioner's mental focus. Your ignorance astounds me. There is not a soul in Khura'in who would not recognize this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A floor cushion? You mean you're supposed to sit on this?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. How else would you suggest it be used?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looks like a torture device to me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, it's a wanted poster for the rebel escapee everyone's talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What? Let me see that. "Datz Are'bal, senior member of insurgent leadership, and former paratrooper of a..." "...foreign land. Wanted for crimes against the kingdom. Considered armed and dangerous."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So he's ex-military, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">His appearance alone exudes menace. He must be captured at once.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The bounty is three million dahmas -- money that comes out of the people's tax payments. I shall have it lowered to about one million dahmas.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You seem unexpectedly concerned with the people's welfare.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">"Unexpectedly"? How rude! Nayna has always taught me that "kingdoms that do not value its people come to ruin." As crown princess, it is only natural that I care for my people!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How about sending some of that kindness this way?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmm... Well, I suppose I could... ...If you quit being a lawyer, and paid taxes to our kingdom, that is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh well. It was worth a shot...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This game looks kind of like checkers or chess.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You mean to say you have never heard of Kachu'demahl? I have heard people describe it as "Khura'inese chess."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So two players take turns moving their pieces in a bid to capture the other's king?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Not quite. In Kachu'demahl, the object is the utter annihilation of your opponent. Furthermore, each piece has a special move that can only be used once per game.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Special moves? It sounds like a game right up Maya's alley...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a Steel Samurai patch on this bag. Guess the bag must be Maya's. She probably left it here while she was performing that rite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Isn't this that justice minister I met? But who's the woman in the picture next to him? She looks really important. Could she be the Queen of Khura'in?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Lady Beh'leeb has not had a change of heart, and simply waiting shall not change that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">C-Can't we wait just a little longer? <thought>I wonder if she'll ever open up?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, you're still here.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Lady Beh'leeb...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mrs. Inmee... Do you think you're ready to talk?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">...Is it okay with you, dear? ...Yes. Yes, I will let him know.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Lady Beh'leeb, you don't have to speak to this lawyer if it is not your wish.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">No, it's quite all right. If my husband were still with us, he would say... "As much as it pains me to have my lovely wife speak on such matters..." "...if it would help to find the truth... then ask whatever you may."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Okay, I'll take you up on your generous offer. <thought>Wait... Did Mrs. Inmee call herself "lovely" just now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Well, whatever are you waiting for?! Ask your questions quickly, so your departure may be just as swift!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, of course...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you have any idea why your husband might have been killed? Was he acting different or doing anything out-of-the-ordinary lately?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">No, I don't recall anything of the sort. ........................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh, this is really difficult.</thought> Did anybody have a grudge against him?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">He was a kind man, and one of peace. He would never do anything that would cause someone to bear a grudge against him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Th-These are... Psyche-Locks! This means Mrs. Inmee is trying to hide something from me. This is the magatama Maya gave me all those years ago... ...and it has a really amazing power. It reacts when someone is hiding something... ...and allows me to see the Psyche-Locks that are holding that person's mind shut. Whenever I see any... ...I only have to touch my magatama (X</thought> to try and unlock them. Unlocking them all usually allows me to coax the truth out of someone.)</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure there was no one who held a grudge against your husband?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">He was a kind and gentle soul. He would have never done anything to make someone want to harm him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Psyche-Locks... I'll have to unlock them before I can get any more information out of her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">-- The High Priest --</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">(Psyche-Locks... They appeared when I asked her whether </line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">That would be Maya, would it not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, of course not. It has to be someone with a motive to kill him. This is who I believe had a reason to kill your husband.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe the escaped prisoner killed your husband. He probably thought that your husband would get in the way of his escape plan.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">But were that the case, wouldn't Maya have been slain as well?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, you're right. <thought>Guess I'd better find someone else with a possible motive...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">So you see, Maya must have been the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, it had to have been someone else.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The rebel leader Dhurke killed your husband. He did it to stop the Purification Rite.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">He must despise Lady Kee'ra for capturing his fellow insurgents. But were that the case, wouldn't he have slain Maya for playing the part of Lady Kee'ra?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...G- Good point. <thought>All right, so it wasn't Dhurke. Time to think about who else might've had a motive.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">So you see, Maya must've been the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, it had to have been someone else.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was the rebel hunter disguised as Lady Kee'ra. Everyone's talking about her. </line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">"I know not of what you speak."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? Because she even made the front page recently.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">"Kwah kah kah kah kah!" "I am but a humble servant of Lady Kee'ra." "What reason would she have to kill someone as insignificant as I?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually... I have something that just might show why Lady Kee'ra would kill Abbot Inmee. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Beh'leeb:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R- Really? B-But doesn't this part here remind you of your husband?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, then... take a look at this part here! It really resembles Lady Kee'ra, doesn't it!</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">I am not seeing this "resemblance."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry. It looks like I was mistaken... <thought>That's strange. I could swear I had something that could prove... ...that the high priest was being threatened by Lady Kee'ra.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">It seems there really was no connection between my husband and Lady Kee'ra.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but I beg to differ.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is a letter of warning from Lady Kee'ra. Maya found it. It was in the Inner Sanctum -- and only Maya and your husband were there at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Augh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This letter reached its intended recipient, your husband -- the high priest -- didn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">And how do you know Maya wasn't lying to you? Because I've never seen that letter before, and I doubt my husband ever did, either.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but... I have evidence that proves this warning was meant for your husband.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Um... I'm afraid I don't understand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I believe you do. Please take a good look.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">..................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.........Still drawing a blank, huh. <thought>Maybe I should really compare the warning letter with the rest of the evidence again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">I don't believe the warning has anything to do with my husband.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, this warning was meant for him.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Wh-What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's an envelope... addressed to the high </line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Augh!</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">"...What nonsense is this?" "How can you prove the warning was delivered in this envelope?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... There's gotta be some way to prove it... Wait a second. Don't the envelope and the warning letter have something in common?</thought> ...I think there just might be something that links the envelope to the warning letter.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">"There is?!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, and that proof is right here on the warning letter. This spot on the warning letter proves that it was delivered in that envelope!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Beh'leeb:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, no, a little lower. Oh, no, a little to the right. Errr... maybe it was all in my mind?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">.........Are you trying to be funny? At a time like this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry... <thought>Didn't the envelope and warning letter have something in common?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">It seems the envelope was for some other letter, and not this warning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I'm positive the warning letter was in the envelope addressed to the high priest. Look at this spot on the warning letter. It shows that the letter was in that envelope!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The three holes in the envelope... ...are in the same shape and arrangement as the holes in the warning letter. And if you fold the letter in thirds and place it in the envelope, the holes line up.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Augh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As for what made the holes... I believe it was this...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Beh'leeb:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but I'd rather hear your opinion, Mrs. Inmee.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry! <thought>So it wasn't this... I'd better take another look at the shape of the holes in the warning and envelope.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">There was never any connection between my husband's murder and Lady Kee'ra, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, the holes in the warning and the envelope can both be linked to her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They were made by this Warbaa'd Arrow -- one of the weapons favored by Lady Kee'ra. The warning was folded in thirds, placed in the envelope addressed to the high priest... ...and delivered to your husband on the points of this arrow!</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Eeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Are you ready to tell me the truth now?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">.................. I admit the warning was sent to my husband. But he was not an insurgent.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then why did you keep it a secret?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Because... the authorities might've suspected him of being one if I hadn't.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess that makes sense... If the rebel hunter was after him, I can see how people might at least suspect.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">We are a Khura'inist kingdom. As such, rising up against the monarchy... ...is the same as blaspheming Khura'inism itself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your husband was a devout priest of Khura'inism... ...and you feared that his good name would be tarnished if the warning went public.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That makes sense, but is it the honest truth? What if the high priest really was a rebel? The rebel hunter would've had a motive to kill him. Still...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">..................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This just doesn't feel like the right time to ask her about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me a little more about the warning?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">It arrived about three days before the Purification Rite. When we woke that morning, it was already there by the side of our bed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was by the side of your bed?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Yes. We had the whole house locked up tight. And yet, someone still managed to slip in. Oh, it was so frightening, wasn't it, dear?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you didn't contact the police... ...because you didn't want them to suspect your husband of being a rebel?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">...That's right. If only we had told the police, maybe Tahrust would still be alive today.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">What is that badge for?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the attorney's badge used in my country.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Yes... Mm-hm. ...I agree, dear.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">My husband says I should have nothing to do with lawyers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not like we top the popularity charts back home, but c'mon! Can't a lawyer get a break?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">My husband's...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head! Do you not consider the consequences of your actions?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, um... sorry. That was pretty inconsiderate of me.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Oh...? Is that so? You really are a kind soul, dear.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">...My husband says he forgives you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">"I understand that you're desperate, but do not cause my lovely wife undue pain." "Do I make myself clear... Lawyer?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, ma'am! Er, I mean, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Why, that is the escaped criminal who has all of Khura'in astir.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">When I think how he might still be lurking about, I get so scared, I can't sleep at night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't blame her, considering she just suddenly lost her husband.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Yes... Mm-hm... Really, dear?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">...My husband said he would protect me if that escaped criminal shows up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>By "protect," does she mean she'll pummel the escapee with her husband's portrait?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">"Oh, lovely wife... No need to fret, my dear." "My only regret is that I left you all alone..."</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head! That is quite enough!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, you're probably right. Mrs. Inmee, I'm sorry to have bothered you at such a difficult time.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">...Don't be silly. I'm happy if I have helped.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">"Your Benevolence..." "May you swiftly shine light upon the truth."</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head. You seem bent on casting suspicion upon Lady Kee'ra. And by doing so, you seek to deflect the blame from the real killer, Maya Fey. That is the only logical conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Gnrk! <thought>I'm in no position to disprove her at this point. If only I could find something to support my theory that the high priest was a rebel... The only other person who might know more about Abbot Inmee would be Maya. They might be done questioning her by now. Maybe I'll stop by the detention center.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">My mother has said what...? Hm, it seems I must go.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did something happen?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes. My mother has decreed that a rite shall be held for the high priest's passing. And that she shall conduct the Prayer of Lament therein.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Her Eminence has so decreed, has she?! Oh, but she should not concern herself with a humble priest like my husband.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">No, it is only natural, considering his meritorious service. The rite will be held at the palace. You are to </line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Thank you, Your Benevolence. My husband is most delighted, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How wonderful for you, Mrs. Inmee. <thought>A direct decree from the queen. That must be quite an honor.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head, you are coming as well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? B-But I don't have much time left to investigate...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">As the one charged with monitoring you, you must remain within my sight at all times. Besides, it will take but a moment. Now, come along!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... Arguing the point will probably just make things worse for me. I'd better let her have her way this time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Welcome, Lady Beh'leeb.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So this is the queen of Khura'in...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What is wrong with you, Barbed Head?!  Show some respect!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Oh,  um... <thought>Sh-Should I bow?  Or prostrate myself?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">...No, it is quite all right. Stay as you are.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Mother...</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">...Your Eminence, I would like to give thanks to you. You honor both me and my husband.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">His exemplary service deserves to be honored. Oh, but what a terribly trying time this must be for you, Lady Beh'leeb. May my prayer comfort your soul, and that of your dearly departed husband. Nothing would please me more.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Oh, Your Eminence.  Your words are wasted on my humble husband and I... *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that's what I call a commanding presence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">So, you are the lawyer of whom my daughter speaks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Eminence! I am so very honored to make your... n-noble acquaintanceship. I-I'm humbled to bask in your... <thought>Ack... Did I overdo it?  I have no idea how to talk to a queen.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Ho ho...  May the Holy Mother's blessing be upon you. Now then, Lady Beh'leeb.  Let us go to the Chamber of Prayer. Rayfa, you are to accompany us, too.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, Mother.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, the queen is seriously something else.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Heh.  The Prayer of Lament, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Don't see how that'll do any good.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I-It's... Justice Minister Inga!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Inga">Hm? Who're you, buddy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-Nice to see you again, Minister Inga.</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Again? Have we met?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm Phoenix Wright.  We met in the accused lobby the other day.</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Oh, right.  Blue suit, jagged hair... You're that lawyer who brought my daughter down a peg or two.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your... daughter?</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Yeah, Rayfa.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's Princess Rayfa's father? So he's Queen Ga'ran's husband?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Inga">You planning on sticking your fat nose in this mess, too?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The accused is a good friend of mine.</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Like I said the last time... ...you better watch yourself, see?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, do you mind if I ask you a few questions?</line>
<line speaker="Inga">You want to question me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That would be great.</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Heh heh heh heh! You got balls, for a lawyer!  Guess I can play along a bit. But I got things to do, see? So we'll have to talk while I work.</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Hey, keep your paws off that stuff over there. It's all pretty pricey -- more than you could possibly imagine, I'd wager.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah... I'd better keep my hands to myself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wanted to let you know that I'll be the defense lawyer on this case, too.</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Well, don't say I didn't warn you. You only won last time 'cause that idiotic prosecutor filed false charges. But it's gonna be different this time. I got Khura'in's top prosecutor on this one, see?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't care who I go up against. I'm going to prove my client innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Inga">You haven't forgotten that little thing called the Defense Culpability Act, have you? Blow this one, and you'll suffer the same fate as the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How could I forget?</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Heh, you lawyers are all the same. You strut your stuff till the DC Act comes down hard. Then you start begging and pleading for your lives. It's really hard to watch, I tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well, I don't plan on letting it come to that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Were you the one who wrote the Defense Culpability Act?</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Heh, maybe I did, maybe I didn't. What's it to you? Either way, as justice minister I'm gonna enforce the thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.........!</line>
<line speaker="Inga">It started as a way to counter the dirty tricks of your trade like falsified evidence. But it turned out to be quite handy... Efficient, even!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Handy...? Efficient...?</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Yeah, made my job reeeal easy. Any goons who cross me or the Ga'ran administration... ...are gonna get just what they deserve, especially those rebel scum!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......! You can get away with that here?</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Better watch your mouth, lawyer. I enforce the law in Khura'in, see? And being that I'm the queen's husband, that makes me king!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>.........Um, no... I'm pretty sure the queen is the boss around here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Inga">Go on, say what you're thinking so I can charge you with lese-majesty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk! <thought>I can't get myself arrested now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Inga">Listen up, lawyer. We got a low crime rate and a populace that lives in peace. And that's all thanks to the DC Act. So I don't want to hear any more lip about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I can't defend my client unless I can speak my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Heh, even without the DC Act, Dhurke and his insurgent scum buddies' days are numbered.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What's that supposed to mean?!</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Let's just say... I got a little trick up my sleeve. So I'd watch it if I were you. 'Cause you got a defiant attitude -- like one o' them dragon dupes.</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Where do you get off sticking that thing in my face? You forget who you're dealing with? Don't poke your nose where it don't belong. Or do you want a spot on my execution list?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, I'm good! <thought>I'd better end this conversation now, before I really rub him the wrong way.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I bet it'd tick him off if I left now. I should talk to him a bit, and see what he knows.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Inga">Say, White, you know what these are?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...No, what?</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Orders of execution. They really pile up if I start slacking off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Inga">And tomorrow, I'll have even more work to do... processing the one for your little friend. And if you really do defend her, I'll have to add one more to the pile for you. But you're not stupid enough to waste your life on that criminal, are ya?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Don't worry, I'll make sure to lighten your workload, Inga... I won't give you a single execution order to sign tomorrow!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I have returned, Barbed Head.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Benevolence. Are you done with the rite?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes. It was performed flawlessly. Lady Beh'leeb stayed behind to speak with Mother.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I hope this will help ease her sorrow, even if just a little.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">So, you have been speaking with my father?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, you could say that.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">My father is a great man. He works tirelessly to keep the peace in our kingdom. Khura'in as it stands today owes everything to the efforts of my mother and my father. You should feel deeply honored. Under normal circumstances, they would have never spoken so readily with a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, of course. <thought>It seems Rayfa doesn't know what her father is really like.</thought> Well, now that we're done here, let's go see if I can talk to Maya now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, it's you, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, are you okay? The questioning wasn't too harsh, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No, I'm all right. How about you? Make any progress?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I haven't found any conclusive evidence that could prove your innocence... ...but I have a small lead.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But for right now, I'd like to ask you about the high priest.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sure, ask away. ...By the way, what's the princess doing with you still, Nick? Doesn't she have anything better to do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Doesn't seem like it...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I heard that! How rude! Of course I have many other things I could be doing! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's just a thought, but... do you think the high priest could've been a rebel?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A rebel?! Why would you even think that?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because if he was... ...then  the rebel hunter Lady Kee'ra would've had a motive to kill him.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Wh-Wh-Wh-Whaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh-oh. Princess Rayfa overheard me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Wh-Wh-What idiocy is this?! Abbot Inmee, a rebel?! It is beyond the pale! My mother has offered the Prayer of Lament to his soul! That is the sort of person he was!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, all right. I was just raising the possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I will not listen to such...  such...  tomfoolery!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...She stormed out. Oh, well, nothing we can do about that.</thought> Do you recall the high priest doing anything suspicious?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Come to think of it, he seemed unusually restless during the rite. He kept glancing up at the sky, though I have no idea why.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...He was restless and kept looking up at the sky? Hmm, that doesn't really tell us much, does it? Anything else come to mind?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Sorry, that's about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess this is all I'm going to learn about the high priest right now. Oh, but there is one thing I should follow up on...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I want to keep my spirit channeling ability a secret while I'm here, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'll, um... explain later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>With Princess Rayfa gone, this might be my only chance.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, about what you said earlier... Why can't you tell anyone you're able to channel spirits?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, that! You know how all the queens are also spirit mediums here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I heard. It was kind of a shock at first, though.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">In Khura'inism, spirit channeling is a secret art that can only be performed by the queen. No one else is supposed to be able to do it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see. So spirit channeling is a symbol of power or authority, then, in that sense. I can see why it would look bad if a "nobody" from another country were able to do it, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Spirit Channeling in the Kurain Tradition... ...was developed from a Khura'inist style that was brought to the U.S. via Japan. But it seems like my clan's spiritual power is greater than that of the average Khura'inese. It may be a quirk due to how our styles diverged, but I don't really know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So, if spirit channeling is a power possessed only by the queens of Khura'in... ...and it's a power that somehow made its way down the line to Maya... ...then I guess that makes Queen Ga'ran and Princess Rayfa distant relatives of Maya's...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Anyway, it's not like there's some kind of rule about it. It's just, I'd rather not have it become an issue or anything. That's why mediums who come here to train hide the fact that they can channel spirits.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... <thought>I had no idea it was so complicated.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Either way, training here is a must to fulfill the qualification needed to become the master.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what is this qualification to become the master?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">To be able to channel spirits of one's own volition and without fail every time. Like, remember how my spirit channeling was always hit or miss? I only ever succeeded about thirty percent of the time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, and it was more like spirits possessed her, as apposed to her channeling them...</thought> So you can do it every single time now, whenever you want?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yep! ...At least, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You think?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, I haven't actually tried channeling anyone since I completed my training here. But once I get back home, I plan on taking the final spirit medium test. I'll have to try channeling one spirit after another in a marathon channeling session!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Only those who pass the test are worthy of becoming the master, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, but I know I can do it. I'm going to ace that test and become the next master! After all, I can't let my clan and the other villagers down.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right... Maya's the next big hope of Kurain Village. That's got to be a lot of pressure.</thought> So, speaking of similarities... ...I've noticed another similarity between our countries besides spirit channeling. I saw a show on TV earlier that reminded me of "The Steel Samurai."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, you must mean "The Plumed Punisher: Warrior of Neo Twilight Realm"!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, you've already seen "The Plumed Punisher"? You really don't miss a beat!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, it was Her Benevolence who told me all about it.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">There is not a single person in Khura'in who does not know of it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, Your Benevolence. You're back.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">As the royal priestess, I am charged with monitoring your movements. So, I have changed my mind. For in order to fulfill my duty... ...I must not avert my ears -- not even from your blasphemous theories.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Her sense of duty is commendable... ...but I wouldn't mind if she backed off a bit.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Great timing, Your Benevolence. There's, actually, something I wanted to show off to the both of you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Show off? <thought>Maya sure seems excited all of a sudden...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup! Ta-daaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh- What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's an ultra-rare Plumed Punisher strap! There's only one of them in the whole world! It was specially made to promote the TV show!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Y-You're the owner of this strap?! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't tell me... you're a Plumed Punisher fan, too, Your Benevolence?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">N-No, of course not. Only little children watch that show! I have no interest in such things!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">No, I am telling the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Sure, let's just leave it at that. ...So, how did you get your hands on that, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eh heh heh! I found a kindred spirit in a Plumed Punisher fan here in Khura'in! It resulted in an exchange of cultures transcending national borders!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And by cultural exchange, you mean you swapped TV show promo merchandise?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You bet! I traded my Steel Samurai watch for this strap. It's a super rare watch that plays The Steel Samurai theme song when the alarm goes off. My newfound Khura'inese friend was so happy, I got this one-of-a-kind strap in return!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess there are people like that wherever you go -- even here in Khura'in...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Watch this! When you press the magatama on her belt,  it plays the show's theme song!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That sounds just like The Steel Samurai theme song.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you talking about? Can't you hear the folk instruments in the intro and the exotic tones throughout? Plus, the Steel Samurai has Japanese taiko drums that go... ...daka don-don-don in the intro!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm, right...Guess my ears just aren't as good as yours.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Anyway, I have this amazing idea for a new show. "The Plumed Punisher vs. The Steel Samurai"! I'm going to totally go pitch it to some TV stations when I get back home! It's going to be a huge hit! Right, Your Benevolence?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I-I have no interest in such things!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, if nothing else... ...talking about "The Plumed Punisher" has, thankfully, seemed to cheer Maya up a bit.</thought> It's getting late. Try to get some sleep, okay, Maya? And leave tomorrow to me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Okay. Thanks, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I've covered just about everything. Time to head back to the temple and go over everything I've learned so far.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why would Lady Kee'ra want to stop the Purification Rite? ...Ooh, I know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You do?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! Because she's only got the one outfit and nothing to change into!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You'd think she'd have normal clothes for when she's not busy rebel hunting, Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">My father is a great man with a gentle soul, is he not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, well... <thought>Are we talking about the same person here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You, too, could become a man of upstanding character if you learned from his example.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sure... <thought>Upstanding character? Him...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...I care little for that tone of yours. It is as if you do not agree!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N- No, you have it all wrong! <thought>Why is my face always such an open book?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You have visited the accused a number of times already. Could it be you are smuggling in tools one at a time for a jailbreak?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course not! Besides, you've been watching me like a hawk!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Well then, perhaps you are cutting the bars in the visitor's room bit by bit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How on earth would I even do that?! </line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">With that barbed head of yours, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now this is getting ridiculous...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Heh, of course it is. I'm merely having a little fun here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, please don't have it at my expense! <thought>I'm mentally taxed enough already...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Ah, the escaped prisoner... He has the very face of evil. It actually reminds me of you... lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I hardly think I look that scary.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. Do not doubt my all-seeing eye in such matters, Barbed Head. It is the appearance of your mitamah that reminds me of his evil face.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, if we're talking about my soul, I guess I just have to trust your professional opinion. <thought>If it wasn't for the express purpose of making me out to be a criminal, that is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Do not flaunt that strap before me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know, I get the feeling you really want this for yourself, Your Benevolence.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You... youuu... nincompoop! You know not of what you speak! I desired it so dearly, that I had all of our retainers dispatch multiple postcards for it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All right, then. It seems "really want" was an understatement.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pictures of the queen and her husband, the Justice Minister of Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, my mother and my father. What do you think? Do they not possess an awe-inspiring air?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, um... <thought> "Terrifying" is more the word I would use...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Well?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes! They are very awe-inspiring!</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Th-That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a strap that Maya received. Would you happen to know anything about it?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">...It's for the Plumed Punisher action hero.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Of course she knows, Barbed Head! It's only the most popular show in all of Khura'in!</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">It would seem... that the royal priestess is more familiar with the matter than I.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What?! N-No! I was... simply advocating on behalf of the show's fans!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's getting late. Won't be long till sundown.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Mr. Wright, Your Benevolence!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Are you done with your investigation for today?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pretty much. I thought I'd go over what I've learned so far. Care to join me?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Yes! Please allow me to help!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay. First, we know that the high priest received a warning three days ago. It was from someone claiming to be Lady Kee'ra, and it told him not to perform the rite.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">That's right! It was that rebel hunter. But what of it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what I'm not sure of yet. Why would Lady Kee'ra want to stop the rite?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">If you could solve that mystery...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. I could figure out her motive for threatening the high priest. It might be the break I need, but I just don't know enough right now to act on that lead.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">How unfortunate for you, Barbed Head. Your only hope is pure speculation. That shall not stand up in the Hall of Justice. You have no actual proof of Lady Kee'ra's involvement in this crime, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah...The warning letter alone can't prove who killed the high priest.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I'll give you one last chance to withdraw before you are charged under the DC Act.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Your Benevolence!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">While it is true you did not forge or suppress any evidence... ...that is, perhaps, a product of my careful monitoring of your every move.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wasn't planning to do anything like that in the first place, Your Benevolence. But I AM going to prove Maya's innocence, within the confines of the law!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">H-How can you be so sure you will?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because of my undying faith in my clients. That is a lawyer's greatest weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">.................. Hmph. What nonsense. You have chosen to dig your own grave. When next we meet, it shall be in the Hall of Justice. As royal priestess, it is my duty to reveal the truth through the Divination Séance. This time, I will prove that the insights I glean thereof are the very truth itself. Prepare yourself, for this shall be your last trial... and your last rites. Tomorrow shall end with you under the headsman's axe!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Tomorrow... I'll be defending Maya in that so-called Hall of Justice again. That whole Séance thing makes trials here completely different from those back home. Plus, I don't have a shred of conclusive evidence. On the other hand, I've got plenty of confusion and anxiety to spare. I'll have to think of something. After all, I'm the only lawyer in all of Khura'in. I have to do this. I WILL do this! I'll prove Maya's innocence if it's the last thing I do!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nothing particularly interesting here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've already searched here, but it never hurts to take another look around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I have all the information I need. Maybe I should go over everything I have.</thought></line>
</xml>