<xml>
<title>The Resolve of Ryunosuke Naruhodo</title>
<line speaker="Sholmes">We have returned, my dear fellows!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Welcome back to Britain. And thank you for your timely help.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Think nothing of it. I believe you've had an even more wearing day than Mikotoba and I, no?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You could say that. We were on the brink of defeat in court earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So this prosecutor, Asogi, had you on the ropes, did he? And he's your best friend, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well... ...he's not really the man I knew in Japan any more. Kazuma's...changed.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I mean, it's incredible... To think that he'd even entertain the idea of acting as the Reaper's assassin...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well nevertheless, you must introduce me. After all... ...I've only ever met the young man as a corpse.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>When all this started...almost a year ago now. Mr Sholmes still hasn't told us the truth about what really happened back then. About the motivation for what he himself described as a 'great detective's lie'.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Now then, I must say...it's really quite a journey all the way to France.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well it is another country, Mr Sholmes. So...what news of Judge Jigoku?!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">We took him to Scotland Yard. The investigating detectives there have a lot of questions for the man.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Poor Professor Mikotoba. This must be quite a shock for him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah yes, I picked this up at the telegraph office on our way home.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Surely you haven't forgotten already. I put upon you for the matter only yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">You put upon me, Sholmes. I had to fill out your telegram to Japan and foot the bill as well.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! You've had a reply already?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What was so urgent though, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Such matters can wait until later. I'm far too hungry for an involved conversation at present!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well that's good news. Because supper is ready, everyone!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, and what a feast it is! If I were none the wiser, I'd think the trial were won already! Roast beef, kippers, stew, steak and kidney pie, Yorkshire pudding...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Tomorrow could be a very long day, so eat up!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In that case, I think I'll seat myself just here. This place appears to be the only one set with a helping of pheasant as well.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh sorry, Hurley, not there.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm? Why ever not? Are we in set places this evening?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes! And that place is for Susie's daddy.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">For me?!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's right! I made it especially for you, Professor Mickey!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I see... Well that's terribly kind of you.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">......... It's...a shame, really.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well...for a brief moment, I believed it. That Susie and I were half-sisters, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Iris, do...do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, I know now. I overheard yesterday. I secretly listened in to the conversation you had after I tricked you all into thinking I'd left.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Wha... WHAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The misunderstanding arose because of that autopsy report from ten years ago. But actually... ...it turned out that neither Dr Wilson nor Professor Mikotoba are Iris's father.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, about that, Iris. You know I...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I know. You can't tell me at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh Iris...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">......... The pheasant is by way of an apology. I'm sorry for eavesdropping.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Oh...no no, that's quite alright.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Then why don't I get any apologetic pheasant?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So just who is Iris's father? I suppose that's not something we'll be finding out today...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So then, let us dine...while our largely pheasantless plates are still piping hot!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">A fine idea, Sholmes. It all looks absolutely delicious.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Eat as much as you like! There are always seconds!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This could be our last chance to ask questions before tomorrow's trial. About that telegram from Japan...and about Kazuma. I can't let this opportunity slip away!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Roast beef, kippers, stew, steak and kidney pie, Yorkshire pudding... It all looks mouth-wateringly good.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed it does! And if it were accompanied by even a morsel of pheasant, it would be perfection.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You're still on that?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, it really does look like a feast for celebrating a victory in court!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Or indeed for drowning one's sorrows after defeat.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I hope you weren't referring to the trial tomorrow, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He's clearly still in mourning over the pheasant at the moment...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Mr Sholmes...what are you doing?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Surely it's abundantly clear... ...that I wasn't brooding over Mikotoba's refusal to share his pheasant with me. Nevertheless... ...I felt the need to withdraw from the social circle for a while and look on with hungry eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Sorry, Hurley, but I cooked that pheasant especially for Susie's daddy.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Even though I've played the role of father to you for far longer...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Mr Sholmes... ...could I discuss some things with you?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Certainly, my dear fellow! I find myself quite in the mood for a spell of conversation. No doubt you're hungry to learn more of my deep love of game!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I can probably contain my curiosity on that one.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... You needn't look at me in that fashion.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In what fashion?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It seems...that before we discuss the pheasant, we have some rather 'unpheasant' matters to discuss.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...what was in the telegram you received back from Japan then?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, this? I thank my lucky stars it arrived in time. 'Record found as indicated. Duplicate follows:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...? <thought>Those four names! We've...come across that exact same list before!</thought></line>
<line speaker="They came up in that unforgettable case last spring... What appeared to be a simple case of aggravated murder turned out to be masking monumental intrigue. A plot that involved the sale of British governmental secrets to foreign states. In exposing the means by which those secrets were being leaked, we deciphered a fragment of a message">'K. Asogi / A. Shin,</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! Where did the sender of your telegram discover them, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I have here the message I had wired yesterday. Allow me to read it to you. 'Enter Judge Jigoku's office undetected and investigate telegram records. Expect to find communication from Britain dated one year ago. List of four names. Need by tomorrow. Naruhodo.'</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I sent it to a detective I know who specialises in clandestine missions of this nature.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You asked Inspector Hosonaga to undertake such an onerous task for you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And in my name? <thought>I wonder what guise he opted for this time...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellows, it was a matter of great urgency, you understand!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Anyway, the list of names was found in Seishiro's office, as Sholmes predicted.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you mean, that mysterious collection of names that was sent from Britain to Japan was...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was sent to Judge Jigoku! He was the intended recipient!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I don't believe it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">But that doesn't answer the question of what the list of names actually signifies...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... ...I did formulate a hypothesis about that. But without a shred of evidence, I couldn't possibly have shared it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Mr Sholmes... ...looks deadly serious for once.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...what was in the telegram you received back from Japan then?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, this? I thank my lucky stars it arrived in time. 'Record found as indicated. Duplicate follows:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...? <thought>Those four names! We've...come across that exact same list before!</thought></line>
<line speaker="They came up in that unforgettable case last spring... What appeared to be a simple case of aggravated murder turned out to be masking monumental intrigue. A plot that involved the sale of British governmental secrets to foreign states. In exposing the means by which those secrets were being leaked, we deciphered a fragment of a message">'K. Asogi / A. Shin,</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! Where did the sender of your telegram discover them, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I have here the message I had wired yesterday. Allow me to read it to you. 'Enter Judge Jigoku's office undetected and investigate telegram records. Expect to find communication from Britain dated one year ago. List of four names. Need by tomorrow. Naruhodo.'</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I sent it to a detective I know who specialises in clandestine missions of this nature.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You asked Inspector Hosonaga to undertake such an onerous task for you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And in my name? <thought>I wonder what guise he opted for this time...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellows, it was a matter of great urgency, you understand!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Anyway, the list of names was found in Seishiro's office, as Sholmes predicted.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you mean, that mysterious collection of names that was sent from Britain to Japan was...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was sent to Judge Jigoku! He was the intended recipient!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I don't believe it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">But that doesn't answer the question of what the list of names actually signifies...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... ...I did formulate a hypothesis about that. But without a shred of evidence, I couldn't possibly have shared it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Mr Sholmes... ...looks deadly serious for once.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That 'tragedy' we had to go through on the SS Burya... It was all for nothing! Kazuma wasn't dead at all! We were completely taken in by the lie you told us. Your 'great detective's lie'...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... I took no pleasure in deceiving you. However, at the time... ...all that concerned me was preventing the young man's study tour from taking place, whatever the cost.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I capitalised on the events that transpired to see that he was sent back to Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">His 'remains', you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Precisely, Miss Susato. And then I made sure that somebody else was sent to Britain in his stead.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! You mean...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The arrangement between our two countries was already in place: One university student lawyer and one judicial assistant to be accommodated on a study tour. In other words, by arranging for someone else to fill the place originally intended for Mr Asogi... ...I would successfully prevent the man from arriving on our shores for several years at least.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait, do...do you mean to say that... ...it was all in aid of stopping Kazuma coming to Britain? That's why you...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Think back, Mr Naruhodo... Was there not somebody who quite casually urged you to continue on the voyage to England?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">The terms of this study tour were negotiated by the Department of Justice in both Great Britain and Japan. In the light of Mr Asogi's unfortunate death... ...I'm afraid the study tour can no longer go ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellows, the majority of problems have an extremely simple solution, you know! All you require is one lawyer, and the study tour can continue, surely?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But there is no one else with the necessary qualifications, Mr Sholmes. We know of no other lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...The voyage to London still promises a good month of time. Ample opportunity, I would say, to find yourselves another suitable lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you manipulated me?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I've often remarked on the extraordinary lengths to which friendship will drive a man. I was quite sure that you would rise to the challenge for your late friend.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't believe it...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But if it was all contrived... I mean, what happened was treated by the authorities as murder. A woman was mistakenly arrested as the perpetrator! What do you suppose became of her?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Naturally, I didn't allow the misapprehension to have any serious repercussions. I subsequently explained everything and assisted the unfortunate soul in finding the foreign refuge she sought.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I seem to remember Miss Susato and I had some rather strong words for her...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, she was certainly not devoid of all guilt. She deserved every word, I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I wonder if she made it to America, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... I'm afraid I simply cannot comprehend it. Why would you go to such lengths, Mr Sholmes? Why were you so determined to stop Kazuma-sama from reaching Britain?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... The truth is, twelve months ago... ...there was already a very tangible omen of the impending tragedy, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">An omen that, at this very moment in time, is close at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>An omen of all these tragic events, that already existed a year ago...is close at hand? We need to find out exactly what Mr Sholmes knows...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As I said, when I learnt of Dr Wilson's murder in Japan... ...my mind immediately turned to those four names. Because, you see... ...there was someone else on the list who I believed to be recently deceased.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! Who?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">'A. Shin' as it was transcribed in Japanese script. In actual fact, Miss Asa Shinn. That was a familiar name to me. She was a professional killer, well known among London's unsavoury classes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But she had completely vanished from existence several months before Wilson's murder. So I came to the logical conclusion that she had herself been killed. And accordingly, I became fearful for the lives of the remaining two persons on the list.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah! 'K. Asogi' and 'T. Gregson'...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Owing to our proximity, I decided to take measures to protect Gregson myself. But I determined it would be safest if young Asogi were to stay away from Britain.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...so that's why you went to such lengths to prevent his study tour from going ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So...you already knew who Kazuma-sama was, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Oh yes. Sholmes and I have exchanged correspondence for years. I'd recounted many tales about Asogi to him in my letters. And the news of Dr Wilson's death, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">......... So...Dr Wilson is dead then... I didn't know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Iris...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I know he wasn't my daddy, but still...that's very sad.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm so sorry, Iris. We knew the significance of the name, obviously, but... ...we just couldn't bring ourselves to tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">No...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But what you just told us, Mr Sholmes... ...doesn't completely tie in with the facts. There's one big hole in your hypothesis.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">A big hole, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Ah yes, you mean about Asa Shinn, I presume?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Exactly. She wasn't killed, was she? She was in Japan, posing as a visiting student under the assumed name of Jezaille Brett.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm glad you're keeping up, my dear fellow! But I only became aware of that fact... ...two days ago, in the foyer of the Great Waterloo Hotel.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And upon hearing that startling revelation... ...the hypothesis that I'd formed surrounding those four names... ...was completely turned topsy!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? Topsy?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean when you say your hypothesis was turned topsy, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I had believed all four names on the list to be the names of victims. However...I was mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Very much so! Asa Shinn was a killer! So this telegram is a list of both victims and killers, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed. And it would seem that Miss Shinn... ...was dispatched from Britain with the sole intention of dispatching Dr Wilson. Her visiting student status being merely a front.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Which would of course explain why no motive could be determined for her actions...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So the real reason Dr Wilson was killed by Asa Shinn... ...is because he was the target of an assassination!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And forearmed with that knowledge, fresh consideration of this telegram... ...puts the list in a very different perspective.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, does it not strike you? There is another among the four... ...who subsequently became a visiting student.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait, you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But of course. A name you know only too well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You... You mean...KAZUMA?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ohhhhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He...did say in court earlier today...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, on 31st October, I accompanied Inspector Gregson to Dunkirk... ...in order to carry out a mission.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">And the mission was...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...The assassination of the mark.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Young Asogi accepted that mission a year ago now.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Surely not...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In conclusion, this document is a contract of sorts. An international agreement, one might say...detailing an assassin exchange.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">An assassin exchange?! <thought>How could Kazuma possibly have got involved in something like that?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Let's assume that we have two parties, each wishing to dispose of a distinct individual. Those two parties then make a contract to swap their respective assassination targets. That would then be an assassin exchange.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So to begin with, the British assassin is dispatched as a visiting student to Japan, where she kills her target. And then the Japanese assassin is dispatched as a visiting student to Britain in order to eliminate his target. ...It certainly does sound like an exchange.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But... ...what on earth is the point?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Don't forget, Naruhodo, that the British assassin at least escaped conviction... ...thanks to diplomatic immunity afforded by consular jurisdiction.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Such jurisdiction should be null and void under the terms of the new treaty between our two countries. So the fact that it was brought into play suggests intervention at the very highest levels.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The highest levels...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">These murders were two sides of the same coin. Linked not by a common motive, but by contractual agreement. As such, they appeared utterly unrelated. Yet in truth, the assassins were complicit in one singular, devilish scheme. That dissociation, and the safeguard of diplomatic immunity, were, I believe, the motivation behind this plot.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">But wait a minute, Sholmes! If this telegram really is describing the exchange of assassins as you're suggesting... ...it would mean that the Japanese killer's target was never Seishiro Jigoku at all. It would mean that Asogi's target was actually Inspector Gregson!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! Kazuma was here for Gregson?! <thought>So Judge Jigoku wasn't actually the mark?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's exactly what it would mean!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... I hold myself personally responsible for failing to keep the inspector safe.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I told him of my fears and implored him to seek a transfer to an overseas position. Obviously with the young pickpocket in tow.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, Gina...</thought> Come to think of it, Inspector Gregson did mention that to us at the Great Exhibition. That he'd be transferring to the Paris police and taking Gina with him.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But without informing me, he engaged in one last assignment, it seems. And sadly...it turned out to be his very last.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This is too much to take in...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There was no room for doubt with your instructions in this telegram, Mr Sholmes. You were very clear that it was Judge Jigoku's office that should be searched. So... ...you obviously knew that's where the list of names would be found.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">'K. Asogi / A. Shin,</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But we only learnt of those four names just over six months ago now. And only because they appeared as part of the top-secret government communications that were leaked.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">That's true, yes. But at the time, you were unaware of the background. You see, those four names were wired to Japan... ...around six months before that. Approximately this time last year in fact, when you were both still in Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It really would be hypocrisy on my part to reprove others for intercepting state secrets. Because after all... ...I'm perpetually eavesdropping on communications between the British and Japanese governments.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're perpetually doing what?! How?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Never mind the details. But you should know... ...no secret is safe from Herlock Sholmes when he has designs on knowing it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! Mr Sholmes! ...What a fabulous line!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Now, one month after that list of four names was wired to the recipient 'Jigoku' in Japan... ...Dr John H. Wilson was murdered.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As soon as I learnt of the incident, a hypothesis rapidly took shape in my mind. As it turned out, I was partly correct...and partly mistaken. Nevertheless, it was the beginning of all the tragic events that were to follow.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes, please...tell us all you know! Tell us about these four names and the tragedy to which they're all somehow connected!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There was no room for doubt with your instructions in this telegram, Mr Sholmes. You were very clear that it was Judge Jigoku's office that should be searched. So... ...you obviously knew that's where the list of names would be found.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">'K. Asogi / A. Shin,</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But we only learnt of those four names just over six months ago now. And only because they appeared as part of the top-secret government communications that were leaked.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">That's true, yes. But at the time, you were unaware of the background. You see, those four names were wired to Japan... ...around six months before that. Approximately this time last year in fact, when you were both still in Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It really would be hypocrisy on my part to reprove others for intercepting state secrets. Because after all... ...I'm perpetually eavesdropping on communications between the British and Japanese governments.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're perpetually doing what?! How?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Never mind the details. But you should know... ...no secret is safe from Herlock Sholmes when he has designs on knowing it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! Mr Sholmes! ...What a fabulous line!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Now, one month after that list of four names was wired to the recipient 'Jigoku' in Japan... ...Dr John H. Wilson was murdered.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As soon as I learnt of the incident, a hypothesis rapidly took shape in my mind. As it turned out, I was partly correct...and partly mistaken. Nevertheless, it was the beginning of all the tragic events that were to follow.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes, would you mind looking at this?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">This is hardly the time, Mr Naruhodo, as I'm sure you will appreciate.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My attention is entirely drawn to one single matter now: ...the pheasant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Anyone would think you hadn't eaten in weeks!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, quite right, Iris. We must conclude our preparations for tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What preparations?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well, I think I shall make my way back to my hotel room now. This has certainly been a night to remember!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It is a little bit sad, though.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I mean, I liked the idea of you being my daddy. Because then Susie would have been my big sister.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm sorry, Iris...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... I know, Iris. I was thinking quite the same thing.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Were you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But if somebody like me would be worthy... ...I would be delighted to become your sister!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">What? Really?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes! Without question!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">So...you'll teach me all the ways you know to throw Runo to the floor?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes yes, of course. It would be my pleasure!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You didn't have to agree quite so readily...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, but wait a minute! If Susie's going to be my big sister... ...you could be my big brother if you want, Runo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh? I, I mean, yes, of course! If you'll have me, I'll gladly be your brother.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well done, Iris. We must always be mindful of feelings. I've raised you so well! Ah ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha hah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Because being sensitive is your strong suit, naturally...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Right, I'm going to work extra hard for tomorrow now... because it's for my big brother and sister!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um... ...what is all this talk about preparing for tomorrow? Preparing what?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hee hee! You'll just have to wait and see!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Good luck in court tomorrow. I'm expecting a sterling performance!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'll do my very best, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't find anything out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Nothing particular of note...</thought></line>
</xml>