
<xml>
<title>The Monstrous Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Apollo">You okay, Athena? You've been really antsy ever since we got here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I'm just excited. This IS my first real court case after all!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yeaaah, a real ball of excitement she is... I know just what she needs.</thought> ATHENA!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eek! Didn't you ever learn about indoor and outdoor voices?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm just trying to show you the best way to relieve your pre-trial jitters.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">By scaring the daylights out of me?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, I find that shouting "I'm fine!" in a loud voice really relieves stress. It's part of my "Chords of Steel" voice workout, and a must before every trial.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-You want me to shout? Here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right. Here, I'll go first, then you try. I'm Apollo Justice and I'm fine!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">All right, um... I-I'm Athena Cykes... ...and I'm fine!!! ............Hmm... I think that actually worked!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I thought it might help. Always works for me. And old friend of mine from junior high and I say it all the time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I see... A proven remedy to calm the soul. I like it! Hey, how about we finish off with... ...a race around the courthouse!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The point is to relieve stress, not get totally exhausted!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's with all the racket, you two?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah, Mr. Wright. Heh heh, just a little voice workout. Hey, what's with the suit?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, this? I was thinking about getting my attorney's badge back, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's all?! That's huge news! ...But why now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have a feeling I'll be needed in the courtroom again sometime soon. But we can talk about that another time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>No fair. Inquiring minds want to know. But wow... I'm so used to him in his usual laid-back clothes... That suit makes him look like a million dollars.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By the way, have you heard about the prosecutor assigned to this case?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, he's serving time, but before that, he was a prosecutor. He also uses psychology...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. I've heard the rumors about how he was back before his conviction. Using the power of suggestion, he could make even the most stalwart defendants confess.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Psychology in the courtroom. Been hearing a lot about that lately.</thought> So, he must be a pretty scary guy, considering he's a prison inmate and all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So they say. They also say he'll cut you down if you talk too much.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! I knew he was gonna be bad news!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha, it's probably just hyperbole, at least I hope for your sake.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, so is it true or not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's just say you should be concise and choose your words carefully. ...if you'd like to keep that head of yours attached to the rest of your body, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yikes! <thought>Better tone down my Chords of Steel, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, are you all ready? It might be a good idea to check the Court Record again before stepping into the ring.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Right, Mr. Wright! B-But I'm fine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll be watching from the gallery. Good luck!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, let's do this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The odds of pulling this off are ridiculously low, but that's nothing new. Believe in our client. Seek the truth. That's all we can do. Hang in there, Mayor Tenma, here comes Justice!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Damian Tenma.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo Justice, defense team leader, is ready, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'd know that big, booming voice anywhere. As chipper as ever, eh, Mr. Justice? But who is the young lady next to you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm Athena Cykes, Mr. Justice's junior partner, and fresh out of law school!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, now, full of beans, too, eh? Excellent! Makes an old man feel young again. Now for the prosecution. Hmm... It appears the prosecution is not ready yet.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Never fear, for I shall explain! It's just a minor procedural complication, Your Honor. The prosecutor for this case is being escorted from prison as we speak.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prison? Oh, yes, of course. I almost forgot that he is currently serving time.</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Yup, Prosecutor Blackquill's an inmate. But even a convicted murderer's still got a job to do and duties to perform.</line>
<line speaker="???">.........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... who's that with his back to us over there?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's him. I'm sure of it. ...Prosecutor Blackquill.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*ahem* Is the prosecution ready?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...............Hmph. ......Enough jabbering. Get on with it, already.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aah! Of course, forgive me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Urngh! Why are all the people related to this case so scary?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Prosecutor Blackquill. Your opening statement if you please. Aah! Wh-What's the matter?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">......Must we continue to fritter away time like this? It is all right there in the indictment. An opening statement... would be pointless.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Pointless? Oh, um... well...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like the cat -- or in this case, the prosecutor -- has the judge's tongue.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But, but... we need an opening statement as an overview of the case at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Well, then, Your Baldness, if it's so very important, why don't you do the honors?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who?! Me?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">There's a term for people who whine and fuss about how they need silly, useless things... ...and then decide they no longer want them once it's theirs: a selfish old fool.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, was that the prosecution's opening statement?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Old dotards such as you are a plague upon the young. I pity your poor grandchildren, or is it great grandchildren?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">! All these years, I thought the opening statement was the prosecutor's job... ...but I suppose I could give it try. [sic] Might be a nice change of pace.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?! <thought>He actually fell for that?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">That must've been the power of suggestion Mr. Wright was talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*ahem* The opening statement, huh... Hmm... Let's see here... The victim was one Rex Kyubi, alderman of Nine-Tails Vale. And the defendant, Damian Tenma, mayor of Tenma Town, is accused of his murder.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...And why, pray tell, was the mayor arrested?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">His prints were on the murder weapon. Plus, he had a motive: the elimination of the biggest roadblock to the municipal merger. The caretaker and the secretary, other potential suspects, both have alibis. And his daughter, who was also in the vicinity at the time of the incident, has no motive.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">So, in a nutshell...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'd have to say the charges against the defendant are incontrovertible.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Bravo, Your Baldness. Your years of experience shine bright like your head.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho ho. Flattery will get you everywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He's playing Simon Says with the judge!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Moving right along now, let's hear from our first witness for today, Detective Fulbright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, please state your name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">I am the detective assigned to this case, Bobby Fulbright! Oh, and I'll also be keeping tabs on old Blackquill here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I also heard you would provide protection if it ever came to that.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Hmph. It would seem that I have been sorely underestimated.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait, who's protecting who from what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Still, I truly believe anyone can turn their life around, even ol' Blackquill here.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Fool Bright! Save your platitudes for funerals. Get on with your statement.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! That's the spirit! Justice must be swift and true. I see it in your eyes! There IS hope for your rehabilitation and return to society! I will never give up on you!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prosecutor Blackquill doesn't seem to intimidate Detective Fulbright.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, you know what they say: ignorance is bliss.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, so that's why Detective Fulbright was assigned to Blackquill. He's so oblivious!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, let's have your first statement, Detective Fulbright.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">You got it! But first, I'd like to say to the defense that justice will ultimately prevail!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Alderman Kyubi was murdered with a spear that had been on the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Alderman Kyubi had been slipped some kind of sleep-inducing drug?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's right. The accused was scared because the alderman was a former pro wrestler. So he slipped him a drug to make sure he'd be out cold and defenseless! Here's the autopsy report to prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And the victim managed to attack his attacker, despite being impaled by a spear?! That sounds almost superhuman. Is it even possible?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well, he WAS a former pro wrestler, after all! That spear was probably nothing more than a mosquito bite to him!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Never heard of the incredible feats of which man is capable of in a pinch, have you? Like the samurai of yore, wrestlers can battle through intense pain. It sharpens their senses. I used to talk about it with a former wrestler I met in the clink.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I dunno... It still sounds a little far-fetched.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Does it now? ......Then perhaps we should test the theory on you with the edge of my blade!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I didn't sign up for this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Hmph. And so your life is spared... for now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Please let those shackles be made of titanium... I don't want to die.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha! My investigations are as thorough as they are foolproof, or my name isn't Fulbright! I vow to resign immediately if I ever make a false arrest!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The accused's prints were on the weapon. And he's the one person without an alibi. Quite decisive evidence. Wouldn't you agree, Your Baldness?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... The defendant IS sounding guiltier by the minute.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He has the judge leaning toward a guilty verdict, and the trial's just barely begun!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. What's more, a curious rumor about the accused is making the rounds. They say he seeks the merger for the purpose of freeing Tenma Taro from his imprisonment. Truth be told, I can think of no real reason to show interest in that backwards burg. Perhaps he's a complete nutter and really does seek to release an imaginary demon. Either way, he is raving mad and more than capable of murdering the alderman.</line>
<line speaker="Man">That mayor is a strange one, all right. I heard he went to a blood drive, but instead of donating, he tried to make a withdrawal!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! There will be no gossiping in my court!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Your Baldness. Please take a gander at those charms plastered around his cranium. I hear they're meant to keep him safe from possession by the demon Tenma Taro. Then again... Perhaps he's already under the demon's spell. Behold! The lunatic appears poised to lunge at you at any moment.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Eeeep!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Come to think of it, such things don't seem relevant to the case, do they?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The prosecution will refrain from dragging our client's reputation through the mud!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Oh, what a dreadfully fearsome lass we have here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whew, thanks for that lifeline, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Careful, Apollo. He has the judge dancing in the palm of his hand! The power of suggestion is one of the more powerful tools in Simon Blackquill's arsenal. He's trying to manipulate everyone's impressions to suit his objectives.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This guy really is bad news.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">In any case, it seems the victim did manage to defend himself, despite being impaled. What sort of weapon did he used against his attacker?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">None other than this statue right here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It appears to be a statue of two strange creatures locked in battle.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Two yokai to be exact. On one side is the Nine-Tailed Fox and on the other Tenma Taro. Quite interesting if you think about it. It's as though this very case were rendered in art.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Fox and Demon Statue updated in the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice, you may proceed with your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Alderman Kyubi was murdered with a spear that had been on the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">No matter what he collected, the alderman insisted it be the real deal. For instance, he had a real demon's club in his possession. Apparently, one of his ancestors claimed it after defeating a demon in battle.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wha--?! <thought>That's got to be an old wives' tale.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! The alderman had pure, unadulterated justice flowing in his veins! Whatever he did, he did it right! We've... lost a real champion of justice in his death!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Nothing but claptrap and balderdash if you ask me. Now stop your bleating and tell us about the weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Your wish is my command!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">The fingerprints of the defendant, Damian Tenma, were found on the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hm. You do have a point there.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I'd venture to say, he did NOT wipe off the prints because he COULD not.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Looks like he wants YOU to figure it out. Well, don't just stand there! Show him who's boss!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm... totally lost... so why don't you just tell me the answer already?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't think he saw that plea for help.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">You feeling all right, kid? Running a fever, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I wish trials came with a reset button.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, the specifics may yet come to light. Please proceed, Detective Fulbright.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">At the time, Alderman Kyubi was asleep from a drug he unwittingly ingested.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Bingo! We found traces of a sleeping agent all over the inside of the cup!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">And that is why he was out cold. That is until he leapt to his feet upon being impaled by the mayor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What an awful way to wake up.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Heh. A rather stimulating eye opener if you ask me. I, too, would have risen to the attack, for to die in battle is the samurai way. Paradise awaits fallen heroes, but that hole in his stomach would make eating a challenge...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Prosecutor Blackquill, please! Those morbid jokes of yours have no place in this court!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Hmph. Says the jester in detective's guise.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Moving right along...!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Mayor Tenma attacked his helpless victim, impaling him like a human shish kebob!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Did you see those rock hard muscles of his? I'm surprised the spear even managed to pierce that armor-like musculature! I admit, I'm completely jealous of that righteous body of his, ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, he did look pretty buff, even in that suit he had on.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Quite a difference when compared with a yellowbelly like you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yellowbelly? Who even says that anymore?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, and the color's all wrong, too......... Ooh, I know! How about a squishy red tomato!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I move to strike both of your comments from the record!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice's character is not the issue here. Now, let's get back to what happened after the far more muscular alderman was impaled.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yes, well, your average person would likely have died on the spot.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">But the sudden pain jolted the victim awake, and he grabbed a statue and struck back!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Absolutely! After all, he was once a pro wrestler. The injustice of being drugged, then speared was answered with a righteous counterattack!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But does being a former pro wrestler make him superhuman?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Absolutely! After all, he was one of the good guys, like a superhero on the side of justice. Even though he was retired, he could still don his superhero guise in times of need!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Setting aside the halfwit's flights of fancy, the fact is this. The court-ordered post mortem concluded the victim moved after his skewering.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So, he found the strength somehow to attack his attacker, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Detective Fulbright's testimony sounds airtight. No wonder he's so confident.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, he only thinks it's airtight. It's up to us to poke some holes in it. That part about the alderman fighting back sounds like a big hole waiting to be poked.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did the alderman really strike the mayor?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">What?! Are you questioning my sense of justice?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your so-called "justice" need to find itself a pair of legs to stand on. You claim the alderman struck back after the mayor put a spear through him. But the statue he supposedly used to defend himself creates a major hole in your theory.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would appear that the defense has a counter-argument. Very well, let's hear what the defense thinks is odd about the detective's statue theory.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, the alderman was a former pro wrestler, so why would he even use it as a weapon? He could've defended himself with his bare hands! I mean, that's what pro wrestlers do!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. You've a lot of nerve... ...but will you raise an objection in the face of swift punishment as solicitors are wont to do?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... Well... Not if I deserve it...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And you do! The defense will look before they leap next time! Is that understood?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sorry, Your Honor! Can I try that again?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If the statue really was used as a weapon, why are there no signs of breakage?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um, Apollo? When was the last time you had your eyes examined? The statue is clearly broken. See the area around their hands?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah! Eh heh heh, guess I missed that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid I can't let that one slide without a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Please, let me try that again! <thought>Detective Fulbright claims that the alderman used the statue to attack the mayor. But there's a hole in his theory!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There are no fingerprints on this supposedly crucial piece of evidence. And if you look at the crime scene photo... ...you'll notice that the alderman isn't wearing gloves.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I believe he is quite gloveless indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If he touched the statue with his bare hands, he should've left some fingerprints! Detective Fulbright, you DID take that into account during your investigation, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Arrrrrrgh! This can't be happening! D-D-Did I arrest the wrong maaaaan?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You did it, Apollo! You knocked Detective Fulbright off his high horse!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, it's just one point in our favor.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Who do you suppose clubbed the mayor if it wasn't the alderman?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... Well, if it wasn't the alderman... ...that means someone else must've clubbed the mayor.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You mean there was a third party there in the Fox Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Exactly! And this could be the big break we've been looking for!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... There does seem to be a hole in the prosecution's argument. Prosecutor Blackquill, would you care to respond to the defense's assertion?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The least you could do is look at me while being dismissive.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Your mind is as dull as an unhoned blade, Justice-dono.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Justice... dono? <thought>He's been watching too many samurai flicks.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It will take far more than that to cut down Simon Blackquill. A whelp such as you has no hope against my superior swordsmanship.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is a trial, not a swordfight, Prosecutor Blackquill!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. There is a perfectly good explanation for the lack of prints on the statue. You might recall that bloodstained cloth found at the scene of the crime. Well, it just so happens... that the blood was the mayor's.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, um... what are you getting at?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hone your mind, boy! Why was there blood on that cloth? Solve that riddle and you shall see that the hole you thought you found is but an illusion.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now let's see... How was that cloth used...? Was it used...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The alderman was probably wearing it over his head.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wha--?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Do you truly think the alderman would show up to a meeting over the fate of his village... ...wearing this ridiculous-looking cloth over his head?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sure. They had a festival that day, didn't they? Who's to say he didn't party a little too hard and just forgot to take it off?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, fine. So maybe he didn't do that... Can I try one more time?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe the cloth was used to wipe as much of the mayor's blood as possible off the statue. And in the process, the culprit inadvertently erased the alderman's fingerprints as well.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gimme a do-over on that one! Please!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe the alderman wrapped the statue in the cloth. In short, he wasn't touching the statue directly when he used it to strike back at the mayor. Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Precisely. Bully for you, boy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aw, it was nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, don't let him start manipulating you, too! You just closed the hole for the prosecution!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I did? ............Ack, I did!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Right. That a statue wrapped in cloth would leave no fingerprints is as plain as day. But this also proves there are no holes in our theory of the alderman striking back.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Oops. Arrrrrrrrrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Now do you see how dull your mind is?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'll make sure to sharpen it next time.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">A particularly frightening inmate once told me that... ...he always tenderly honed his blades before he went to work, like the samurai of yore.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Samurai? Sounds more like a homicidal maniac to me!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Actually, he was working in the prison kitchen at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait, so the inmate was a murdering samurai prison chef?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It would seem that the victim and his killer were the only ones there after all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I was kinda attached to that hole... Now what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, I just thought of something. If they didn't find anyone's fingerprints on the statue... ...who's to say someone other than the alderman didn't hit the mayor with it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why didn't I think of that! Anybody could've NOT left prints on it!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Then who, pray tell, struck the mayor with the statue? Please, illuminate us with your wisdom, young lady.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There's only one answer -- the real killer!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Prove the existence of this "real killer" then. What evidence have you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, I'll give you evidence, all right!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena, are sure [sic] about this?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">To borrow your words, Apollo, I'm fine! Take a look at this! Black feathers and tracks, allegedly from a yokai, were found at the scene. I believe they're from the third party who struck the mayor with the statue.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is the defense actually suggesting some sort of monster killed that alderman?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's exactly what I'm suggesting!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">.........Aah! Sorry, sorry! Guess I got carried away.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice, we've no time to deal with objections between members of the defense.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sorry, Your Honor. It's just, this kid's still, well, a kid...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ouch... You meanie! I'm reporting this to Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, is this court to believe the feathers and tracks are from a "yokai" as you put it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uhh, no, Your Honor. I believe they are a fabrication. The real killer wanted us to believe some sort of monster murdered the alderman.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, interesting. And why do you suppose the killer would do that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Umm.... Why, indeed?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice, you seem as new to this as your partner is.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ouch... <thought>This, I'm not reporting to Mr. Wright...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hoy, Fool Bright, explain to His Baldness what these brats are missing. You know, the who and why behind those feathers and tracks.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wha--?! <thought>You mean you can explain all that?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! Our investigative prowess is without equal!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm starting to think I chose the wrong profession.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, let's hear about these so-called yokai feathers and tracks.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">This entire case centers on one man's attempt to crush opposition to the municipal merger!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Those feathers and tracks stoked the villager's [sic] fears?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Absolutely! He knew exactly how to prey on their superstitious minds.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Those feathers only gave weight to the idea that the alderman was slain by a demon. The accursed demon Tenma Taro, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Tenma who?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Tenma Taro -- the legendary demon locked away in the village's Forbidden Chamber. From a young age, the villagers are taught to fear the great, black-feathered demon. And thus were they blinded to other, more plausible explanations.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice, please explain yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">On the day of the incident, there was a special event held at Kyubi Manor. And as part of this event, there was someone dressed in the likeness of Tenma Taro. Obviously this person is a much more likely suspect than any legendary demon!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Listen here. The feathers and tracks were merely red herrings. The villagers believe the murder to be the work of the real Tenma Taro. However, the police believe that the person in the Tenma Taro suit is the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ahh!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The defendant sought to sow this confusion in order to deflect blame away from himself. However, he was knocked unconscious by the alderman... ...and thus our mentally deficient mayor was caught red-handed at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Right. It was the mayor's last-ditch effort to stop the opposition before things got crazy. The Amazing Nine-Tails was fueling both the yokai craze and the anti-merger movement. Plus, he's one of the better-known masked wrestlers, and the hometown favorite. That's why the mayor panicked and set out on the path of injustice.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But do the people of Nine-Tails Vale really believe a yokai is behind the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yokai sightings are an everyday event there, so I wouldn't be surprised if they did.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I must say... A crime that preys upon innocent, impressionable minds.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Just so. A particularly silver-tongued inmate once had the following words for me. The innocent of heart are the easiest prey.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't say? Was this inmate a con artist?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........No. He was framed for the murder of his beloved. I actually felt sorry for the poor chap.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait, so he wasn't the predator, but rather the prey?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, well... Now then, the defense may proceed with their cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">This entire case centers on one man's attempt to crush opposition to the municipal merger!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Oh, absolutely! They parade around in yokai costumes shouting, "Down with Mayor Tenma!" And just the other day, they stormed Tenma City Hall, claiming it was a den of vipers!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. But when the accused showed his face... ...the angry mob scattered like leaves upon an autumn wind. For you see, lowly yokai are no match for Tenma Taro, the Dark Lord of their kind.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, are the villagers scared of Mayor Tenma or Tenma Taro? I'm confused.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think he means Mayor Tenma. It's easy to get the wrong impression about the guy.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Detective Fulbright, why do you suppose the defendant would commit such an act?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Mayor Tenma panicked when The Amazing Nine-Tails helped embolden the protestors.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's right. And he was a lone wolf, or in other words, he didn't belong to a wrestling federation. He appeared like a shooting star, defeating one Tenma Town wrestler after another. And before anyone knew it, he was a champion!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Like the samurai of yore, surrounded thick with enemies, he cut them down one by one. It was a complete and utter loss of face for Tenma Town Pro Wrestling.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">He was amazing! If ever there was a real superhero, it would be him! I dream of becoming a true champion of justice like him someday!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I bet Detective Fulbright would be a great pro wrestler. He could even team up with Prosecutor Blackquill.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A police detective and a prisoner in chains? .........You know, I think people would actually pay to see that. I know I would.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha. So you DO understand the greatness that is The Amazing Nine-Tails!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">So he stoked the villagers' fears by fabricating a monster!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Absolutely! It had an immediate effect! The presumed return of the dreaded Tenma Taro has them shaking in their boots!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh my, is it really that bad?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph, that superstitious lot? It's as if Jack the Ripper had been set loose in their village. The mere thought of that demon lurking about is enough to spark a mass exodus.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... That's a very persuasive argument.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The mere thought of His Honor buying into Simon the Psycho-Slasher's words... ...makes me want to spark my own exodus out of the courtroom right about now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">So you see, there can be only one reason why anyone would plant those feathers and tracks!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">The strange feathers and tracks he planted made it look like a yokai was the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hm? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You claim that our client planted the yokai evidence to stoke the villagers' fears. If so, then why not stop there? Why murder Alderman Kyubi?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Excellent point.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It is, isn't it! So, Your Honor agrees there was no reason for the murder, correct?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're saying it wasn't premeditated?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">From the outset, I had no intention of paying heed to any of your babble. However, the fact is, the mayor made a startling discovery.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A startling discovery? <thought>Why don't I like the sound of that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Alderman Kyubi's secret identity.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo... I think Prosecutor Blackquill has figured out the alderman's secret identity. But even if he has, why would it be a motive for the mayor to commit murder?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...This is not good!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">This patch of fur was discovered at the crime scene. It's from the mask worn by The Amazing Nine-Tails. Therefore, we can conclude that this mask was at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my. But why would it have been there?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The victim was a former pro wrestler and a member of the anti-merger movement. ...Need I say more?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, um............ Ah! C-Could it really be?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Your Baldness has had an epiphany I see. Our victim, Rex Kyubi, was The Amazing Nine-Tails! And the mayor's discovery of such was his motive for murder!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Noooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order!!! What a shocking development. A motive clearer than crystal clear!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What do we do now, Apollo?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I didn't think they'd tie the alderman's secret identity to the mayor's motive for murder!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">At last we've reached my real point: why did the alderman have to forge a secret identity? Does it not pique your interest, Your Baldness?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I admit it does... It IS odd that he had to create this other persona... ...just to secretly participate in the anti-merger movement.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Very astute of you, Your Baldness.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Right, now take a look at this! If you value your dearest's life, you will merge Nine-Tails Vale with Tenma Town. This blackmail letter was found in Alderman Kyubi's pocket!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Wh-Whaaaaaat!!!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">At present, the alderman's wife is in the hospital. And that letter is clear evidence the mayor was blackmailing him by threatening her life.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, didn't the blackmail letter sent to Mayor Tenma go missing... ...right after the alderman's murder?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You think maybe the killer took the letter from the mayor after the murder... ...and planted it into the alderman's pocket?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's possible... but we don't have any proof that that's what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Talk about being up the creek without a paddle...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Mayor Tenma would've made a clean getaway if he'd just left after planting the yokai things. But he was knocked out cold by his sudden decision to kill The Amazing Nine-Tails!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, it was The Amazing Nine-Tails's counterattack that brought the entire crime to light.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait a sec... <thought>Fulbright's claiming that the mayor killed the alderman after planting the yokai evidence. And that the mayor was knocked out cold immediately after that?</thought> Detective Fulbright, please add your previous statement to your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"Mayor Tenma killed the sleeping alderman after planting the feathers and tracks."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's right. The motive only came after he discovered the alderman's secret identity!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Well, I guess that does make sense.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What do we do now, Apollo?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I didn't think they'd tie the alderman's secret identity to the mayor's motive for murder.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Let's get on with the testimony, shall we!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Mayor Tenma killed the sleeping alderman after planting the feathers and tracks.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Absolutely! And then he was knocked out cold by the alderman's last punch! He wouldn't have had a chance to plant the evidence after that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... Something's not right here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hard to believe that a stiff, humorless man like the mayor could be behind such a stunt.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Argh... We have to do something, Apollo, before they pin it all on the mayor!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then we're going to need to prove that Mayor Tenma didn't plant that yokai stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">How are we supposed to do that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Detective Fulbright, your sense of justice is anything but fair!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">What's this?! You are question my justice again?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, and I'm going to prove it to you. Take a look at this photo.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This... is the crime scene photo. And just what does this prove?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It proves when the feathers and tracks were planted.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">But I already told you, they were planted before the murder! The defendant planted the yokai evidence, then was knocked out cold while killing his victim!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But that would be impossible. If you look right here, it's clear when the feathers and tracks were left at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The only thing clear to me is that the defense is barking up the wrong tree.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Really up a tree now, aren't we?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, and a stiff penalty should help you learn that correct assertions don't grow on them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh... I wonder if bandages do... <thought>There is clearly something wrong with the assertion that... ...the feathers and tracks were there before the murder.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aren't you just pointing to the yokai feathers and tracks, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes. See how the feathers are on top of the blood, and the tracks were made in blood? In other words, the yokai evidence could've only resulted AFTER the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Th-Then the mayor must've planted the evidence after killing the alderman!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But you said it yourself, the mayor had been knocked unconscious thereafter. There would've been no time for him to plant any evidence at all! Therefore! There must've been someone else besides the mayor and the alderman at the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Arrrrrrgh! There must be some mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order!!!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Wh-Where's your evidence?! You can't possibly have any, can you?! Ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Evidence? Oh, I have evidence. In fact, I have an eye-witness's testimony for you.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">You do?! But hooooow?! Was my vaunted sense of justice really just half-baked?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He's taking this really hard.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Mr. Justice. What is this testimony regarding a third party that you claim to have?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I have it right here, Your Honor. It's the sworn testimony of Mr. Tenma's daughter. The witness, Jinxie Tenma, saw a yokai in the hallway after stumbling upon the scene. It was the demon Tenma Taro... He's the source of those feathers and tracks!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">.........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Will somebody please say something?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...The defense will explain to the court exactly what he means.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">You... You dare to mock this court and justice itself?! You're unfit to bear your name, boy!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You Baldness, it appears our defense attorney here is delirious from exhaustion.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you think I'm trying to do?! Before you decide whether I should step down, please... hear me out...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Justice, I'm all ears. But you had better explain yourself well. What was this yokai you were talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's all in this statement here -- Jinxie Tenma asserts that she saw Tenma Taro. After she discovered the crime scene and called the police... ...she came around a corner in the hall. It was around here... ...that she saw Tenma Taro fleeing toward the foyer! The defense asserts that whoever was impersonating this monster... ...is the one who left those feathers and tracks behind, intentionally or otherwise!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Whaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">How incredibly unjust! Why haven't I heard about this before?!</line>
<line speaker="Man">The defense just proved there was someone else!</line>
<line speaker="Woman">So the mayor isn't the killer?</line>
<line speaker="Man">Was it all just a set up? The prosecutor IS a convicted felon, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! The momentum has shifted in our favor!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Good. Now let's keep it that way!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">My sword? <thought>I didn't know I had one to break.</thought> Are you implying there's a problem with my claim?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Consider this: if that yokai impersonator had indeed fled toward the foyer... ...that fool and that fop would have seen him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Fool and fop? Oh, you mean Filch and L'Belle. Hmm, now that you mention it...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Both Phineas Filch and Florent L'Belle were in the foyer at the time. But they haven't stated that they saw a yokai, have they? Did you ever consider that yokai was but a figment of a scared little girl's imagination?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Argh. Why DIDN'T those two see the Tenma Taro impersonator pass by?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why don't we ask them ourselves?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I was just about to say that myself. No, really, I was! The defense would like to call Mr. Phineas Filch, caretaker of Kyubi Manor to the stand! I just know he must have seen something!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I suppose we can't ignore the fact that the little girl believes she saw a monster. I trust you have no objections to Mr. Justice's request, Prosecutor Blackquill? I understand that Mr. Filch is enjoying a nap out in the lobby.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. I knew that tanuki was a rare find. But when we captured him, I didn't think he'd end up a witness. Do with him as you will.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>D-Did he just say captured? No, wait. I don't want to know.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, then. Bailiff, please go wake Mr. Filch and escort him to the witness stand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Will the witness state his name and occupation, please.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">The name's Filch, Phineas Filch, caretaker of Kyubi Manor. Oh, and... This is for you, Your Lordship. Just a little something I though ya might like.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my, what a fabulous pair of shoes! And "Your Honor" will do just fine, Mr. Filch.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Ah! It's those shoes again!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um... Don't they belong to Detective Fulbright?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't tell me Filch stole them again.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">They're all yours, Your Honorship, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?! But they seem awfully expensive.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yep, too expensive for me, but I reckon they'd be perfect for someone like Your Honorship.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It's a kind gesture, but legal ethics dictate I can't accept such gifts.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Aw, ethics smethics. Just take 'em if ya want 'em. Polished 'em up real nice for ya, too.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sorry about the shoes, Mr. Filch, but I WILL accept your testimony. The court would like to hear whether you saw Tenma Taro in the foyer after the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">At the time of the murder I was on guard duty in the foyer, just like Mr. Kyubi's asked.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">That yokai you keep jabbering on about was but a phantom of a little girl's dreams.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you're telling this court you never saw anyone dressed up like Tenma Taro?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yep! Was guarding the whole time. That's the truth, the holy truth, 'n' nutter-butter the truth! And Tenma Taro? Bah, ya don't really believe in all that yokai mumbo jumbo, do ya? I certainly don't!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hm? <thought>My bracelet, it's...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Something the matter, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">My bracelet keeps squeezing my arm.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really? So you think Mr. Tanuki--er, I mean, Filch has been lying to us?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wouldn't rule it out. <thought>Now, if I could just zero in on a tell -- some sort of nervous habit...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">*Screech!*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A-Aaaaaaagh! What in the--?! <thought>W-What's a hawk doing in here!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Allow me to introduce my trusty cohort, Taka. He seems to have taken quite a liking to the courthouse. Made it his new home, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...He doesn't live with you... you know, in jail? <thought>Who's ever heard of a courthouse bird?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Taka simply loathes trickery and fraud. And that queer power of yours seems to have offended my dear, bosom buzzard.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This isn't some sort of trick or-- Aaaaaaaaaagh! <thought>I won't be able to spot squat like this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Filch">Wh-What the heck's goin' on 'round here?! Run for the hills!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">N-No pets or other animals allowed in the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Taka">*Screech!*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ack! Somebody help!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Oh, he's merely having a bit of sport. He won't harm you, save when truly famished.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In that case, Prosecutor Blackquill, you will ensure your feathered friend is properly fed.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Looks like we have to do this the old-fashioned way.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We'll be fine... I think. <thought>If there was someone dressed as Tenma Taro there, Filch should've seen him. We'll just have to put our faith in Jinxie's statement for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice, please proceed with your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">At the time of the murder I was on guard duty in the foyer, just like Mr. Kyubi's asked.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Eh-heh heh... 'Cause he trusts me. I AM the manor's caretaker, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you took said guard duty seriously?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Eh-heh heh... Lemme tell ya something about me. I'm-- Yipes!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Listen here, you little tanuki. Get straight to the point and be quick about it. The court wishes to hear what you did or didn't see in the foyer, and naught else.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Y-Yes, of course, sir! Right away, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Blackquill's got him completely under his thumb.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Filch">Like I said, I was guarding the foyer entrance that day!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">I was making sure no one -- fair, foul, fishy, or otherwise -- could get to our guest.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">That's 'cause there's always lotsa sneaks 'n' thieves 'round festival time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And the solution was to entrust the manor's security to a thief? That's not even funny.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe it's a matter of stopping thieves by hiring one. After all, it takes one to know one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I dunno, it seems more like letting the fox guard the henhouse to me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. So, the witness testifies that he took his guard duty seriously?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yes, sir, Your Honorship, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">I was still in my office keeping a good watch when the murder happened after 3 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">*sigh* Poor old Filchy... Been working hard my whole life... ...only to be smeared by some greenhorn in his fancy-schmancy suit and silly haircut. Ah! Sorry, sorry, Mr. Blackquill, sir! Didn't mean to get off subject there!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sheesh... Blackquill didn't even say anything.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Filch">To answer your question, yes, I kept an eye -- no, both of 'em, in fact -- on the foyer!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">But I didn't see nothing outta the ordinary, no siree!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Someone all fidgety and shifty-like, you know, like they're about to steal something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He......... just described himself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wonder why Mr. Filch didn't see Tenma Taro.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe Jinxie only thinks she saw Tenma Taro. Or...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe Mr. Filch is lying.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And if he's lying, we might be able to spot a contradiction in his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't lie to the court like that, Mr. Filch.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Hey, it ain't right to bushwhack a fella like that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Unfortunately for you, I have evidence that proves you're lying. If you look at this TV listing here, you'll see that at the time of the crime... ...there was a pro wrestling match scheduled -- something you'd never miss.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Ack! I didn't watch that one, no siree! I was doing my job, just like I was s'pposed to!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This guy doesn't know when to give up.</thought> Mr. Filch. Someone even circled the match. It was you, right?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yipes!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not only that, you even told me you watched it. You said, and I quote: "It was a complete disaster."</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Hrrrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, do you admit to slacking off?!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Y-Y-You can't trick me with your rudy poo lawyer talk! I'm one of them professional-types, too! I can do double-duty, watching TV and the foyer at the same time!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The only thing Filch can claim to be a professional of is "professional thief"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice. You would have this court believe the witness was slacking off?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's correct. He claims to have been watching TV and the foyer at the same time. But that's nothing but a bald-faced lie!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bald, you say? But I'M not the one who's lying! Perhaps you meant the witness, Mr. Justice? And in that case, let's see what evidence you can offer. You claim Mr. Filch is lying about watching TV and the foyer simultaneously. Now, prove it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm? How does that prove anything?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, it, um... <thought>Whoops! Way off on that one!</thought> Heh heh, sorry. Don't know what I was thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, well, I have moments like that myself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Whew, looks like he'll let this one slide.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">But random guesses and speculation must be punished!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yargh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! We should think about how Mr. Filch was when he was watching TV!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Please, lemme try that one again!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense will look before they leap this time. So, what do you have for us, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Please take a look at the direction the TV is facing in this diagram. Now, unless Mr. Filch has eyes where his right ear should be... ...I'd think it would be impossible to watch the foyer entrance and the TV at the same time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, yes! Someone watching TV there couldn't possibly see the entrance!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Exactly. And that means, Mr. Filch... ...you were slacking off and were NOT watching the foyer as you claim!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yiiipes! The bag's outta the cat! Er, I mean, other way 'round!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!!! But Mr. Justice, is Mr. Filch's less-than-stellar work ethic relevant to this case?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's very relevant, because while he was slacking off watching TV... ...there really could've been a Tenma Taro impersonator in the foyer!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Granted, this tanuki was law in his duties, but he still had the foyer entrance covered.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........This.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... I'm not a mind reader. Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Auditory sense. His eyes may have been slacking off, but his ears were still hard at work. Right, tanuki?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">...They were? ............Er, I mean, yes! Yes they were!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But you already admitted to slacking off. Now you say you weren't?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">My eyes might be lazy, but my ears ain't. I woulda heard anyone in the foyer, eh-heh. Ya see, the foyer floor and stairway get all creaky squeaky when someone walks on 'em! Creak, creak, creak! Loud enough to wake the dead, I reckon!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you're saying you didn't hear anybody walk by?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yep! My ears were working fulltime. So, who's the liar now, ya no-good shyster!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A lying thief calling me a shyster. This HAS to be the low point of my fledgling career...</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Gotta hand it to ya, Mr. Blackquill, sir, ya really are something else, eh-heh heh! I mean, ya don't miss a thing. And them bags under yer eyes? They're darker than mine!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Fair warning, Mr. Filch. Taka is particularly fond of tanuki. Should you lie to this court again, you may suddenly find yourself on the menu.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yiiiiiipes! Please don't eat me, Mr. Taka, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness will henceforth testify truthfully under penalty of painful bird attacks! And with that in mind, the court requests that the witness revise his testimony accordingly.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">It's true, I was watching a pro wrestling match on the office TV.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Superstition is the religion of feeble minds. Understand? A simple, rational explanation is best. Forget yokai, demons, and such. We must use common sense, for lacking that, our entire world would be but upside-down.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Says the convict prosecutor who is totally a sign of the end times for the legal world.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Filch">And besides, if there were any yokai roaming about, I'd nab 'em 'n' sell 'em to the zoo!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wonder whether Jinxie was just seeing things.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That seems to be the general consensus, but I'm sticking to my guns.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But if we can't prove she saw Tenma Taro, the mayor's sure to be convicted!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then we'd better hope my guns fire bullets, not BB's...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">It's true, I was watching a pro wrestling match on the office TV.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">A-A-Arrgghh! B-B-B-But...! It ain't easy being me! I mean, I can't watch TV when we have visitors and there's no way to record stuff!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sorry, am I supposed to be consoling you over your first-world problems?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">If those are his only problems, he should consider himself lucky.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess pro wrestling's serious business to Mr. Filch.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">My eyes mighta been slacking off, but my ears? They were working overtime.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Oh, uh, that? Ain't no harm in bending the truth a little, right?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Listen to me, you little tanuki. Lie again and Taka shall feast upon that forked tongue of yours.</line>
<line speaker="Taka">*Screech!*</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yiiipes! Sorry! Just lemme keep my tongue!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>At least leave it until we get the truth out of him, in any case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You were negligent in your duties, were you not?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yes, sir, I was sir! But it ain't like that...</line>
<line speaker="Filch">The floor there's all creaky squeaky-like. No way I woulda missed someone walking by.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">As good as they come, I'd say. Ain't nothin' to hear a creaky floor. Plus, that Tenma Taro makes a sound when he goes by. It's like a jingle jangle.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Jingle jangle? How does he do that?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">It's that staff o' his. That's what jingle jangles.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's he talking about, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Beats me, but I guess Tenma Taro has a staff that makes noise.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Come to think of it, didn't Jinxie mention something like that, too? She said she saw Tenma Taro holding a staff-like object that made a jangly sound.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess that's the source of the noise then...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? Mr. Filch says Tenma Taro "jingle jangles." Would you consider that vital information?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Doesn't seem particularly important to me.</thought> No, Your Honor. I don't think it's of any importance.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness may continue with his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Extremely vital! I request that it be added to his testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"If Tenma Taro was to pass by, his staff woulda gone jingle jangle."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Nope, not even a ninja. That's 'cause even the tiniest mouse makes that floor creak, eh-heh. Real creaky squeaky, it is!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I can vouch for the tanuki's keen ears. He came running from across the building the moment Fool Bright dropped his wallet. And true to his name, Filch filched it before Mr. Less-Than-Bright knew what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's some scary good hearing.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Wads o' cash or expensive shoes on the pavement... Sounds like that don't get by ol' Filch's ears. Got years o' practice, eh-heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Remind me not to bring anything of value to the manor next time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The sound of shoes makes sense, but wads of cash? What does that sound like? ...Anyway, it sounds like they need to hire somebody to take care of their caretaker.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">If Tenma Taro was to pass by, his staff woulda gone jingle jangle.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yep, like a jingle and a jangle.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, Jinxie said something like that. Something about Tenma Taro making a jangly sound.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmmm... I think we're missing something here, but I can't quite put a finger on it. <thought>Perhaps I should take a look at the Court Record again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">So ya see, there weren't no Tenma Taro in the foyer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">She's always going on about seeing this yokai or that. Just an active imagination, I reckon. She won't even come near me 'cause she thinks I'm some sorta tanuki monster!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Can't say I blame her.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, Mr. Filch, you'd chalk it up to a child's active imagination?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yep. No Tenma Taro or anyone else got in or outta Kyubi Manor on my watch.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, what could this mean? Do you think Jinxie was just seeing things?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, if that's the case, the details she provided were pretty impressive. But if we're to continue believing Jinxie's statement...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We'll have to uncover Filch's lie?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right, or.... find out why he can't tell the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tenma Taro's staff would make a jangly sound, you say? Well, I'm going to say that your story doesn't add up.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is there something the defense would like to share with the court?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Filch, you say that you didn't see Tenma Taro on the day of the incident. Why then, did you assume just now that Tenma Taro would be holding a staff?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You see, the Tenma Taro Jinxie saw held a staff in his hands. And she described its sound just like you did -- as a kind of jangly sound.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yeah, so he was holding a staff. What's yer point?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You see, this is the only known document depicting Tenma Taro. Is there a staff in that picture, Mr. Filch?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're right! There's no staff! Not even a cane or a walking stick!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, the question is, why does the witness think Tenma Taro uses a staff?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I believe the answer will overturn the prosecution's case on the most basic level!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........Well now, this IS getting interesting.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right, Mr. Justice, it's time to show the court where you're going with this. Please tell the court why Mr. Filch believes Tenma Taro carries a staff.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe the scroll is incorrect. There could be an older drawing that shows Tenma Taro with a staff. And Mr. Filch could have seen that.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. If that were the case... ...then the fact that the witness believes Tenma Taro had a staff would not be an issue.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, in that case, I retract my previous statement.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not so fast, Mr. Justice. You must be held accountable for your flights of fancy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Argh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ouch. A legal smack down...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Filch believes Tenma Taro has a staff... ...despite the fact that Tenma Taro has never been drawn that way! So how could he have possibly known about the staff?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's try that again, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Filch obviously has a few screws loose. So, it's no surprise he would make a mistake like that!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Now, hold it right there! As caretaker o' Kyubi Manor, I keep every screw nice 'n' tight!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I rest my case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">With an assertion like that, this court wonders whether the defense has a screw loose, too. Here's a penalty to make sure you keep your screws in tighter next time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Filch believes Tenma Taro has a staff... ...despite the fact that Tenma Taro has never been drawn that way! So how could he have possibly known about the staff?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's try that again, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Filch actually saw Tenma Taro right after the crime occurred! That's the only way he could possibly know about the staff!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">B-B-Busted again!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Bloody hell! You duplicitous little--!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yes! How'd that feel, Blackquill? Not so fun when you're on the receiving end of the blade, is it!</thought> Admit it, Mr. Filch! You DID see Tenma Taro that day, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Um... Uhhhhhh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well?!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">I'm beggin' ya! Please don't make me say it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But you clearly did see Tenma Taro! Stop stalling and testify to that fact!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">No can do! No way, no how! You ain't got no idea how terrifying he can be!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...He? <thought>Mr. Filch still won't admit seeing Tenma Taro, even though everyone already knows he did. The question now is, why?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Filch is scared to death!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is that why he can't admit the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... Come to think of it...</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">They say you must not gaze upon Tenma Taro. But in the event that you do look... ...and then tell anyone what you saw, Tenma Taro will claim your soul.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Jinxie wouldn't admit to seeing Tenma Taro after hearing about the village superstitions. She said that if she told anyone that she had seen Tenma Taro, he'd claim her soul.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, you think Filch believes that, too?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Ah! So Mister Big-Time, City-Slicker Lawyer has heard about 'em?! Them old village superstitions?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Will the defense please explain what the witness is talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The people of Nine-Tails Vale believe some pretty strange things. And their superstitions may be the reason our witness here can't admit the truth... ...the truth that he really did see Tenma Taro.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">D-Darn straight, that's why! It's all right here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ignoring the superstitions will cost you your soul?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">See?! That's why us folks in Nine-Tails Vale can't talk about seeing Tenma Taro!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That clears up one mystery. The killer took advantage of the superstitions by wearing a Tenma Taro costume. They knew that that way no one could talk about him, so it was as if he never existed! The defense holds that this Tenma Taro impersonator is the true killer!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Grr! Raaaaaaaaaaawwwwwwrrrrrrrrrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order, I say!!!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You fool of a tanuki! Two times now, your lies have cost me!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">S-S-Sorry, sorry! I promise not to do it again!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Taka, my fine-feathered friend, have at him!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yiiipes! He's gonna eat me alive! Head for the hills!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah! He took off.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-B-Bailiff! What are you waiting for?! After him -- and with your fastest men!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's certainly not something you see every day.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, it would seem a new and important fact has come to light. A third party disguised as the yokai Tenma Taro was at the scene. And now we have two witnesses who can attest to that fact. Any objections, Prosecutor Blackquill?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.............................. ..............................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh-oh...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wha--?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Huh? ............Ahhhhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">His shackles...! Urk! <thought>I... I'm too young to die!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Justice-dono, long has it been since I've been forced to draw my blade. You had best say your prayers.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeek! D-Detective, do something!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! Have no fear, Fulbright is here! When the going gets tough, the Champion of Justice gets going!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Oh, but I stand in awe of Simon Blackquill, for it is his sense of justice that set him free!</line>
<line speaker="Judge"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn> <cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn> I object to Detective Fulbright's definition of justice!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. I'm not in the habit of cutting down unarmed cowards.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, w-well, in that case, Prosecutor Blackquill, can I ask you to, umm, you know...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think the judge forgot he's in charge here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">So, Justice-dono's assertion is this: Tenma Taro is the real killer, not Mayor Tenma. According to him, there was a yokai at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right! And that yokai, or rather, whoever was impersonating him, killed Alderman Kyubi!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Care to explain why Jinxie, being the first to discover the murder... ...did not see your alleged killer yokai there in the Fox Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? <thought>He's right, she said nothing about Tenma Taro being in the Fox Chamber...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........Hmph. Let me enlighten you. That little scamp heard a dying scream right before she opened the chamber door.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...And your point is...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Upon opening the door, she found a freshly skewed murder victim -- the alderman... ...and the homicidal maniac who had killer him -- the mayor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, there must've been someone dressed up like Tenma-- Aagh!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Then why does that little scamp claim not to have seen a yokai in the Fox Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Considering her father is accused of murder... ...surely she would've mentioned any third party that might have been in the room.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't understand. Why didn't she see Tenma Taro inside the Fox Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. There is but one way to find out: Ask Jinxie Tenma whether she saw your killer yokai at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh-oh...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The final battle draws nigh. Only one of us will leave here alive. Heh heh heh. Long has my blade thirsted for blood. At long last, it shall be sated!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, this IS still a trial, right?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Show me what you're truly capable of, Justice-dono!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">V-Very well, then. Both parties no doubt need some time to regroup... ...so the court will take a 10-minute recess in order to-- Aagh!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Three minutes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I'm sorry, but... a three-minute recess?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Just so. Plenty of time if your destination of intent is the loo.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The loo? You mean the bathroom?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sheesh... At least include enough time to wash our hands.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">See that you take no more than three minutes. All latecomers will be punished.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes, sir! I hereby declare a three-minute recess before the battle begins!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I declare Prosecutor Blackquill the winner of this round of Simon Says...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Doesn't bode well for us if the prosecutor is running the show, does it...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He busted out of his shackles.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, what was that about? Guess they don't make shackles like they used to.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Better be careful, Apollo. You've really brought out the samurai in him. Especially after you proved there was a Tenma Taro impersonator at the manor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's with that guy and the whole samurai act, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Such fine swordsmanship... That is no mere act. Mr. Justice, it's high time I challenge this jailhouse prosecutor to a duel!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, wait! Let's save the dueling until after we prove your innocence!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Hrmmm... I suppose it could wait till later.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>*sigh* Does ANYONE remember we're conducting a trial here?</thought> Athena, I'm gonna go wash up.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Remember what Blackquill said, Apollo. Don't be late!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, I believe our next witness is Ms. Jinxie Tenma, a maid at Kyubi Manor. I believe we can proceed now -- if the witness is ready, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">N-N-Nurarihyon! Leader of the One Hundred Demons! He really does exist!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow... That is one well-polished tray...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness will show her face while in court, or her testimony will be inadmissible.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, my child?!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Be gone, Nurarihyon, Leader of the One Hundred Demons!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho ho. You think I'm a yokai? Well, I WAS once known as a judicial monster of sorts. The beast of the bar, the demon of due process, if you will.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Eek! My charm has no effect...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The demon of due process? Not sure I can see that one...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........Now, you little scamp.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I trust you know why you're here.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">.........B-B-Bags.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Bags? Oh, that tricksy tanuki? Try the noodle stand. And go enjoy a big bowl of tanuki tail noodles why you're at it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Everyone's a comedian.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">No... I meant YOUR bags. The one's [sic] under your eyes. You must have trouble sleeping. Here. This charm will keep Azukiarai away.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Azukiarai? The yokai that washes azuki beans? The only thing needing washing will be your father's neck before I take his head clean off!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Azukiarai often keeps people up at night with the noise he makes washing beans. But if you stick this charm on your forehead, you won't hear him anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........I-Is that so? Well, thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Looks like Prosecutor Blackquill got more than he bargained for.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They're bad enough alone, but together, those two are just plain creepy.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your testimony, if you please, Ms. Tenma. Specifically, whether or not you saw Tenma Taro when you discovered the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Did I see Tenma Taro in the Fox Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So there was a yokai at the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">*shiver* Uh-huh, lots... and lots of them!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, more than one yokai? Did Tenma Taro happen to be among them?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">I don't know! I just don't know! All I know is the room was swimming in yokai! Kasha, Nurikabe, Setotaisho! Eeek! They were all there!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well this is an unexpected turn of events. We've gone from no yokai to a flood of them.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">This is ludicrous. You would have this court listen to this delusional little scamp's testimony?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yurk!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What a fabulous idea! Please proceed, Ms. Cykes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You sure you know what you're doing, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">She's obviously not herself. The trauma of discovering that crime scene... ...and fear of testifying have her dazed and confused. A regular ball of confusion! But my analytical psychology-based approach should be able to help.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Any objections, Prosecutor Blackquill? Shall we let Ms. Cykes proceed?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Hmph. It makes no difference to me. Do as you will, but I doubt we shall get any viable testimony. She'd be better served by bearing witness to the sword skills I forged in a distant land!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmph! I'll show you!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Did I see Tenma Taro in the Fox Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Well, when I opened the door... *shiver* I saw... I saw...</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Yes! Now I remember!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Y-Y-Yokai! Yokai! Right there in that room!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Found something! Hmm... Looks like an out-of-control emotion.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, Athena? What exactly are we looking at here?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, this? It's one of Widget's functions. Right here you can see images and emotions extracted from the witness's voice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa! You mean that little thing can do all this?!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Pretty cool, huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And here I thought it was just some kids' toy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Unfortunately, all I'm getting is an overflow error right now. See how Sad is brightly lit there at the bottom left? She's under an uncontrollable amount of distress, which is masking her other emotions. It seems the sheer terror she experienced has made her a confused mess.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So all those yokai she thinks she saw are a product of rampant emotions?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, that's right. Her fear has instilled in her hallucinations and false memories. She's seeing normal everyday objects as monsters in her mind. It's a form of schizophrenic hallucination brought on by emotional trauma. And the trauma in Jinxie's case is fear.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So she was, and still is, seeing ordinary objects as yokai...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">We'll have to find the root cause of her extreme fear before I can treat it. Now, let's see... Apollo, can you point out the yokai on the wheel of fire? She seems particularly terrified of that one. Start by tapping Probe <thought>L</thought> on the bottom screen. Next, point to what's causing Jinxie's out-of-control emotion. Finally, tap Probe again <thought>X</thought> to try and get to the heart of the matter!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Okay, let's give this a try.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Jinxie, what's the name for that yokai on a wheel of fire?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Th-That's... a Kasha, a yokai that steals the bodies of the recently deceased! I bet it came to steal the alderman's!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's almost creepy how well that fits the actual situation.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Exactly! It's a form of hallucination where the patient can't see things for what they are! There must be something at the scene of the crime that she's mistaking for a Kasha! Apollo, you need to point out what she thought was a yokai on a wheel of fire!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... I think I know the answer now.</thought> Jinxie, that wasn't a Kasha you saw. Could you have possibly mistaken this for a Kasha?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? That thing?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">I'd never mistake that for a Kasha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You have to consider what a Kasha looks like, Apollo. Think, brightly blazing wheel near the ceiling.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Okay... Let's give this another try.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">The light fixture?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This one right here. It has a flame design and is up there on the ceiling. There was never a yokai on a wheel of fire. The Kasha you saw was just a light fixture!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Eeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's one memory back to normal! Nice job! Now that you've got the hang of it, it should be a cinch to point out the rest!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Jinxie! What about this white wall-like monster?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Th-That's Nurikabe! It's a wall monster that blocks your way or leads you astray!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's no yokai, Jinxie! It's a folding screen!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Eeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And this racoon dog isn't a tanuki monster, it's just the statue of one!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Eeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And look! These are just coffee cups. And this right here? It's nothing more than a fox statue!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Eeeeeeeeeeeek! I don't know what I was thinking!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You did it, Apollo! Her extreme fear is under control now!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">It was all just my eyes playing tricks on me. There weren't any yokai after all!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">See! A clear-cut statement. That's the power of my psychology and your intuition, Apollo! And just like we thought, there never really were any yokai in the Fox Chamber!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........Right. There never really were any yokai there. So, the defense is asserting the exact opposite of their original assertion?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............Wait. Um, Jinxie? What about Tenma Taro?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">There wasn't anyone there dressed up as Tenma Taro, or any other yokai, either. I remember it clearly now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You've--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Gotta--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Be--</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think we just dug our own grave.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Allow me to push you on in. It's the least I can do.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nooo...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! Can I interrupt your freak-out for just a minute? I'm still picking up some noise! It's an unexpected emotion!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Does that mean Jinxie hasn't remembered everything yet?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Exactly! We should be able to get something else out of her! I'll enter the new information we have and run an update!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Did I see Tenma Taro in the Fox Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">I was so scared when I entered the room...</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">... my legs gave out and I fell to the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">There in the Fox Chamber I saw... *shiver*</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">...the alderman dead on a table and papa collapsed in a chair.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Nobody else was there! And that includes Tenma Taro!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait. What am I supposed to do?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Try to find the emotions that contradict her statements.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So if I find a contradictory emotion, I should point it out?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right. But it's not just contradictory emotions you should look out for. You should also keep an eye out for sudden changes in an emotion's intensity. Her emotions might get stronger or weaker as you move from statement to statement. It's important to compare how the same emotion changes throughout the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Contradictory emotions and changes in intensity... Okay, I'll give it a shot.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The amount of fear you felt is rather low despite your legs having given out from fright. Could something have lessened your fear?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Actually, I did experience a sudden burst of courage at that moment.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You did? Where did it come from?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Um... uh... Let me think... Oh, it was Mama. I suddenly felt as if she was there with me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, I'll enter, "Sudden burst of courage." Now, let's see... Ah! Look! Apollo, the noise is all gone! Jinxie seems to have remembered everything now!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A sudden burst of courage... Now where could that have come from? Jinxie, was there something that gave you a sudden burst of courage?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Um, yes there was, b-but... um... I, uh... I realized I had done something naughty when I thought about it later.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Any idea what could have given Jinxie that courage?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, there IS one piece of evidence that comes to mind. I wonder if she saw something like it at the scene of the crime. Jinxie, did your sudden burst of courage have anything to do with this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh... That's not encouraging...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">The evidence you presented seems to have produced confusion rather than courage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Guess I got that one wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, if at first you don't succeed... You know the rest, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Jinxie, you didn't happen to see a Nine-Tails Flower there at the scene, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Ah! The demon lawyer strikes again. I can't hide anything from you. I found a small case with a picture of a Nine-Tails Flower on it. I liked it so much, I kept it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You what?! You can't remove evidence from a crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's right, young lady. Removing evidence is a big no-no. Now, the witness will produce said evidence this instant!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">S-Sorry, sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It does seem to be some sort of case. Oh, look, something slid out. It... appears to be a key!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Might I have a look, Your Baldness? Hmmm......... Ah! This is none other than the master key to Kyubi Manor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you certain of this, Prosecutor Blackquill?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It matches the serial number of the key that went missing after the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A master key... that went missing? <thought>Why don't I like the sound of that...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Our little scamp here has stumbled upon an article of unimaginable consequence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's a little melodramatic, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Heed these words, for I shall say them but once. The sole key to the Fox Chamber has been in this little scamp's constant possession. Ergo, she was the sole person who could use it before, during, and after the murder. Which leaves the master key as the only other key that could have opened the chamber. But this master key... ...was found in a room that had been locked by this girl.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And your point is?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Until Jinxie Tenma opened the Fox Chamber with her key... ...the room had been locked tight from the outside world. And there was no one else in there, save the victim and his killer. I trust you have figured it out for yourself by now. A killer other than Mayor Tenma himself would be utterly inconceivable!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Noooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense's assistant will refrain from growling her frustrations!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A-Athena, are you all right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh! I know Mayor Tenma's innocent, but there's nothing we can do!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">This sucks!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Cykes-dono. Allow me to put you out of your misery.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Can I decline your offer?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Abandon your client and your misplaced faith in him. Let the relief of a clear head and a clean conscious come rushing in. That will make the inevitable guilty verdict far easier to accept.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Great. Now he's playing Simon Says with us! Well, he's not going fool us [sic] with his stupid mind games!</thought> Athena, don't fall for his tricks!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uuh... Now I'M the one who's dazed and confused. I can't even think straight.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, are you all right?! <thought>She fell right into his trap!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Now, I suggest you make a mad dash from the courtroom and into the wild blue yonder. Only by running shall your mind be cleared and your conscious cleansed.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">All right, I'll be back in 10!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice? ...I heard the word objection, but what is it you object to?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...? Oh, right... <thought>That objection was more of a reflex than anything else... ...though I was hoping something would come to me while I was trying to stop Athena...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court is waiting, Mr. Justice. Though as it stands now... ...I'll be forced to declare your client guilty and your legal skills suspect if this is it. Now, do you have anything that could overturn the prosecution's case?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, well... Actually, I do! I'm Apollo Justice, and I'm fine!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! You do have something more than your Chords of Steel, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not really, but we'll be fine!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-B-But...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I've got absolutely nothing, but that's never stopped me before! I have to explain how the real killer could have escaped that locked room. Because it's all over if I don't!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, this calls for a new approach! Try to think outside the box!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Or in this case, inside the box! <thought>And what a doozy that locked room is, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? Do you have anything that can counter the prosecution's argument?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-You bet I do! The real killer must have escaped from the locked room one way or another!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Vague conjecture shall only earn you a taste of my blade, Justice-dono.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Err... <thought>Time to do or die, literally!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense will now explain how it would be possible to escape the locked room.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-You sure about this, Apollo? Can you really explain what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I'm fine! We just need to think this whole escaping-a-locked-room thing over from the beginning! So... let's see. If the killer had escaped... ...how could they have done so?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The choices are pretty limited. The room has a window, but... ...it doesn't open wide enough for anyone to get through, and there's a sheer cliff outside. As for the air vent... ...it's up too high and there's nothing you could stand on to reach it. And needless to say... ...the Forbidden Chamber wouldn't open no matter what we did, so that's out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, that [sic] why we gotta keep the solution simple. Like they say, simple is best. We need to rule out all of the absolutely impossible escape routes. Then, whatever's left just might lead us to how the Fox Chamber was compromised! Your Honor! The defense proposes that the killer escaped through here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! I wish I could escape right now.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid there's no escaping a penalty for your random guessing, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, could I try that one again?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The hallway door? Well, yes, I suppose that would be the only way out.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........Hmph. It would appear you've already forgotten. The only available key until Jinxie Tenma came on scene was within that locked room. How would one exit the Fox Chamber, and then lock it without a key? Hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I should've seen this coming...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Remember Apollo, keep it simple.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Simple, right. I could understand if the killer had exited the room with the key, but...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? The prosecution has some fine Japanese steel waiting unless you explain yourself quickly.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I'm fine! I can explain myself! The reason the Fox Chamber's hallway door was locked was because...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mayor Tenma locked it himself after the killer fled the scene... ...just in case the killer decided to return. That would explain why the room was locked!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I see... Then again, wouldn't Mayor Tenma have mentioned that himself?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, uh, maybe it slipped his mind because of that blow to his head? Aaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. I have already considered and investigated such possibilities.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You have?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The mayor's fingerprints were not found on the door or its doorknob. The only fingerprints found belonged to the alderman. Ergo, the mayor did not so much as touch the door.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oops.</thought> Okay, then how about...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe the door closed accidently [sic].... on its own. Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The killer will never be identified if we attribute key moments to mere chance. Perhaps that spear just happened to fly off of the wall and impale the alderman, too. And perhaps that sedative just happened to make its way into his coffee. Mere chance could explain any number of things.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right, um... next idea, then...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What if the door was locked from the outside? In other words, the killer took the key through the hallway door, then locked it-- Youch!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Consider this: The master key was found inside the tightly locked Fox Chamber. Any assertion that the key was removed from that room is a blatant contradiction of fact.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Exiting the room before locking the door WOULD require taking the key outside. But the key was found inside the room, which does seem like a contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If only we could explain both. Like, how the key could be inside the room AND be used to lock the door from outside.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, let's see if the defense can response [sic] before Prosecutor Blackquill draws his sword. How could the master key be at the crime scene, despite the room being locked tight?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe someone threw it in from the hallway when Jinxie opened the door? That would explain-- Aaah!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........Hmph. Perhaps we should ask the little scamp herself. When you opened the Fox Chamber, did you witness anyone throw the master key inside?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Sorry. I didn't see anyone else there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What a pity. Or perhaps you intend to accuse the witness of murder?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You leave me no choice. A penalty for random speculation and lack of foresight.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh. <thought>How could've someone gotten the key into that locked room?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's try that again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If the door had been rebuilt after the key was placed in the room... ...that would explain how it got there!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... And the original door? Where did that disappear to?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I guess it's highly unlikely that the door was rebuilt in the first place, so-- Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh. <thought>How could've someone gotten the key into that locked room?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's try that again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What if someone threw it into the room from outside -- you know, something like... ...go out the hallway door, lock the room, and then toss the key back in through the window. That would explain how the master key could be inside the locked room!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...And where would you throw it from? There is a cliff outside the Fox Chamber's window. Throwing the key in from there is an impossibility.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Oh! Right... Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wonder if the key could've been tossed in from somewhere other than the window.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Somewhere other than the window? Hmm... Could the key have been tossed in through somewhere other than the window?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It seems the defense has developed a case of amnesia. A sheer cliff lies just outside that window. No one tossed in anything through there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What if you threw it in from the bottom of the cliff? I bet you could get it in if you threw it as hard as you could?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. I'm afraid you would still have no ground to stand on, just as with your case. For you see, a raging river lies at the bottom of that cliff. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">A penalty for the amnesia-prone attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh. <thought>So the key didn't get in through the window. Guess I'd better rethink this</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... And how would that even be possible?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, um... Very carefully, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......... The defense will refrain from tossing around vague answers to key questions.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's try that again. How could the key have wound up in that locked room?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Well, if it isn't the window, from where else could it have been thrown inside?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The air vent?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes. The window may be out of the question, but the air vent's not!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, that's right! The Fox Chamber's air duct... ...leads out into the hallway.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right. The real killer entered the air duct from the vent outside the Fox Chamber... ...then dropped the key into the room through the vent inside the chamber!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hrgh! That's preposterous!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, that explains how the key got in there after it was used to lock the door perfectly!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice! Um... I'm afraid I'm a bit confused...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't worry! I'll explain it so even Your Honor can understand. First, the real killer, disguised as Tenma Taro, murdered the alderman in the Fox Chamber. Then, they fled the room through the hallway door and locked it. Next, they entered the air duct from the vent outside in the hallway. Finally, the killer tossed the key into the room through the air vent in the ceiling there! All that was left to do after that was go back through the duct and flee the manor! Well, Your Honor?! Could that be any clearer?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Amazing! Even I could follow that!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The judge seems really pleased.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That explains everything! The real killer was someone dressed up like Tenma Taro. And there WAS someone else other than the mayor and the alderman in that room!</line>
<line speaker="Man">Hey, it looks like that lawyer has beaten the jailbird prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Man">Whoa! That was a total turnabout!</line>
<line speaker="Woman">That massive forehead of his seems so much more attractive now!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order, I say!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now that I've proved a possible third party, I don't see how our client could be guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">..........A valiant effort, Justice-dono, but your final thrust missed its mark.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Both that little scamp and the tricksy tanuki saw the yokai after it left the room. But then what? Did that irksome yokai simply go through the foyer and waltz right out the front door?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-That's exactly what happened! The killer fled from the-- Youch!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">But that is impossible -- without being spotted by the foyer's security camera, that is. The electric eye here would have captured any pesky little yokai trying to escape. However, there is no sign of Tenma Taro anywhere in the security footage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Wh-What?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Save for the foyer entrance, there is no other way to flee the manor, is there?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't feel so good.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, you're right!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Must I point out every crucial detail to the defense? It seems you lack not only brains, but investigative prowess to boot. That is the cliff side of the manor. The only killer escaping that way would be a dead one.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-Nooooooooon!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait... So the killer didn't escape out the foyer window?</line>
<line speaker="Widget">What the heck, right?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">....Ha! I suppose your next proposal is the killer sprouted wings and flew off into the sunset?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That would mean the killer really was a yokai...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">...If only we had some sort of evidence that could point to a flying killer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who's saying we don't? <thought>As completely far-fetched as it might be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">WHAAAT?! You're saying you can prove the killer could fly?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa! I thought I was the one with the Chords of Steel!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, I can't wait to hear this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, Your Honor...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What evidence do you have that the killer flew away?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Never mind. Lemme try that again.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice! You wouldn't be trying to escape without a penalty, would you?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I know we have some kind of evidence of a flying yokai.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Justice-dono, surrender yourself now or suffer the death of a thousand cuts.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-Never!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Take a look at this special edition paper.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Tenma Taro: Real or Flight of Fancy?" ...What does this article prove, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The photo in that article was taken shortly after the murder. Maybe the yokai in that photo is the killer shortly after they fled out of the window...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Justice! You're not seriously suggesting--!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, I'm serious! I mean, it all adds up! The killer, disguised as Tenma Taro, flew away! You know, by some way or another!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It is your brain that has flow [sic] the coop. That image is naught but trick photography or some other form of artifice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, then, how about the Tenma Taro figure Mr. Filch saw? It just vanished into thin air?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........No, there is a rational, common-sense explanation for that. That infernal yokai our tricksy tanuki witnessed never reached the entrance. He -- or should I say she -- turned back before the camera's electric eye.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......She? <thought>I don't like where this is going one bit!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Now, the fact that we know the yokai had come from the Fox Chamber... ...means that it was likely either Mayor Tenma or his daughter Jinxie Tenma. However, we know that Mayor Tenma was already unconscious at that time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*gulp* <thought>Not good. Not good at all!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Do you understand the gravity of the situation now, Justice-dono? The falsified yokai remnants... ...and the appearance of "Tenma Taro" were the work of one individual. And that individual is none other than Jinxie Tenma!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaargh! Nooooooooooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! The defense will stop competing for the greatest freak-out ever!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The little scamp was, no doubt, simply trying to protect her father. And it's no wonder that her superstitious mind conjured up this mad masquerade.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor Blackquill's assertion makes perfect sense to me. It's far more convincing than saying the killer escaped by flying out of the window.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Did you truly believe this could end any other way?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Did we fall right into his trap?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">What do we do now, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Our case no longer stands without a real yokai. If only we had one.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Bailiff, seize her! It is time I interrogated her as the samurai of yore would.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. This farce is over. How does it feel, seeing your own daughter accused of a cover-up most foul?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">......... Tenma Taro's true identity is--</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Now, now, Mr. Mayor. It would be futile at this point to claim you were the yokai. After all, you had been knocked out cold by a blow to the skull. Slipping into a yokai costume and roaming about the manor would be all but impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Consider this well. As it stands, your daughter will be arrested for obstruction of justice. But if you confess, the prosecution would be willing to overlook her little yokai farce.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Confess? The defendant intends to confess?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! Prosecutor Blackquill's up to his mind games again!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mayor Tenma! No! Don't fall for his twisted words! If you're sent away for murder, Jinxie will be left all alone!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">.........The real killer is...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mayor Tenma's going to confess unless we do something!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>But... But I can't prove how the real killer could've flown away...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tenma">............ Caw caw-caw-caw! Look upon me and despair, for ripe is the time for my return.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hm? <thought>Uh-oh... I should watch what I wish for.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Caw caw-caw-caw! Foolish mortals! I am Tenma Taro, the yokai you seek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... M-Mayor Tenma?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Silence! I am Tenma Taro -- freed from the bonds binding me to the Forbidden Chamber! Behold! The return of the Demon King!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What the--?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Demon King...?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, I think it's time for me to... ...t-take a vacatioooon! The witness will...! Um... He will explain himself! Are you saying you're Tenma Taro, the yokai we've been chasing this whole time?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Indeed, it is I, Tenma Taro, the one whom you seek -- come to reveal the truth. This child is Tenma Taro, you say? Hah! What nonsense!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, Mayor Tenma... is a yokai now?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Caw caw-caw-caw! His body is now mine!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, you're saying that Mayor Tenma is... being possessed by you? And that the yokai that Jinxie Tenma and Phineas Filch saw... ...and the one captured in the newspaper photo... Those were all you?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">The accursed power of these warding charms prevents me from revealing my true form.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Your Baldness! .........Can this not be interpreted as an admission of guilt?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, a confession by a yokai would be quite unprecedented.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Be that as it may, the defense's case has been overturned.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? What?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You claimed the yokai that little scamp saw was some third party -- the true killer... ...the one who escaped from the locked Fox Chamber, but it was the accused all along.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Argh!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ironic, is it not? Your yokai turned out to be real in a manner of speaking. For the alderman's killer is none other than Mayor Tenma! And the yokai at the scene? That, too, was Mayor Tenma, or should I say, our dear Tenma Taro! The pieces have all fallen into place.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">H-How so, Prosecutor Blackquill?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. It seems I must spell it out for you. Mayor Tenma killed the alderman in the Fox Chamber -- which was locked at the time. He then removed the warding charms from the Forbidden Chamber's door... ...but then fell unconscious from the blow the alderman had delivered to his head. That's when his daughter Jinxie Tenma stumbled on the scene of the crime. The little scamp fled in terror, whereupon the spirit of Tenma Taro... ...freed at last from the charm's warding effect, took possession of the mayor. The newly freed Tenma Taro then fled from the Fox Chamber. So, you see, the yokai Jinxie Tenma saw was her father possessed by Tenma Taro.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Then, what? Do you mean to say the maid of Kyubi Manor, Jinxie Tenma, was Tenma Taro?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............Oh. Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Tenma:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. It would seem the pieces are still in place.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is Blackquill up to his tricks again?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I don't know what to say. Is the defendant a real live...?</line>
<line speaker="Man">So that rumor about Mayor Tenma is true? I knew yokai were real!</line>
<line speaker="Man">You mean he really did kill the alderman just so he could release Tenma Taro?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Now he's got everyone in the courtroom believing in yokai!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's Simon Says on steroids! He wants to convict our client any way he can -- even if it means blaming a yokai!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The proverbial ducks are all in a row. You should now have no qualms about finding the accused guilty, Your Baldness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... This is one of the most bizarre cases in my entire career. Otherworldly, in fact. Can yokai even be prosecuted under our legal system?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Since both sides have raised valid points, I've no choice but to--</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph! This is the dark age of the law where defense attorneys are not to be trusted. This is but a ploy to gain time for them to fabricate evidence! How will I sleep tonight... ...knowing you will not let the run rise on the mayor's day of reckoning, Justice-dono?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Then prove it by joining me. A night in the clink will ensure you will not succumb to temptation!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How about I just promise not to succumb to anything?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">We have both evidence and a confession. The killer is this yokai before us. It is beyond dispute. A guilty verdict is all but-- Uuuwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa! Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's wrong with him?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Prosecutor Blackquill! We've had enough of your hijinks! The foundation of justice is fair play, and you are in serious violation of that!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">*huff* *huff* What in the devil was that? Fool Bright! Have you tampered with my shackles in some manner?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha ha! It seems you found that quite shocking. It's my special Jolt of Justice device. Each press is a shocking reminder to behave.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You shall pay for this. I, Simon Blackquill, vow to-- Uuuwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Your Honor! You need not fear now! I believe Prosecutor Blackquill will remain on his best behavior.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...A bit late with the reassurances, aren't we, detective?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Well, in that case... *ahem*... This concludes today's deliberations. The prosecution and the defense will use this opportunity to further their investigations. This court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. I object to you on personal grounds. The sole contradiction lies in what your faulty logic dreamt up just now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. The defense will think twice before making such erroneous statements!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It seems that statement didn't particularly conflict with the evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Your gall knows no bounds. It's shocking, really.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's that supposed to mean?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You stand there, brazely objecting to perfectly factual statements... One does not see such shameless behavior that often.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A penalty for our shameless attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, no. Looks like Blackquill is turning the judge against me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...........................Your Baldness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Who, me?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What do you make of this objection of his?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, I don't know if I should, um, well...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I've no patience for vagaries. Now, answer my question.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes, sir! The defense's objection was clearly misguided!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Bravo. Nicely done.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho ho. It seems our misguided attorney has earned himself a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Erk... I better look before I leap next time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... There has to be a contradiction here somewhere. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Too bad I'm drawing a blank.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">There was a statement that I thought was a little strange, but... ...I wouldn't bet my life on it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........And which statement would that be? Since I'm the one betting my life on it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hee hee hee. Okay, if you must know, I'll show you the one I'm thinking of.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Time to swallow my pride and let her lend a hand.</thought> <thought>There must be an inconsistency in the testimony Athena's pointing out!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... I can't flag any inconsistencies.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So there haven't been any contradictions in the testimony so far... That can mean only one thing...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Time to press the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. We'll have to work to get the testimony we need. Let's press the heck out of any statements that stick out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... This seems like an unnatural reaction...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really? Because I don't see it that way. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So it isn't unexpected given her testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hello? Is there anybody in there? Just nod if you can hear me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yes, there is someone at home, and that someone is going to try that again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The defense's argument is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims! This court finds the defendant, Damian Tenma...</line>
</xml>