<xml>
<title>The Kidnapped Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Where's the costume, Detective Gumshoe!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Just on the other side of the fountain, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Was it out here in the open all along?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No, it was discovered in the tall grass back there! We moved it out here in order to examine it more thoroughly.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then let's get down to it.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You look rather deep in thought. Care to share?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmm... Now, it might just be my imagination, but that costume earlier... ...I think we need to take another good look at it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You feel that there might be something else there?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmm... I can't say, but I really feel like we should give it another once over.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Alright, I'll see to it that we do.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you the one who moved the costume out from the tall grass?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Sir! Yes, sir! I moved it as I was instructed to by Detective Gumshoe, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is that a hint of hero-worship towards Gumshoe I detect in his voice...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe, was this costume found just lying out here in the open?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No, it was discovered in the tall grass back there! We moved it out here in order to examine it more thoroughly.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... Then let's get down to it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like to investigate that room again, if you please...</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Sir! I'm sorry, but as for the request I received from Detective Gumshoe... ...I have already fulfilled my end of the bargain, sir! Now, I have to keep my orders from Agent Lang, and protect this crime scene, sir! Which is why I can't let you in anymore, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow... Looks like Detective Gumshoe really holds some sway over these guys...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... I suppose I don't really have a choice but to retreat for now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's the Blue Badger's body section. What a waste.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How so?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Going through all the trouble to steal this costume, only to throw it away in the end... A real thief wouldn't do such a thing, nope, no way!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I wouldn't think a real thief would steal something so gaudy to begin with...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This headpiece... This must be the Blue Badger Officer Meekins crossed paths with.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ooh, the nerve of someone throwing a Blue Badger away like this! I worked so hard to create this character; it's like my baby! How could someone do this, sir!? How!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective. How about channeling your anger towards finding the culprits?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Good idea! Ooh, wait until I get my hands on-- So, who are they, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why don't you try figuring it out yourself for a change!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do we have here?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, it's another pendant! That's two treasures in one day! How lucky is that!? And hey! This pretty baby's made of platinum silver, too!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Another pendant on top of the one we found on Mr. Deacon? Is it possible that these two...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Hold it right there!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hands off, Mr. Prosecutor. You sure know how to cross the line, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arghn!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">A pendant, huh... This is a very decisive piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How can you tell?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Look here and read off what you see.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">"Lauren"... Hey, it's a name that's engraved on this!</line>
<line speaker="Paups">I... I...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a pendant in the shape of a pair of wings. Hmm... It has a rather nice aesthetic to it.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! Nice to see that even you can appreciate its beauty! Things made of platinum silver tend to have a nice feeling about them, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I was only talking about its shape, Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, is that what you were talking about...? Umm... but you know... ...if we're talking about wing shapes, I think the broach on my scarf is way cooler!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But that's not made of platinum silver, is it...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...It's hand-made, OK? So I'm sorry that it's not made of the expensive stuff!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She made that by herself...!? ...It's incredibly well-crafted...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Lauren D." is engraved into this pendant.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I see that they wrote out her first name, but why just the "D."?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Maybe it's the result of poor planning?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I guess... Well, at least if I had to shorten my name, I could make it "K. Faraday"! That was, even if you just sounded it out, it'd still say my name, "Kay Faraday"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose if I had to do the same, I would rather it be abbreviated as "M. Edgeworth".</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hold on! I think you should abbreviate it as "M. E." Get it!? Ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Who would've thought that this little pendant could stir up such a strange conversation?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Aha! We have you now, Ms. Kidnapper!</line>
<line speaker="Paups">No, you don't understand! I... I...!</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Lolli... I can't believe you were one of my kidnappers...</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Lance...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You're kidding! Ms. Paups was one of the kidnappers!?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">..................Yes. It... It was me... I held Lance hostage...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So Ms. Paups is one of the kidnappers... But even knowing that, I can't call this case solved... or over.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey! Guys! Case closed! Get the car ready, and I mean the special one for this young lady!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Heh. Again, Mr. Prosecutor? What is it this time?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you proposing that Ms. Paups is also the culprit in the murder case? What happened? I thought Officer Meekins was your suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hmph! We found it...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Found what?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">That officer's gun. He literally dropped it in the middle of a thick patch of grass. Your country's police are a sham. Just look at how careless they are!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Who are you calling a "sham"!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">The officer's gun didn't show signs of having been fired, so it can't be the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So Officer Meekins has been cleared of all charges, I see...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">And that's when a brand-new suspect comes walking onto the scene. The murder only happened because the kidnappers started fighting amongst themselves. As I recall, it was you who said that, right, Mr. Prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ms. Paups! Did you... Did you really kill Mr. Deacon...!?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">.................. I... Yes, I killed him.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I-I can't believe it...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Thanks for the confession!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang, it's much too early to declare this case closed!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Look at you, so sure of yourself. We've got the culprit's own confession and some very incriminating evidence. What more could you ask for?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Lauren Paups.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Y-Yes!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I want to hear it from you. Tell me your side of all that has happened today, from the kidnapping to the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">B-But why? I... I'm a kidnapper and the killer! Isn't that enough!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's fine if you're the one behind everything, but only if that is the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, will you tell us the truth? Or is there some reason why you can't?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">..................</line>
<line speaker="Lang">.................. I've had a change of heart. I think I'd enjoy seeing you sulk away as the losing mutt. Alright, you heard me. Let's hear about all the evil deeds you committed today.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">The one who came up with the kidnapping plan was the butler, Mr. Deacon.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">There. Are you satisfied? She just confessed to her crimes a second time. At least you have the guts to admit what you've done. I can at least respect that much.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Paups... Is what you said really the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Y-Yes... it... is...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If that is the truth, it certainly isn't the whole truth. Because there is something that seems a bit too improbable in her confession.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Paups">The one who came up with the kidnapping plan was the butler, Mr. Deacon.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How well did you know the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">I've spoken with him only a few times at Lance's house.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A "few times"? That's it?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">...Um, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If they only met a few times, I don't see how they could've trusted each other...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">But if you hardly ever talked, then how could he trust you not to steal his plan?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">That's completely irrelevant. He was planning to betray her from the very beginning. Which is why he chose someone he wasn't especially close to. Isn't that right, Shih-na?</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">Yes, however, Mr. Deacon made a very poor choice. In the end, he was killed by the one he intended to betray himself.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah! I bet he didn't see that one coming!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Paups">.........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Paups, you really are clueless, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You never knew what your role in the kidnapping was, nor do you know who you really are. But I do, and I can show you with this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Why are you showing this to me...?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">So what about the pendant!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This horse pendant, along with this piece of evidence, shows who you really are!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Paups">Does that really have anything to do with the pendant?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What the heck, of course not!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I suppose not. <thought>There is something that is very clearly connected to this pendant! And this pendant is the key that will open the door to the truth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Paups">Why are you showing this to me...?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">So what about the pendant!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This pair of wings, along with this piece of evidence, shows who you really are!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Paups">Does that really have anything to do with the pendant?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What the heck, of course not!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I suppose not. <thought>There is something that is very clearly connected to this pendant! And this pendant is the key that will open the door to the truth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Paups">We knew that we could get rich by holding Lance hostage.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You knew? How did you know something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Aah! Oh, no! What should I do...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............Kay, what's wrong with her now?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Come on, isn't it obvious!? You're making your scary face again, that's why! Why don't you try asking her in a nicer, more gentle way?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Paups">No, stop it, Lauren! You're always like this! You always fall for the stern-looking one... That's why you'll always be unhappy!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">............Or maybe that's it. She's been bewitched by your icy glare.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mind your own business, Kay. ...Now then, Ms. Paups, let's continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Oh! Y-Yes, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Mr. Amano would pay anything to get his son back, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why did you believe that?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Anyone who knows Mr. Amano would think the same...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I bet Lance is that old man's greatest "treasure".</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I suppose he would be to a doting father like Mr. Amano.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Paups">I always figured that was it, too. And I was always envious of Lance for it.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh... Because your dad's...</line>
<line speaker="Paups">I got this pendant from my father... And I believe that as long as I have this, I'll find my father again someday. He'll welcome me into his arms, riding on the back of Pegasus.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That pendant... She must truly believe it or be the wings of Pegasus.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Paups">Everything was going according to plan, but as soon as we got the money...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Would you mind telling us a little about the plan itself?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Well.. First, we captured Lance...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ooh, how did you do that?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Um... That... Well, Mr. Deacon did that on his own, so I don't quite know...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Bah. And here I thought you knew how to steal people away.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I shudder to think what she would do with such knowledge..</thought></line>
<line speaker="Paups">Sorry, I really don't know, but somehow, Mr. Deacon was able to contain him. All we had to do after that was wait for the ransom to be paid, but...</line>
<line speaker="Paups">...Mr. Deacon turned on me, and tried to kill me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why do you think he did?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">I have no idea. But maybe he had planned on doing so from the very beginning.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Ms. Paups...</line>
<line speaker="Paups">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wait. Mr. Deacon planned to kill Ms. Paups from the very beginning...? Was that ever really likely to happen? What should I do? Should I raise an objection?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>No, I shouldn't show my hand this early on. Let's see where the rest of this testimony takes me first.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah, I see kidnappers also weep when they get stabbed in the back. Even as you betray the one you claim to "love" the most!</line>
<line speaker="Paups">That's... No... You don't understand...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What's there to understand?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sorry, but I don't think what you just claimed is all that likely.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't think Mr. Deacon would have ever been capable of killing you.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">But why!? We were total strangers! It's not uncommon for people to kill each other over money...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Paups, you really are clueless, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You never knew what your role in the kidnapping was, nor do you know who you really are. But I do, and I can show you with this piece of evidence! This proves that Mr. Deacon wouldn't have been able to bring himself to kill Ms. Paups!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Paups">Why are you showing this to me...?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">So what about the pendant!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This horse pendant, along with this piece of evidence, shows who you really are!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Paups">Does that really have anything to do with the pendant?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What the heck, of course not!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I suppose not. <thought>There is something that is very clearly connected to this pendant! And this pendant is the key that will open the door to the truth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Paups">Why are you showing this to me...?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">So what about the pendant!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This pair of wings, along with this piece of evidence, shows who you really are!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Paups">Does that really have anything to do with the pendant?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What the heck, of course not!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I suppose not. <thought>There is something that is very clearly connected to this pendant! And this pendant is the key that will open the door to the truth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Paups! You don't know, do you? But this piece of evidence will tell you exactly who you really are!</line>
<line speaker="Paups">............Looking at it, I still don't feel anything within me at all! But now, I REALLY feel like I don't know anything!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey, Mr. Prosecutor. Are you sure the one who doesn't know anything isn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh! <thought>I guess this wasn't... Alright, I should calm down and listen to Ms. Paups's testimony once more... ...and take another good look at what is in my Organizer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah, I see kidnappers also weep when they get stabbed in the back. Even as you betray the one you claim to "love" the most!</line>
<line speaker="Paups">That's... No... You don't understand...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What's there to understand?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Paups, you really are clueless, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You never knew what your role in the kidnapping was, nor do you know who you really are. But I do, and I can show you with this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Why are you showing this to me...?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">So what about the pendant!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This horse pendant, along with this piece of evidence, shows who you really are!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Paups">Does that really have anything to do with the pendant?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What the heck, of course not!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I suppose not. <thought>There is something that is very clearly connected to this pendant! And this pendant is the key that will open the door to the truth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Paups">Why are you showing this to me...?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">So what about the pendant!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This pair of wings, along with this piece of evidence, shows who you really are!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Paups">Does that really have anything to do with the pendant?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What the heck, of course not!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I suppose not. <thought>There is something that is very clearly connected to this pendant! And this pendant is the key that will open the door to the truth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's wrong, Kay?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I can't believe she was betrayed... I... kinda feel sorry for her.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I feel a little sorry for her, too, however, I also wish she would tell us the whole truth. Because there is something that seems a bit too improbable in her confession. But I'll give it another careful listen and see.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">These two pendants resemble each other, wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, you're right! They're the same color, and they're even made of the same material!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe that these two pendants are actually one.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Ehhhh!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Shall we give it a try?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow! It's...! It's totally Pegasus!</line>
<line speaker="Paups">B-But why!? Why does my pendant match up with Mr. Deacon's!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're a smart lady. I'm sure you can imagine why that might be.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Wh--! No! That can't be!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">So the two make a set. Heh! It's just another trinket. It's not as though this changes anything!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. You lack imagination, Agent Lang. Very well, I'll show you with this evidence! This is the piece of evidence that gives meaning to the Pegasus pendant!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence clearly does not demonstrate the meaning behind the pendant.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And? So what?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hold your horses. I believe there might exist a piece of evidence that can better explain the meaning...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You "believe there might"? If you have it, why are you playing coy with it!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh! Very well then, prepare yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Oliver Deacon" was just an alias for this man. His real name was "Colin Devorae", the name that is etched on the horse pendant.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What!? An alias!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose he had to hide the fact that he was a felon somehow in order to live. And it makes sense, given what is written in Mr. Devorae's dossier. But what I really wanted to point out was this. This specific section is what reveals the true meaning behind those pendants!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sure I'm not the only one who recognizes this face.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Isn't that the murder victim?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">And? Don't tell me that's it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I still have yet to figure it all out. <thought>The truth is buried in here somewhere! I just need to read it in a little more detail!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">His real name was "Colin Devorae", the name that is etched on the horse pendant.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What the--!? Do you pay attention to what you say!? You just told us about his alias a few seconds ago! And in the exact same words!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Knngh! <thought>Written in here is something other than the victim's real name that is very important.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like you to take a look at around this area...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Lang Zi says: "The timid never reach the land of Truth." You'll have to be more specific than that if you want to convince me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh! Do I have to spell it out for you? Alright then, I'll direct you to the exact section.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Devorae had one daughter. And her name is Lauren Paups.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">That's a lie! That person was not my father!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He couldn't come out and tell you he was your father because he was in hiding. However, I believe he was trying to secretly watch over you.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you still believe that a man like that could kill the daughter he was separated from? Or even, that such a man would allow his daughter to get involved in a kidnapping plot?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what is so funny, Agent Lang?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You're good at making things up in your head and deciding it's the truth, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What are you trying to say?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Your thinking is much too innocent. After all, I've thought of another possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is that so? Well, let's hear it.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I'll grant you that the two of them are father and daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So this is his version of how things might have been...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">You don't have any proof that either one didn't know of their true relationship, right?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You mean they knowingly committed the kidnapping as father and daughter?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">That's right. As one really rotten family!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is that really what happened? I had better take a long, hard look at the evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">I'll grant you that the two of them are father and daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely. And what father would ever willingly kill his own daughter?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I've seen a lot of things in my travels... ..and I can tell you that being related by blood is sometimes proof of nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">But, isn't it possible that they both knew that fact?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You think they knew?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Yeah, I don't think only the victim knew. I think the girl realized it as well. They both knew who the other person was, but they had to pretend that they didn't!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Because he was on the lam?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You got it. The victim couldn't exactly go around flaunting who he was. Furthermore...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">It was no coincidence that the reunited pair became involved in the house of Amano.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">One as a butler, and one as the friend of the son, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">They probably thought that was their best shot.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is that what you honestly believe?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">And the two of them made good use of their meetings to plan this little kidnapping.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You mean how they plotted to commit this crime as blood relatives?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Can you think of a better partner? They're certainly a clever pair.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The butler and the girlfriend. No one would ever suspect that they were, in fact, family.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Yes, from the very beginning, they painstakingly practiced those roles well.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Wouldn't you say my scenario is perfectly probable as well?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe you're being a bit too over-confident for someone with no evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Am I? Because I don't see you presenting any evidence to the contrary.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mnngh... <thought>Without evidence to counter him, we're stuck at a draw.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Agent Lang isn't wrong: his scenario is certainly a probable one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">You'd better hurry up and do something, or Lauren's gonna wind up looking really bad.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know, but first thing's first. Is Agent Lang's line of logic factually correct...? <thought>Did the two of them really knowingly commit the crime as father and daughter?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This kidnapping wasn't planned by just two people alone.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">And what kind of proof do you have of that!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Quite simply, there were three kidnappers.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Three!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Four costumes were stolen from the Wild, Wild West area's backroom. We found one of them in the kidnappers' hideout. But as for the other three, we can assume they were being worn by three different people. We also found a set of three cups and three folding chairs that were used in the hideout. It all clearly points to a three-man group! And I believe this third person is the real mastermind behind the kidnapping!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Wh-Who!? Who is this mastermind!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I present to you, the brains behind the kidnapping!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The real puppet-master of this kidnapping is this person. I can think of no one else.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">......?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I can think of no one else with such faulty logic as you, Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh! It wasn't this person...!? <thought>Thinking back, there really is only one person the third kidnapper could be!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Well, who is it? Who is the mastermind behind it all?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Lance Amano!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, this abduction was, in fact, schemed up by Lance himself! Recall what he said when he appeared before us.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Did you see the faces of your kidnappers!?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">No... I didn't see their faces... but... two... One was a w-woman...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, there were three kidnappers, which is in direct contradiction to what he said.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">But, but... I know I only saw two people...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">This guy was being held hostage. It's possible he couldn't see all three of them.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, yes, about when you were being held... I have my doubts about what happened then. Lance, would you mind telling us what happened while you were being held captive?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">I really don't remember much anymore... Honest... But if I don't tell you at least something, you won't believe me at all, will you?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">I was kidnapped yesterday morning.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Through the underground passageway, I presume...?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">............</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Are you OK?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Sorry, I really didn't want to recall that horrible ordeal, but... ...but now you believe me, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, not quite yet.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Aaah! How can you not!? Why do you look at me with icy daggers in your eyes?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Because he's a prosecutor. and because they're all like that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll have you know, Agent Lang, a prosecutor's eyes are for discerning the truth. And should they be interpreted to be cruel at times, then so be it.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">............Tch.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There is a sticking point in Lance's testimony. Let's see what he offers up when I push a little.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lance">I was kidnapped yesterday morning.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Can you tell us about when you were abducted in a little more detail?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">It was a strange morning. I felt like I was right in the middle of a great calm.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And where were you when you experienced this... calm?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Our family garden, of course! Where else could it have been!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Well! Excuse me for asking! This child is more princess than prince...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lance">I was out taking a walk to shake off the morning blah. Then, out of the blue, someone from behind clamps a hand over my mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You didn't see your attacker?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">They must've used some drug to knock me out. Because before I knew it, I was off in La-La Land again. When I woke up, I was in kidnappers' hideout already, all tied up.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">They had me shut in that room, blindfolded, the entire time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">By "that room", you mean the room in the kidnappers' hideout, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Yes, but I was blindfolded the whole time, so I didn't know that until I made my escape.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then, you were in the same room as your kidnappers?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">They spoke in hushed tones, but I could catch bits of their conversation. It was definitely two people, and one of them was definitely a woman. I was so scared. I could tell they were nearby, so I didn't dare make a move.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">But the kidnappers suddenly disappeared around the time I heard rain falling outside.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The kidnappers disappeared?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">The room fell into a sudden silence. I had been left behind like an unwanted mutt.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what do you mean by "unwanted mutt"?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What a pointless question. It's not like he's going to tell you anything new, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">It's a poetic smile, You should learn how to use them, too. You may look refined on the outside... ...but it's no good if you're not refined on the inside as well.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">My hands were cuffed, but it was a stroke of luck that they left me alone.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then, those cuffs on your wrists... I suppose you are still cuffed, in that case.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">I am well aware of how I am chained to reality. I couldn't find the key, so I'm afraid that I'm stuck like this. Even thought I escaped from that jail cell, I will forever be a prisoner.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">I made my escape and ran away from that room as fast as I could.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How did you manage to escape?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">I wanted to just get out of there, but the door leading outside was locked. Which is why I had to use the underground passageway to make my escape.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I remember our escape to be equally as hard... This is an invaluable piece of testimony. I mustn't let it go unexamined.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"The door leading outside was locked tight, so I had to use the underground passageway."</line>
<line speaker="Lance">The door leading outside was locked tight, so I had to use the underground passageway.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">By "underground passageway", you mean the one the staff uses to travel unnoticed?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">I suppose that's what it's for, but I didn't run into any staff members on my way out. And once I was up top, I was busy trying to find a member of the police.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And that is when you found us congregated at the stadium, I suppose? Let me ask you, then. How did you get ahold of the key to the underground door?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">That was easy. It was hanging right there in the room on the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I do recall a key hanging on the wall right beside the table...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Boy does that bring back memories of our situation and how we made our escape.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. And although the door in the floor of our room left to an underground room... ...the door in the floor of the room next door had a secret passageway.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">A secret passage under a theme park! Ooh, that just sounds like so much fun!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I wonder... Is there something off about the way Lance made his escape...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You say that the door leading out was locked, but was it really?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">We're talking about that room behind the saloon front, right? Look, I heard that it took quite a few men to get that thing open. Right, Shih-na?</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">Yes, that's correct.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then, take a look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What is that? A sword? It's not an especially reliable one if it's broken like that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Allow me to start from the end. My conclusion is that the door was never locked. It was simply held shut by this sword, which was used to jam the handle.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Lance, even though your hands were cuffed together, you could still use them. If that's the case, then why did you not just simply remove the sword and escape?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Wh-Why didn't I...? I was disoriented... Yes, that's it! I didn't notice it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As if I should accept such a bold-faced lie! You locked yourself in that room because you had to make yourself look like the victim. But you did not, in fact, possess the key to the door. That is why you used the prop sword to improvise and create a prison of your very own!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You've been making this guy out to be one of the kidnappers for some time now. I wonder if you've forgotten something very important along the way.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">A motive! What else!? Do you honestly think that an upright, pure boy like him... ...would hatch up a completely pointless scheme such as kidnapping himself!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This proves that Lance did indeed have a motive to commit this crime!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Lang">That is this boy's motive!? You lawyer-types sure have active imaginations! That type of flimsy logic may work in court, but it'll never stand up to my strict scrutiny!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh! This wolf's bite is far worse than his bark...</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Hmph! Serves you right!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Look, this boy has no motive whatsoever!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's where you're wrong. And I have the evidence to prove it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To put it simply, Lance has a very urgent need... for money. This is hardly your typical love letter. It is, in fact, a collections bill. It appears our upstanding boy has accumulated quite a debt. Isn't that right, Lance?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Uuugh...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Looks like it's hard being the son of a rich man, too. It must be rough when you have to resort to stealing from your own old man, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Gnn! A-Alright! I give up! I abducted myself.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Lance!</line>
<line speaker="Lance">It's over, Lolli. In this life, we really are bound to our fates after all. All I wanted was to go with you to a new town, somewhere where no one would know us. I wanted us to be well off with that $1 million, but now... that dream's over.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Oh, Lance!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then, you are giving yourself up?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Yes. I had planned to run away from this world with my Lolli. Oliver even helped us with the plan, but then, he had to go and stab us in the back!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He turned on you?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Maybe he didn't want to split the ransom money. That's my guess. It happened almost right after you made the drop-off. When we were alone, he attacked me all of a sudden. After a brief struggle, I was able to contain him and keep him under control. We left him inside that room as Lolli and I made our escape. We wore different costumes and split up. Lolli left first in the Blue Badger costume. </line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That would mean the person Officer Meekins saw was Ms. Paups.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lance">But right then, the old man just had to wake up! I was careless, and he tackled me pretty hard from behind. Then, Oliver put on a Bad Badger costume... ...took the suitcase with the million dollars and ran! I contacted Lolli right away, and warned her that he had a gun. They had no idea that they were related, so I thought that is could only end badly.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">I still don't believe it! That person was not my father! Because... Because if he was... I... I just killed my own father!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Lolli! Then... Then it really was you...?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">That man was not my father! I mean... Because... at the stadium...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I think the big picture is finally coming into focus, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Lolli... Forgive me. I didn't think it would turn into something so frightening. If only... If only I could've protected you!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So... Ms. Paups... She shot her own dad without even knowing who he really was?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If what she says is true...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Are you saying she's lying? But why would she lie about something like that!? What purpose would it serve!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You would be surprised how often people lie without even realizing it themselves, Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh? What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What I mean is, listen very carefully to her confession once more and you'll see.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">That man was not my father! I mean... Because... at the stadium...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please calm down and let's slowly talk through this.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">But! I...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">All you have to do is simply tell us what happened at the stadium. Leave it to us to search out the truth. Can you do that for me?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">.........! A-Alright. So... at the stadium...</line>
<line speaker="Paups">...there was a Bad Badger pulling the suitcase with the $1 million in it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That was the ransom money, wasn't it!?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Yes. That's how I was able to identify Mr. Deacon almost immediately. It was all thanks to what Lance told me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what did he tell you?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Well, he called me on my cell phone and told me... ...that Mr. Deacon had betrayed us and had run off with the ransom money. And... about how he had a gun.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">But that Badger pointed his gun at me, aiming to shoot me dead!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Were you able to clearly see the gun?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Yes, I got a very good look at it while it was pointed at me. Oh, father... Why would you try to shoot me?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Do you really think a father would shoot his own daughter, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I... don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I don't want to believe it myself...</line>
<line speaker="Paups">But it's true. My father's left arm was raised with a gun in it... ...pointed straight at me! "I'm about to die!" I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Paups!</line>
<line speaker="Paups">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please calm down, and take a breath. And then, would you allow me to please hear that last statement once more time?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">...Y-Yes, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"But that Badger pointed his gun at me, aiming to shoot me dead!" to "But that Badger pointed the gun in his left hand at me, aiming to shoot me dead!"</line>
<line speaker="Paups">But that Badger pointed the gun in his left hand at me, aiming to shoot me dead!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And you felt that your life was in danger, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Yes. "I'm about to die!" I thought. So... So...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Paups">That's why I... I used the gun I got from Lance...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You shot Mr. Deacon...?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">..................</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ms. Paups...</line>
<line speaker="Paups">..................Yes. I-I shot him.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha ha ha! And that, as they say, is that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang, Ms. Paups is far from done. She hasn't even finished her testimony yet!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You're going to continue questioning her? What a waste of time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Paups, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">...Alright.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">There was a gunshot, the other person crumpled to the ground, and I ran, scared for my life.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Did you take off immediately following the gunshot?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And you didn't attempt to approach the victim at all after he was shot?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">I... I was scared...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I don't blame you. I would've done the exact same thing...</line>
<line speaker="Paups">..................</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Poor Ms. Paups... What will become of her, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">She seems to be telling the truth regarding what happened at the stadium. However, I don't believe it to be absolutely correct. Listen very carefully to her confession once more and you'll see.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have here a dossier on your father. And according to this, your father was right handed.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Ah! Then!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The person pointing a gun at you from atop the stage was not Mr. Deacon.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hold on there, Mr. Prosecutor. I think you need to take a refresher course. The Bad Badger has a model gun attached to his right hand. Which is why the only hand he could've held the real gun with was his left. Isn't it possible that is went down like that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang, were you paying attention to what Ms. Paups was saying? Then again, I suppose I can't expect someone who has never set foot in court to catch it.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Enough with the smugness. Out with it already.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Paups told us earlier:</line>
<line speaker="Paups">...there was a Bad Badger pulling the suitcase with the $1 million in it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">According to you, the Bad Badger had the gun in his left hand... ...which would mean that he was pulling the suitcase with his right hand. Is that correct, Ms. Paups?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">...Yes, exactly. And I'm sure it was the Bad Badger! It had those huge sunglasses on its face!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">But if that's the case, even I can see there is a huge contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Ms. Paups claims to have seen the Bad Badger. And yet, the Bad Badger had both of his hands full. These two pieces of information contradict each other, so one must be wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Paups. What you saw was not the Bad Badger. Think back, and recall which character was it that leveled a gun at you.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">But it was wearing a pair of sunglasses, and it had that strange blue beard.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That sums up the Bad Badger pretty well, I'd say.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Too bad for you, but it looks like the Bad Badger wasn't the mistake here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arrgn! <thought>I need to think carefully about the facts here. Ms. Paups claims to have seen the Bad Badger. And yet, the Bad Badger had both of his hands full with something or another.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Holding a gun in his right hand as he pulls the suitcase with the same hand... ...isn't it possible for a right-handed person to do both things simultaneously?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Your deduction is full of one too many conjectures, don't you think, Mr. Prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arngh! I suppose it IS pretty difficult, if not possible. It would appear that both of the Bad Badger's hands were occupied. Yet Ms. Paups claims to have seen the Bad Badger...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They are both correct.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Impossible! That just leaves us with an irresolvable contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ms. Paups's entire statement rests on the fact that she saw his sunglasses and beard. But what if that Bad Badger wasn't wearing pants on his lower half...?</thought> This proves that there was a way for the Bad Badger to freely use both of his hands!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Get your head on straight, Mr. Prosecutor! That doesn't show me diddly-squat!</line>
<line speaker="Paups">I knew it. What I saw was just a miraaaaaage!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait! I can explain! Ms. Paups said the Bad Badger had a gun in his left hand and the suitcase in his right. But the Bad Badger costume has a model gun attached to its right hand... ...which is what created this contradiction about which hand did what.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The costumes have two parts to them, a head and the body.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh! I get it now!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The head Ms. Paups saw was probably really the head of the Bad Badger. However, is it not possible that the body was that of an entirely different Badger?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">A different Badger...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Or to put it more bluntly, I believe it was the lower half of this Badger! The body of the Bad Badger Ms. Paups saw really belonged to this Badger!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Kay">It was the Bad Badger's body...?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">The Bad Badger...?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha ha ha! You're a real laugh riot! You claim that the body was from a different Badger, and then do a complete 180! If the body of the Bad Badger was that of the Bad Badger, then we've resolved nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>C-Curses!</thought> P-Precisely! Therefore, the body of the Bad Badger must have been of a different one!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">His head may have been the Bad Badger, but his body was the Blue Badger's!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">The Blue Badger? Hold on, let's see here... Who was it that had one of these on...?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">I did...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And so did Officer Meekins, pal...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha ha ha! Nice try, but your logic is just a tad illogical! Officer Meekins has been placed under arrest, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait! I'd like to strike what I just said from the record, and give my explanation anew...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Paups">Umm... I think even I would've noticed that...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, Mr. Edgeworth. The Pink Badger is, well, pink, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh! Y-Yes, well, that may be true, but... I-In that case!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Lang">I don't see a Badger where you're pointing, do you!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">S-Sorry. My finger must have slipped due to excessive force. Please allow me to try again.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Wh-What!? .........The heck is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">It's the Proto Badger...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and it's a simple matter of process of elimination. Ms. Paups was wearing the Blue Badger's costume, so we can eliminate that one. And the Pink Badger is of the wrong color, which would have been incredibly obvious. All that is left is the Proto Badger costume! Ms. Paups! Who was the one who wore the Proto Badger costume?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">.........Th-That... w-would be... Lance...</line>
<line speaker="Lance">.........!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Are you saying what I think you are!? That Lance Amano donned the Bad Badger's head... and pretended to be Mr. Deacon? On top of which, he plotted to shoot Ms. Paups while wearing that hideous thing!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The stage that was set up in the stadium was nothing more than that, a set-up... ...and its purpose was to lead Ms. Paups into believing she had committed murder. Standing there in front of Ms. Paups, and pretending to be the victim... ...it was all done so that she would pull the trigger.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Hahahaha. I have no idea what you're talking about. Why exactly would I have had to do all that, huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is but one reason. Lance Amano! You are the real culprit behind the murder of Mr. Oilver Deacon!</line>
<line speaker="Lance">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">N-No!</line>
<line speaker="Lance">That's slander! Take it back! You take it back right now!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just out of curiosity, Lance, which is your dominant hand?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">I-I'm left-handed... but what does that have to do with anything!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It depends. According to Ms. Paups, her attacker held a gun in his left hand.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah! Who is what-handed doesn't prove a thing! And besides! Now you're just being absurd! It's not like the Proto Badger is bulletproof. One misfire, and he would've found himself dead, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course. Logically, if he had been shot, he probably wouldn't be here with us. But I believe he had thought of that as well, and prepared accordingly. And this should be all the evidence you need. This is how Lance made sure that he wouldn't be hit by a bullet!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He prepared this, thinking he could set it up and use it to protect himself.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">That's completely illogical! Besides, you'd think it would've been mentioned in one of the testimonies by now!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......Hm. <thought>Lance was pointing a gun, meaning it's unlikely he was using some sort of barrier. I may need to turn my entire logic on this upside-down.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Do you really think he had a way to prevent himself from being shot?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's not impossible. Especially if he used this!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We found one half of a Bad Badger costume in the hideout, a broken one. It was not the same one that the victim was wearing. Plus, it was missing something. And that something is the model gun that the Bad Badger carries, which can fire blanks.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Wh-Whaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Paups, where is the gun you used now?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">I... I threw it away into the sea.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That... makes it a bit tough to veryfy what it was... Although, I believe that we can safely assume that it was the model gun in question.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I've heard enough. All you've been spouting so far is pure conjecture.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I admit that as long as the model gun is lost to us, I can't prove I'm right. However, I can say that the probability that I am right is very high.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">OK, let's pretend that you're right, and that the murder at the stadium was a fabrication. In that case, where do you think the murder really took place, Mr. Prosecutor!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I... don't know yet.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha! I knew you were full of it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, I do believe that the murder took place during an earlier timeframe.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Please, wait a second! It's simply not possible! Because... Because... I saw Mr. Deacon after he was restrained by Lance.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She saw the victim in the state of being restrained?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Paups">I came back to the hideout long after the other two.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">So Mr. Deacon must've escaped after two of you left, right?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">We thought that it'd attract too much attention if we left together, so I left first. We planned to meet up again at the stage in the stadium. But then! As I was walking through the park, I got a call from Lance on my cell phone.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Oliver managed to escape. It looked like he was waiting until I was alone. He also stolen the gun from me at that time...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">And then, the murder happened. Mr. Deacon must have overheard their plan to meet up at the stage. Well, Mr. Prosecutor? Ms. Paups saw the victim with her own eyes... ...which means that the victim was still alive at that time, wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............ <thought>Why does that sound wrong to me...? There must be something amiss about this account! Let's see what happens when I examine it in more detail.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Paups">I came back to the hideout long after the other two.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">When exactly did you arrive back at the hideout?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">It was after we had picked up the ransom money.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And where were you up until the time you returned?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">I was scouting the park out, and making preparations for our escape. I walked around in the various areas, looking for the best route.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ah, so each of them had their own roles to play.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Paups">After I was done, I went back to the hideout.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">By that time, Lance had already subdued and restrained Mr. Deacon.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How did Lance look at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">He, well... He looked shocked. He also looked a little down. When I saw that sadness in his eyes, I...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thank you, that's enough for now. And what of Mr. Deacon? What was his situation like?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">He had tied Mr. Deacon securely to the beam in the room next door.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You are sure that it was Mr. Deacon that you saw?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Yes. I am certain of what I saw.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Did you go into the other room to check?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Lance said that it was best if I didn't get too close to him... Lance... He's such a kind soul.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then, are you telling me that you did not confirm that it was Mr. Deacon for yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">I checked through the slit in the door that separates the two rooms. He had a Bad Badger's head on, so I'm absolutely sure. That just had to be Mr. Deacon!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She saw a Bad Badger head?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"The captive had a Bad Badger's head on, so I'm absolutely sure it was Mr. Deacon."</line>
<line speaker="Paups">The captive had a Bad Badger's head on, so I'm absolutely sure it was Mr. Deacon.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So the tied-up Mr. Deacon was still in his Bad Badger costume?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Yes... And...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It would appear that she misread the whole situation... What now? Should I raise an objection?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Perhaps I should listen to more of what she has to say.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The person you saw was not the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">What!? Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I will tell you why not... with this! This, Ms. Paups, shows us that the person you saw was not the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Paups">.................. Umm... I'm not sure what you mean by that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Knngh! <thought>It would seem that I made a mistake. But why was he tied up in his Bad Badger costume? If I think a little more on this, the answer should come to me. Perhaps I should listen a bit more carefully to her testimony this time around.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Paups">After that, the two of us put on our costumes and made our escape.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I assume you two split up, but planned to rendezvous later at a set time and place?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Yes. We planned to meet up at the stage, and then I left the hideout not long after.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what about the ransom money?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">You mean that absolutely tasteless suitcase? Lance was supposed to bring that with him.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">But Oliver stole it from me, along with the gun, when he escaped.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">If Mr. Deacon was alive in the hideout, then the murder must've happened after that. Meaning it probably all went down at the stage. I mean, I can't really see why Ms. Paups would lie at a time like this, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, I don't think she is lying, but rather, that she is making a bad assumption.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">She is?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and I intend to show what that bad assumption is.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Paups. The person you saw was not Mr. Deacon at all.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The person you actually saw was this person:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Paups, the person you saw tied up to the beam was, in fact, Kay...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! Hold on! I was never tied up like that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">R-Right, I suppose not...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The one tied up to the beam screaming, "Nnngghhooooooh!!" was...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That will do, Kay! Anyway! The person you saw was most definitely not Mr. Deacon.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The person you saw tied up to the beam was none other than Lance!</line>
<line speaker="Paups">But Lance was the one who showed me the tied up person in the next room...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You're claiming that the boy somehow showed himself tied up to the beam? Are you serious!? Or perhaps you believe there was a rip in the space-time continuum?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nnngh...! Who was it that was tied up to that beam... Aha! I see! Now I know who it was!</thought> As I thought, the person you saw was most definitely not Mr. Deacon.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was me.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Huh? The person I saw was you. Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I always thought it was a bit odd. Why would the kidnappers abduct me, even after I had handed over the ransom?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's not as though I saw the face of the kidnappers. If I were them, I would have just taken the million dollars and ran. But, in the end, there was a point to it all; it was to make me look like Mr. Deacon. And if that was the reason for which I was abducted... ...then, I believe we can assume that the victim was already dead at that time. Well, Lance? Am I right?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Nngh... Th-That's...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You showed Ms. Paups a person, namely me, with a Bad Badger's head on. And then, made your costumed escape together... Or so you pretended.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Huh!? What do you mean he "pretended"!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Exactly that. I believe Lance watched you escape, and then doubled back to the hideout. Probably to come and remove the Bad Badger head from my unconscious self...</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Unnnnngh..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And to create his fake "prison" with the prop sword. He then escaped via the passageway.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hold your tongue, boy! Don't get caught up in that tidal wave of words coming out of Mr. Prosecutor's mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tidal wave?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">We've heard a lot come out of you, but I've yet to see a shred of evidence. The victim's betrayal, and his subsequent detainment... All of that could've happened while you were out cold.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Th-That's right! You were out for quite a while, Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even if that were the case. Ms. Paups would have still seen me tied to that beam.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">I... I was scared of Mr. Deacon, so I didn't go into the next room. So I really have no idea if you were in there or not, Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You see. It would seem that you can't prove a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Wh-Who said that!?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Please, wait.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Amano!</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Ho ho ho. Miles, my boy. It looks like you're really giving it your all. And Lance... It's not good to cause trouble for others.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">D-Dad!</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Let's see... You are the one in charge of the investigation, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Yeah, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">I'm sorry that my son has been nothing but trouble. This probably won't make up for anything, but I have some evidence for you.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Oh? Do you, now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is that what I think it is!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's the Bad Badger costume the victim was wearing! And a gun!</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">I couldn't wait around for the police, so I went and found these myself. It appears that they were disposed of in the sea.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Argh! Is there no one in this country who actually obeys the law!?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">There, there, now. Agent Lang, please calm down.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hm? What the heck is that scrap of paper?</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">.........This appears to be a letter from the Chief of Police. "Please allow Mr. Amano complete freedom to do as he sees fit," it says.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Th-The Chief of Poliiiiiice!? What the......... Just who does he think he is!?</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">The person who wields the highest authority in this area...</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Ho ho ho. There, there, now. There is no need to be so upset.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Heh. I'm not a cop from this land. So I'm not bound by the laws of your country.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Now, now, now. This wasn't meant to strong-arm you into anything. It's just a request. I'm only asking that you please respect the laws of the land.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Argh. I can't really say no to that. However, returning to the topic at hand... ...it doesn't matter who found the evidence. Its value remains unchanged. Alright now, let's take a look at this new evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">I've already got the results back. I had a special forensics research lab that I'm on good terms with conduct the tests. They verified that the blood on this costume belonged to Oliver. As for the gun... ..the only fingerprints they could find were yours, Lauren!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">You disappoint me, Miles. I can't believe that you... that you would... cause my son such stress and heartache! Thank goodness I was able to find the final pieces of evidence. With this, you'll have no reason left to push my poor boy around!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's it? These are the case-making pieces of evidence? Hah! I'll be the judge of that! I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm? What's this? It looks like there's something inside the costume head...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! They sparkle! I bet they're really valuable!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry, but they're just pieces of a mirror... <thought>But why are they in here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This bullet hole...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It looks kind of burnt around the edges.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait! Those burn marks were left by the gunpowder... This is a most important fact.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Why is that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Because it is proof that the victim was shot at point black range.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Could this gun be the actual murder weapon?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They found Ms. Paups's fingerprints on this gun.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Can you let me hold it for a sec?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I shouldn't if you don't know how to handle it. Besides, Ms. Paups's prints are on it.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Look! I'm wearing gloves! It'll be OK! I just want to take a look, that's all! It's not like I'm going to run off with it. The only things I don't return are treasures!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Stealing either one would land you in jail, you know...</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Well? Are these not the most definitive pieces of evidence you've ever seen?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Thank you, Dad. This should be enough to convince even Mr. Edgeworth over there.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Make no mistake. There are fingerprints on that murderous gun.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The fingerprints on the weapon, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, no! This isn't helpful at all!</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Look, Mr. Edgeworth... All I want to do is save Lolli. But in the end, all I can do is watch on as she takes the punishmebt for her crimes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That may be all you can do, however... ...I still have a case to solve and a job to do. The job of unraveling your insidious lie!</line>
<line speaker="Lance">...You wound me. Why won't you believe me, even in the face of all this evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Make no mistake. There are fingerprints on that murderous gun.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Those fingerprints... Are you sure they belong to Ms. Paups?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">There's no mistake about it. Through my connections, I had the best forensics techniques money can buy performed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I find that to be a bit peculiar.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">What? Are you trying to pick an argument with me!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What should I do? Should I raise an objection?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Perhaps I should wait and see how this pans out first...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Frankly, I don't believe that Ms. Paups's prints should be on that gun to begin with. And the reason why Ms. Paups's prints should not be on the gun is...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">With this piece of evidence, there is no reason for her to have left prints at all!</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Which piece is that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Look here! This is what I speak of!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Your logic is so hard to follow you should provide a map!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Knnngh! <thought>Even if she did it, there is something specific that makes it impossible to leave prints.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Lance">And they proved that it was Lolli who killed Oliver.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You sure are calm for someone who is accusing his own girlfriend of murder.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">You have it all wrong! Allowing her to pay the price is a form of love. She says that she also wants to pay back her debt to society, but...</line>
<line speaker="Lance">But Oliver was also after Lolli's life.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And why do you believe that the victim was set on taking Ms. Paups's life?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">I suppose it's because he wanted to silence her. To keep her quiet, because she knows the truth behind the kidnapping.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In that case, why did he not target you as well?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">...Th-That's because... ...because he knew that if he killed me, he wouldn't be able to control my father.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Ho ho ho. Right you are. Even if it cost me millions, I would have had the killer found.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe he didn't kill you for an entirely different reason, however, I digress...</line>
<line speaker="Lance">L-Look, more than why he didn't kill me, I'm worried about what'll happen to Lolli!</line>
<line speaker="Lance">So Mr. Edgeworth, even you must see that Lolli was only acting in self-defense.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Justified self-defense? I suppose that is a possibility, given the circumstances.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Really!? Oh, thank goodness...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, self-defense was not necessary in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Wh-What do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Paups is innocent. She didn't do anything, so why would she need to defend herself from nothing?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">You still don't believe a word I say, do you...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>His entire argument hinges on the fact that her fingerprints are on the gun. However, the truth does not lie there. It lies in whatever he is hiding from me, but not for long!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's simply not possible for Ms. Paups to have left any prints on the murder weapon. Because, while she was at the stadium, Ms. Paups was wearing a costume.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">But there's been no mistake! We found fingerprints!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, Ms. Paups? Do you remember touching the gun at all at any time?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">............ Ah, yes! As a matter of fact, I did hold it for a bit back in the hideout! I handed it off to Mr. Deacon when he and Lance left for the haunted house.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>To retrieve the ransom money, I suppose...</thought> And there you have it. That is when Ms. Paups's prints found their way onto the gun.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Grrrrrr...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you understand now, Mr. Amano? The fingerprints do nothing to prove that Ms. Paups is the murderer.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">But you still don't have anything to prove that she ISN'T the killer, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You seem very adamant about insisting that your girlfriend is a cold-blooded killer...</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Oh, Lance...!</line>
<line speaker="Lance">What!? No way! I'm incredibly worried about her! But that doesn't change the fact that you don't have any evidence, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. That's where you're wrong. I have the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">What... How...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The story that Ms. Paups killed the victim at the stage in the stadium... The whole affair is simply not true, because that was not the real crime scene, but a set-up. This proves that the real murder was not committed at the stadium at all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence proves that the real crime scene is not, in fact, the stadium.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Mr. Prosecutor... I'd have to rate that piece of logic a 0 out of 10.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Z-ZERO!? It's at least a 6.8 out of 10!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lance">At this rate, Lolli is going to wind up getting arrested...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I must remain calm and think clearly. If the murder did not happen at the stadium... ...then the scenario where the victim was up on the stage and Ms. Paups was down below... ......There must be something that invalidates it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let us take another good look at the costume the victim was wearing. Then, I believe you will see why I insist he was not shot at the stadium. This is the part of the costume that proves it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you look in this area, all will become clear.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">"This area"? Do you really think that sort of vague statement is going to fly!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Mnngh! He saw right through me! I just know that it's not possible for the victim to have been shot at the stadium!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The burn around this bullet hole was made when the victim was shot at point-blank range.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! So then, you mean the "murder" Ms. Oldbag saw at the stadium really was...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. She saw two people, but they were separated by a distance. If the victim was indeed shot from below the stage, there shouldn't be a gunpowder burn!</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Argn!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Heh, look at you, Mr. Smarty-Pants Prosecutor. Since you seem to know all the answers, why not tell us where the real crime scene is then?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Lance set me up to look like Mr. Deacon back at the hideout. If that's the case, then the murder must have happened prior to that! And the location where Lance and the victim were at just before I was imprisoned was... I've got it! I know the real scene of the murder!</thought> The real location in which Mr. Deacon was killed is here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The real scene of the murder was here, at the stage inside the stadium!</line>
<line speaker="Lang"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> YOU'RE the one who just claimed that the stage was not the real crime scene! Now, take some responsibility for that time-wasting outburst!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnngk...! <thought>How could I forget the point of my own argument!? And at this critical junction...! The murder could not have taken place at the stadium.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This hotel in the center is the real scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey, Mr. Prosecutor! If there was even the echo of a gunshot at the hotel, there'd be wide-spread panic by now! But I haven't received word of even a slight disturbance!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh... <thought>Where were the two of them just prior to my imprisonment...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The real scene of the crime was here, right in front of the main gate!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">If the murder really happened here, you'd think there would be a witness or two... And yet, not a single person has yet to come forward!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnngk...! <thought>Where were the two of them just prior to my imprisonment...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The real scene of the murder was here, in the Wild, Wild West area!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">The place where you and I first met, huh... But didn't you already check there? I know I did, and there wasn't a single sign that someone had been killed there!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, well, I suppose there wasn't. <thought>The murder took place before I was imprisoned. And the only place where the victim and Lance were together alone was...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Lang">What the--!? Where is that supposed to be!? Shih-na, find out for me, will you!?</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">It doesn't have a name. It just simply is.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Well, that was a big waste of time, thanks to your below sub-par reasoning skills!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh--!? <thought>I've come so far! I can't be far from the truth now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think it's not unreasonable to assume the murder took place in the haunted house.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">The haunted house?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and I have proof that it is highly likely that the victim was killed there! What proves that the real scene of the crime was the haunted house?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence tells us that the haunted house is where the victim was killed!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I don't hear anything! Other than the sound of desperation!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Gnnnhhhooooh! The haunted house, the costume. and the gun... They're all connected, and the final piece of this complex chess set is this!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">These were inside the costume the victim was wearing. They're fragments of a mirror.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">A mirror? And what does that have to do with anything?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. You don't exactly expect to find pieces of a mirror inside a costume.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, that's actually pretty dangerous.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, there is one place I can think of where there is a plethora of mirror fragments. And that is the haunted house. Lance Amano! I propose that you killed Mr. Deacon with the revolver in the haunted house! After that, you stole the Blue Badgermobile to move his body to the Wild, Wild West area. The timing of when the Blue Badgermobile was stolen confirms this as fact!</line>
<line speaker="Lance">..................</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Miles, my boy. Say no more!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm so sorry, Mr. Amano, but I cannot do that.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Be quiet!</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Yes, please, do something! Stop that boy from speaking any more nonsense!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ernest Amano, correct? I meant you. Now be quiet, gramps.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">H-How dare you!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I don't need words. The only thing I require is evidence. Decisive evidence! And to call these mirror bits "decisive" is a bit too presumptuous, Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Shih-na! Wasn't there a mirror in the kidnappers' hideout?</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">Yes, there was a mirror there. A mirror that's for the haunted house.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You see! Isn't possible the fragments got into the costume there!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But, Agent Lang, there was no fragments on the floor, so the probability is very low.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">"Probability"? Ha ha ha ha ha ha! Lang Zi says: "On truth's path, the word "probability" does not exist." The only thing that does is definitive proof. The question, Mr. Prosecutor, is, "Do you have the definitive proof you need?"</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, Mr. Edgeworth? Do you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............ <thought>Do I have solid evidence that proves the murder took place at the haunted house...?</thought> The answer is... no.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">See! So since you don't have any, shut up!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I don't have evidence yet... But... I'm certain the murder occurred around the time I turned the ransom over. At that time, the only people at the haunted house besides myself... ...were Lance and Mr. Deacon. If I can prove that the murder took place at the haunted house... ...then I can prove Lance's guilt in connection to the murder!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">What now, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang. I have a special request.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like to prove to you that the scene of the crime was indeed the haunted house.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Why in the world are you asking the werewolf for permission!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Because I don't really have a choice, if I want to find the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Alright, permission granted. But you're not to touch a single thing, got it!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That won't be a problem. All that's important to me is that the truth be brought to light. It doesn't matter by who or how it's done, as long as it is.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">..................Tch! Shih-na!</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">I'm here.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Put in the paperwork for the authorization immediately.</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">Understood. I'll go get the Gatewater Group's approval.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Wh-Who was that!?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Now, now, let's hold on for a second. There is no need to obtain approval.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Amano...?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Agent Lang. If you would please take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What is this...? Shih-na!</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">It's... the deed to the haunted house.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The deed?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Read it, out loud!</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">"Gatewater Land, Inc. hereby bequeaths the property known as the "Haunted House"... ...to Mr. Amano for the lump sum of $1 million, paid in full in cash."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Ho ho ho. As you can see, I am now the legal owner of the haunted house.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Are you kidding!? When did you--!?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">I ran into the owner of the park earlier, and we made the deal almost immediately. How quickly things move when you can prepare a million dollars in the blink of an eye.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-That $1 million you paid... Don't tell me it was...!</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Oh, that's right. This disgusting suitcase belongs to you, doesn't it? I don't have any more use for it, so you may have it back now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-You used the ransom money...!?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">My Lance is a good boy. He even apologized for the kidnapping a bit earlier... ...so I do believe that I will forgive him. After all, he did return the ransom money. That's the way things are, so if you would please discuss things with me now on...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Discuss? What is there to discuss?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Why, permission to enter the haunted house, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>While we were busy listening to Lance's story, Mr. Amano was out there preempting us!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Permission to search the haunted house is denied. End of discussion. Agent Lang, I want you to arrest that girl. And Miles, you should hurry on home now, my boy, before I really lose my temper.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Arngh! Mr. Amano definitely has the deck stacked in his favor here... What should I do? If I leave it like this, the truth will be lost forever!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If I can't get permission to investigate the crime scene, then the truth will be lost...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> <cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> Hooooold it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! What are you doing spacing out!? Have you forgotten!? There's only one thing you should do at a time like this!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what is that?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">When the people are in a bind, the hero of justice appears to save the day! Look, you just leave it to me! For I am Kay Faraday! The second of the great Yatagarasu!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But I thought you were a thief, not a hero...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The Yatagarasu is noble, and is always a thief of justice!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's...! Of course...!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">If we have enough information, I can re-create the inside of the haunted house with this! Plus, if we then factor in everyone's testimony...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You can re-create exactly what happened when I dropped off the ransom money. <thought>We may be able to figure out some new information through this. It's worth a try!</thought> Agent Lang.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ah, so you want to use your little toy? Be my guest.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK! Hang on! You're all about to witness the true power of a real, modern-day Robin Hood!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe! Is there a copy of the haunted house's blueprint among the police's reference documents?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir! We got it just in case we needed it for the kidnapping case!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Alright! I'll input the haunted house data, then!</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Wh-What is this...? Where are we...?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">It's... It's like we're inside the haunted house!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Even if we can't inspect the real location itself... ...the path to the truth slumbers here. If I can successfully navigate my way using logic, I'll ultimately arrive at the truth!</thought> Now then, I believe I'm ready to investigate the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK, what should I re-create first?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You haven't figured it out yet?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Heh, maybe I have, and maybe I haven't. But I'm going to make you do all the hard work!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very well. I'd like to inspect the moment in which I was ambushed by my abductor. <thought>The two of them were definitely in this place at that time. If I can verify that, it may provide me with a new lead.</thought> I had just come out into the hallway after leaving the money inside the dining room. At that time, I saw a Badger, slumped over on the floor at the end of the hall.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ehhh!? What was a Badger doing all the way down there!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I also thought it strange. However, I thought that maybe it was simply a mannequin that was set there for atmosphere.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Do you know which Badger it was?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...No. It was too dark to tell. All I saw was its silhouette.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmm... In that case, I guess I'll just program a Badger silhouette in for now! OK, programming complete!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then, I started walking towards the exit.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And that's when you were struck from behind, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But, that's odd. The hallway is a dead end. Where did your assailant come from?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is only one location I can think of. I believe my assailant was lying in wait here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Kay">.........What are you thinking, Mr. Edgeworth!? That's a terrible hiding spot! He'd have to be a real ninja to get away with hiding there!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-That was not exactly the nuance I was trying to convey... <thought>Where could my assailant have hidden himself in this haunted house...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That "doll" I saw wasn't really a doll; it was, in fact. a costumed kidnapper.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, so he used the costume as the perfect camouflage to blend in with the rest of the house!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely. He waited until I had made the drop off, and was about to leave. Then, just as he saw me take a step forwards the exit, he stood and launched his attack. I can think of no better hiding place than this.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, not bad! I'm beginning to think I should steal this tactic for myself!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Just don't use it to do anything criminal, Kay. Well, Lance?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Wha--!? Wh-What are you asking me for...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As one of the kidnappers, I figured I should give you the chance to confess first.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">.........I was one of the kidnappers, b-but... I don't know anything. I did come up to the haunted house, but I never set foot inside. I left Oliver in charge of picking up the ransom money.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He didn't set foot inside? Is he telling the truth, or is this another lie?</thought> Alright, then you're claiming that it was Mr. Deacon who assaulted me?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Yes. I'm sure it was him.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK, inputting the new info, now! Mr. Deacon was the Bad Badger, right? Since the Bad Badger has a gun attached to its right hand... ...I'll have to change it so the weapon is in its left hand!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Now to verify the facts of this re-creation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, how is, um... Little Thief...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Totally fine and re-creating the crime scene! All that's left is more info. But you know, I can't believe I'm replicating a haunted house. And that we're talking about the fate of a million dollars! Pretty exciting stuff!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't say I understand what is so exciting about re-creating a crime scene...</thought> In any case, I believe that it is very probable that the murder occurred at this place. And if I can prove that, then we will finally arrive at the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah! So what are you waiting for!? Let's get investigating!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I... I can't believe what I'm seeing, sir! This space that I'm standing in... It's like out of some crazy dream!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Except that this isn't a dream. This is something Kay's gadget...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No, wait, this is EXACTLY like a dream, sir! I've never been so impressed! It's a miracle!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......... <thought>Someone sure is easily impressed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hee hee, I'm so glad you like it!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! So this is a product of your gadget!? Now I wish I had one, too!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, once this is over, I'll let you play with it for a bit, if you want!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You'd do that for me, pal!? Thanks! Alright, let's wrap this case up already!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's times like these that I wonder if they understand the seriousness of the situation!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Thanks... for letting us use... um... Little Thief.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Lang Zi says: "Reject not those who seek the truth." So keep in mind that I'm not doing it for you; I'm doing this for the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't worry, I understand. We may have different methods, but our wish is the same.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, have you noticed anything worthwhile?</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">...I have no obligation to talk with you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, I'm fine with just Little Thief in solving this case.</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">...That toy. It's very well made.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ha hah! That's because it's the heart of the noble thief, Yatagarasu!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, that may not be something you want to advertise to everyone.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">So, Shih-na. What exactly is the source of this extra-dimensional-like space?</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">I believe this is nothing more than a projection from that girl's toy.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">So, it's all an... illusion, right?</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">..................Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! Don't treat this like some sort of silly right now!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a replica of myself...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You were totally oblivious to what was behind you, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I suppose I am also to blame for what happened to me. It was incredibly dark, which was all the more reason I should have been more alert. <thought>I vow to never be caught by surprise again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You didn't re-create the weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, I can't exactly re-create something I know nothing about. So tell me, what were you hit with?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The attack came from behind, so I have no idea. But I doubt it was someone's bare hands.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Um... OK, then where were you hit?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was hit on the right side of my head, just above my temple. There was a bit of blood, but it wasn't anything serious.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ouch! Sounds painful!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Why are you smirking like that when you say it!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's just your imagination! Now, let's see... I wonder if there's anything in the hallway that could've been used as a weapon? I'm looking for something the culprit could've used to hit you with.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The object the culprit used... Could it not have been this?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...I... don't really think that's it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I wonder if there's anything in the hallway that could've been used as a weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have it. There was indeed one such object lying here in this hallway. A prop sword.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Are you talking about this thing here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... Although, we did find it at the kidnappers' hideout... Wait... Yes! It's possible that the culprit took it with him after using it on me.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">To leave no evidence behind, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correct. It may be worth a more thorough examination yet.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK, so what test do you want to run on this sword?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The culprit was wearing a costume at the time, so a fingerprint analysis is useless.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We should first run a fingerprint analysis...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But wasn't the person who attacked you wearing a costume? Somehow, I don't think he left any prints on here for us...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose not... <thought>Curses. How could I have made such a rudimentary mistake?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's run a Luminol test. It's possible that some of my blood found its way onto this. Agent Lang, may I ask for your cooperation in this matter?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">...Hmph. Like I have a choice! Shih-na! Call the lab boys!</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">...Understood.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Except for a dab on the left side, it would appears that the blade is spotless.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So it must have been the left side of the prop sword that hit you then, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK, I'll update the re-creation with this new piece of info!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">You know, the Bad Badger is pretty bad-looking when you see him up close.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well? What did you expect from a character named the "Bad Badger"...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And those sunglasses! Wearing them in the dark makes him seem extra bad!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Now I'm lost. Which meaning of "bad" does she really mean...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">And in the next instant, this Badger will swing his left arm, complete with weapon in hand!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, to club me with the left side of the prop sword.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Shall I re-create the moment of impact? I wanna see the pained expression on your face!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's just fine the way it is! <thought>Hm...? Wait, maybe not... Is it just my imagination, or is something not quite right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's me... I have to say, it's rather embarrassing to see myself like this.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, so what were you thinking about at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't recall, but I would guess that I was thinking about the kidnapping.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Really? Because I don't think so at all! Your face practically screams, "I'm about to be conked over the head!" Hee hee.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If I had known that at the time, do you think I would've let myself be hit!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this spot somehow connected to any of the evidence I hold...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Finally! I've found a clear contradiction of facts about this sword! Except for a bit on the left side, this prop sword is absolutely spotless! However, if the culprit had used his left hand, the blood would be on the opposite side!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The opposite side? Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If the culprit held the sword in his left hand, then the sword's right side would hit.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I see. But the blood was on the left side of the sword, right? Which means... that he used his right hand to hit you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Exactly. This prop sword has a large hand guard attached to the hilt. It would be impossible to hold it with two hands while wearing a costume with such big hands. Therefore, if it couldn't be the left hand or both hands... It must have been the right.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'll change the data to reflect a right-handed swing...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not yet, Kay! There's no sense in changing anything yet. If you change the parameters to the right hand, it'd create a new contradiction. Changing the prop sword to be in the culprit's right hand would conflict with what?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would create a conflict with this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Are you sure...? They seem kinda unrelated to me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Gnnnrk!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Guess I really should just go ahead and fix the data to reflect a right-handed swing...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait, Kay. If you change the parameters to the right hand, it would really create a contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Bad Badger already holds a gun in his right hand, so he can't hold a sword in addition.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, that's right! Then what now? If it wasn't in his left or his right hand...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It means that the one who struck me could not have been the Bad Badger!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">According to this document, the victim was right-handed.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aha! I guess I should change which hand is holding the weapon, then...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hold on, you two. You didn't think I was going to ignore something like that, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What are you talking about!? Look, no interrupting when I'm about to have a little fun!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha! Even if you changed your re-creation, you'd only be wasting your time. It's not possible for that thing to hold something in its right hand, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But Mr. Edgeworth's logic is...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What's that thing called? The Bad Badger? Just take another good look at its right hand.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh! I forgot the weapon isn't in its right hand because there's already a gun in it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Precisely.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Tch! You knew that already?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and I also know that the Badger was holding the weapon in his right hand.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Huh? Are you aware of what's coming out of your mouth? You just contradicted yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have evidence, of course; proof that the culprit held the sword in his right hand.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Sounds interesting. Alright then, show me this "evidence"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece proves that the culprit held the weapon in his right hand when he struck:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like to point you to this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">............</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">............</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What the heck kind of proof is that supposed to be, Mr. Prosecutor? Can it be... ...that you don't know your left from right!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Poppycock! <thought>Perhaps that wasn't the evidence I was looking for...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">What are you doing, Mr. Edgeworth!? Get your head on straight! Look! Think about when you're picking a lock. You hould the lock pick in your right hand!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Kay, that's only if you're right-handed, and interested in thievery. Agent Lang, accept my apologies. I will now show you what I had meant to show you all along.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">In that case, hurry up and show it to me already!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The answer is the weapon itself! Except for a bit on the left side, this prop sword is absolutely spotless! However, if the culprit had used his left hand, the blood would be on the opposite side!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But the replica Bad Badger isn't holding the sword in his right hand! Hmph! I don't know what's going on anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Giving up already? It's simple. If he can't hold the sword in his left or his right hand... ...then the one who struck me could not have been the Bad Badger.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This here, contradicts this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmm... You know, I think you're overthinking it just a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh! Maybe I wasn't through enough in my explanation... <thought>I must remain calm. If I struck in the head in exactly the way this re-creation portrays... I believe that it would go against a certain piece of evidence. It's a piece that is deeply connected to this case... It's definitely worth a try.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You can lie all you want, but it will all be for naught, Lance. As soon as I expose the truth, you will be placed under arrest.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">H-How can you do this!? After all that my dad was done for you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What your father has done for me is unrelated to the charges you face now.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Nnrrrgh... Unbelievable...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You know, you sound kind of like a bully right now, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If I'm not serious about this, he will never understand the true gravity of his crimes. I will not allow him to remain a child forever.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ha ha! Now you sound like a dad!</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Miles, my boy... What is the meaning of all this!? Do you plan to pay me back for all I've done for you with the conviction of my son!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have not forgotten my debt to you, however, your son's crimes are a separate matter. Further, I can't ignore the truth when it's right before me.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Gnnnnnnrrrrrrrrr! You will regret this. I promise you that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>No matter the outcome, I never regret the choices I make!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Paups, by my hand, I will prove your innocence in the murder of Mr. Deacon. Therefore, please don't fret. It will soon be over.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm...? Do you not trust me?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">I! I-I! Um... That is...!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Your face is all beet-red, Ms. Paups.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">N-No, I can't! I-I have Lance...!</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Lolli...! Don't tell me that you like that guy more than me...!</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Th-That's...! Oh! Why am I so pathetic!? I'm so easily swayed by even a single glance! I'm! I'm!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Um... What eactly is she going on about?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I think you have another "guilty" person on your hands, Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">When you take a look around, it almost feels more like a house of mirrors.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Indeed. Who has ever heard of this many mirrors inside of a haunted house before?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, at least we know this is the real crime scene, thanks to these mirror shards <thought>Mirror shards - Like a mirror house - haunted house hybrid, this place is full of mirrors.</thought>. Hey, wait... These shards... There's something different about them.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The ones we found earlier are thicker than the shards from these mirrors on this wall! And... Look! There's some sort of design on the back, too!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The pieces from that costume are certainly different from the other mirrors... <thought>What does this mean? Could it be that our pieces are not pieces of these mirrors?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Pieces of a set of armor are in a pole here.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Why do you think they almost always have sets of armor inside haunted houses?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose this sort of interior design is meant to bring out a sense of the abnormalcy.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Why do all your explanations have to be so hard to understand, Mr. Edgeworth!? Now try explaining it again, but this time, so that even a thief like me can get it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That... may prove to be a most difficult task.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">I imagine this is how he snuck up on you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That gadget of yours can even replicate people's movements?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, it's used to plan heists, so of course it's gotta be able to simulate the police.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-It's definitely very well made. <thought>Perhaps too well made... Maybe I should confiscate it after the investigation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I remember glancing over, and seeing this figure sitting here as I left the dining room...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So I guess I got it spot on when I put it here in my re-creation!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I didn't take a good look, but I'm sure there was a Badger here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you paying attention, Lance?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Deacon could not have been the one who struck me. Which leaves only you as our primary suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">......Rrrnngh. Fine! It was me! I hit you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It appears that you lied to me yet again, but see how quickly they catch up to you, Lance?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wait... Isn't Lance left handed?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, yes. But that's what makes this deception all the more interesting. He used his right hand to make it look like Mr. Deacon had been the one to strike me. For you see, firing a with one's non-dominant hand is difficult... ...but that level of dexterity isn't required to swing a prop sword.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Argn!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay! Please input this new data. The one who hit me from behind was Lance... ...or should I say, the Proto Badger.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You got it! Here I gooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, we have a faithful re-creation of the situation around the attack on me.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Alright! All we have to do is examine this new re-creation and...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what exactly is so funny, Agent Lang!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">That amusing little gadget, it sure packs a punch, right, Shih-na?</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">Yes. It was all I could do to hold my laughter in.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! Don't make fun of Little Thief, you mean ol' werewolf! He and Mr. Edgeworth bring out the best in each other!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You've had your little fun, but now it's my turn. I've sat quietly by, listening... ...but the crude conclusions you two keep spewing don't whet this wolf's appetite!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">There's no guarantee that your toy will always show the real situation at any given time. All it displays is whatever information you put in there, right?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, when you put it that way...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Your suppositions are wrong. It's not your fault, so I'm going to let you in on this. There is a trick to this haunted house.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what may that be exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">A trick beyond what your tiny imaginations can produce! Shih-na!</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">Here you are.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Now then, what you missed, girlie... ...is written right here in this pamphlet.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"The Seven Wonders of the Haunted House: The Disappearing Badger!"...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wh-What is this?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I'd say that someone around here is fond of theatrics. And as you can see, they set a doll down at the end of this hallway for that purpose. Basically, the Blue Badger you saw was just a stupid doll!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">H...How can this be!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Guess that throws your whole theory about it being your attacker right out the window!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kkknnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">B-But that can't be right! Maybe the culprit hid the doll somewhere! And then, he laid down and pretended to be it instead!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">If the criminal couldn't even hide himself in the hallway, how could he hide a giant doll?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmph...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Do you get it now? Thanks to your presumptions... ...your logic started off weak, and led you to the completely wrond conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Knngh!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Now get off your high horse!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............Kay, I wonder if you could please input the new information for me.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">! You don't know when to quit, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can't quit, not until I can declare that I've found the truth. Agent Lang, for the additional information, you have my thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Tch! There you go again... Well, see if I care!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK, I'm updating the re-creation now!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That looks really weird... Look at how it changes from the Blue Badger into the Proto Badger all of a sudden.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If the slumped-over Badger was just a doll, where was my attacker hiding?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, that's what we're going to find out, right!? So, come on, Mr. Edgeworth! Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, let's. <thought>This re-creation can't be right, which means there must be a contradiction somewhere.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the Proto Badger who struck me. I suppose I should really say that it is Lance.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ooh! Are you going to get him back?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I need not resort to violence when the lawsuit I plan to bring to court will suffice.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Really!? Because, I would totally have decked him right back! If someone steals from me, I steal something from them. If I get hit, I hit them back. If I get paid, I return the money. That's the secret to how a Great Thief works!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Her third statement doesn't seem to be of much benefit to her survival...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">This is where the Proto Badger shows up in our re-creation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Now the question is, "Where did he come from?"</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, but there's no place to hide in our current model.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There must be an inconsistency somewhere...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This Blue Badger is just a doll for use in this haunted house.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I bet the one who killed this Blue Badger was the Bad Badger, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">According to the Blue Badger Bible, it says that they are each other's worst enemy.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">All because one's an "ally of justice" and the other's a "vile criminal with a gun"?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps, they were just destined to battle each other. <thought>Much like the Steel Samurai and the Evil Magistrate...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The Blue Badger in the pamphlet photo is in reverse to the regular Blue Badger. But why? There must be some sort of explanation...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this spot somehow connected to any of the evidence I hold...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hold on a second here! There is something wrong with this Blue Badger!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh? Like what?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The way the belt is on him is opposite of how it should be. Did you make a mistake?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That can't be! I inputted the image data exactly as it is in the pamphlet!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So then, why is the Blue Badger dressed up in reverse (Blue Badger in reverse - The Blue Badger in the pamphlet is wearing his belt in the reverse direction.</thought>?)</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is in complete contradiction to this piece of evidence! ...Well, maybe it's not in "complete" contradiction...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hold it, Mr. Edgeworth! Which is it? Is it a contradiction or not?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">S-Sorry... I don't quite now. <thought>There is something wrong with this scene. That much I know for sure. ...Or maybe it's just a trick of the eye... No, that can't be it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, do you remember what you said earlier?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What I said earlier about what?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">About how this building might as well have been a house of mirrors.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">A house of mirrors...? Oh! That would explain the reversed, or mirror, image!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, this Blue Badger might be nothing more than the reflected image of a real one.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Then was the Blue Badger you saw just a reflection?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">When I looked down this hall, I thought it was perfectly straight. However, if there was a mirror...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh! Then it would actually form an L-shape, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely. I was deceived. The hallway was almost pitch black... ...and there was a beam in the way that obstructed my view of the other hallway.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wait, but why build this place like that? It sounds pretty pointless to me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, this house is just another attraction at an amusement park. They created a mirror-wall for a very specific purpose, one I can point out to you. This was the reason they built a mirror-wall:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Kay">......I don't get it. What's the connection between that and the mirror-wall?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's up to you to deduce if there is a connection or not.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">.................. Wait, that's your job!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Gnnrk! I should've  figured I couldn't get away with that one... Alright, this house is one of the attractions here at this park. It should be pretty easy to reason out why they placed a mirror-wall here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As it's written in the pamphlet, the main draw of this attraction... ...is the mystery of the "disappearing Badger".</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You mean they built the mirror for that trick alone? But You said you saw the Badger, so it was definitely still there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That was true, at the time, however... Doing this allows someone to make the Blue Badger disappear in a flash:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">All they would have to do is move the Blue Badger.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But do you think someone could really do that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, it's a rather expensive prop, so perhaps it isn't possible...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Um, doesn't that kinda... ...ruin the whole point to having the mirror in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..........I suppose it does.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! Come on, you can do better than this!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Alright, once more...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">All they would have to do is dim the lamps.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So that's how it's done! If it was completely dark in here...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Then you wouldn't be able to see the Badger anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah............ Wait, hold on! That's completely pointless! You wouldn't be able to see anything at all, not even where you were going!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... Is that necessarily a bad thing?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, it is if it negates the point of the attraction!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'd better rethink this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To remove a reflected image, simply move the mirror. First, the mirror was constructed so that it could be moved. Then, beyond where the mirror was, an empty hallway had to be created.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, so when they wanted people to see the Blue Badger, the would open the mirror...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And when they wanted to hide it, they simply had to close it again. This explains why the other side of these fragments have a design on them.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ahh, and if the pattern is the same as the other walls in this hallway...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Then, when the mirror is closed, it would blend in with the rest of the walls. This is the mirror trick that this haunted house employs. And this... also proves the existence of a hiding place for the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh? How so?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Think about it, Kay. There was a place that was outside of my field of vision! The culprit kept out of sight by hiding here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Kay">..................Umm... I'm not sure how he "kept out of sight" by standing there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You mean to say that even a Great Thief like yourself couldn't hide here?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Even the Yatagarasu has walls she can't overcome, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As I thought... I suppose it wasn't possible for the culprit either, in that case.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">If you already knew that, then why did you bring it up in the first place!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nnrgk! I need to rethink this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There was a very large blind spot, one I could not see beyond, and it was here! If my assailant hid on the other side of the movable mirror...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Then you wouldn't be able to see him! He didn't even need to do anything to the Blue Badger doll!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Exactly. All he had to do was wait for me on the other side of the mirror.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wait... Hold on... I just thought of something.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well... Shouldn't the mirror-wall be broken right now, in reality?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... Since we have a few shards of it, we can probably assume it is. <thought>Yes... It most definitely is broken. The question is, "When was it broken?" Since we found these inside the victim's costume... ...that would mean that the victim was there when the mirror was broken. Wait... That sound...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">LeAVe tHe MoNEy aND GO. NoW.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That sound I heard was most definitely the sound of a mirror breaking!</thought> Kay, I'd like you to input some new information!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aaack! Don't scare me like that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry. But I need you to re-create something for me.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Sure, whatever you need! So what DO you need, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you could first re-create this hallway just before I entered the dining room...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You got it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now this... I believe this is how it was right before I entered the dining room. Although, at the time, I thought it was but a single straight hallway. And then, I went inside. It was around then that I heard the sound of a mirror shattering!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You heard what...!? Then...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I believe it was then that the mirror was broken.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK, so then when you stepped outside into the hallway again...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...The mirror-wall should not longer exist. Kay, please re-create that!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wait, but with the mirror gone, the culprit lost his hiding spot! So where did he go in his Proto Badger suit, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hah, that's easy enough. With the mirror gone, he simply hid himself in the branch hallway.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmm... I think this about wraps it up. Looks like we finally solved everything!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, not yet. An even larger contradiction has now reared its head.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps you did not notice... ...but this re-creation contains a very troubling inconsistency. The inconsistency between what I saw and the re-creation lies...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Here!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh!? Are you sure that contradicts what you saw?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, well... that's something even I must look into a bit more.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What!? If even you're having a tough time with this, then it must be one tricksy trick! .........Hey! Wait, you didn't mean what you just said, did you!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Urnnngh!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Stop messing with me and just tell me the answer already!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Very well. <thought>Thank goodness. It would seem that she failed to notice my slip-up... The scene I saw before me, and what's being presented in this re-creation... There's something that was there on site that isn't in this re-creation...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, take a good look at the end of the hall.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh! There's no Blue Badger there!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Exactly. The Blue Badger that I saw in reality is not here. This is the final point on this long chain of logic; the last remaining contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So, let me get this straight. When you came out of the dining room... ...you saw a Badger, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And that is precisely where the final contradiction lies. Something that shouldn't exist was there before me. Who, or what do you suppose it was? I believe this is the real identity of our mystery Badger!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is what I really saw at the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You mistook that for a Badger? You disappoint me! We've worked so hard to get here; don't get all weird on me now!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Gnnrk! The last contradiction...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Badger I saw was, in actuality, the dead victim's body!</line>
<line speaker="Lance">...Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang, the entirely of my complete logic is my final, decisive piece of evidence. The murder happened in the hallway of the haunted house at the time of the drop-off. And you can consider the moment I heard the mirror breaking... ...to be the real time of death for Mr. Deacon.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Noooo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Maybe it was due to their fighting, or perhaps it was the life-shattering bullet... ...but no matter what the cause was, the hallway mirror-wall was broken.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha! You were in the house at the time, right? Are you telling me that you missed the sound of gunshot!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There were a variety of sound effects playing at the time... All for theatrics, I assume. The gunshot must have blended right in.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Aiya!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, I'd like you to recall something for me. Who was it that was with the victim at the haunted house?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">...Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Who was the one who had the opportunity to rob the victim of his gun and use it on him?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">...Nnnguuurk!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was you! Lance Amano!</line>
<line speaker="Lance">I'm sooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooorry!</line>
<line speaker="Lance">It's not like I had a choice! Oliver turned on me all of a sudden! He snapped and turned violent right after I hung up with you! He shoved me to the ground and straddled me! I fought back as hard as I could, grabbed his gun, and... I shot him! The bullet must've went through his body and shattered the mirror...! If I hadn't taken his gun and shot him first, I would've been the one you found! He's a hardened criminal! He escaped from jail!</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">See! That's justified self-defense! My boy was only trying to protect himself!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That remains to be seen, and will have to be resolved in court. Agent Lang, I leave the rest to you.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Heh, as if YOU were the one in charge around here! Guys! Arrest these two and get them out of my sight!</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">W-Wait! I had nothing to do with the murder! The only person you should be arresting is Lance!</line>
<line speaker="Lance">D-Dad!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Sorry, but you're not slipping away that easily, Mr. Ernest Amano. You tampered with the evidence so that you could cover for your son. What a great dad you are, willing to risk it all! Truly touching.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Grrrrrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">By the way... Do you know why I'm really here?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">And how could I possibly know the answer to such an asinine question!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You wound me. I came all this way from across the sea, just to see you, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">You came to see... me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What's that supposed to mean...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">I have a few things to ask you, Mr. Amano, about a case from 10 years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A case from 10 years ago?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Oh, what's the name that you use here for that case? Shih-na!</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">It's known as the KG-8 Incident.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The KG-8 Incident...!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Oh, so you remember it? Good. Then you'll recall that the trigger in that case was the Amano Group scandal. Specifically, the charge of an internal smuggling ring.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Smuggling... There's that word again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">At the time, the person that was arrested as the ringleader... ...was Mr. Amano's very own secretary, Mr. Colin Devorae.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Ah! Father...!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Even though you pushed the crime onto your then-secretary, Mr. Devorae... ...I always suspected that you were involved with the smuggling ring, Mr. Amano. Mr. Devorae was arrested in place of you... ...which is why when he broke out, you hid him from the police, right? You hid him in exchange for his silence on your little, dirty secret!</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Now, now, now, now, now! Please calm down. I honestly have no idea what you're talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Heh, pretend to be ignorant all you want. We're taking you down to the precinct anyway for a nice, long chat.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">..................</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What the--!? Who the heck was that!?</line>
<line speaker="???">I'll take him down to the precinct, if you don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">And who the heck are you?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I'm Jacques Portsman, and I'm the prosecutor in charge of this case.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Oh, Jacques! Thank goodness you're here...!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Don't jerk me around! This is an Interpol case, so keep your paws off of my suspect!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Sorry, but I can't comply. I've got the backing of the Prosecutor's Office. See, in this country, we prosecutors work with the police to bring cases to court. So if you could please cooperate with me here, that'd be great! Now, how about a handshake to seal the deal!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Sorry, but I hate prosecutors, the whole lot of you! Guys! Arrest the two suspects!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Oh, I almost forgot. Prosecutor Mile Edgeworth... is it? I'd like to thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thank me?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Yeah. For working so hard to fulfill my goal.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! Is that any way to thank someone!? And what the heck is that supposed to mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You were so relentless with Lance that you forced Ernest to tamper with the evidence. Thanks to that, I finally had a legitimate reason to arrest him. So, how does it feel to bite the hand that feeds you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The hand that feeds me? I'm not sure I follow.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Heh! It's no use pretending with me! You're the one, right? You're the corrupt prosecutor that's working for Mr. Amano and the smuggling ring, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...No. I would never do such a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Tch! What the heck!? Our intel's never wrong! In your Prosecutor's Office, there's definitely someone working with the ring.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ah, so Agent Lang suspected my relation to Mr. Amano... That must be the real reason behind his antagonistic attitude!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">On top of that, your mentor was Manfred von Karma, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">There were non-stop rumors flying around about forged evidence with that guy. You're not twisting the truth behind those closed courtroom doors, too, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........The courtroom... is a place where the truth is revealed!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha ha ha ha ha! Well, don't worry; it's not only you. The whole lot of you can't be trusted. "A prosecutor who never lost in 40 years"? "Every defendant must be found guilty"? Fueled by those ideas, is it any wonder that courts produce nothing but falsities and lies!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It would seem... that his disdain extends beyond just me. Prosecutors, the courts... Why is this man so angry with us all?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Rest assured, the next time we meet, I won't be so forgiving. So, don't you forget it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please, wait.</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Shih-na... Why does Agent Lang hate all prosecutors so?</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">............ Lang is the head of the long-honored House of Lang in Zheng Fa. The heads of all police-related divisions in that country were of Lang blood...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Were"? What do you mean by that? Aren't they still?</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">They were revered, but that was long ago. They don't hold that sort of sway anymore. ...And it was all because of the courts.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How can that be...?</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">A prosecutor once withheld and tampered with the evidence one of the Lang detectives found. That evidence's purity was tarnished, and cost the Lang family its honor and trust.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But... not all prosecutors are like that.</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">.................. Even so, Lang will never respect the court again. ......Or any prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So Agent Lang is a man who hates all courts, and is unwilling to forgive prosecutors...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Man, what a piece of work that guy is. Come on, Jim. We'd better catch up.</line>
<line speaker="Faith">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">We've still got to deliver that thing to the old man, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe. I believe it's time we wrapped up and headed home ourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. Are you going home, too, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No. I've done nothing but be entangled in one mess after another since my return. If it's alright with you, can you drop me off at my office?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No problem, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Um, excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Um... I... That is... Thank you very much!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aww, it's OK. No need to thank me, pal! Just doing my job as a detective!</line>
<line speaker="Paups">I guess I was fooled pretty badly by Lance... Oh, cruel fate! What's a woman to do when she's been hurt by the one she loves? And to think I never realized my father was right there... I never said anything to him... I knew it! I'm...! I'm... a failure!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah, there she goes again, talking to herself!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Ms. Paups. I wonder if you know why your father participated in the kidnapping?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">No, I have no idea...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your father died while he was trying to stop Lance. Which means, that from the beginning, he had no interest in the staged, self-abduction.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wait, then why did he...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe it was because of your presence, Ms. Paups.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Me...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Lance realized that the two of you were related. Which is why he used you as a hostage, to coerce Mr. Devorae into cooperating.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Father...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As a felon, he could not tell you of his real relation to you. However, as the Amano family butler, at the very least, he was able to watch over you. It was all he could do, but that was the shape of his overflowing love for you.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? Go on, speak your mind.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">I! I-I! Um... That is...! Th-Thank you very much!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're welcome... although, there is no need to thank me...</line>
<line speaker="Paups">.................. Ah! No, Lauren! Stop! I mean, this man's so much older than you!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hee hee, looks like you've completely stolen her away, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Way to go, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Your technique is way beyong the level of a Great Thief!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">? What are you going on about now?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow... Your deducing skills may be sound, but you have no street-smarts.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's Mr. Edgeworth for you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah... I mean, he still hasn't figured out who I am at all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">If you haven't remembered in all this time, I guess I'm just going to have to say it. This isn't the first time we've met, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What do you mean, pal!? Mr. Edgeworth!? How do you know this girl...!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmph... Looks like you totally forgot me, too, Gummy.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">"Gummy"?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Here. Maybe this will jog your memories. I promised I'd return this to you one day, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That single piece of cloth took me back, far into my past... ...to that fateful day seven years ago, when I first met the then-child Kay... ...and Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, the pieces don't fit together quite right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't see a clear connection between these two pieces of information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Not exactly a shining example of the perfect line of logic.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang, about this piece of evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Lang Zi says: "Confidence is like a soul, and words without confidence are but empty shells." You shouldn't waste your breath on words you have no confidence in, Mr. Prosecutor. Although, it's just as bad to say something in full confidence and be wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arghn!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Are you going to let him lecture you about your self-confidence like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I don't need to be overflowing with self-confidence; I just need to think rationally. After all, I only need to be confident in the facts!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang, if you could take a look at this piece of evidence... ...you'd see that there is a very big flaw in your logic.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Flaw? Are you sure it's not your eyes that are flawed? Talk to me again when you can see straight!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Gnnrk! Maybe this wasn't the piece I was looking for after all!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That statement just now stands in contradiction to this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">That thing has nothing to do with what I was saying. Now, put it away! And your logic is so badly in need of repair that you might as well throw it out, too! This is the real deal here. Your courtroom mannerisms are worthless at a crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnrk...! You dare to insult the courts!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Paups, this evidence stands in clear contradiction to your statement just now.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">.........Huh? Where?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hmph. It's not polite to confuse poor, helpless girls, Mr. Prosecutor. Until you have something significant to add, stuff that jabot of yours in your mouth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh! It's a cravat, and It's a fashion statement, not a gag! <thought>I need to calmly listen, and then present my evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Take a good look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Paups">What about it...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, Mr. Edgeworth, sir... I don't think you pulled out the right piece of evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hahaha! Wonderful subordinate there, so willing to point out his boss's mistakes!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnnrk! Detective Gumshoe, you will refrain from excessive talking!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-I'll try, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even after looking at this, can you still claim what you just said to be true?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">A-Actually... I can.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha ha ha! She showed you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnrghk!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He's laughing pretty hard at you, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I know... But I refuse to allow him to ruffle my feathers. <thought>I'm going to remain calm and collected, and find my contradiction!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're lying, Lance! Even you must have realized that by now, Agent Lang.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey, now... Mr. Prosecutor. I'm not your pal, or even your ally! It's your line of logic, so explain it yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">S-Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Look, just hurry up and get to the point. It's not like I've got all the time in the world.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So you say, but you're not exactly at liberty to leave, either.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Lance... I think you'll find that this evidence speaks to the contrary.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Are you sure you want to phrase it that way? There are no take-backs when you make a guessing mistake, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha ha ha! Guessing mistake! Yup! That's our Mr. Prosecutor alright!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnngk... <thought>I certainly didn't mean for it to come out sounding like a guess...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That statement just now contradicts this piece for evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">How... How... How dare you call me a liar!? And in such a loud voice with evidence that doesn't make any sense!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You have no idea how to put two ideas together to make a logical argument, do you!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Aaah! I didn't think my reasoning was as bad as that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I admit defeat. I can't seem to find a way out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Looks like our only choice is to wait, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh! But we were so close!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A few hours later, Kay and I were freed by the police. Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I think your half-baked logic needs some more time in the oven, Mr. Prosecutor! You guys! What are you waiting for? An engraved invitation? Take this young lady away!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait! We still don't know the truth behind what was happened...</line>
<line speaker="Paups">It's alright... I need to pay the price for what I've done...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Look, we all know you're just chasing your delusions, so let's stop wasting time, alright? You want to suspect me, Mr. Edgeworth, but you haven't got a single shred of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Now, now... I say we let the courts resolve the rest.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A few days later, Lance was acquitted of all charges due to lack of evidence. Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's nothing unusual about this area.</line>
</xml>