<xml>
<title>The Adventure of the Great Departure</title>
<line speaker="???"><thought>I still can't believe it. I still can't believe this is happening. How can it be that just beyond the doors to this quiet little chamber... ...is the highest court in Japan, waiting to decide my fate?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">What?</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh! No, nothing...</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Save your glares... murderer!</line>
<line speaker="???">......... Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>My name is Ryunosuke Naruhodo. I'm a second-year student at the Imperial Yumei University. Three days ago, I somehow found myself in the middle of a horrifying incident. And now here I am, awaiting my trial.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">That's enough! He's not obliged to listen to such abuse, Officer.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">And who are YOU?!</line>
<line speaker="???">I'm this man's lawyer. I'll be defending him today.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="???">Yes. And until the judge has given his verdict on the case... ...no one has the right to treat him as a criminal. So you will hold your tongue!</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Tsk! Technicalities! Look at you, you haven't even graduated yet!</line>
<line speaker="???">And yet, I still seem to know better than you how a court officer should behave. Right, Ryunosuke?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Y-Yes, of course! Sorry!</line>
<line speaker="???">......... What are you apologising to me for?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, I... No, I suppose that wasn't my fault. ......... But really, Kazuma, I never meant to drag you into this. I'm sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ha ha ha hah! There you go again, apologising! Just like always.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Though I must say, you've been all over the newspapers these past few days. 'Yumei University Professor Murdered in Cold Blood by Student!' But obviously...you didn't actually do it, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of course not! You have to believe me! I didn't do it! I... I could never murder someone...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Then there's nothing to worry about. Straighten yourself up. Hold your head high.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I believe you. I know you're innocent, Ryunosuke.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma Asogi, my best friend. Also in his second year at Yumei University. But he's far more clever than I. A star student, in fact. He's even a qualified lawyer. Impressive, considering he's still an undergraduate.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's not that impressive. The very concept of lawyers is only a few years old. Here in Japan, anyway. My qualifications don't mean much. Yet.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You said exactly the same thing three days ago. But I'm proud to have a friend like you, Kazuma. Truly. <thought>Three days ago... Yes, that's when all this started...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Congratulations, Kazuma! It looks like you're going to get to study abroad at last!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I know! I've been forever dreaming of this day. Finally, those government elites have acknowledged my academic achievements and successes in court.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you'll be representing Japan as you immerse yourself in the most sophisticated legal system in the world! I'm really happy for you. And proud, as your friend. <thought>There's not a soul in the university who doesn't know Kazuma's name. He's a living legend! It's like there's some mysterious aura billowing around his temple.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I want to bring about change in our own legal system. That's why I have to cross the ocean to see the real thing with my own eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The heart of the British Empire... I wish I could see it, too.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Then come with me! We'd have a wild time tearing up the streets of Her Majesty's City of London together!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If only it were that simple...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Oh dear, look at the time. I'd better be going.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright, I'll see you later. I think I'll stay and enjoy this place a while longer.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Good idea. After all, it's not every day you get to visit a high-class Western restaurant like this! See you in English class tomorrow, then...partner!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It was straight after that. That's when it happened...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Asogi. May I have a word?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Professor! I didn't know you were coming. </line>
<line speaker="???">Well, this case has personal significance to me. But never mind that for now. Asogi... You should go immediately to the judge's chambers.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">To His Excellency's chambers? Why?</line>
<line speaker="???">He was looking for you before. You advocating for the defence in this trial was a sudden decision. It seems there may be some confusion about procedures today as a result. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Who is this man? I feel as though I've seen him at university before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I see. I'll go at once then. </line>
<line speaker="???">I shall accompany you.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Alright then, Ryunosuke. I'll see you in the courtroom. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. Thanks, Kazuma. .........</line>
<line speaker="???">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>Ugh, this is awkward...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">If I may...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, sorry?</line>
<line speaker="???">You must be the defendant. Ryunosuke Naruhodo, I believe?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes! Yes, that's right!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">My name is Yujin Mikotoba. I'm a professor of forensic medicine at Yumei University.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, Professor Mikotoba... <thought>I've heard that name from Kazuma before. As I recall, he's been pushing to get the government to agree to Kazuma studying abroad.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Asogi has told me about you. You and he are best friends, I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">As such, I feel you should know...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Know what?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well, as you've no doubt heard, Asogi has been granted permission to go and study in Great Britain. However... If he should fail to defend you in today's trial... ...I'm afraid that that permission will be revoked...and never granted again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Ah, as I suspected... You were unaware of this. I had a feeling Asogi may have chosen not to tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>He's agreed to defend me, knowing that if he fails, his dreams will be shattered?</thought> But I don't understand! Why would the government do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">The administration has to choose from a large number of applicants for overseas study. It's very difficult to persuade them to grant permission, even in the most favourable of circumstances.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't believe it... ......... But I... I didn't do it! I swear it! I'm not a murderer...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I'm sure that's true. Nevertheless... I can assure you that proving your innocence will be no easy task. You see, there are certain...'peculiarities' about today's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">You'll soon understand, once proceedings get underway.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! But... Then what should I do?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well... Naturally I'm not going to suggest doing anything that could lead to a conviction.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right, so...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">As soon as the trial starts... ...the judge will pose a certain question to the defence. When that happens, you must answer before anyone else. You must say, 'I do'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'I do'...? But, what will the question be? Surely...not...? 'Do you accept the accusations brought before you?'...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Of course not.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Defendant! Court is about to begin. Proceed to the courtroom at once!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Ah, it would seem our surreptitious discussions are to be cut short. So allow me to summarise... Kazuma Asogi must not be the defence lawyer in this trial. Of course, as the defendant, the final decision is yours.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">What are you waiting for? Do you want to be found guilty for failing to appear?! Get moving! There's no point in anyone advocating for the likes of you anyway!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is it... If this trial goes badly... ...Kazuma's dreams of studying abroad are over. And what's more... ...I'll be found guilty...of murder.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So this... is a courtroom... </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The Supreme Court of Judicature. No court in the land has more power. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't much like the look of those people sitting in the public gallery. <thought>Lots of military and other uniforms in there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The powers that be have demanded that this be a secret trial. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A secret trial?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">A trial that's closed to ordinary members of the public. Only military and government officials may attend. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? But why?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It'll become clear in time. But for now... ...you need to concentrate, Ryunosuke. It's about to begin.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will now hear the trial of Ryunosuke Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">The prosecution is ready, Your Excellency.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">As is the defence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Before we begin, there is one point of order I would like to confirm. Yesterday evening, the defence made a last-minute request for a change of advocate.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">That's correct, Your Excellency. I made the request myself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Normal procedure is for the defendant's advocacy to be decided two days prior to trial. As this is an unusual circumstance, I am obliged to ask for final confirmation now. Who advocates for the defendant in this trial?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This is it! This must be the question! Who's going to defend me? That's the question the professor meant. But then, if I say, 'I do'... ......... I need to answer quickly! What should I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Kazuma is the lawyer here. I can't defend myself. If I said 'I do', it would be tantamount to lying. And I've been accused of murder, for goodness' sake! This is no time for lies.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Try to stop fidgeting, Ryunosuke. It's distracting.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>But if I don't say I'll defend myself now... ...things could end very badly for my friend.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Your Excellency, no confirmation is needed. As I'm standing here beside the defendant, I hope it's clear who will advocate for his defence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I would like to inform the court that, that... ...I, Ryunosuke Naruhodo, will be defending myself! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">You'll be... WHAAAT?! </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What are you playing at, Ryunosuke!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Professor Mikotoba told me everything. Just now, before the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">He did what?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He said that your dreams of studying abroad would be dashed if you were to lose.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... How sad. It means you don't have faith in me. You think I won't be able to get you off.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No! It's not that, really! It's just that... Well, on the off-chance that things don't go well for me, I couldn't bear to be the reason that you...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... Yes. I knew that's how you'd feel. Which is exactly why I decided not to tell you. Tsk! Professor Mikotoba shouldn't have stuck his nose in.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court hereby recognises the defendant's desire to advocate for himself in today's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Well, well... Does the accused admit defeat already? Renouncing his own counsel! Really!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Make no mistake, Counsel... This merely shows that the defendant's innocence is so apparent, he's confident he can speak for himself. Isn't that so, Naruhodo-san?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm? ...Oh! Yes, exactly! <thought>Exactly what I WASN'T thinking! I'm not confident at all. In fact, my mind's a complete blank...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I realize you're in charge now, but still... Try not to look so bewildered.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Hmph. Well, for a mere university student to be brought before the Supreme Court... ...you must have perpetrated a most heinous crime indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As you are no doubt aware, this is the Supreme Court of Judicature of Japan. Accordingly, the very highest standards of conduct are expected of all present. Do I make myself clear, Defendant Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes! ...Your Excellency!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is therefore my duty to assess your competence for the task you have undertaken. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My competence? <thought>What does that mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">He's questioning your ability to do the job.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well, he can't be questioning it more than I am!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, let's start with the very simplest of questions.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, um... Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Kindly state before the court the name of the victim in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well that's easy enough. I've heard his name more times than I'd care to remember. But... Wait. Ugh, I'm so nervous, I can't even remember that! What was it again?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ryunosuke... Let me guess. Your mind's gone blank?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm... <thought>You know me so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">All the relevant information for this case can be found in the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but I can't even find that...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's simple. You can access the Court Record with a press of [R / E]. If you ever find you've forgotten something, just consult that. It's all in there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I just have to press [R / E] for the Court Record? Alright, there's no time to lose!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">This is the list of evidence you've collected. Now try switching to 'People' instead with [R / RB / E]. You'll find details about the victim in here. When you're done, just press [B / Z] to go back. So remember, everything to do with the current case can be found in the Court Record. Now, you'd better not keep His Excellency waiting any longer. Go on. Find the victim in the 'People' section of the Court Record, then press [X / Y / R] to 'Present'. Try it now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Oh? Then why is that pompous-looking boy with the billowing headband still there standing next to you?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oops!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">'Oops!' doesn't do that justice. Not content with having killed Dr Wilson, now you're claiming my murder as well?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I haven't killed anyone!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Then concentrate! And actually read the Court Record before you answer!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I must say, you are not instilling the court with much confidence here.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Quickly, give him the correct answer before he turns his gavel on you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Then who's the uptight, bespectacled topknot standing opposite?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Who's a 'bespectacled topknot'?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... Sorry, for some reason that just came out, even though I know it's wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Perhaps you're unaware that I am a master of the ancient Noh-style sword art! A pathetic little child like you would be sliced to pieces before you even came close to taking my life!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I wouldn't provoke that proud Edo spirit. He might draw his blade on you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I, I thought courtroom sparring was supposed to be done with words...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I must say, you are not instilling the court with much confidence here.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Quickly, give him the correct answer before he turns his gavel on you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Stop. You're just saying a random name that you come across in the Court Record, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um... How did you guess?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's blatantly obvious... ...from your wide-eyed look of bewilderment.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I must say, you are not instilling the court with much confidence here.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Quickly, give him the correct answer before he turns his gavel on you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The victim's name was Dr John H. Wilson.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Tsh huh huh... Well, at least you can remember the name of an esteemed member of your own university.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Dr Wilson was a visiting professor from England, invited to Yumei University three years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. Which is the reason why this case has such profound implications. The British Empire... ...is at present, our country's most valuable foreign ally. And as most of you will be aware, we have just signed a new treaty together, after lengthy negotiations.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">There can't be anyone who hasn't heard of the Anglo-Japanese Treaty of Friendship and Navigation.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">And yet despite these delicate circumstances, the blood of an Englishman has been spilt on our soil! You two are both undergraduates at the Imperial Yumei University, are you not? Murdering a professor from the very institution that provides your education... Have you no honour?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... <thought>But I didn't do it...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Judge">This case is coming under great scrutiny from our allies on the other side of the world. The court therefore wishes for a speedy resolution to this matter.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Hmph. In other words, our feeble government is scared of upsetting England's policy makers. And you're a convenient and expendable scapegoat to blame for this crime.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So that's why this trial has these unusual peculiarities, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Exactly. Our government needs to convict someone as quickly as possible. All because the victim was an Englishman.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, Dr Wilson was an Englishman... But nationalities and treaties won't make any difference for me here. The fact is, I was there at the scene of the crime...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Oh dear, look at the time. I'd better be going.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright, I'll see you later. I think I'll stay and enjoy this place a little longer. </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Good idea. After all, it's not every day you get to visit a high-class Western restaurant like this! See you in English class tomorrow, then...partner!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The British Empire... Wow, it's incredible to think- ......... Wait. I've seen that man at university. I'm sure he's a visiting professor from Great Britain. I don't know his name, but still... I should go and say hello.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So I went over to the professor's table... ...and introduced myself to Dr Wilson.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then...let me pose my next question to you, Defendant Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, Your Excellency!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How did this professor of medicine, Dr John H. Wilson, lose his life? State before the court the cause of death.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The cause of death... Well, obviously, that was...um...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ryunosuke... Remember that in court, every assertion must be backed up by evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">By evidence? But, how?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Find the piece of evidence that shows the professor's cause of death, and select 'Present'. Do it now!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And on what basis do you present this evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, um... Because it was in the Court Record, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Slow down. Why did you pick that? Isn't there something more relevant-looking?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, now that you say that, I suppose...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Pick the wrong piece of evidence again, and it won't be a mystery as to YOUR cause of death!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yikes! He sounds - and looks - deadly serious!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, well... According to this document, the victim suffered a 'he-morr-hagic death due to gunshot trauma'.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Learn to read, you imbecile! That's the post-mortem report, I take it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry, yes! That's right. The, um, post-mortem report.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In the West, a doctor dissects corpses to identify the cause of death in an 'autopsy'. But here in Japan, a police officer merely inspects the body, and draws conclusions that way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, I see! <thought>As long as I'm not going to be tested on any of this later...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">This is a so-called photographic print of the scene of the crime. You can clearly discern scorch marks around the bullet hole produced by the powder explosion. In other words, we should assume that the victim was shot at close range.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, Counsel. The court will accept this modern scientific evidence into the record.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So that's a photographic print. Well, that's something I've never seen before... It's clearly superior to a drawing. The detail is incredible...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. I am satisfied with your answers. Let us start the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Certainly, Your Excellency. So, without further ado, in order to better apprise the court with the facts of the case... ...the prosecution hereby calls its first witness, who was there at the scene of the crime when it happened!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... This is it, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Hmph.. I think I may have worked out what the professor had in mind. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The professor? You mean, Dr Mikotoba?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes. Clearly, you're the defence lawyer today, not me. But that doesn't mean... Well, I can still act as your assistant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! <thought>Of course!</thought> When he was speaking with me before, he simply said: 'Kazuma Asogi must not be the defence lawyer in this trial.'</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Hm, he really has been sticking his oar in, hasn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Maybe, but...any help you can give me would be greatly appreciated, Kazuma!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well, my first piece of advice is: Rein in that crazy look of bewilderment and control the cold sweats!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Only if you rein in that crazy headband and control the cold stares first...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Witness. State your name and occupation for the court, please.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Of course. My name is Satoru Hosonaga. I am the head waiter at a Western-style restaurant called 'La Carneval'. Ahem! ...Ahem!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...are you alright? You seem to be coughing up some, er...</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">It's a regular occurrence. It really doesn't bother me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well, it really, really should...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">As everyone knows, the capital's south-eastern quarter was developed for foreign visitors some years ago. It's become a very fashionable district now, full of hotels to accommodate overseas guests. This grim crime occurred in one of the district's so-called 'restaurants' - an occidental eatery - three days ago.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Understood. Hosonaga-san, you will kindly tell the court everything you can about the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">At once, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">And no petty interjections from the aspiring lawyer boy, please.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, um... <thought>Perspiring, maybe, but aspiring...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">It was just after 2 p.m. on the day in question. We have few diners at that time of day. The lunchtime rush was over, and there were only three tables still occupied.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That fits in with my memory of it, too. There was hardly anyone else in the place.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Ahem! ...Ahem! It was when I was in the kitchen, putting away crockery and cutlery... A gunshot rang out, so I hurried out to the dining area to see what had happened. I found the victim - an English gentleman - slumped in his chair. And standing immediately beside him, gun in hand, was the accused university student.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">I believe I asked you to refrain from petty interjections. The court wishes to listen to the witness's report of what he saw, you amateur!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The next time you interrupt at an inappropriate time, you will be penalised, Defendant Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Don't worry, Ryunosuke. You'll have your chance to fight back. For now, we must just quietly listen to the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">If I may confirm one point, waiter... Standing beside the victim with a gun in his hand was the same man we see here in court today?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Yes. Without question. </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">I see. And apart from the accused, was there anyone else standing beside the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">No. There was no one else around that table but the deceased Englishman and the university student.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh? <thought>Wait, what did he just say? 'There was no one else around that table'?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What's the matter, Ryunosuke?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's... That's just not right! When I went over to Dr Wilson to say hello... ...there was a woman sitting opposite him at his table!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And that's not something the waiter could have missed! <thought>I've been warned about interjecting, but still... What should I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I desperately want to say something, but I was told not to interject.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ryunosuke... If your parents tell you to study, you're the kind of man who would diligently get to work, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I suppose I am. I'd never have got into Yumei University otherwise.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">But you can't just always follow the rules in life, you know. If you don't say what you want to say right now, you'll seriously regret it when you're found guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Alright, you've scared me. I won't forget that piece of advice in a hurry! <thought>And there IS something I want to say. I'm just going to shut my eyes and say it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just a moment, please! Dr Wilson wasn't alone that day! I'm sure of it. There was a lady sitting with him at the same table!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Dear me, dear me. What are we going to do with you? With your blatant disregard for court proceedings, I'm beginning to wonder if you're not a fraud. Could it be that the accused - this mere student - is not a real lawyer after all?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...I'm sure of what I saw!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Hosonaga-san, is there any chance you're mistaken? Perhaps your memory of events is hazy?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">......... No. The deceased gentleman came to dine alone.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I don't believe it...</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Ahem! ...Ahem! I actually have a rough plan of the restaurant as it was that day. Please, have a look if you'd like to.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let me see... Ah, a sketch of the establishment's layout drawn by yourself, I presume?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">That's right. I'm afraid I used the back of my business card. It was a...turbulent situation. However, as you can see, the gentleman in question was seated alone.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, you're clearly a very conscientious waiter.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Thank you, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will take this plan and add it to the Court Record as evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Oh, um... Well...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is there a problem? Hand the plan to the court officer at once!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Um...of course. Here you are.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What was that about? He's been completely calm and collected until now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Something certainly seems to have shaken him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">So...the court has now heard a precis of the case.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, at the moment the gunshot was heard in the restaurant... ...the only person in close proximity to the victim was the defendant on trial today. It would seem we are looking at a black-and-white case here.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defendant Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, Your Excellency?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you admit your guilt at this stage, the court is willing to look mercifully upon you.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">In other words, you may have some small reprieve in terms of your inevitable punishment. I called this waiter as an unsworn witness in order to explain the details of the case to the court. But I must warn the defence, if you are determined to pursue matters further in this trial... ...the prosecution has decisive evidence from sworn witnesses who were present at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... What do you think I should do, Kazuma?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I'm going to be found guilty one way or another, it seems. Wouldn't it be sensible to plead guilty at this stage and hope for a more lenient sentence?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Everyone keeps telling me that this trial is unusual - about these...'peculiarities'. You've said it, Professor Mikotoba's said it...and so has the judge and the prosecution. I'm... I'm scared of what lies ahead if I push this.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... As I said from the outset, I believe you're innocent. I trust you. And yet, despite knowing that... ...you're willing now to throw that trust back in my face? Is that it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">If the accused is in fact innocent... ...then a defence lawyer is duty-bound to prove that innocence by whatever means necessary. Are you just going to abandon that duty? Are you going to give up on yourself? The battle hasn't even begun yet, Ryunosuke.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The defence pleads not guilty, Your Excellency! We invite the prosecution to stop making empty threats and bring out its witnesses. Then we'll see just how decisive this evidence really is!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. Prosecutor Auchi, please continue with proceedings.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Tsk, well, you were warned. The young can be so reckless. You know, many call me a saint. But I can be a devil when I want to be.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">In a few short moments from now... ...that dumbstruck young mouth of yours will be silenced, forever! The prosecution calls its next witnesses!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Officer! Bring forth the witnesses at once!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Witnesses, kindly state your names and occupations for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Yessir! The great Nippon Imperial Army's Sergeant Iyesa Nosa reporting for duty, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Myself, I find employ as a purveyor of fine articles of antiquity from the efflorescence of our nation, Nippon... ...and conduct my trade from Rasu-tei, a humble premises in the second district. Kyurio Korekuta, at your service.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">An antique dealer and a soldier... What an unusual pairing!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Both of these gentlemen were present at the restaurant on the day in question.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">They must be the diners at the other table that the waiter mentioned.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Myself, I habitually take tea of the most exquisite aroma at the establishment in question. Always post noon. And, not infrequently, converse with interested parties regarding the curios with which I make my business.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I can't understand a word that old man is saying...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">He's an antique dealer. And it sounds like he's a regular at La Carneval. He seeks out potential customers who may have an interest in antiques and tries to sell his wares to them. He obviously targets La Carneval because it's a high-class restaurant with rich clientele. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right, I see. Although, to be honest... ...that sergeant looks more like he'd be a seller rather than a buyer.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Now, you both witnessed the precise moment of this most atrocious incident. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Affirmative! The enemy unit was seen attacking the foreigner in what can only be described as an act of war! Sir! It was that black-uniformed rogue infantryman over there who unloaded his firearm, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This man's as impossible to understand as the other... But I'm almost sure I heard a strange noise during that last thing he said...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So, this is the decisive evidence the prosecution was threatening. The soldier is claiming that he actually saw the precise moment you shot the victim dead. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well? Are you starting to feel uncomfortable?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If I'm honest...I was feeling uncomfortable from the start.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, the court will hear your formal testimony, please. You will state everything you saw at the precise moment that the incident occurred.</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Sir, yessir! Standing by ready to report, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Hm... Unsavoury memories of a most acerbic afternoon...</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">I was ingesting a regulation beef steak at the restaurant while having a tactical discussion with the old man.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Myself, I was extolling the virtues of a particularly fine golden curio to the military gentleman.</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">At that precise moment, a firearm was discharged! I observed the enemy's actions with my own eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">I was on my hands and knees, investigating the where-abouts of my mysteriously absconded precious curio.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well! So you, Sergeant Nosa, actually witnessed the vital moment! You saw the split second when the defendant fired the weapon at the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Yessir! Affirmative, sir! That wicked university cadet, sir! The cruel and unforgivable enemy!</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">What times we live in, when an English gentleman may be assailed in the broad light of day...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but this is ridiculous! I didn't shoot anyone!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Is that really true, Ryunosuke?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes! All I did was pick up the gun that I saw lying on the floor! After I'd said hello to Dr Wilson, I went back to my table and sat drinking more coffee. Then, when I'd finished, I got up from my seat to leave the restaurant... ...when I noticed an English-made gun next to the chair where the professor was sitting. I thought perhaps the professor had dropped it. So I bent down, and just as I was picking it up...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well, if that's the truth, there was obviously a criminal on the scene somewhere. And somewhere in these two witnesses' testimonies, there's a clue as to who that criminal was.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There is?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ryunosuke! You must exercise your right to cross-examine the witnesses!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Cross-examine?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Do it now!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">As we have heard, Your Excellency... ...there is no room for doubt in the testimony of these witnesses. The defendant is clearly guilty. It is time to bring this despicable student to justice!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Certainly, the testimony the court has just heard eliminates any vestige of doubt. Therefore, it is my grave duty to declare the verdict of this tri-</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What in the name of the Emperor is the meaning of this outburst?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, am, erm... I mean, the defence... ...demands its right to a cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Dear me, dear me. Let me guess? 'The hachimaki headband boy next door told me to do it.' How pathetic.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh? <thought>How did he know?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">The prosecution objects! This is a clear waste of time. The defendant obviously has no experience. How can he possibly carry out a cross-examination?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The defence is asserting its RIGHT to a cross-examination! Whether or not you think he's capable of it is irrelevant.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">*Gulp!*</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Kazuma is so commanding!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Let the defence conduct a cross-examination of the witnesses. </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Alright, this is where the battle really begins, Ryunosuke!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...I don't even know what I have to do in a cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Isn't it obvious? You have to expose the lies in the witnesses' statements!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You didn't fire the gun, which means what that soldier said has to be a lie.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well yes, but...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's just a case of proving it. And the key to doing that is evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right... Evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">All you need to do is present some decisive and indisputable evidence that proves the witness is lying. Now let's go, Ryunosuke! Don't let them beat you!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright then! <thought>It's all or nothing...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Nosa">I was ingesting a regulation beef steak at the restaurant while having a tactical discussion with the old man.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Why, why aren't you saying anything? Is this some new interrogation technique?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I...hadn't actually thought of what I wanted to ask...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Just ask about anything that catches your attention. Anything that bothers you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright then, um... This 'beef steak' you mentioned. What kind of food is that?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Teeen-shun!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Beef steak is a delicious cut of veal, vigorously cooked on a cast-iron grill and served piping hot. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">If food could receive medals of honor, beef steak would be almost as highly decorated as a cutlet!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right! I see. Um, thank you, sir. So, next question... ......... This 'cutlet' you mentioned. What kind of food is that?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Teeen-shun!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Cutlet is a delicious cut of veal tossed in breadcrumbs and deep fried in cooking oil! Accept your guilty verdict, atone for your crimes, and when you're released from prison, TRY IT!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yessir, I will, sir! On the double, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Sorry to interrupt, but... How about trying to stick to questions that are relevant to the case?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oops, sorry! I'll do my best. So, next question... Is it just me, or do you keep hearing a sort of 'wah' crying noise...?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Negative!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, at least we've learnt that he's a big beef lover. </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...Affirmative.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It's not easy knowing what questions to ask...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Myself, I was extolling the virtues of a particularly fine golden curio to the military gentleman.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">A koban, boy.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A 'koban'? You mean an old Edo coin?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">The day prior to the incident, a treasure of exceptional value from the Hoei period entered my possession. I took myself to the restaurant the following day, with said item secreted in my bosom pocket... ...in the hope of an affluent cognoscente appraised of its indisputable value being present. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you were hoping to sell your koban coin? To Sergeant Nosa, whom you met at the restaurant?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Yes, yes. It's quite clear where you're going with this, boy. You were about to assert that a penniless soldier would have no hope of purchasing a precious koban. Isn't that so?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um... Well...</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">You little upstart cadet! You want to add disrespecting a superior officer to your list of crimes, do you?! Blatant subordination! </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, no, I didn't say anything! <thought>Although 'penniless' might be just the word I was looking for...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">In any case, the hour was already advanced beyond that of the midday luncheon. There remained precious few present with whom I could engage in discourse about matters of business. The gentleman aside me, who was grappling with his braised veal at the time, was my sole prospect.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">At that precise moment, a firearm was discharged! I observed the enemy's actions with my own eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Aaaaaaffirmative! I saw you! Laughing - cackling - like a madman as you trained the barrel of your gun on the English civilian! </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But that's impossible! I, I only-</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Allow me to confirm just one point, please.</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">What's that, private?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Thinking carefully about the statement you just made, it seems to me... ...that it must have been just after you heard the gunshot that you looked over to the victim's table.</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">And so what if it was?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well, if that really is the case... ...it would mean that you didn't in fact see the precise moment when the killer actually fired the gun.</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">......... Argh! And double 'argh'! My sixth sense...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">My sixth sense of danger! I picked up the waves of murderous energy radiating from your foul mind! Which means...a split second before you pulled the trigger, I was looking right at you, cadet!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Surely that's not really possible...is it?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Do you think I'd have got where I am today in the army if I couldn't sense danger in the air, son?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well... It would seem this soldier is absolutely convinced that he saw you do the deed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This is not good...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nosa">The black-uniformed varsity cadet fired on the English civilian! And from the back, the cowardly little weasel!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Argh! I've had just about enough of your sauce, cadet! Who else do you see around here in black uniform, hm?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well, there's someone standing right next to me who fits the description as well, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nosa">It was you, you little weasel! You unloaded the firearm on that man! From behind his back! And you call yourself a citizen of the great Empire of Nippon?! You disgust me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What is it, Ryunosuke?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm, I'm not quite sure... It's something that the sergeant just said, but I can't put my finger on it. Something's playing on my mind...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In that case, check back over the details of the evidence you've gathered in the Court Record. And if you find an inconsistency there with what the witness just said, then...don't hold back! Present the evidence to the court! Thrust it in the witness's face and make him choke on it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">.........</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">What, what are you playing at, cadet? What is the meaning of this subordination?! Thrusting this wad of papers in my moustache!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In... Inconsistency! Sir! I mean...yes! There's a clear inconsistency here!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Tsk, what nonsense! What can this document possibly tell us that we don't already know?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...obviously... That, um... <thought>I know what I want to say, but the words just won't come out of my mouth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Hmph! I think this proves beyond any doubt, Your Excellency... ...that there is no place for an amateur student here in this grand courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Argh! <thought>This is so frustrating!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Oh, please. Surely this doesn't require an explanation. It couldn't be more plain. To spell it out would be an insult to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma, what...?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's apparent from a single glance at the post-mortem report presented by the defence... ...that there's a clear discrepancy here with the sergeant's statement!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Sergeant Iyesa Nosa...</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Yessir, what, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The statement you just made was this: 'The black-uniformed varsity cadet fired on the English civilian! And from the back, the cowardly little weasel!' </line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Yessir! Affirmative, sir! I witnessed the crime with my own military-grade eyes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">And why not, cadet?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Because... Because... Because...! </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">As is clearly stated in the post-mortem report... 'Fatal haemorrhage from pectoral ballistic trauma. No exit wound. Bullet did not pass through the body.' The photographic print of the victim clearly shows the same thing.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">.........</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">What, what are you playing at, cadet? What is the meaning of this subordination?! Thrusting some photographic print in my moustache!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In... Inconsistency! Sir! I mean...yes! There's a clear inconsistency here!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Tsk, what nonsense! What can this print possibly tell us that we don't already know?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...obviously... That, um... <thought>I know what I want to say, but the words just won't come out of my mouth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Hmph! I think this proves beyond any doubt, Your Excellency... ...that there is no place for an amateur student here in this grand courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Argh! <thought>This is so frustrating!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Oh, please. Surely this doesn't require an explanation. It couldn't be more plain. To spell it out would be an insult to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma, what...?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's apparent from a single glance at the photographic print presented by the defence... ...that there's a clear discrepancy here with the sergeant's statement!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Sergeant Iyesa Nosa...</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Yessir, what, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The statement you just made was this: 'The black-uniformed varsity cadet fired on the English civilian! And from the back, the cowardly little weasel!' </line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Yessir! Affirmative, sir! I witnessed the crime with my own military-grade eyes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">And why not, cadet?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Because... Because... Because...! </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Take a close look at the print.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">I was on my hands and knees, investigating the where-abouts of my mysteriously absconded precious curio.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">That's right. Spurning the arthritis, I was, in order to retrieve the lost piece.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What 'lost piece' are you referring to?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">The koban, of course! The exquisite Hoei-era koban coin! I had just been showing the rare treasure to the military man as he masticated his meal. After averting my eyes for the briefest of moments...it was there no more! It simply vanished!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">The koban... vanished?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Hence I began to acquaint myself with the intricacies of the floor, in order to locate it. And then it happened.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You heard the gunshot, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">None other than! Though it was no concern of mine. I was frantically scouring the floor for the aforementioned lost treasure!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So, in fact... ...you didn't actually witness the precise moment when the incident occurred?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Indeed. Myself, I did not.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... I have no idea what I'm supposed to do here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Listen, Ryunosuke... We know there are lies lurking in these statements. It's time to expose them.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I understand that. The question is...how?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Like I said before, the key to this is using evidence that you've collected. You can examine and Present evidence while a witness is giving testimony by pressing [R / RB / E]. Go through each witness statement and the details about each piece of evidence, and compare all the facts. Somewhere in there, you'll find something that doesn't add up. In other words, an inconsistency.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">An inconsistency...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">When you find a statement and a piece of evidence that seem to contradict each other... ...Present your evidence with [X / Y / R], and rip the witness apart!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Just be careful, because if you assert a contradiction that has no basis, you'll be given a penalty. If you're dealt too many penalties, the defence's case will fall apart, and you'll receive a guilty verdict. So that's it. Peruse the evidence in the Court Record and find an inconsistency with a witness's statement. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright, I'll give it a try!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You can hear the witnesses' statements over and over again, as many times as you like. So keep your head, and be measured in your attack. Good luck...partner!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The victim, Dr Wilson, died from a bullet wound to the chest.</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Sergeant. According to your witness statement... ...the culprit shot the victim from behind. And that is the obvious discrepancy here. Well? How do you explain it?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Ooh...erm... Agh...um... Well, er... Hnn... Hnn...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What...the...? What was that? Something just popped up from behind his back but he pushed it down again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Certainly, there is a clear discrepancy with the facts here. Would you not agree, Sergeant Nosa?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">......... Yes, sir... At this juncture, that...would appear to be indisputable. Until the moment I heard the firearm discharge, my eyes were... ...firmly fixed on the delicious La Carneval steak! Sir!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The last testimony the court heard has proven one thing beyond all reasonable doubt. The witness, Sergeant Iyesa Nosa... ...did NOT see the defendant firing a gun at all!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Ugh... That's, that's absurd...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I think the conclusion we must draw is simple... There is no place for an amateur prosecutor here in this grand courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Kgnrk... KYAAAAAAAAAAAARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>There's been a complete turnabout in the mood of this trial...just from that one discrepancy. So this is what being an ace attorney is all about!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nosa">But... But I definitely saw him! That university cadet, there! He was pointing the firearm directly at the victim's back!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... And you, old man. You didn't see the moment the victim was shot, either?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">......... Myself, I have already been quite clear. The gunshot interested me not. I was far too busy on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, yes. You were looking for your koban coin, weren't you? </line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Indeed! The prized Hoei-era koban! </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Too busy on the floor'? Sorry, what were you doing?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Hunting for treasure.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Treasure?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Indeed! The Hoei-era koban! My prized coin! On each occasion when I visit that restaurant... ...it is my habitude to place in my bosom pocket a particular trinket of interest from my shop, Rasu-tei. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In the hope of meeting a rich diner who might like to buy it from you?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">On the day under scrutiny, it was to the military man that I proffered my Hoei treasure. Believe that he would purchase such a rare find, I did not. But I was presented with little alternative. And then... After averting my eyes for the briefest of moments...it was there no more! It simply vanished!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">The koban...vanished?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Hunting around under the table, I was, in case mayhap it had fallen there. ...And then it happened.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You heard the gunshot, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Indeed I did! But I heeded it not, for I was concerned only with finding my absconded Hoei treasure! NOTHING could distract me!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Out of interest... ...did you find the coin in the end?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">......... No.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Hm. I see.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">That lamentable day...the precious Hoei koban was lost to me. No doubt some unscrupulous scoundrel pocketed the prize coin for himself! </line>
<line speaker="Nosa">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As I am sure everyone present is aware... ...this case demands a swift and decisive resolution. Our government has promised to send a full report to Great Britain by telegraph this very afternoon.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Nevertheless! The witness testimony the court has just heard was inconclusive. No matter how subservient our government feels it must be to the British... ...it would be unforgivable to deliver a verdict on this trial right now!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... What is your position, Prosecutor Auchi?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Tsh huh huh! Worry not, Your Excellency. The defendant may have fled a tiger at the front gate, but he will find a wolf at the back.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">My witnesses have further testimony to make. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Explain.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Upon hearing their next statements, it will become abundantly clear... ...that there is only one person who could possibly have committed this despicable crime. The equally despicable defendant, Ryunosuke Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">He really seems to have a despicable opinion of you, doesn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, the court invites the witnesses to testify again. You will thoroughly explain the reasoning behind the prosecution's allegation. Is that clear?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">As clear as kiriko glass, Your Excellency. </line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Yessir, at once, sir! Awaiting signal to testify, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, excuse me, but there's something - or someone - peeking out over your shoulder, I think...</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Affirmative! The newest member of the Nosa family to rise up through the ranks, sir. Name: Aido.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Hm, it would seem those straps are a sign of the sergeant being too strapped to afford a nanny. </line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Aido... Teeen-shun! Your father is about to quell the enemy! Watch and learn, my boy!</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Even if what I saw wasn't the precise moment the firearm was discharged, it's almost the same thing!</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Yes, pointing his gun at the foreign man, he was, that young lad in black. That much I myself did see.</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Furthermore! A visual search of the premises at the time confirmed that we were the only personnel present. </line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Indeed. Alone, he was, the Englishman. Dining all by himself.</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Therefore! No one other than the black-uniformed cadet could have dispatched the Englishman. Over and out!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm, these testimonies are certainly...compelling.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Please! Enough of these outbursts already!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But there was a woman! There was a young woman at his table! You must have seen her! Everyone there must have seen her!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">If you call yourself a lawyer, then you will respect the rules of the court and speak accordingly! We are not here to listen to your fantasies!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">It is evident beyond all reasonable doubt that the victim was alone at the time of the incident. The prosecution has photographic evidence of this fact. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is this a photographic print of the scene of the crime, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Indeed. Of the table at which the victim was dining, taken by an investigator immediately after the incident. As can plainly be seen, there is only one place set.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Certainly, based on the appearance of this print... ...it would be reasonable to conclude that the victim was not in the company of anyone else. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Arg... <thought>This doesn't make any sense...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will add this new photographic evidence to the record. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't understand... <thought>What's going on here? It's just not possible that nobody else saw that woman.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The waiter before said the same thing. He maintains that Dr Wilson came to the restaurant alone as well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But that's not true! I...I saw her...! I swear that I saw a woman with him...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would seem that we'll be able to telegraph the report to Great Britain on time after all. The witness testimonies we have just heard leave no further room for doubt.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">These are very sensitive political times, as we all know. The ink is still fresh on the treaty with Great Britain. To think that I, Taketsuchi Auchi, will have contributed to the amity of these two great empires is an honour.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>How can this be happening? The judge is ready to rule!</thought> </line>
<line speaker="???">Stand tall, Ryunosuke. It's not over yet.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">If what you say is true, then there's something going on here behind the scenes. And now is your chance to expose it. To draw out the truth. ...In your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I don't know, Kazuma...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence is entitled to cross-examine the witnesses. But make it quick. Understood?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Tsk. Rules can be so unbending at times.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Even if what I saw wasn't the precise moment the firearm was discharged, it's almost the same thing!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">We have a difference of opinion on that. The opinion of a uniformed officer versus that of a fledgling cadet.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, I don't think so...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Consider this, Defendant... Just a moment ago, I blinked.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Did you see it? Did you see me blink?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How could I!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">And yet! It is an undeniable fact that I did blink! So there you have it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Er... Have what...?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Teeen-shun! The sound of the firearm rang in my ears, and the very next moment... ...I saw YOU waving the gun at the Englishman!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">I think that says it all...don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Grrr...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">And let us not forget that the antiques dealer witnessed the accused in this most incriminating position as well. Isn't that so, Korekuta-san?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">.........</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Yes, pointing his gun at the foreign man, he was, that young lad in black. That much I myself did see.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Well obviously, as the culprit, that's the only way you could explain it away.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I had just finished drinking my coffee, and I was about to leave the restaurant when... I noticed a gun on the floor at Dr Wilson's feet, so I picked it up. And at exactly that moment...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A gunshot rang in my ears.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Hmph. Full of events beyond our control, life is.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">In your case, you found a pistol on the floor and picked it up, which precipitated this testing predicament. Whereas conversely... ...I failed to pick up the koban from the floor, and find myself in an equally testing predicament as a result. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Anyway, the fact remains... Myself, I did see you. With pistol in hand, standing over the foreigner.</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Furthermore! A visual search of the premises at the time confirmed that we were the only personnel present.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">As you have been at pains to point out time and again. I feel I'm growing a callus in my ear! And yet, no one else appears to have caught even a glimpse of this woman!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Argh... <thought>If only there'd been more people dining there at the time! Then someone else would have noticed her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Unfortunately, it was already past 2 p.m. when it happened. The quiet time between lunch and dinner in any restaurant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know... Of course the place was almost empty. It's what you'd expect...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Certainly, 2 p.m. is neither here nor there in terms of a time to eat. I wonder if there was a reason why the victim was eating at that time of day. And why he was alone. </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Yes, Your Excellency, there was indeed a reason. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There was?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">This was found in the victim's jacket pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is that, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">It is a medical report card, Your Excellency. It would seem that the victim had an appointment at a clinic prior to visiting the restaurant.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm... Hotta Clinic? Yes, there would indeed appear to be an entry for the date in question. '19th November, Noon to past 1 p.m...'</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Hm, the very day of the incident. </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">So the victim went for a late lunch following his appointment. The explanation couldn't be more simple. The prosecution felt no need to submit this evidence before, as it really has no bearing on the case.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I wonder... What do you think, Ryunosuke?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm? Well, it is hard to see how it could be related, really.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Remember, you can request for it to be entered into the Court Record as evidence if you think it could be useful. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Should I ask for Dr Wilson's medical report card to be submitted as evidence or not?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'm not sure I can really push for it to be submitted as evidence if I don't even know why it might be relevant. That wouldn't be good court etiquette, surely.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Don't tell me you're worrying about court etiquette at a time like this.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But my father always brought me up to be respectful and polite.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Right now we can't afford to overlook anything, no matter how insignificant it may seem to be. So let's ask for this medical report card to be added to the record. It won't be a problem...assuming you're polite.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright, I'll do it! As politely as possible!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If I may, I'd like to ask for that medical report card to be submitted as evidence, Your Excellency.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">On what grounds?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">The court has already heard conclusive witness testimony. Additional evidence would be extraneous. Not to mention that the victim's movements prior to his arrival at the restaurant are of no concern. </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Whether or not they are of concern is up to us to decide! We have a right to explore all possible avenues.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">I, I beg your pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You have no authority to refuse a perfectly valid request for the submission of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court will grant the defence's request.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Tsk! Youngsters these days are forever asserting their 'rights'! It's a most disturbing trend...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Officer, kindly add the victim's medical report card to the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What we need right now is new clues. We have to explore things from every possible angle, even if they don't seem relevant at first. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right, I hear you!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Hmph! You can conspire to prolong this trial as much as you like. But it's the day after the festival already for you! Or perhaps you'd forgotten...that these witness testimonies leave no room for doubt! Feel free to reiterate for the accused, Korekuta-san.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">As you have been at pains to point out time and again. I feel I'm growing a callus in my ear! And yet, no one else appears to have caught even a glimpse of this woman!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Argh... <thought>If only there'd been more people dining there at the time! Then someone else would have noticed her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Unfortunately, it was already past 2 p.m. when it happened. The quiet time between lunch and dinner in any restaurant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know... Of course the place was almost empty. It's what you'd expect...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Certainly, 2 p.m. is neither here nor there in terms of a time to eat. I wonder if there was a reason why the victim was eating at that time of day. And why he was alone. </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Yes, Your Excellency, there was indeed a reason. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There was?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">This was found in the victim's jacket pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is that, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">It is a medical report card, Your Excellency. It would seem that the victim had an appointment at a clinic prior to visiting the restaurant.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm... Hotta Clinic? Yes, there would indeed appear to be an entry for the date in question. '19th November, Noon to past 1 p.m...'</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Hm, the very day of the incident. </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">So the victim went for a late lunch following his appointment. The explanation couldn't be more simple.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Indeed. Alone, he was, the Englishman. Dining all by himself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">......... That I did. Forgive me for the position I place you in.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">So the testimonies of the old man, the soldier, and the waiter all agree on that point. Isn't that interesting? And let us not forget...the incontestable evidence we have to support their statements as well. As can clearly be seen... ...there is only a single beef steak on the victim's table. A meal for one.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... The antiques dealer, the sergeant and the waiter who testified before... It's not impossible that they're all lying. But if so...then why?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If I'm perfectly honest, I have absolutely no idea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Therefore! No one other than the black-uniformed cadet could have dispatched the Englishman. Over and out!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Wha...What did you say, cadet?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I clearly remember... There was a woman sitting across the table from the professor.</thought> Perhaps one of you might not have noticed... ...but for both of you to have failed to see the professor's dining companion? It's just not possible!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Unfortunately for you, Defendant Naruhodo, it's not just a case of these two witnesses alone.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The waiter, whose testimony the court heard earlier, clearly stated the same thing. He also said that the victim was alone.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Precisely! In other words... ...you are the sole proponent of this phantom lady!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but I...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">If such a woman were indeed present at the scene, the prosecution demands to see proof!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">And if no such proof exists... ...the prosecution demands that no further mention of this phantom woman be made! It is a blatant waste of the court's time!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>There's nothing I can say to that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Tsh huh huh huh huh!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What do you think, Ryunosuke?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... Um... Ooh...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What's the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't find anything. I can't find a clear discrepancy anywhere! I'm done for! I can't win this trial! No... No, no, nooooo...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Listen. The first thing to do is calm down. You can't expect witness statements to be full of holes very time. So just take your time, and try to tease more information out of them first.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You can choose to either 'Press' or 'Present' against each of the witness statements. If a witness is saying something you're suspicious about, Press him on it with [L / LB / Q]. With a little luck, you may get more details, which could prove to be crucial.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The important point is, there's no sense in holding back. If anything even slightly jars with you, press the witnesses on it, and press them hard!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright, got it! I'll press them like blocks of tofu! <thought>The professor wasn't alone in the restaurant, I'm sure of it. And one way or another, this cross-examination is going to prove I'm right! It's time to 'Press' them for all they're worth! My fate depends on it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Excellent work, Ryunosuke! We've gleaned some new information now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, yes... But I don't feel like it changes much. I can't see that it brings any real discrepancies to light.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I wouldn't be so sure. Let me see that medical report card you got before.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, you mean this?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes. This is a brand new piece of evidence... ...so perhaps we should examine it in a little more detail.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You'll notice that some pieces of evidence bear a magnifying glass. These are the ones you may Examine. Press [A / Space], and you can take a closer look at the piece in question. Use [right analog stick / arrow keys]... ...to rotate the evidence in all directions and examine it from all angles. By using [left analog stick / WASD]... ...you can move the crosshairs around to hunt for clues that may have been missed before. If the crosshairs start to pulsate... ...press [A / Space] to Investigate further. So, partner...I think you should take a closer look at this medical report card. See if there isn't something new to be learnt by examining it in more detail.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright, I'll see what I can do! <thought>I need to use [right analog stick / arrow keys], [left analog stick / WASD], and [A / Space]...to inspect any areas of the evidence that look suspicious...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It says 'Hotta Clinic' on this medical report card. I hate clinics. Almost as much as I hate hospitals and surgeries.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Aren't they all the same?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When I was five, I caught the only cold I've ever had in my life. And I remember, even though I felt awful already, I had to have this hideous injection in my right arm. Brrr... I'll never forget it! Never in my whole life!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Most people would give their right arm to have had only one cold in their whole life. Anyway, I don't think this is a clinic where they treat people for illnesses like that. Let's keep looking for clues. We don't want to miss anything.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It looks like this medical report card was first issued quite some time ago.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's probably a record of long-term treatment, that's why. With a family doctor, I imagine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well I can't imagine. Going to a doctor, I mean. As long as I'm alive, I'm never consulting one!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well if you were dead, there'd be no point. ...So you don't like doctors, then?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why would you? They make you drink horrible-tasting medicine, they give you painful injections... ...and then they demand lots of money from you for the privilege...all when you're at your lowest ebb!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... You sound like a model patient. With a bad case of stubbornness no less, for which the only cure is very bitter medicine indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Let's have a look... This is some kind of medical history. ...Ah, and there's an entry for the day the professor was killed. 'Extraction of molar with topical anaesthesia'...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Extraction of molar'? You mean, he had a tooth taken out?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It would seem so. Just before the incident, he'd had a bad tooth removed. Perhaps they used laughing gas. That's the most modern practice in the West for pain relief.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I've heard of this 'anaesthesia'. <thought>Although it's hard to believe there's anything that can actually stop you feeling pain.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ah, there's a cautionary note from the medical practitioner as well. 'Strictly no food or drink besides water for three hours post-procedure, until anaesthetic effects have passed.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Sounds like information worth bearing in mind.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>With this new information... ...the meaning of that one particular statement totally changes!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So, I think it's time we listened to the testimony again, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Definitely!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">This is clearly a record of some kind of medical treatment. And there's an entry for the day the professor was killed. 'Extraction with the use of anaesthesia'...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Extraction'? So he had a tooth out.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, it sounds like just before he went for lunch, Dr Wilson had to have a decayed tooth removed. They probably used laughing gas so he couldn't feel anything. It's the latest medical advancement in the West.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I've heard people talking about this new idea of anaesthetic. <thought>It's impossible to imagine not being able to feel pain, though.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">There's a cautionary note at the end from whoever wrote this. It says: 'No food or drink other than water for three hours post-procedure while anaesthesia wears off.'</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well done, Ryunosuke! We have even more to go on now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I still don't feel like the situation has really changed, though. No discrepancies have come to light, and that's what we need.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... Oh, I think the situation has changed a great deal. We've come a long way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How so?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Because we have just what we need. It's simply a case of using it to our advantage now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Then, do you mean... <thought>...there IS a discrepancy somewhere?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The crucial point is, the victim had been prohibited from consuming anything but water when he was shot. That fact has not yet been brought to the court's attention.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He's right... Thinking about Dr Wilson's circumstances at the time of the incident... ...puts that particular statement in a totally different light!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Always keep your eye on the progress of the battle. That's the only sure way to win.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, the symbol of Yumei University... Every student wears this pin with pride. It's funny, but most emblems seem to be either round or rectangular. I like this spiked design, even though it doesn't really make any sense. Although, it does cause problems. Lots of students end up cutting their fingers on their badges. Perhaps it was the idea of one of the founders. 'A sharp pin for a sharp mind' or something...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My personal student number is engraved on the back here. If you lose your pin, they won't accept you as a Yumei student at the university. 'Yu mei not come in!' they say. Of course, you can get a new pin made if you can just tell them your number. I've actually lost mine twice already, but I still don't know my student number by heart. I always say to myself, 'I mustn't forget to write it down somewhere.' But then I forget not to forget that...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">This plan of the restaurant raises a number of questions, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Definitely!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's supposed to show the relative position of everything in the moments following the incident... ...but there's nothing to show the woman you say you saw there. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Exactly! And that's not all! Look here in the upper left where it says 'kitchen'.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Hm? Oh yes. What of it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No one would use those complicated characters to write 'kitchen'! Especially not if they were in a hurry!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You mean you don't remember those characters yourself, don't you. Study harder, Ryunosuke!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well, that's unexpected.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What is?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Look, do you see it says the witness's name here? 'Satoru Hosonaga'...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well yes, business cards do tend to show the person's name. That's sort of the point.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's not the name that's unexpected. It's his job title.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">His job...? Oh! 'Chief Inspector Satoru Hosonaga, Primary Criminal Investigation Division, Imperial Police Bureau' Inspector? What on earth?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... I have no idea. But let's face it, the police have a lot of power and influence. If they're wielding it somehow here...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Chief Inspector Satoru Hosonaga, Primary Criminal Investigation Division, Imperial Police Bureau'... So he isn't a waiter at all. He's a detective.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And let's face it, the police have a lot of power and influence. If they're wielding it somehow here...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...erm... Well, I think, um...</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">About what are you wittering, lad? Call yourself a lawyer?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I wish I could... But first and foremost here, I'm the accused.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ryunosuke... Everyone stumbles on their words occasionally. Under the circumstances, I wouldn't worry about it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thanks, Kazuma.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I could see it quite clearly in that cross-examination you just carried out. When you raised your hand straight up like that, so purposefully... You knew exactly what it was you wanted to say. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Don't feel like you have to choose your words carefully. Just say what you're thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Alright. ...And thanks for the advice. Korekuta-san, this is a medical report card belonging to the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Ah, I see... And...I don't see. What of it, boy?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Comparing what is written on this report card with your witness statement... ...something clearly doesn't add up!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Dear me, dear me. Have you forgotten my words so soon, you amateur?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry, what...?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">You are not to interrupt court proceedings with your amateurish drivel!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Let's see if I can explain in words you might understand. It was after 2 p.m. in the afternoon when the victim was murdered at the restaurant. Whatever he may or may not have done before that time...is completely irrelevant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Grrr... But, but that's...um...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Remember, Ryunosuke, you don't have to use clever language or fancy words. Just make your point.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Your Excellency, I believe we're finished here. There is surely no need to prolong this trial further.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">The witness testimonies the court has heard have been clear and concise. This medical report card has no bearing on the matter at all. For the simple reason that... ...there is no one else besides this pale-faced pupil who could possibly have perpetrated the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This medical report card has nothing to do with the case? DO you really believe that?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Wha...? That outburst half petrified me, boy! Of course I believe it! How could it POSSIBLY be relevant?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Perhaps because Hotta Clinic, which issued the report card...is a dental clinic!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">A dental clinic? Is that supposed to mean something to me?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Perhaps if I told you that the victim...had just had a tooth extracted...?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">...! What's this now...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And furthermore... ...if I told you that as a result, the victim had been forbidden from eating...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">...!</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">...!</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">...! Just, just what are you trying to say, cadet? He had orders not to eat? So what?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's all written up in here. 'No food or drink other than water for three hours post-procedure while anaesthesia wears off.' </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">WHAT?! No, that, that can't...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Korekuta-san!</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">What, boy? What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As you just heard... When he was killed, some time shortly after 2 p.m... ...the victim couldn't have been eating anything at all.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">No...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Additionally...</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">There's more...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You have assured the court with unwavering self-confidence... ...that the victim was dining alone. But that cannot possibly be the case!</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Grrr...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Because the victim, as we now know... ...had just had one of his teeth extracted, and was still experiencing the effects of the anaesthetic! </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Expertly done...partner!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What... What is this nonsense? You little upstart!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">These are baseless accusations! Just, just look at this photographic evidence! You can clearly see the plate of food at the victim's table!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Use your head. That's the very discrepancy we're talking about. Or can't you follow the logic?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">How, how dare you?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I think it's fair to say that the 'tables' in this restaurant case...have turned. Wouldn't you agree, Ryunosuke?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm? Yes! Most definitely!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So having just undergone some dental surgery, the victim was unable to eat. Which leaves one very crucial conundrum... Who in fact was eating the pictured beef steak? The court will hear the opinion of the defence on this new puzzle. I assume you're ready, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........'Counsel'? Oh! That, that means me, doesn't it!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Alright, the answer to this question is going to be pivotal. This is the start of you turning this trial around! Show them what you're made of!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Got it! So, um... The person eating the steak at the victim's table must have been...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The victim himself! Obviously!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ryunosuke, come on! Pull yourself together! The victim couldn't have been eating at the time. You just told the court that yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes! Haha, of course! I, I thought it didn't sound quite right...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Look, you've even stunned the judge with that ludicrous answer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright then, I can use his state of shock to give me time to think...and come up with the right answer!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I suggest you think it through more carefully, and try not to shock him in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're, you're right. Sorry. Um...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"> </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I think it may have been me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">It's not enough that you took the man's life, but you took his meal as well?! That's a bee sting on a crying face! Hmph, some people seem to think they can do whatever they like.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And some people seem to think they can say whatever they like... Ryunosuke. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry, you're right! Of course I didn't eat it!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The next time you make a quip like that, I'll make you eat your words. Then you'll be needing some dental surgery yourself. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Al-Alright, I get the message... Um...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I bet it was the sergeant and the antiques dealer, Nosa-san and Korekuta-san!</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Argh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Are you taking the cake, cadet?! You think I'd share rations with this decrepit greybeard?!</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Insult me by associating me with this brutish carnivore, would you?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You were both present at the scene. Neither of you can deny that you had the opportunity.</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">You addlebrained idiot! I had my own regulation beef steak set before me at my own table! And as any soldier worth his salt will tell you, you seize whatever rations are put in front of you! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would seem you may need to reconsider your answer, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of, of course, Your Excellency! Erm...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Obviously! It can only have been someone else who was sitting at the professor's table!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">You will not let this go, will you? There was no such person!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">When the incident occurred, we know that the victim couldn't have been eating anything. Yet we have evidence of a half-eaten steak on his table! Therefore! The only logical conclusion is that there was somebody else there eating it.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Urgggghhhh...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">We have strong evidence to support our assertion. It's clear that these witness testimonies are unreliable. If the court decides to push through a ruling at this stage... ...we will lodge a formal complaint with the Ministry of Justice and pursue a fair retrial. Relentlessly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Are you insane? You, you would take on the government?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Don't worry, Counsel, I have no issue with you.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I have issue with THEM! Those two witnesses in the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">We have demonstrated with evidence that the victim was not alone. So, if it now turns out that the two of you deliberately lied when giving your testimonies... ...obviously you will be charged with perjury.</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Perjury...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And, since this is a murder trial... ...you will also be deemed complicit in the killing.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Complicit...in m-murder...? N-N-N-NOOOOOOOOO! </line>
<line speaker="Nosa"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Nosa">N-N-N-Negative! There, there was no mention of this at the tactical meeting! I was just following orders!</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">That's right! As the man says! 'Just say you never saw the gentlewoman!' That's what...they, erm...told...us... .........Oh. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What?!</thought> What did you just say, Korekuta-san?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Oh, um... No...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You were just 'following orders'?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Now hold on, lad! I was, um...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">'Say you never saw the gentlewoman'?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Grrr...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">When you say 'gentlewoman', do you mean... ...you saw the victim with a lady from overseas?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What, what is the meaning of all this? These witnesses...gave false statements? Is this true, you pair?!</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">.........</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Just one... Just one simple slip of the tongue!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Counsel, explain what is going on here!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's painfully clear now... You tried to prevent these witnesses from telling the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Absolutely not! The prosecution knows nothing of this!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Then who's behind this?! Who tried to make you keep your mouths shut?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">W-Well, um...</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">That's classified!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So you're prepared to be tried as a conspirator to this murder, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">You, you wouldn't... This can't be happening!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ryunosuke... Judging from the way they're reacting to this... ...I'd say they were sworn to silence by someone with considerable influence. However... ...I don't believe Auchi had any idea about it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What are you saying? I mean, to wield that kind of influence... There are only a handful of possibilities! <thought>It could only have been the government, the military or... Or the police, I suppose...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well? Any ideas about who might be behind this? If we can affirm who tried to silence these witnesses, then we can continue our pursuit! </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So we need to name whoever it was that tried to make the witnesses keep their mouths shut...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Of course, we'll need evidence before we make any firm accusations. Evidence that proves whoever it was really did wield his or her power here... </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But how? How can we possibly...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Remember how we made progress before?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Before?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">We examined this piece of evidence in more detail and found a new clue as a result. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well, that's not the only piece of evidence we have, is it? We need to re-examine everything, and make sure there's nothing we've missed. There's no time to lose!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I want answers! If it's proven that these witnesses have been manipulated, I assure you, the penalty will be severe!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Please...wait... Your Excellency! I had no idea about any of this! I swear to every Shinto god! I knew nothing! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what does the defence have to say about all this? Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm, well, Your Excellency! <thought>Ugh, no time to think... I'm just going to have to close my eyes and shout out the first name that comes into my head!</thought> Besides the prosecution, the only person with the necessary influence to manipulate the witnesses is...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think, Counsel, that you may want to close your ears as well as your eyes. Otherwise the sighs of disappointment in the courtroom may very well deafen you. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">If you feel you must close your eyes in a crisis, might I suggest you keep your mouth shut next time, too? Otherwise, I may have to use the influence I have in this courtroom to shut it...permanently!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I don't know what it is about that prosecutor exactly, but he really makes me wince in pain sometimes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I don't have a great deal of influence myself, but believe me... ...I can find other ways to make you keep your mouth shut as well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright, don't get angry... I'll think again. </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">There must be a clue somewhere in all that evidence in the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Actually, now that I think about it... ...there might be some pieces of evidence I haven't thoroughly examined yet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, surely that would be...Satoru Hosonaga-san!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hosonaga-san? The waiter who took the stand earlier?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Poppycock! What possible reason would the waiter have to make these witnesses give false testimony? Not to mention the fact that even a head waiter could not possibly have that level of influence!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">For once, I would agree with you. If, that is, the man truly were a waiter.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Wha...? If he truly were..?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Come on, Ryunosuke! Time to hit this court with the truth! The truth about Satoru Hosonaga-san's real identity, as proven by this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"> </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"> </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. I'm not sure what this is supposed to prove, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">I think, Your Excellency, that what this proves is not the true nature of the waiter... ...but the true nature of the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">A blackguard, who would stoop to presenting irrelevant evidence to incriminate an innocent man. That is the true nature of this rookie!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Waaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Try again. Go over all the evidence we have one more time. There's something in there that proves who this waiter really is, I'm sure of it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Al-Alright then. I'll try!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The plan of the restaurant sketched by the man in question? Hm, I agree it shows a great deal of attention to detail, but I'm not sure we can conclude anything-</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry, Your Excellency. That's the back of the card. It's the back...of the back of the card that's of interest.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I...beg your pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Or, or perhaps I should have said, the front? Yes! It's the front of the back of the card! That's where the telling detail is!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......... Would somebody please explain what this overexcited student is trying to say?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Hosonaga-san sketched the plan of the restaurant on the reverse side of his business card. The front of that business card reveals the man in question's profession. His true profession.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The waiter's profession? But that's surely... Good... Good gracious!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">That's right, Your Excellency. The card reads, 'Chief Inspector, Primary Criminal Investigation Division, Imperial Police Bureau'. </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">WHAT?! The, the waiter is...a police detective?! I, I haven't heard any mention of this before! Why haven't I heard any mention of this before?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The Imperial Police Bureau has immense power. Absolute power, as far as regular civilians are concerned. So, witnesses there in the stand...</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">...!</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Was it in fact the waiter who gave you your orders? Was it he who told you not to mention that you'd seen this foreign gentlewoman at the scene?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Erm, well...</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">.........</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In-Inspector Hosonaga...!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">I was worried something like this may happen. The moment you asked me to submit my sketch as evidence, I realised it was a possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will take this plan and add it to the Court Record as evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Oh, um... Well...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is there a problem? Hand the plan to the court officer at once!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Um...of course. Here you are.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, I remember now... He did act strangely when the judge asked him to hand over his business card.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">I strive to carry out all investigations flawlessly. It's my guiding principle. But I let myself be distracted when I made that sketch. It was an unusually careless mistake. </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">So...you mean to say... You really are a detective?!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But why would a detective be working as a restaurant waiter? Ah! Of course! Your salary must be terrible!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">I was working undercover.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Undercover...?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Yes. There have been a series of incidents at the restaurant recently. In order to investigate, I decided to get a job there as a waiter, working undercover.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Incidents at the restaurant? What kind of incidents?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">That would be classified police information, which I am not at liberty to divulge. However, I can state categorically that they are unrelated to this case of homicide. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Very well then, Inspector Hosonaga. But you will elaborate on one point for the court...</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Of course, Your Excellency.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We have just heard new information from the two witnesses beside you. That at the time of the shooting, there was in fact another person present at the victim's table.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that is indeed true... ...clearly you would also have been aware of this person's presence, having served at the table in question. However, your testimony did not allude to this other diner. Therefore, I am led to assume... ...that in your professional capacity as a police officer, you required these witnesses to be in agreement. Would that be correct?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Ahem! ...Ahem! ......... Correct, Your Excellency.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Unbelievable!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Hm, as I suspected...</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">.........</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">As soon as I heard the gunshot, I ran out of the kitchen to see what had happened. The victim sat slumped in his chair, and beside him, gun in hand, stood the accused student. Sitting opposite the victim at the same table was a young lady whom I guessed to be an Englishwoman. </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So the truth comes out.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">I immediately sealed off the restaurant and reported the incident to the bureau. It was then that I received some...special orders. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Special orders? You mean to say...?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">'Remove the Englishwoman from the scene at once.' ......... It was made clear that the Englishwoman's presence at the restaurant was to be concealed. Those were my orders. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But! But what if this Englishwoman was the killer?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">I think it would be in everyone's best interests not to pursue that idea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">The empire views the friendly terms of its relationship with Britain more highly than anything at the moment. An Englishman has been murdered on our soil. To name an Englishwoman as the primary suspect... Well, without irrefutable evidence, that would be completely out of the question.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So that's the reason for the disappearance of the phantom woman in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But it's not right...!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">.........</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... ...One possibility does spring to mind.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean, Kazuma...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yumei University is currently hosting a number of exchange students from Great Britain. And I'm fairly certain that one of them, studying in the medical faculty's research laboratory... ...is a young Englishwoman.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">...You're a shrewd man. I can see why you're the chosen candidate for the overseas study tour. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! You mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">When I removed the woman from the scene of the crime... ...I thought it prudent to check her identity first. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then the court demands that you name the lady in question at once, Inspector!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">The Englishwoman sitting at the university professor's table was a certain Miss Jezaille Brett. She is indeed a foreign student studying in the research laboratory of Yumei University's medical faculty.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Wha... What is happening heeeeeere?!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">I admit that under orders from the police bureau, I erased all evidence of this lady's presence at the scene... ...and ordered these witnesses to make no mention of her in their testimonies. It must now be up to Your Excellency to decide how to deal with this situation.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......... Very well. My thoughts on the matter are as follows... Thus far, the case presented to the court has been underpinned by a particularly critical premise. Namely, that the victim was dining alone.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">However, as we have now discovered that this premise is false... ...it would be a desecration of our justice system to ignore the truth and give a ruling at this point.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">But, but, Your Excellency! That would mean missing the noon deadline of a ruling in order to send the telegraphic report to Great Britain! Our own government will surely be very displeased by such actions.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Calm yourself, Counsel. I will not allow the government of our country or any other to influence the proceedings of my courtroom. </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Ugh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Inspector Hosonaga...</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Yes, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You will locate this Jezaille Brett and escort her to the courtroom with the utmost urgency.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">At once, Your Excellency.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">But, but that means you'll be going against the special orders you were given from the police bureau!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">......... As I said before... ...it is my guiding principle to carry out all investigations flawlessly. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So, it won't be a problem?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Ahem! Ahem! Ahem, ahem! Nothing will get in my way!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court will adjourn briefly. The prosecution must call the English student, Jezaille Brett, to the witness stand. Do I make myself clear?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Yes... ...Your Excellencyyyyyyy! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good. Then we will have a thirty-minute recess before reconvening. </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Excellent work, Ryunosuke! That was superb!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... My heart was in my mouth the entire time.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It was almost unbelievable. I mean, looking at you in there... You were drenched in sweat, your eyes popping, your knees knocking AND you were grinding your teeth. It was a grim sight, but before I knew it, you'd started finding inconsistencies in the testimonies. I think you might have a natural talent for being a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Forget it! It's terrifying! If I get through this, I don't ever want to see the inside of a courtroom again!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ha ha ha ha hah! Anyway, it looks like we've exposed your phantom lady at least.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Miss Jezaille Brett... A student from Great Britain...is she?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's what I was trying to tell everyone from the start. Dr Wilson wasn't alone! There was a young woman with him. Like I've been saying all along! </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, you have, haven't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I might not be overly confident in the courtroom, but my powers of observation are one thing I am sure of.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, I can see that. So...about this young gentlewoman... Thanks to our detective friend, she was hastily escorted away from the scene, it seems. Did you see what happened with that?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, I didn't see any of it. I was just on my way out of the restaurant myself. Then, on the floor next to Dr Wilson's table... ...I noticed there was a gun lying on the floor. And just after I bent down and picked it up...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I didn't have time to think about where the sound of the gunshot had come from. The waiter ran over to me, looking as white as a sheet... ...and he bundled me into some sort of small pantry next to the kitchen.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Fast thinking by the detective. He apprehended his suspect without a moment's delay.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, and because I was shut in the pantry... ...I have no idea what happened outside in the dining area.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, there you are. Well done, both of you.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Professor Mikotoba!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well... It seems I was right. The pair of you make an outstanding team. You've exceeded my expectations, I have to say.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes...it seems you planned this from the start. You arranged things so that I wouldn't be able to act as a lawyer in this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">......... Our modern country is still in its infancy. Our justice system, even more so. Which is why... ...I firmly believe that we need to send our brightest young stars overseas to learn all they can. I wanted to avoid a situation that may have resulted in your study tour to Great Britain being cancelled.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... Well, it makes no difference. Lawyer or otherwise, if I'm the kind of man who can't help his best friend avert the worst crisis of his life... ...I shouldn't waste everyone's time by going to study overseas anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! What are you saying, Kazuma?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Hmph. So that's your stance... I was afraid you'd feel that way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well then, it looks like it all comes down to you, young man.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">To, to me?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Yes. You need to prove your innocence, and uncover what really took place in that restaurant. I  must say, I very much want to know the truth. After all, I have a personal connection to this case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Come to think of it, he said the same thing earlier this morning, didn't he?</thought> Um, if you don't mind me asking, Professor... ...did you know the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Yes, I did. As you're probably aware, Dr John H. Wilson was a visiting professor at Yumei. And it was I who invited him.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! I, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I...didn't know that before. </line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Anyway, you're about to go into battle. The victim was a university professor from Great Britain. And a well known one at that. Naturally our government is looking to identify and punish the culprit as quickly as possible.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">But let's not forget who we're going up against. The 'gentlewoman' whose involvement our police bureau went to extraordinary lengths to hide.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Yes, and I'm sure the prosecution will be using every tool at their disposal to quash your case. But I've no doubt that you pair will put up a good fight, right to the last. Best of luck!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Now then... ...I need you to run an errand at the university at once. There's something I think we may need. </line>
<line speaker="???">Of course. Good luck...Kazuma-sama.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Defendant Naruhodo! Court recess is over. Please make your way back inside the courtroom at once!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's time. Let's get back to it, partner. Let's go in there and deal a decisive blow before those old fossils know what's hit them!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Um, Kazuma...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you. Really.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What for?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, if you hadn't said you believed me, then... ...I'm fairly sure I'd already have been found guilty by now.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Look, I have faith in you. As a lawyer, and as a friend.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Coming from you, that means a lot. <thought>If I'm found guilty in this trial... ...he's really going to give up on his dream of studying abroad. That's the kind of true friend he is. So this isn't just my battle any more. Whoever we're up against, we absolutely cannot afford to lose!</thought> Alright then... ...I'll save the thank-yous for after the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You can treat me to one of those sukiyaki meals I like from 'Yumei Cafeteria' on University Street. With an extra large portion, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court hereby resumes the trial of Ryunosuke Naruhodo. Prosecutor Auchi, have you managed to subpoena the witness?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Yes, Your Excellency! Against all odds. And thanks to a certain young stripling, the prosecution is now under rather painful scrutiny from the government.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Let the government scrutinise. That's their job. It's nothing to worry about.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">It's highly unlikely that the good relations we've forged with Great Britain will emerge from this trial unscathed. Will you still think it's nothing to worry about when the new treaty breaks down and our nation founders?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Again... Terribly sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">If the friendship between our nations is really so fragile, then the treaty isn't worth the paper it's written on. You really have nothing to worry about, Ryunosuke.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">A secret trial, anxiety over some foreign government's opinions, a bungled investigation, missing witnesses... Is this what our nation's justice system is? Is this the Supreme Court of Japan, or of England?!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Shut up! Shut up, you jumped-up rookie boy! You and your friend know nothing! Nothing of the situation our nation finds itself in! By aligning ourselves with this great world power, we'll become strong! Diplomacy has never been more critical! Steady political manoeuvring is what will secure our futures!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I won't deny that I'm no expert. I'm just a student. And one who could arguably study harder, too. But standing here now in our Supreme Court, there is one thing that I feel very strongly: A country that fails to uphold the truth in its justice system is a country with no future at all.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well said, Ryunosuke. Despite the wide-eyed look of terror.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">You little braaaaats!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, Counsel. This court is the pinnacle of our nation's justice system, and exists solely for the pursuance of truth. With that in mind, this trial will now resume with the next witness taking the stand. The visiting student from Great Britain, Miss Jezaille Brett!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Yes... ...Your Excellencyyyyyyy!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Well, what a delight it is to welcome such a fine gentlewoman to Japan! And from such a distant land!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Tea! Someone bring English tea! In England, no discussions take place without tea!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Is that true?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...No idea.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">So, erm... Ahem! Could we possibly trouble you to state your name and occupation for the court?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Of course. My name is Satoru Hosonaga. I have been working undercover as the head waiter at La Carneval, but my true-</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Yes, yes, we know all about you already!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Inspector Hosonaga! Where are your manners? In England, it's always ladies first!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Is that true?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...No idea. More importantly, a little earlier today you said something to me. You said your powers of observation are the one thing you're sure of.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, yes... I think I did, didn't I?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yet your description for this amazing sight was simply 'a woman'. Sorry, Ryunosuke, but powers of observation aside, your powers of description are sorely lacking.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">So, dear lady, once again, if we may trouble you for your name and occupation, please.</line>
<line speaker="???">[Foreign text].</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Um, I'm terribly sorry, dear lady, but...what?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">[Foreign text]?</line>
<line speaker="???">[Foreign text].</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">The lady says her name is Jezaille Brett. She comes from London, England. She's a visiting research student, currently enrolled in Yumei University's medical faculty.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Oh, my! What a rare treat to hear the dulcet tones of the delightful language of the British people! I'm afraid I don't understand a word you said, but it was as beautiful as a hummingbird's song! </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">As far as I can tell... ...the detective is translating her words faithfully enough.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I agree. Haha, you'll obviously do fine in England, Kazuma. Her English doesn't rattle you at all, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Nor you. You've clearly been paying attention in your English classes, Ryunosuke.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court thanks the beautiful lady for taking the stand. Now...if we may trouble you to confirm something, Miss Brett.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Three days ago, at a restaurant called La Carneval, a grim murder took place. The court has been led to believe that you were dining there with the victim, Dr Wilson, at the time. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">[Foreign text]?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">[Foreign text].</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">She says...'Yes.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This could take some time...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So even though she's studying here in Japan, she can't speak any Japanese?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">[Foreign text]. [Foreign text].</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">She'd like to apologise for disappearing from the scene. She says that she was due to make a presentation at the university, so she had to leave immediately. </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Interesting, when you're the one who engineered her escape...</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">I was just following special orders from the bureau.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Well now, dear lady, would you be so kind as to cast your eyes over this photographic print? Seeing as you were, so unfortunately, present at the scene of the crime... ...could it be that your resplendent eyes caught sight of the wicked perpetrator, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">[Foreign text].</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Apparently it was a very frightening...and sorrowful sight.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you mean to say...?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Yes. It would appear the lady did witness the crime. The very moment when the accused, standing right there in this courtroom... ...shot the victim in cold blood!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in court!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Did, did you hear that, Your Excellency? Here we have an absolutely conclusive witness statement!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well, it looks like it's clear now. Clear who our real enemy is!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Unfortunately, I will have to ask you to formally testify, if you please. Kindly tell the court the exact nature of this frightening and sorrowful sight you described.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">[Foreign text]?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">[Foreign text].</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">'I had arranged to meet for a slightly late luncheon with Dr Wilson that day.'</line>
<line speaker="Brett">[Foreign text]!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">'After a while, the accused came over to greet the professor, and they got into a fierce argument.'</line>
<line speaker="Brett">[Foreign text].</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">'I don't carry a gun myself, so obviously I couldn't have been the culprit.'</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. This is a condemning testimony indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Quiet, you filthy wretch! Look at you, you black-hearted blackguard! And look at this snow-white angel! I'm sure even a dark-minded scoundrel like you can imagine whose words the court is going to believe!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You're still making the same mistakes, Ryunosuke. You mustn't blurt out when you're goaded like that. That's a lesson you need to learn.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh, but he's so annoying!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Of course, I was at the scene as well. I took statements from this lady and the two witnesses who testified before, and reported back to the bureau. It was decided that Miss Brett was not involved, so I let her go.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The testimonies of the last two witnesses were completely worthless, however.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Well, even so... On the day in question, the lady was wearing the same outfit as she is today. As you can see, there is nowhere about her person where she could conceal a firearm. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I would think she could hide a gun almost ANYWHERE in that outfit if she wanted to...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Unless and until the precise location where the witness is to have hidden a weapon can be shown, this is moot.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">'There are no pockets in my outfit. I have nowhere to hide a gun.' Those are the witness's own words on the matter.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Argh! That's ridiculous! If only I was allowed to lift up her dress, I could prove it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Don't think about doing anything rash, Ryunosuke.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But I didn't fire the gun I picked up! There must have been another gun there that day!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You're right about that. Which means...this lady was hiding a gun somewhere... Yes, that's what we have to prove now. And to do so, we will need to pull her testimony apart.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence may now cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Yes, Your Excellency!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">'I had arranged to meet for a slightly late luncheon with Dr Wilson that day.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">You don't keep up with the latest fashions from Britain, do you? Late luncheons are en vogue. Isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">No.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Hm, a decisive English 'no' has quite a sting to it.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">The gentlewoman is currently working in the victim's research laboratory, it seems. So it was apparently a daily occurrence that they would lunch together.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">But on the day in question, the victim had another appointment at the clinic first.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, which we can prove from the medical report card that was submitted as evidence earlier.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">That's right. Miss Brett and the victim went to lunch following the victim's treatment, which is why it was so late.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, yes, that all makes perfect sense.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Such wonderful logic! What a shining example of English intelligence this fine gentlewoman is!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So you both arrived at the restaurant. What happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga"> 'The professor was unable to eat, so I ordered for myself only. A beef steak.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Um, you're supposed to actually check with the witness before answering...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Was Miss Brett aware of that fact?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">It seems so, yes. She'd heard that the professor was to have some dental treatment.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So that would mean... ...that it WAS you who ate the steak pictured here. Is that right, Miss Brett?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">That's right, yes. The print you have there shows the table exactly as it was left after the horrifying events.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>'Exactly as it was left'...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Dear me! What a harrowing experience! To have travelled to a distant island on the far side of the world and be embroiled in such a tragic incident... Have no fear, my dear lady! I swear I will crush the evil fiend that has subjected you to this terrible plight!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So the victim, Dr Wilson, had nothing to eat or drink at all?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">That's right. Other than some carbonated water.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just water?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Yes. The professor was unable to eat, but he had been given permission to drink water. So it appears that the diners toasted their lunch with a glass of water each.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Hm, they each raised a glass of carbonated water...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What do you think, Ryunosuke? About the witness's last statement.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That last statement of yours, Miss Brett...has a profound bearing on this case!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Well, well, how fascinating. Do tell us, what is this 'profound bearing', hm?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... .........</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The significance of the statement will become apparent when the time is right. The defence calls for the witness's last statement to be formally added to the testimony. </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Hmph! Well sidestepped, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Miss Brett... Kindly repeat what you just said to be added to your official testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">'Gladly,' she said.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That was brilliant, Kazuma! I'm going to remember that one.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Which one?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'The significance will become apparent when the time is right.' I could really use that phrase!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I'd hope there are some other useful tips you're picking up from this experience than that, Ryunosuke.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, I can't really see anything wrong with it.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Really? Alright then, if that's what you think. .........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Kazuma... ...do YOU think it's significant in some way? </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well, perhaps. But let's do this your way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Maybe I should press her on that statement again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">'I ordered a beef steak for myself, and the professor and I said "cheers" over a glass of carbonated water.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Yes. Being the waiter, I poured the two glasses myself. I clearly remember doing so.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Except you're actually a detective...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And the beef steak... That was for you, Miss Brett?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">The lady says that she'd heard it was not customary to eat beef here until Japan opened its doors to the world.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">'What a frightful place!' ...is the lady's opinion.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And I've heard it's not customary to eat sashimi in Great Britain. Now THAT'S frightful!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Every country has its own cuisine. As long as people have food to eat, what does it matter what it is?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">True. Come to think of it... ...the first time I tried carbonated water, it was much more of a shock than the first time I tried beef! <thought>But anyway, back to this witness's statement. Somehow, I feel like there's something out of place in what she's saying...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">We need to pounce on even the slightest thing now. Because you never know what might lead us to our goal. Our goal of turning this trial around.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Understood, Kazuma.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">'After a while, the accused came over to greet the professor, and they got into a fierce argument.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Please, don't get angry with me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no! I, I wasn't directing that retort at you! It was meant for the lady next to you. But anyway! As I said, I did NOT argue with the professor!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">......... I'm afraid your words are in vain.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Miss Brett does not appear to speak Japanese.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">No, no, of course not! Japanese is such a cumbersome language anyway! English is the future! We must all su-pii-ku Ingurisshu!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I wonder if the prosecution will feel that way forever, or only in the presence of a beautiful woman, hm?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well, that 'beautiful woman' is telling blatant lies with a completely straight face. I have to find something that will unravel her testimony, no matter how seemingly insignificant it may be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Anyway, it seems that after the argument, the accused briefly returned to his own seat. </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">That part ties in with what you said, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...I still had some coffee to drink. </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And the next time you got up after that...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Was when I'd finished my coffee and stood up to leave.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">'Then, not long afterwards, the accused took the professor's gun, and shot him right before my eyes!'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And like I said! There's no point repeating that assertion over and over!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I wasn't expecting to be attacked by my own side.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Nevertheless, Defendant, you can't deny... ...that when the shot rang out in the restaurant, you had a gun in your hand!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, yes, that's...that's true, but...! But all I did was pick up the gun I saw on the floor next to the professor as I was leaving the restaurant! In fact... Yes! There was someone much closer to the victim than me at that time. The highly suspicious lady in the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">That will do, you dirty rotten scoundrel!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Dirty?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Your baseless accusations could very well cause an international incident...boy!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It seems to me, that your accusation is just as baseless as ours.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Tsh huh huh! What nonsense!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">The lady is merely stating what she saw.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And this is already an international incident as far as I'm concerned, anyway.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">'I don't carry a gun myself, so obviously I couldn't have been the culprit.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Absolutely. I verified it personally.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You...verified it?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Yes, immediately after the incident, I checked to make sure the lady was not carrying a weapon. I distinctly remember her saying, 'I'm not.' </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's...all you did? You just asked her?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Surely you carried out a physical search, Inspector?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">...No.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why on earth not?!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">The honourable English gentlewoman clearly stated that she did not possess a weapon. There was obviously no need for any further probing into the matter!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Or...there was no permission given for any further probing into the matter perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Think what you will! But if you're going to continue with this preposterous claim that the refined lady was concealing a firearm... ...the prosecution demands that you support your assertion with facts!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In other words, he wants evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Brett">[Foreign text].</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">The lady wishes to point out that of course she wanted to stay and assist with the investigation... ...but she was in a hurry to give a presentation at the university, so she was compelled to leave.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Not to mention the fact that your office had told you to get the woman out of there.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Not 'get her out of there'. I just urged her to leave. The lady would like to point out that she in no way meant to 'run away' from the scene of the crime. Which is why she is only too happy to cooperate and testify here in court today, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Unlike a certain student who refuses to admit when the game is up!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">You could at least have the courtesy to pay attention when I'm goading you!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So she's maintaining that you got into an argument with the professor, at the end of which, you shot him.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Which is an out-and-out, totally unfounded lie!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Still, her statement is very compelling. After all, she's an elegant, refined, young and beautiful gentlewoman from Great Britain. In stark contrast to you, dressed from head to toe in a dull black school uniform.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm dressed exactly the same way as you are, except for the flapping red ribbons!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well anyway, this is our only chance to expose her testimony as the fiction that it is.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">If we can't do that, the trial's over. Even you with your thick skin must be able to feel the murderous looks you're getting from around the room.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Only too well. I feel half dead already. <thought>And the fact that I can't see a single inconsistency in her testimony isn't making me feel any better, either!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The first thing to do is press her on any of her statements that seem even slightly off to you. Do that, and an opening will present itself. I promise you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I need to expose the true face of this exotic foreigner that's hiding behind the mask. That's what I should be aiming for in this cross-examination...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... That's it! Let me just confirm something, please. It's...to do with this photographic print. Just a short while ago, you spoke of this print showing the victim's table at the crime scene... ...that it was 'exactly as it was left'.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">'That is correct,' the lady says.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well! That is... It's, um... It's odd! Very odd!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Dear me. What's odd is the defence's inability to express itself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ryunosuke, what is it about the print that looks odd to you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well obviously, it's...it's the 'cheers'!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">The...'cheers'?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Brett just told us that she and the professor said 'cheers' over a glass of water. But if that's true... ...there should be two glasses on the table, not one!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're quite right, Counsel. There's only one glass pictured here!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Are we supposed to be impressed by this nit-picking over minutiae? What possible difference does the presence or absence of a glass make on the case?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Minutiae, you say? Could it be that the detective here removed a glass from the table to conceal the lady's presence?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Of course not! I would never do something so reckless.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But there should have been two glasses on the table! Or are you going to try to tell me you can clink with only one?!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">......... You're quite right. I certainly took two glasses to the table.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">[Foreign text].</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Inspector! What did the lady say?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">It would seem that it was Miss Brett who took the glass from the table.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">'It was all so terrifying, everything that happened. I panicked and thought I should try to hide the fact that I'd been there at all,' she's saying.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">...Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">There, as I assured the court before... this is of no consequence at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, please...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">We must remember that this student had just murdered the lady's luncheon companion before her very eyes! Who could blame her for concealing a glass or two in her state of disarray?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's absurd!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Oh really? So do we take it that you are now going to accuse this vulnerable, young and beautiful woman of...mischief?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! No no no! This, this can't be put down to 'mischief'!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I'd like to know... ...exactly how the lady took the glass from the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">[Foreign text].</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">It would seem that she slipped it into a small handbag she was carrying.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A handbag, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Yes, Your Excellency. A small, handheld pouch commonly carried by well-to-do women in England. </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">So, the beautiful lady has very graciously explained how and why she removed the glass from the scene now. However! The fact remains that this glass has absolutely no bearing on the case!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">This student has been trying to confuse the court with logical reasoning! But in the end, it comes to nothing. No more pretentious accusations! You have wasted enough time already!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed, the lady has offered a satisfactory explanation as to why she removed this glass. I think henceforth we can consider the matter to have no bearing on the case. Counsel for the Defence, are you in agreement?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, well... <thought>I don't know, really...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">If you want to pursue this matter further... ...you're going to need to show that it has some deeper significance.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, you're right. <thought>So she took the glass away in her handbag. If there's a deeper significance there, it's...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you ask me, it's the fact that she took the glass that has a deeper significance here.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Why do you think that?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Because! It's the property of the restaurant! It's not some harmless act of pilfering, like taking a bar of soap home from the public baths, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You...take soap from the public baths?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? No! I, I mean... Ahem! That isn't significant here...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's very significant! But this isn't the time or the place. There are more important things to concentrate on now. I think maybe you should reconsider your position, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh, sorry... I will.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well... I'm not really sure there is a deeper significance here at all.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You do get it, don't you? If you can't find a reason why this glass matters, you'll almost certainly be found guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... I knew you were going to say that.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And I presume you've got this, too? It's the fact that she took the glass away in her handbag. That's the deeper significance.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If I'd worked that out, I would have given it as my answer in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Think about it. The lady was carrying a handbag. It could have had almost anything inside it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So! It's time to reconsider your answer, Ryunosuke.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait! The lady put the glass in her handbag, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Yes. Do try to keep up. It's already been explained to the court that all English gentlewomen carry handbags for small items.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Let me see... A little while ago, Miss Brett stated the following... 'There are no pockets in my outfit. I have nowhere to hide a gun.' But! What she forgot to mention, was her handbag. In which it would be perfectly possible to conceal a gun!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well done, partner. I had a feeling you'd pick up on that, too.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What are you insinuating, you vile blackguard?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's really very simple. The gunshot was heard when the defendant picked up the gun from the restaurant floor. As he didn't fire that gun, we can deduce there must have been another firearm at the scene. The true murder weapon, if you will.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">You, you can't seriously be suggesting...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Inspector Hosonaga!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Did you or did you not search Miss Jezaille Brett's handbag on the day of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">No, sir, I did not.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>As I thought!</thought> In other words, another gun - the one that was actually used to kill the professor... ...could have been hidden in Miss Brett's handbag!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Nnn... NOOOOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What is the meaning of this, Inspector?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">The meaning of what, Prosecutor Auchi?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Why on earth did you not have the lady open her handbag and show you the contents at the time? Thanks to your bungling incompetence, now she has to endure these...uncomfortable accusations!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Brilliant work, partner! Now we have a chance to expose the real woman behind the mask!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you think so, Kazuma?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Ahem! ...Ahem! AHEM! ...AHEM! ...AHEM, AHEM! Well, what a sorry situation. Clearly you have no faith in the police.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">As I said, I did not search the lady's handbag after the shooting. Simply because...it was unnecessary.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Unnecessary in what way?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">I ought to thank the student lawyer, really. I have a piece of evidence here that I had completely forgotten about. This photographic print. This print is of a photograph that I thought would be prudent to take immediately after the shooting. As you can see, it clearly shows Miss Brett's handbag.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well I never! You can see right through to what's inside!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">That's right. Apparently, meshwork bags like these are the height of fashion in London at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm, so the contents are clearly visible.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Exactly. So there was no need to search the lady's handbag. If there had been a gun inside, it would have been immediately obvious.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh! </line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">As you can see, there's nothing to imply Miss Brett's guilt here. Thank you for helping to prove that, Naruhodo-san.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Uh... UWAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Inspector Hosonaga, you will submit that print as evidence at once!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Certainly, Your Excellency.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think you've had long enough to cross-examine the witness, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court has now been shown considerable evidence. As the photographic print just submitted into the Court Record appears to have no further significance... ...I am satisfied that there is no longer any room for doubt in this matter, and I must make my ruling.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Indeed. And there is only one logical conclusion. That the pathetic rookie slumped over the bench before us is the only possible perpetrator of this crime.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>No... Just when I thought I was beginning to turn things around... I'm in a worse situation than I was at the start!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Kazuma...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... I'm sorry, Ryunosuke.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Now that the cross-examination of the witness is over, there's no way to force the trial to continue.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! You, you mean, this is it...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Tsh huh huh! I must say, you put up quite a fight...for a rookie student. But the weak are meat, while the strong eat! You were wasting your time. There is no way to defeat true justice! A fact you can chew on to your heart's content...from the inside of your cell!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This can't be happening...! Am I really going to be found guilty of a crime that I didn't commit? And Kazuma... His dream of going to study in Great Britain will slip through his fingers.</thought> ......... Kazuma...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is there really... Is there really no chance now of turning this trial around?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You heard the judge. There's nothing about that last photograph the detective produced that we can contest. Which means...there's no basis on which we can argue for the trial to continue.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. I will now proceed immediately to the ruling.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">It seems we will be able to report to the British government on time after all!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">That smug little...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ryunosuke Naruhodo, having considered all of the evidence placed before me, I hereby find you-</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...Ryunosuke?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I don't think you can rule on this case yet!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">This amateurishness is getting tedious! When His Excellency deems that the trial is over, he gives his ruling. That is the most basic protocol of the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">This is blatant straw-clutching! Look at this photographic print! All it shows is the handbag the gentlewoman was carrying on the day in question. There can be no 'problem' with this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You'd better know what you're doing, Ryunosuke.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm... I understand your objection, Counsel. Certainly, the new evidence submitted by the detective has not undergone the court's scrutiny. However, I fail to see how we can glean any new information from this handbag. </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Ha! My thoughts exactly! Really, the prosecution is becoming tired of this rookie's desperate wheezes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, I am desperate! But this isn't a wheeze. There's something about this photograph which just doesn't seem right. If only I could put my finger on it...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, I will grant the defence one final opportunity.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But be warned that if I am unsatisfied by your response here, the trial will be over with immediate effect. Do I make myself clear?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, Your Excellency.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, take another look at the photographic print Inspector Hosonaga submitted before. You will identify for the court where in this print we see the 'significant detail' to which you have alluded!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What's significant is your inability to positively identify anything wrong with this picture at all!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I concur. And praise the prosecution for his quick-wittedness. </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I know it's the handbag that stands out in this picture. But you need to look further. Examine everything. Otherwise you might miss an important clue. Always try to see the whole, and don't be blinkered by individual details. I know you can do it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>If I could do it, then I wouldn't have pointed out the wrong part of the picture just now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, unfortunately, I must do as I promised.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Wait, Your Excellency! The court should give consideration to the fact that this man is an amateur! One more chance, please.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Well, I suppose he is just a callow student lawyer with little sense of protocol in these matters.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'm starting to feel insulted here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at this, here... There's a very unusual mark on the victim's wrist.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is true. It looks almost...like a burn of some description.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">...!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Dear me! I was pondering what new piffle you would come out with. A burn, you say? On the victim's wrist? Clearly that has nothing whatsoever to do with the magnificent lady's handbag!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Yes, that is a burn mark, you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Go on, Inspector.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">The police coroner also noticed it when he was performing the post-mortem examination. It was deemed unrelated to the cause of death, so he didn't note it in his report.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What did I tell you? In any case, we have no idea when the victim suffered this burn, do we? And no possible way of knowing, either.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The more I look at it, the more I find myself intrigued by the curious shape of this mark... However, as Prosecutor Auchi points out, unless a firm connection to the case can be shown... ...I cannot allow any further time to be spent on the precise details of this burn.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">[Foreign text].</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Excuse me, Your Excellency... It would seem Miss Brett has a lunch appointment with the dean and other university staff. She would like to know if she may be excused from the stand now.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Oh, of course, of course, dear lady! We shan't hold you up any longer! I'm quite sure His Excellency is about to give his final ruling anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What's your thinking on this, Ryunosuke? Do you believe this burn does have something to do with the case?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">To be honest, I'm not really sure. But if I don't keep pushing, then it's all over. So I was thinking I should keep digging and digging... in the hope that I might uncover something useful.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... Yes, you're right. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I am?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">If we can just link that burn to the case... If we can do that, we might be able to prise this shutting door back open again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Just give up, Counsel! You can't possibly hope to do that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. I'm afraid that without evidence, I can't allow you to pursue what is little more than conjecture.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">But if we had evidence? Evidence that irrefutably linked the burn on the victim's wrist to the case. Then you would allow it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I would, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">To tell the truth, I hadn't noticed that burn. But as soon as you pointed it out, what I did notice... ...was the colour draining from Miss Brett's face.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? <thought>I have to find some link between that burn and the case... This is the moment of truth. It's time to find some evidence that proves what that burn really means!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So then, the defence will now present its evidence to the court. The evidence that demonstrates an inextricable connection between the victim's burn and this trial!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Then explain to the court in five words or less what the nature of that connection is!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Erm, well, it's obviously, um...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Thank you. Five highly illuminating words.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">As I suspected, the rookie student is bluffing! Again!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You've been burned there yourself, Ryunosuke.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry... <thought>I do feel like I've seen the shape of that burn somewhere before, though...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Look through the Court Record again. Carefully, this time!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes... Yes, I will!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this, Counsel? Yet another print?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, Your Excellency. I believe photographic prints are an amazing invention. When we humans look at a scene, we miss things. But in a photograph, things we may have overlooked at the time are recorded forevermore.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Do hurry up, rookie! What are you trying to say? To inconvenience this poor lady any further really would be quite inexcusable.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Actually, we may need you to stay with us a little longer, if you don't mind...Miss Brett.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You see, it's very clearly visible in this other photograph. How did the victim come to have that unusually shaped burn on his wrist? The reason is recorded here forevermore!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">What? How?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">You can't fool me with your little bluffs, boy! If that's your game, then let's see how it plays out! Show the court exactly what you mean! What is it in this photograph that explains the reason for the victim's burn?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And...you don't think you could suffer a burn from this?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">This ludicrous response? Oh certainly, you could. Not that I expected any different...from a rookie like you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph! Perhaps my gavel can help clear the smoke from your mind, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'll, I'll try to get my head straight before that's necessary, Your Excellency.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It takes some skill to get something so wrong after you've got so much right already. But see if you can use one of your other skills this time. Otherwise...you'll have my sword to answer to!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I preferred the first half of that, when it sounded more like a compliment...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Dear me. Like I said...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">The, the beef steak?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Actually, the point is the metal plate the steak was served on.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The plate? Ah... AAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Your Excellency! Are you alright?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As you can see, there's an emblem on the plate. I would guess it's some sort of trademark of La Carneval.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The emblem on the plate... ...and the victim's burn... ...are exactly the same shape!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Aaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ryunosuke! You genius!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">You're spot on...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Which means... ...the victim must have suffered this burn while he was present at the restaurant!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">But... But even if that is the case... ...we can't know if it happened on the day in question or not. It could've been the day before! Or the day before that! It most likely happened at some other, unrelated time!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...um... Hm...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Sadly, Prosecutor Auchi, the chances of that are extremely slim.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thanks...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Why?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The outline of the burn is clearly discernible. Such a serious injury would have caused quite a commotion in the restaurant. Wouldn't you agree, Inspector Hosonaga?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">I can't imagine having missed such a terrible disaster, certainly.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">But, but...</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">I would say, looking at the picture of the wound, that it wasn't suffered very long ago. And, although it's not a particularly large burn, it's extremely well defined, as the defence just pointed out. This was no mild burn, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Can you be more specific, Inspector?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Well, let's see... ...if the plate was at around ninety degrees centigrade, a burn like that would have taken around three seconds.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's inconceivable that the victim wouldn't have let out a scream of pain, then.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">I've been investigating at the restaurant for several weeks already, but I've not heard anyone scream at all. As the head waiter of La Carneval, I can testify to that without hesitation.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">But you... You're a detective, not a waaaiteeer!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And yet Inspector Hosonaga never heard the professor scream. Not on that day, or any before it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right. And the strange thing is... ...on the day he was shot, I didn't hear him cry out, either.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What are you suggesting?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, if the professor had carelessly laid his wrist on the plate for anything like three seconds that day...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That would be beyond careless, I think, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...then the rest of us in the restaurant - myself, the sergeant and the old antiques dealer... All of us would, without any question, have heard him scream. Wouldn't you agree, Prosecutor Auchi?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Hm? Um, well... Yes, I suppose...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So the question is... ...why didn't a single person hear Dr Wilson scream?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I, I almost don't believe it! Ryunosuke, do you think...? </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Can it really be true? I never dreamt we'd arrive at a conclusion like this, but... I'm starting to think that maybe... ...we've been led into a terrible trap!</thought> There's only one explanation I can think of to make sense of this apparent impossibility. On the day in question, when he suffered the burn to his wrist, Dr Wilson...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, the professor, being as absent-minded as usual... ...was unaware of his hand falling onto the piping-hot plate, and didn't even notice the burn happening!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You didn't even know the professor, and yet here you are labelling him as a bumbling scatterbrain.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">How about I hold your wrist on a hot plate and we see how YOUR bumbling scatterbrain copes? Perhaps the scream you let out will wake you up a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, it's nice that there's this frankness developing between us, partner.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Don't call me 'partner' after coming out with nonsense like that! This is a critical moment. It may very well be our only chance to turn things in our favour. So come on, Ryunosuke. You can do it. Or rather... You have to do it! You're the only one who can!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, the professor, with his tendency to nod off... ...was asleep when his hand fell onto the piping-hot plate, and didn't even notice the burn happening!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You didn't even know the professor, and yet here you are labelling him as a dim-witted dozer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">How about I hold your wrist on a hot plate and we see if YOU can sleep through it? Perhaps the scream you let out will wake you up a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, it's nice that there's this frankness developing between us, partner.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Don't call me 'partner' after coming out with nonsense like that! This is a critical moment. It may very well be our only chance to turn things in our favour. So come on, Ryunosuke. You can do it. Or rather... You have to do it! You're the only one who can!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No man could remain silent while his wrist was burning on a piping-hot plate for three whole seconds. That's clearly impossible. Apart from in one particular situation...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel, are you suggesting...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, it's only possible...if the man was already dead.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">A-Already...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Dead?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Knowing what we know now, it's the only possible explanation. When the beef steak was brought to Dr Wilson's table that day... ...the professor...was already dead!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">That's... That's... ...madneeessssss!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">That's right! That's absolutely right, Your Excellency. This, this is just another ridiculous ploy by the rookie student! But clearly, he has no grasp of the facts!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">No, Prosecutor Auchi, it's you who has no grasp of the facts.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">I beg your pardon?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">As soon as it became apparent that the victim had suffered that burn while at the restaurant... ...this whole case was turned upside-down. Or have you not grasped that yet?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Urrr... Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Your Excellency! The court MUST hear from this witness again. If it's true, as we now believe, that the victim was already dead before the gunshot was heard... ...it's highly likely that Miss Brett knows something about it!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Incredible... I certainly didn't anticipate this twist of events. I'm sorry to say, Miss Brett... ...that you will have to forget your luncheon engagement. </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">B-But, Your Excellency!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The justice system in our country may be in its infancy... ...but rest assured, all reasonable doubt must be dispelled before I am prepared to pass judgement. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you, Your Excellency.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What was that smile?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brett">Yes, of course... I mean- I'd be delighted to help. Especially if it helps relations between my country and yours.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Ah... Miss, Miss Brett... You...speak Japanese?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Well, of course I do. I am studying in your country, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But...then...why have you been speaking through an interpreter until now?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">My mother tongue - the Queen's English - is the most refined and elegant language in the world. As a gentlewoman, I try to avoid speaking in your vulgar tone as much as possible.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">.........</line>
<line speaker="Brett">But it seems the men in this land possess none of the chivalrous virtues of English gentlemen. So I can see that I shall have to lower myself to communicating with you all on your own level.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Oh... Ah...well... You are the epitome of a true English gentlewoman! We are truly honoured by this... This lavish consideration you so graciously afford us!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......... I see. In that case, Miss Brett, I will now ask you to testify in your own words... ...about the events leading up to the death of the victim, Dr Wilson!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So, we're finally going to hear her own words on the matter. Things are getting interesting, Ryunosuke!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Unfortunately, I have no idea when the poor man burnt his wrist like that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...That most captivating and beautiful testimony will go down in the Supreme Court's history. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Easy does it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brett">I hope that this is the last time I will have to sully my lips with the coarse tones of your unbecoming tongue. Oh.... Forgive me. I do hope I haven't insulted anyone.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Not at all, not at all! It is a delight merely to hear you speak, dear lady! And it seems very clear from your testimony, that this boorish talk of the victim's burn is utterly irrelevant.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">I will be speaking to your country's Minister of Justice about what has happened here today.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">The...Minister of Justice...?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">May that irritating little bully of a student be given the harshest punishment possible! ...Amen.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh? ...Um, thanks? <thought>Was, was that a prayer then?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well you'll have to forgive the irritation, Miss Brett, and put up with a cross-examination now. </line>
<line speaker="Brett">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I expect you've noticed that this 'little bully of a student', as you put it... ...doesn't miss much.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sure I don't need to remind you, Counsel, that this will be your final cross-examination in this trial. If you fail to demonstrate any problems with this witness's testimony... ...I will be ruling on the case immediately. Is that clear?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Yes, Your Excellency.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then you may proceed with the cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Unfortunately, I have no idea when the poor man burnt his wrist like that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Do you think so? Let me ask you something...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Ever since I arrived at this courtroom, and even still now... ...the fly on those unsightly black trousers of yours has been wide open. You can't not have noticed...can you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh? Wha...? Aaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Haha, what fun! You hadn't realised!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">The dear lady is absolutely right!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">As your friend, you've embarrassed me as well as yourself, Ryunosuke.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why didn't you tell me...?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Dr Wilson was a true English gentleman. He chose honourable silence over a vulgar scream. ...Can your tiny brains imagine such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Oh yes! I think my tiny brain can!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Brett">When the waiter brought my steak, the professor and I raised our glasses in a toast.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Dr Wilson was only permitted to drink water at that time, if you remember. Which explains why he ordered that drink. Correct, waiter?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Exactly as you say, sir. Although...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Al-Although...?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Whether or not the professor actually drank any of the water when I delivered the steak to the table... I'm afraid I don't remember that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm...</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Damn you...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Ah! I have enough English to understand that, at least! For the benefit of others in the court, it means, 'bless you'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Um, I think it means the exact opposite...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brett">Anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Brett">As far as I've heard, the post-mortem report showed no other possible cause of death besides the gunshot.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Brett">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Luckily for all of us, a little burn on the wrist isn't going to kill us. And as there were no other signs of trauma on the victim's body to indicate some other cause of death... ...it can only have been the bullet from your gun that put an end to this innocent man's life!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But it doesn't make any sense! The burn must have happened straight away, when the plate was first brought to the table by the waiter.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, that's true. If it had cooled even slightly, it wouldn't have been able to make a burn like that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And if the victim burnt his wrist on the hot plate as soon as it was brought out from the kitchen... ...then he must already have been dead at that point!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">And yet! The fact is that the victim was killed by a gunshot to the chest! Until you're able to show the court evidence to disprove that, this is a complete waste of time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I concur. Prosecutor Auchi is right.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Argh!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Brett">If there's some other way a man's life can been [sic] taken without leaving a trace, please, do show me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Brett">If someone is shot, or strangled, or stabbed or thrown from a height... However a person's life is taken, there are always telltale traces on the body.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Quite right, dear lady. And as our police force has thoroughly examined the body of the deceased, there can be no doubt. Isn't that right, Inspector Hosonaga?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">As I've said, I always aim for a flawless investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Hm... There would be physical traces with all those causes of death, that's true. But maybe there's some other way of killing someone that doesn't leave a mark...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brett">If - heaven forbid - you doubt me, young man... ...you're going to have to tell everyone how exactly you think the professor did lose his life. Otherwise, I'm afraid your argument falls rather flat, doesn't it? </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Oh no, perish the thought! Calling such a sweet young lady's innocence into question?! On my honour, I, Taketsuchi Auchi, will cut down any who dare cast such aspersions!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Hm... A way of killing someone that leaves no trace...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">We need some evidence to back us up here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Brett">But of course...this country's inferior investigative techniques probably wouldn't pick up on it anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Brett">In the lands of the great British Empire, the police store everything found at a crime scene for later examination. But in this country, you investigate once, and that's the end of it. ...Isn't that so?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Quite right! La Carneval is open for business as usual today, just days after the incident!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Exactly. Which means that even if the investigation takes a different direction, vital evidence may be lost. It doesn't even occur to your naive detectives to try to preserve the crime scene. I'm...trying to be as tactful about this as I can, you understand.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Haha! A killer blow! The lady is as formidable as she is beautiful!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Amazing! He's actually admitting our police may be flawed. Perhaps Prosecutor Auchi is finally starting to see sense.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I very much doubt that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Still...there's something about what Miss Brett just said... There was a moment before, when something didn't seem quite right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Brett">In the lands of the great British Empire, the police store everything found at a crime scene for later examination. But in this country, you investigate once, and that's the end of it. ...Isn't that so?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Quite right! La Carneval is open for business as usual today, just days after the incident!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Exactly. Which means that even if the investigation takes a different direction, vital evidence may be lost. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, there it is again! The detective's reaction is just the same as before. Why...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Up until now, the detective has been in the stand with Miss Brett as her interpreter. But things are very different now. For this testimony, the detective is just listening to what the Englishwoman has to say. This could be a golden opportunity.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">When people are actually testifying, they're usually very careful not to let anything slip. However... When they're listening to someone else speak, you'll find they often let their guard down.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're right... <thought>Look at him! He's lost in his own thoughts!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's time to pursue the man and his train of thought!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry? Pursue?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I'll explain how to do it now, Ryunosuke. It's all to do with the witness marker.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What marker?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">At the moment, we're focused on Miss Brett, who's the person actually making the current statement. But by moving the marker left and right with [D-pad / A D], you can turn your attention to other people in the stand. While you're looking at the other witnesses, you'll be able to 'Pursue' them with [A / Space]. If you can catch the person at just the right time, you might uncover some new information to pursue. If you ever notice a strange atmosphere amongst the people on the stand, take a good look around. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright then, so first I should move the marker across with [D-pad / A D], and focus on the detective. Then Pursue him with [A / Space], and see what's on his mind! <thought>Here we go...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">GYAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH! What the...?! What's the meaning of this?! Ahem! ...Ahem! AHEM, AHEM! </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I'm so sorry. I, I didn't mean to shock you. <thought>He really was lost in his thoughts! Deeply!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It looked like you were thinking something just now, Inspector. Perhaps having heard what the lady next to you had to say...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If there's something you'd like to say, please... share it with the court!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What is the meaning of this? It's the delightful Englishwoman who's testifying at the moment. If you can't find fault with her testimony, then the cross-examination should be over. Immediately! </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...is, is that how it works?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Absolutely not.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The detective is in the stand! Which makes him a valid witness.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes! Not to mention the fact that he's intimately involved in the case!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Inspector Hosonaga... </line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you have something to add? In relation to the statement just made by Miss Brett?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">......... Well, yes... If you don't mind, I would like to speak.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">The lady is right. Our country's police practices are not as modern as those used in Great Britain. Which is why! ...I...Satoru Hosonaga! Always strive to make every investigation I'm involved in flawless!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you really mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">I'll tell you what I mean! I won't have evidence lacking on my watch! I'm not afraid to take everything I can from the scene of the crime. It's preserving evidence, you see. I don't care if they call me a crime scene thief! I'm not ashamed of what I've done! Ahem! Ahem! Ahem, ahem! </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A crime scene thief...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well, it looks like the lady's remarks touched a nerve there.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Take this, for example!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is, is that...?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">This is the bottle of carbonated water that I took to the victim's table on the day in question. And yes, it's lost all of its fizz, having been opened three days ago now. But it WAS carbonated water! I don't care what anyone says!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, there's some left in the bottle! I can see it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">One day our police force will be among the best in the world! The time is coming! I guarantee it! Ahem! ...Ahem! Ahem, ahem!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can't say I condone the witness's actions, but I do understand the sentiment. The court will accept the glass bottle of water as evidence! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm...  Miss Brett... Can you confirm this is indeed the bottle from which you drank on the day of the victim's death?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">...Yes. It was that bottle.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What was that about? She seemed to avert her eyes when she answered the judge's question...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Counsel, you may resume the cross-examination. And the inspector will kindly control his...fervour.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">...Ahem!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The label is written in a foreign language that I don't recognise. Do you know what it says, Kazuma?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I think it's French. This must be very expensive water.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, but what does it say? That's what I was asking.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Then go to France and ask.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You could just say that you don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So this carbonated water is the last drink Dr Wilson ever had...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It looks like there's a little left in the bottle. Although it's just plain water now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You know, I've been sweating so much, I'm absolutely parched! I'll just have a sip of this to keep me going.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">No, Ryunosuke! You can't do that. For one thing, that's evidence. You can't go drinking evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh no, you're right. We don't know what might be inside, do we?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...You never cease to amaze me, Ryunosuke. In more ways than one.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>I wonder... Could there be anything in this water?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What's the matter? You've gone quiet all of a sudden.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think I might have just worked something out. An interesting possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What do you think, Ryunosuke?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't know... I think this could be hard work. She can speak Japanese brilliantly, but she doesn't seem to want to say very much.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The more she says, the more she's likely to give away. This Englishwoman knows that only too well. She's...quite formidable.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Dr Wilson's burn tells us something, I'm sure. I need to use this cross-examination to find out what.</thought> First things first, I'm going to press her on everything she's said and try to make her blurt something out!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What is it, Kazuma? What are you thinking?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Oh, um...don't worry. It's nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What do you think, Ryunosuke?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I think it's going terribly! No matter how much I press her, I'm not turning up any new information.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, as I suspected... She's a tough witness. We need to find a way to break her testimony, or the cross-examination will be over. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but that would mean... <thought>I have to find a way! There must be some clue somewhere to help us find a chink in her armour!</thought> ......... Kazuma...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What, Ryunosuke?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There IS one thing I noticed. Something that's been bothering me.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Bothering you? You mean...about Miss Brett?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Actually, no. About the person standing next to her... Inspector Hosonaga.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The detective?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. He seemed to react a little strangely to Miss Brett's last statement. I was wondering if it might be significant. If it might present an opening, maybe.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... Alright, I have an idea. Try pressing her on that last statement one more time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you think so, but...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">But this time, instead of targeting the woman herself... ...let's see what we can get out of the detective. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright then... <thought>I wonder what Kazuma's thinking. I'll find out soon enough, I suppose. Once I press Miss Brett on her last statement again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">New evidence! Excellent work, Ryunosuke. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I never even thought of pursuing another witness over the current witness's statements. That was a great idea of yours, Kazuma!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well, it was all thanks to you noticing that the detective had reacted strangely to what the lady said.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'd never have guessed he had all that bubbling away under the surface!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">To be honest, you keep surprising me at every turn.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Oh... Never mind. So we know that Dr Wilson was killed at around the time the steak was brought to his table. And by some means that left no physical trace on his body. If we could just demonstrate how it was done...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well, I do have one idea about that. About how the professor was killed. Maybe I should just present the evidence and see what happens...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is this? The bottle of water? </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Actually, there is one method of killing a man without leaving a trace that comes to mind...</line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Obviously, I'm referring...to poison.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Poison?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">On the day of his death, we know that Dr. Wilson drank from this bottle of carbonated water. Could it be...that there was poison inside?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Could it be that the professor actually died after taking a sip from his glass?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And on that day, who was sitting at the same table as the professor and able to slip the poison into his drink? There's only person [sic] who could possibly have done it! Jezaille Brett! It was you! </line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">This is outrageous! To suggest such a thing without a scrap of evidence! You little rookie imbecile! Have you even considered the delicate situation our country finds itself in now?! Have you forgotten that we have only just signed an accord of friendship with the British Empire?! Have you even the vaguest inkling that your rash accusations could jeopardise the entire treaty?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">This is not a political arena. This is a trial to determine one individual's guilt with respect to one crime.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The fact that this woman is British makes no difference. We are here to determine the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Kghrrr...</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Ahem. If I may...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">I will silence you forever for this disgraceful attack on the lovely young-</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Brett:</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Of, of course... ...dear ladyyyyyyyy!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Where did that come from? She, she just snapped!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brett">I'm afraid I may have spoken unfairly before. I offer my most humble apologies.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sorry, my lady, to what are you referring?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">I described your police force as 'inferior'. But no matter how inferior they may be, you still investigated this particular point thoroughly, I believe? The bottle, I mean, Inspector. And whether it contained poison or not.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">......... Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You, you did?!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Have you forgotten what my guiding principle is already? I strive for a flawless investigation every time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't believe it...!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Naturally we tested the inside of the bottle and its contents.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And...? What did you find, Inspector?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">I ordered tests for every toxin that's available in this country at the present time. We could find no trace of poison of any description in the bottle of carbonated water, Your Excellency.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What? Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">The tests were meticulously carried out by the Chief Coroner himself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No... NOOOOOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">I'm very grateful to all you Japanese. You've successfully established my complete innocence in this horrid affair. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">But, but of course, dear lady! The pleasure was all ours!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>I was so sure...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">This...can't be right! Everything falls into place if he was poisoned...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, Counsel. I think that cross-examination has clarified everything. As the prosecution have asserted, a shot to the chest from this gun is the only conceivable cause of death. Furthermore... The accused, who by his own admission was holding this weapon, is the only possible culprit!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'm done for...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court wishes to apologise for the great inconvenience this has caused you, Miss Brett.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Oh no... I'm just glad the matter is resolved.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Before proceeding, I must ask the counsel for the defence... ...do you have any further new evidence to present the court at this point?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Kazuma?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... I'm sorry, Ryunosuke. I have nothing more.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Well, if you'll excuse me now, I really must be leaving...</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="???">Please, wait!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>Isn't that...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is the meaning of this?</line>
<line speaker="???">Forgive me for intruding on court proceedings, Your Excellency.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Susato Mikotoba, judicial assistant to the defence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Mikotoba...? In my darkest hour, with nowhere left to go, she appeared like a bolt of lightning. And in her hand...she carried a small package, wrapped in a furoshiki cloth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well? I understand you are the judicial assistant to the defence, but why this sudden ingress into my courtroom? </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Ha! A judicial assistant? And a woman, no less! The rules state...that females are not permitted into this court of law other than to testify!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I fully understand. I ask only for five minutes of time. I have some vital evidence that I must hand over to the defence.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Hah! You're too late, little girl! This trial has already been concluded!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Five minutes. I will not allow a moment more.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">But...Your Excellency!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I am most grateful.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, who exactly are you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm sorry, there's no time. Please, simply accept this for now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What is it? A report about something... Written in English...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's Jezaille Brett's research.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! The Englishwoman's?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">After the trial resumed earlier, I hurried back to the university. I went to Dr Wilson's laboratory in the medical faculty and...borrowed this paper.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Oh yes, that's right. Miss Brett was studying under the professor, wasn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...does this research - whatever it is - have something to do with the case?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm afraid I don't know. I haven't been able to listen to the proceedings of the trial myself. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Oh...no, of course not.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">'Special Characteristics of Curare and its Effects on Human Subjects'... Interesting.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Curare'? What's that? <thought>I've never heard that word before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Time's up. The prosecution demands the immediate removal of this female trespasser from the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">There was too little time for me to read it in detail. But I've summarised what I could on a note just inside the cover. If you think it could be valuable, please cast your eye over it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is wonderful. Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Goodbye, then. And good luck.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You have had long enough, Counsel. We cannot detain our English guest any longer.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I ask the prosecution and the defence now one last time... ...does either side have any further evidence to present to the court? I presume not, but...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">The prosecution has made its case convincingly enough already. Nothing more to add, Your Excellency!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ryunosuke, we're out of options here. This really is our very last chance.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I know. Your Excellency! The defence does have new evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......... Hm, that look... The unyielding stare of a true Japanese warrior... Well,  Miss Brett?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Yes, Your Excellency?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you wouldn't mind, perhaps you could grace us with your presence a little longer?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">It's a delightful invitation. But I'm afraid... ...it's not so very long until tea time. I'll have to politely decline-</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Forgive me, Miss Brett, it seems I wasn't clear. I realise it was phrased as a question. However... ...I must ask you to treat that as an order.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">......... I've said it many times before, but... The Japanese language makes no sense.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">My apologies, dear lady. So, Counsel... What is this new evidence that demands the court's attention?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! <thought>It seems I've chosen poorly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brett">In that case, I'll take my leave of you now and go for some afternoon tea. In civilised English society, tea time is an essential. We'd surely die without it.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Take your tea time now, Ryunosuke, and you'll surely die in a minute yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh, I know...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You know there's only one piece of evidence the court hasn't seen yet! Don't squander this chance! Don't let our judicial assistant's great efforts go to waste.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright! I'm sorry. <thought>Let me think this through...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Jezaille Brett... ...we understand you were studying under Dr Wilson at Yumei University. Doing research.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Research, by sheer coincidence, perhaps...into a deadly poison. </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Poison?! Where are you going with this, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">A toxin known as curare, Your Excellency. Even the slightest amount of this deadly poison entering the body leads to instant death.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What, what complete and utter nonsense! Cu-curare, you say? I've never even heard of it!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You wouldn't have done.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I mean that you wouldn't have heard of curare before for one very simple reason... It doesn't exist in our country.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">It doesn't exist...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Correct. Which means... ...no matter what tests the police can do for toxins, they'd never identify curare. Why? Because there IS no test available here that can identify the presence of this highly deadly poison! </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Whaaaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! Counsel, does this deadly poison truly exist?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">According to this report authored by the visiting research student from England... ...curare has long been used by the tribespeople of South America as a poison to lace their arrows. It seems that it's reasonably well known among European doctors and scientists.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">To, to lace their arrows...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The report states that it is produced from the extract of a tree that grows deep in the Amazonian jungle. And it was first brought back to Europe at the turn of the century by explorers. It claims that animals shot by arrows laced with curare suffer instant death. Doesn't that about sum it up, Miss Brett? </line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Trumpery! These aspersions are utter trumpery! To start with! If the victim had been administered some of this so-called deadly poison... ...he would have been squirming and writhing in pain and the other diners would have surely noticed!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm, that's true. What do you say to that, Inspector?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Obviously I would have noticed a disturbance like that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Hm, I don't remember anything like that, either. I didn't notice the professor being in any kind of pain...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">According to this, however...it's the other way around.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What do you mean, 'the other way around'?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The very fact that the victim didn't show any visible signs of distress... ...is evidence that curare was used.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Explain yourself, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The moment this toxin enters a person's system, it causes instant paralysis. In other words, afflicted victims lose all strength and are completely unable to move. Even if they were in total agony, there would be no visible signs of pain at all.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">How terrible...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Obviously, if a man lost all strength in his muscles, he'd collapse on the floor. But with a chair under him for support, as Dr Wilson did, the effects could go largely unnoticed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But I don't follow, Kazuma. That's just paralysis. I thought the poison caused instant death.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... The full explanation is extremely unpleasant. The poison causes immediate paralysis, as I said, leaving the victim unable to move. But after a short time, the paralysis is so severe, it causes the muscles that control respiration to fail. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Respiration...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In other words, the actual cause of death...is suffocation. And all the while, the victim is conscious and aware. Just unable to move.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">That's...hideous... </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">To the observer, it would look almost like the victim was slipping peacefully into an endless sleep. But for the victim himself, his final moments would be a living hell. That is the true nature of this deadly curare poison.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And you're suggesting that this bottle, Counsel... ...actually contains this terrifying poison? </line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">This, this... This is all very convenient, isn't it? A hitherto unknown poison for which there is no means of testing? What a happy tale for the defence!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Ahem. If I may... </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">All these 'facts'... You think you're so clever! But you must be taught some manner-</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Brett:</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Of, of course... ...dear ladyyyyyyyy! </line>
<line speaker="Brett">......... So. This is how you Japanese behave, is it? </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? </line>
<line speaker="Brett">You steal another's honest hard work and then announce the results as if YOU discovered them! I'm appalled! What a loathsome act!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well, Miss Brett, the feeling is mutual. </line>
<line speaker="Brett">Whatever do you mean? </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Capitalising on the unfortunate circumstances of an innocent man to frame him for a heinous crime? That really is a loathsome act. Wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Enough of this! I, for one, refuse to accept it! The idea of some poison that doesn't even exist in the great Empire of Japan is...is...breaking the rules!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">...Hah hah hah... </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's so funny?!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Oh, excuse me. Your...Excellency... </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes, Miss Brett?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">May I borrow that bottle for a moment, please? </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Um, well... Yes, I don't see, um...why not. </line>
<line speaker="Brett">Don't get too big for your boots, you insignificant little island boys. </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Sorry? </line>
<line speaker="Brett">To an Englishwoman such as myself, this whole affair is a farcical comedy. Your little police games, and these foolish courtroom antics... It's laughable, really. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">But I'm getting bored of it all now. It's time for the games to end. ...Cheers!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What! Wha-What are you doing?!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Hm... No sparkle left at all. How appropriate for this shabby affair. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Goodness... Whatever is the matter? You all look quite stunned. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So...no curare... 'The bottle was clean,' is that what you're saying? </line>
<line speaker="Brett">Hahahaha... You look quite incredulous, little boy. But of course...that's the simple truth. Thank you for presenting the findings of my research so concisely here in this grand venue. Most kind.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Grrr...</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Thank you, waiter. Now then, Your Excellency... </line>
<line speaker="Judge">......... Ah! Um, yes, Miss Brett? </line>
<line speaker="Brett">I should like to be excused now, please. I think I've given more than enough of my time...for the furtherance of friendship between our countries. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, yes, dear lady. We are most gratified with all the assistance you have given. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">This doesn't make sense... There had to have been poison in that bottle! So how...? How did she...? How did she swallow a whole glass and live to tell the tale?! I don't understand it... </line>
<line speaker="Brett">Well, I suppose if nothing else, this little Far Eastern charade... ...will make for interesting conversation at the next party I attend in London.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>There, there has to have been poison in that bottle... doesn't there...? But there can't have been...because otherwise she would have keeled over dead... Come on, Ryunosuke! We have all the clues now. That bottle of water...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As I thought! There IS no poison in that bottle! </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What? Why, Ryunosuke? </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Isn't it obvious? If there was poison in there, she'd be dead by now! </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... Sometimes, your unadulterated naivety really astounds me. But sometimes, it's in need of a good staining...until it's as dark as your uniform in the ways of the world!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Oh, is THAT what this colour is supposed to represent...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That was a guileless ending to a promising line of enquiry, Counsel. For which you will be penalised. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... <thought>This whole trial is poisoned...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The culprit did put curare poison into Dr Wilson's carbonated water! I... The defence refuses to change its position! </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You're serious? </line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Fool! Are you blind? There is no possible way that bottle could contain poison! I mean, we just saw- </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Brett drinking the water from it? </line>
<line speaker="Brett">That's right. Which rather complicates your argument, I think. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And I believe that 'complication' can be explained! </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">How, exactly? </line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I need to think through all the things that don't quite add up here. One by one. I'm sure the answer is in the evidence we have in the Court Record somewhere. It has to be!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. If the defence truly intends to assert this claim... </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...then I must ask you to support the assertion with evidence. What explains how the witness was able to consume this supposedly poisoned water unscathed?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...is the only real source of complication in this case. You'll have to think harder than that, Defendant! </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry, Your Excellency. I'll try to find some better supporting evidence. </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You're making this complication more complicated than it needs to be. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright, I'll do my best to find an answer that fits the facts... </line>
<line speaker="Judge">If the defence - sorry, the wretched accused - truly intends to assert this claim... </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The answer to this riddle...is right here in Miss Brett's own research report!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn> </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">That's not a valid explanation! </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">After all... ...we don't speak English! That report is utter gibberish! This impudent young scoundrel is trying to ridicule the court, Your Excellency!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'm not trying to ridicule anyone... Honest. I'm just reading Susato-san's notes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I concur. This report is too extensive to be considered in its entirety by the court. You will direct us to the pertinent section, Counsel. Which section of the report reveals the alleged answer to this riddle?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's written right here in the synopsis! ...I think. </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Oh really? Go on... </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...it's a synopsis, so... So it's bound to contain lots of vague statements that I really hope are going to help me out here!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">You'll have to do better than that! I shudder to think how we'll fare in the twentieth century if we're led by the likes of you!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, yes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ryunosuke... </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm? What? </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Read properly. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Thanks for the concise advice. <thought>Something that explains how the Englishwoman could have taken curare with no ill effects... I'd better reread her research paper and see if I can spot anything.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Hah! You don't have any more of a clue about that English tome than I do! It's completely intractable.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's written right here under 'Practical Applications'! ...I think. </line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Oh really? Go on... </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...think about it! You want to know how the poison can be drunk without it taking effect. That's a practical application of, um...the poison's use as a drink...maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">You'll have to do better than that! I shudder to think how we'll fare in the twentieth century if we're led by the likes of you!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, yes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ryunosuke... </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm? What? </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Read properly. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Thanks for the concise advice. <thought>Something that explains how the Englishwoman could have taken curare with no ill effects... I'd better reread her research paper and see if I can spot anything.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Hah! You don't have any more of a clue about that English tome than I do! It's completely intractable.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We've been hearing a lot about this curare poison. And it's left me curious about something...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, it sounds as though indigenous hunters have been using this poison for years and years... ...to lace the heads of the arrows that they shoot at whatever prey they're hunting.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So we've been led to believe, yes. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And...the point of hunting is to catch prey to eat.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Get to the point, please! </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...if they were to use these laced arrows... ...doesn't that mean there would be traces of poison left in the prey the hunters were going to eat? </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes! Good point! </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So surely the hunters wouldn't want to eat their prey, would they? Because then they'd be eating poison.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious, Counsel! No, that would be madness!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But I actually found the answer to that conundrum in this research paper here. Under 'Special Characteristics', it says this: 'The poison starts to work after entering the body through a wound.'</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Through a wound, you say? I see, that makes sense.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. The mention of that particular detail seemed a little strange to me, though.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But it all makes sense when you interpret what's written like this: When curare enters the body through an open wound, it has terrifying poisonous effects. However... ...when it enters the body via the mouth, it has no poisonous effects whatsoever!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Brett! You authored this research! You knew curare's special characteristics! And you knew! ...That you could make a spectacle of drinking that water without any danger to yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">......... You...meddling...little... ...rapSCALLIOOON!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well, Ryunosuke, it turns out... ...you're an even better lawyer than I thought you'd be.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? <thought>Me...? A lawyer...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">All, all this poison talk is fascinating, I'm sure... But I fail to see how it possibly-</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Brett:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What are you trying to say?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Your schoolboyish logic has a fatal flaw.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sch-Schoolboyish?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Flaw?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">As even your brain has managed to deduce, curare is safe to ingest. It seems likely that its effects are neutralised by the acidic nature of the gastric succus.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, yes, well...of course! <thought>Gas trick suckers? What are they?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brett">So, if this lethal poison is completely harmless when drunk... ...the professor wouldn't have died when he swallowed it...would he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">That's...right...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">That's basic science. Science that even a schoolboy should be able to understand, no?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in court! Order! The logic holds. If the lady and the professor drank the same poison, they would be affected in the same way.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Are... Are you trying to suggest-</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Yes! This curare poison is completely irrelevant to the case on trial!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">That's right. Surely even a little cockroach like you could understand something as simple as that!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>What is this, welling up inside me...? I've never felt like this before. It's a sort of conviction to break down all the discrepancies... It's so intense. Almost rage-like... And more than anything else, it's an animalistic desire... to take down my prey!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't think so, Miss Jezaille Brett!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">How... How dare you use that tone with me?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You know very well that there is no fatal flaw here. You know exactly why, even though both you and the victim swallowed the same poison... ...you are alive, but Dr Wilson is dead!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel, I'm sure I don't need to remind you... You must provide compelling evidence. As we now know that this poison is completely harmless when ingested... ...why would Dr Wilson alone have been killed by the curare?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Listen, Ryunosuke... There's no need to overthink this. We know that curare's toxic effects only come into play when the poison enters the body via a wound.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right, so that can only mean...that when Dr Wilson drank his glass of water... ...he must have had a wound somewhere that let the poison in.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So we need some evidence that would prove the professor had a wound inside his mouth. Ah! Of course...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As Miss Brett so readily pointed out, she drank the same water as the professor. However...there was a fundamental and fatal difference between the two diners.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A fatal difference?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The toxic effects of curare are only felt when the poison enters the body through an open wound. So, for a healthy person with no injuries, drinking it is completely harmless. But... ...what if there was a wound inside the mouth of the person drinking the poisoned water?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Inside...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. Like the wound you might have... ...if you had just been to the dentist and had a tooth extracted, for example.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">AAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHH!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Brett! You've acknowledged many times in your testimony already... ...that you were well aware of Dr Wilson's dental appointment that day.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So that's it... You used that knowledge to orchestrate this...</line>
<line speaker="Brett">......... Heh...heh...heh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Is, is she...? ...laughing?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brett">I don't like to repeat myself, but honestly, I can't resist. These childish courtroom games and your half-baked arguments are all so puerile. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What, what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Don't worry, little schoolboy, you'll find out soon enough. You see, when you leave vital evidence lying around, you never know what might happen to it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">I mean, it could just...slip. Oh dear, how careless of me. I'm afraid some crucial evidence may have just been tragically destroyed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">N... NOOOOOOOOOOOO!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Officer! What are you waiting for?! Collect up as much of the water from that broken bottle as possible! At once!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">You're wasting your time. This delightful carpet under my feet here was a gift from the British Empire. I assure you, it will soak up the water beautifully. You have neither the technology nor the presence of mind to recover it. Ah ha ha ha hah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How could you?! You... You won't get away with this!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">You can thump the bench and shout as much as you like, little boy. But I'm afraid we'll never know now, will we? If there really was poison in the bottle...or not.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You...</line>
<line speaker="Brett">And let us not forget... ...we still have some very compelling evidence left intact. Isn't that right, Counsel for the Prosecution?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Oh, of course, of course! You're referring to this photographic print, I presume, dear lady?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">That's right. And really, looking at this photograph, it's as clear as day, isn't it? The poor professor was sitting with his back to me. So of course the only person who could have shot him from the front...is the little schoolboy.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">No! You killed the victim that day. Using curare. And then, in order to frame Ryunosuke Naruhodo for the crime... ...you waited until he picked up the pistol you'd arranged for him to find on the floor... ...before you shot the professor's dead body in the chest with your own hidden gun! Then, in the confusion that followed, all you had to do was turn the dead professor and his chair around. You see? You had every opportunity to commit this crime!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Heh...heh...heh... What a wonderful imagination you have, young man.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">A hidden gun, you say? And I shot the professor's dead body, did I? Well, I'm terribly sorry, but...you don't have a shred of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Exactly! And as you have nothing to support your wild claims, the prosecution's stance remains unchanged. The victim, Dr John H. Wilson, was killed by a gunshot to the chest... ...delivered in cold blood by the accused, Ryunosuke Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This is unbelievable! How can this be happening?! We had her! But now... Is she really going to get away with it? The way she destroyed that evidence was obscene!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ryunosuke!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">We've come this far, but now... Now you're the only one who can finish it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">We've lost a vital piece of evidence, it's true. So if there are any clues left for us to use now... ...they must be in your head!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>In...my head?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You told me before that your powers of observation were the one thing you could really depend upon.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well yes, that's true, but... <thought>But I didn't manage to notice that this woman was a foreigner with a swan on her head...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So think back again now. Try to remember every last detail about the scene that day. Everything you saw. Everything you felt. Every colour, every smell...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I've been over it a thousand times in my head. There can't be anything more. At least, that's what I've been telling myself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Let's not forget that a lot has changed since the start of this trial. Your memories of that day have been stirred over and over again in the last few hours.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Actually, Kazuma... ...I think I might have something. Thinking back over everything i saw, I think I might have uncovered another clue!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Haha. You always have something up your sleeve, don't you, Ryunosuke? Come on then! Let's wipe the smug smile off that Englishwoman's face with some evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright, I can't wait! <thought>It's been niggling me for a while that something feels amiss in my memories of that day... Whatever it is could be the key to arriving at the truth about all this...</thought> It's here somewhere. The clue that shows who Dr Wilson's real killer must have been is...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whatever is the matter with you, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Um, well... Something I saw that day is playing on my mind, but I can't quite put my finger on it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I regret to inform you, that I have no choice but to penalise you for that...effusion. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... Like being here in the dock isn't penalty enough...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">They're YOUR memories, Ryunosuke. No one else can see them.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Exactly! That's the problem!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The answer's right in front of you. All you have to do is dredge it up!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright, I'll keep trying!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Inspector Hosonaga! Answer me this!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">......... Y-Yes? What is  it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh, he's still miles away. Probably thinking about that bottle being smashed...</thought> As you've said a number of times now, you strive for perfection in your investigations, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Absolutely!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I wonder, therefore, if perhaps you took anything else from the scene of the crime. Like, for instance, the plate of steak that you took to the victim's table that day? </line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Wait a minute! Where are you going with th-</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Brett:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's just a memory that's been troubling me.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">What memory?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I saw the crime shown in this photographic print with my own eyes that day. And I saw that on the wooden base of the plate that the steak was served on... ...was a spattering of blood.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">......... Oh really? And what of it? Obviously that must have happened when you shot the professor.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, that can't be the case.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Take a good look at the photograph, and the relative position of everything there. The plate of steak is almost directly behind the victim. If I'm supposed to have shot Dr Wilson in the chest from the front... ...there's no way that blood from the victim could have ended up directly behind him!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Hm, yes... For blood to have made it onto the plate, it implies the plate was between the victim and the shooter. Which means the shooter must have been sitting opposite the professor, as you were... ...Jezaille Brett!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">I beg your pardon?!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">This...this is beyond ridiculous! Fabricated nonsense! Is the court seriously expected to believe something the accused has apparently just 'remembered' seeing?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">This... This could be the moment that my entire career in the police force has been leading to.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Inspector! You mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Yes! I took the plate! In the interests of preserving evidence from the scene of the crime! I took it, meat and all! And I don't CARE if they call me a crime scene thief because of it!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">You did WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">I took the steak that you had been eating, Miss Brett. I took the steak that the sergeant had been eating. And I did it all...in the name of justice!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Then we can find out for sure whether or not there's a bloodstain on Miss Brett's plate! We must examine it! Now!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Inspector! The court wishes to examine the plate from the victim's table, immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Sorry for the delay. Here is what you ordered... The steak.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well? What about the blood? Is there blood on it?!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Of course there isn't!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Quickly, Inspector! The blood, man! Show the court!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Of course. Examine the plate at your leisure.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But... But no, that's... Impossibleeeeee! <thought>I know I saw it! I'm sure of it! It was right there on the table behind the professor. There was blood on the side of the plate!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brett">...Heh...heh...heh... What an unbecoming expression, little boy! You see! This is why I always say you can't trust what the Japanese tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Tsk, I couldn't agree more! ...In the case of this disgrace to the empire!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe we may finally have reached a conclusion in this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Let's hope so. This 'let's pretend' attempt at courtroom proceedings is painful to watch. But I do promise to do my best to forget all about it when it's over.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Hah! This sorry-looking steak reveals the facts all too clearly! If the sorry-looking accused wishes to examine it again, be my guest!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Was the plate I saw - or thought I saw - just a figment of my imagination? This is it now. I've lost...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">HUH?! What the- What in the world is this?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I think...it's a koban coin. And the hallmark is from the Hoei era, I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no, I don't mean what IS it! I mean, what's it doing there?! ......... Wait, did you say it was a Hoei koban?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, and apart from the meat juices, it looks to be in good condition. I imagine it's very valuable.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Hm, this isn't the first time today that there's been talk of a Hoei koban...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I've heard of pearls before swine, but I've never heard of bullion in bouillon!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And I don't think you ever will again. <thought>This is extraordinary, though. This means...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I certainly never expected to find a precious coin underneath this thick cut of meat. And it's from the Hoei era, too. That would make it really quite valuable.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's well marinated in the juices, as well, look.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What, are you thinking of eating it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no. But the next time I order a steak in an expensive restaurant, one thing's for sure... My heart's going to be racing as I lift up the meat and peer underneath for a prize!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I think you might have the wrong end of the stick about this, Ryunosuke.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>A koban coin underneath this steak... There's only one logical explanation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This emblem on the side of the plate... Is it a cat?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's a cow. Obviously. Most likely because the restaurant's signature dish is beef steak. It seems a lot of different restaurants have their own unique tableware.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So this is the symbol of La Carneval, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ryunosuke... It's not over yet. Not until the final gavel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Never stop believing in yourself. Keep looking forward, no matter what.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Believe in myself...? Really? Hm, maybe I should at least examine the evidence for myself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">As the evidence requested by the defence has not been shown to be problematic in any way... ...I presume any further examination of evidence in this trial will be unnecessary. Does the defence have any objection?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That bloodstain was going to clinch the trial for me. Can this plate of steak reveal any other clues at all?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>No, I'm really clutching at straws now. That would fly in the face of common sense.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You know, it flies in the face of common sense... ...that someone like you with no experience as a lawyer could last this long in a trial like this.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How did you...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Opportunities are always there for the taking. But only for those with the determination to grab them. Let's have another good look at that steak. If you want to give up, it had better wait until after that!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Hm, maybe I should examine the evidence in more detail...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, a deafening silence from the defence. I will take that as your final answer on the matter.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn> </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your Excellency, please, wait! This plate of beef is hiding another clue! Another clue that will reveal the shocking truth!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">The only thing that's shocking here, is your unhealthy fascination with beef steak!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Your Excellency... I think I've made myself clear, haven't I? I will not be able to turn a blind eye to any more unnecessary procrastination in this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sorry, Miss Brett, but we must ensure a thorough examination of the evidence. I will not give a ruling until I'm completely satisfied that all reasonable doubt has been dispelled.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">I see... As a newly affirmed ally of my country, that's still your position, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you...Your Excellency.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel for the Defence! You will now clearly show the court to what you are alluding! Where precisely on this plate of beef steak is this new clue to be found?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The answer's right here in front of me, I'm sure of it. So there's only one thing to do! Turn this steak over and over until I find something to help me out of this mess!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good, good gracious! That's...</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">A-A-A...koban?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">What on earth...?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">A Hoei-era one, at that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Brett... This...is in fact the beef steak that you ordered at the restaurant on the day in question, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Tell me, why is there an old coin seemingly hidden underneath the meat?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Brett:</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">I fail to see how this is relevant! A coin under the meat? That could simply have been a careless mistake by the chef in a moment of distraction.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Don't be absurd! We're supposed to believe that this happened by accident in the kitchen? A rare Hoei koban just happens to be hidden underneath that piece of steak? If this turns out to be irrelevant to the case... I'll rip up my ticket to Great Britain right now!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He's right. It can't be a coincidence.</thought> Your Excellency!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A rare Hoei koban just happens to be hidden underneath that piece of steak? If this turns out to be irrelevant to the case... I'll give up my lawyer job right now!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">By all means, don't let us stop you! No one invited you, anyway!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Brett:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Even though I'M the one on trial here...?</thought> The point is! It's essential that we ask the owner of this coin if he can explain what it's doing under that steak!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The owner...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes. It's obvious. There's only one person it can belong to.</thought> The owner of the koban that was found underneath the beef steak is...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">No! Come on, Ryunosuke!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh?! You, you shocked me, Kazuma!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Not as much as you shocked me! We've already heard about a koban in this case. Don't you think perhaps it's the same one?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Y-Yes...of course! I, I just couldn't quite find the right name.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Then consult the Court Record! Please?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well, seeing as you asked so nicely...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Obviously, it can only be... ...the antiques dealer and owner of Rasu-tei, Kyurio Korekuta-san!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Kyuri...? As in 'Mr Cucumber-something'? Honestly, these ridiculous Japanese names are quite unfathomable.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, yes... ...the old man who testified earlier alongside the military sergeant, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, Your Excellency.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I remember him saying that he was up to something with his koban coin when it happened. At exactly the moment the gun was fired.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">The gunshot interested me not. I was far too busy on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Too busy on the floor'? Sorry, what were you doing?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Hunting for treasure. Indeed! The Hoei-era koban! My prized coin!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then this Hoei-era koban... Do, do you mean to tell me...?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">No no no! Please, why would Korekuta-san's koban... ...be sandwiched between the victim's beef steak and its plate? It makes no sense!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Officer! Bring both witnesses that testified earlier back in here. Without a moment's delay!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I can't believe we've come back round to that pair again. But I have a hunch - a strong hunch... ...that if we chase down the real significance of this koban... ...we'll find that it's a key element in the case!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nosa">What's this all about? Why have I been called up again? Don't you realise that it's dinner time for little baby Aido? When my son's belly is empty, he's fiercer than a pack of wolves!</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Exploited by the police, we were. Like miserable dogs, forced to bear false witness. And when cast from this courtroom, myself, I became a ruined man in a trice. A worthless, withered antique. Nothing more I have to say. The sun has set on this Rasu-tei shop owner's existence...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Be that as it may, Korekuta-san, something has come to light that requires your clarification. As far as your 'Rasu-tei' memory serves, have you ever seen this koban be-</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">WAAAAAAAAAAAAGH! That's... Yes... That's it! The one! The very one! The very exact one that it is! The resplendent, splendiferous Hoei treasure that my rusty bones managed to misplace that fateful day!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">It can't be...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm, as I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Young man! Enlighten this decrepit old fool! Put me out of my misery! Where? Where was my treasure? Where was it dropped?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Um... I'm not sure if it was 'dropped' anywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">We found your coin sandwiched between a beef steak and its plate, soaking in the seasoned meat's juices.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">S-S-S-Sandwiched?! S-S-S-Soaking?! S-S-S-SERIOUSLY?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Clearly, it couldn't have fallen there by accident. Which means...somebody must have hidden it there on purpose.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Somebody concealed my Hoei treasure...between a slab of meat...and a metal plate...? WHO would do such a thing?! Such an unconscionable thing?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Excuse me... Could I say something?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Proceed, Inspector Hosonaga.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">......... I mentioned this earlier on in the trial, but... ...I was working undercover in the restaurant in order to investigate another case.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, yes, that's right. The secret undercover operation.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">La Carneval is a high-class Western cuisine restaurant. It attracts wealthy diners, including many foreigners. Recently, there's been a run of similarly executed thefts targeting the restaurant's rich clientele. A number of such incidents have been reported to the police bureau.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Wicked crimes indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">We wanted to nip the case in the bud quickly. Especially with so many foreigners being affected.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So that's why you were sent in undercover, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Yes. I took on the job of waiter at the restaurant in order to flush out the criminal. It seems likely...that this koban incident is the work of the same thief.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Hm, so unbeknownst to us, there was a master thief at work in the restaurant on a regular basis. The place was already the scene of several crimes, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't know about the master thief part, but... The identity of the person who stole and hid Korekuta-san's koban is all too clear.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What?</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think the court would like to hear the defence's view on this matter. Tell us, who is the despicable scoundrel that stole Korekuta-san's koban and hid it under the steak!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">No! Come on, Ryunosuke!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh?! You, you shocked me, Kazuma!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Not as much as you shocked me! No one could have approached the table unnoticed. Even if you're a crazy fool, you couldn't have missed that!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm not sure you should be calling Korekuta-san a crazy fool, Kazuma.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's YOU I was calling the crazy fool!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ah... Maybe I'm on the wrong track here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't believe I can have heard you correctly, Counsel. Let me hear your opinion on this matter again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Obviously...it can only be you... ...Sergeant Iyesa Nosa!</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Wha...? How... How dare you, you, you... You monster!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Monster?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">I stole that koban, did I? I'm the master thief of La Carneval, am I? You're seriously accusing ME of these crimes, cadet? But it wasn't me. It was Aido! Aido is the mastermind behind all this!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You would push the blame for your crimes onto your own son, an innocent little baby?! It's you who's the monster, Sergeant Nosa!</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">.........</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Do any of you know... ...of the extraordinarily low wages the Nippon Imperial Army pays those it expects to keep our country safe?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I understand that the temporary increase in taxation owing to the recently ended conflicts remains in place. And I have heard it's hard for lower ranking soldiers to make a living, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">All I want...is to put a hot meal on the table for my son!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's why you were stealing things at the restaurant?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">The place is heaving with money! Every three days, I'd go there and do reconnaissance for a target. And I'd enjoy chomping my way through a good steak at the same time!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It sounds like he doesn't bother with a knife and fork, even. Which...is worryingly believable...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And your 'target' that day was the old man and his koban?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">......... Yes...sir. He...was an easy mark. I...slipped the coin into my pocket without any trouble at all.</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">Hmmm... A veritable phantom thief, you are...</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">I was all set to leave the steak I was halfway through devouring, when it happened.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, when the professor was shot.</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">I knew that if the police conducted a search and found the coin in my pocket, I'd be finished. Aido, too. So I hid the incriminating evidence as fast as I could. On the double! I slipped it under the steak...hoping that I'd be able to rendezvous with it again at a later date.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Korekuta">.........</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Perhaps you could carry on with this absurd prattling in your own time?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, Miss Brett-</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Oh, of course, dear lady, of course! How rude of us! I'm quite sure there's no need to detain you any longer at all. May the esteemed gentlewoman PLEASE be excused, Your Excellency?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm, indeed... The theft of the koban was clearly perpetrated by this... 'baby-saddled' sergeant. It would certainly appear to be unrelated to Dr Wilson's murder.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Of course it is. Hiding a coin under a lump of meat? The sheer nonsense of such an idea astounds me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">N-Nonsense, is it...?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Ah, um...well... Oof...</line>
<line speaker="Brett">And as for picking up your steak and biting into it without using a knife and fork... It's beyond nonsense. It's pure madness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Now that all questions concerning this witness's testimony have been answered... ...I see no further justification for detaining her. Miss Brett, you are free to leave.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Thank you, Your Excellency. Good luck, everyone. ...And good day.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ryunosuke! What's the matter with you? This is no time for daydreaming!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! No, it's just... ...something about Miss Brett's parting words there got me thinking. <thought>I can't quite work out what exactly. But something she said jarred with me. I feel like there was a contradiction in there somewhere. Something didn't quite add up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">If that's the case, don't just stand there thinking! Make your voice heard!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You can think later. But if you don't call out now, it'll be too late. The trial will be over!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait! Miss Brett!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">What is it now?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm afraid...just one last time... There's something I'd like to ask you. I'd like you to explain the contradiction in your parting words from just a few moments ago.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">What are you talking about? What contradiction?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What new student nonsense is this?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well? What parting words are you talking about, Ryunosuke?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Hiding a coin under a lump of meat? The sheer nonsense of such an idea astounds me. And as for picking up your steak and biting into it without using a knife and fork... It's beyond nonsense. It's pure madness!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, I'm right. What she said there exposed an undeniable contradiction!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm going to need to see evidence, Counsel. If Miss Brett's words truly are contradictory, where is the evidence to prove it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's interesting is the plate of steak that you can see on the victim's table.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Miss Brett?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">This attempt to incriminate me is as brutish as the sergeant's eating habits.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I'm inclined to agree.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">AAAAAARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">You really need to learn some more gentlemanly habits, little boy.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'll do my best. <thought>I need to think again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The steak that Miss Brett had been eating before the professor was killed, yes. Go on.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">More accurately, Your Excellency... ...the steak that was on the victim's table just before the professor was killed.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Now you're just splitting hairs!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Not true. Doesn't something about this steak strike you as very unnatural?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">'Unnatural'? What on earth do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's extremely obvious. I'm talking about the shape of the edge where it's been eaten.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I see you've noticed it too, Miss Brett.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Noticed what exactly, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just a few moments ago, Miss Brett claimed... ...no Englishman could even contemplate picking up a steak and biting into it without using a knife and fork.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Of course she did! She's a refined English gentlewoman herself!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Then take a good look at this steak. In particular, the edge where it's been eaten. As you can see, there are clearly defined 'barbaric' teeth marks there!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">......... ...Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It looks like Miss Brett has realised something.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So! If the witness, as she claims, wouldn't contemplate eating anything without using a knife and fork... ...there shouldn't be teeth marks in the steak at all!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">But... What is your actual point? Perhaps the delightful Miss Brett was ravenously hungry and couldn't help her-</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Brett:</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Oh, um... Whatever you say, dear lady!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">As I said, I really must be leaving now. Afternoon tea with the Minister of Justice cannot possibly wait any longer.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Of course, of course! This will all be over in the blink of an eye! Rest assured, I'm about to put this rookie in his place! Just leave everything to-</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Brett:</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Of, of course...dear ladyyyyyyyy!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What's the matter, Miss Brett? Have we ruffled your feathers?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Clearly, the witness knows what this means. She's realised the catastrophic implications these teeth marks in the steak have for her!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ryunosuke! Do you know where you're going with this?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes. Now at last, it's all come together. The mysterious teeth marks in a steak that had allegedly been eaten with cutlery... The reason why the bloodstain I know I saw somehow seems to have disappeared... And most importantly... The evidence that proves once and for all... who shot Dr Wilson that day!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I accept that these teeth marks in the steak are a little... 'unnatural', as you put it, Counsel. But what exactly are you suggesting that tells us?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Everything, Your Excellency.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Everything?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I believe that these 'barbaric' teeth marks in the steak here... ...amount to conclusive evidence in this case. Evidence that will prove beyond any doubt who shot Dr Wilson!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Brett:</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">How can you be so sure?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Oh, it's quite simple. If you really had such conclusive evidence, you would have presented it to the court long ago!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Actually, the evidence I'm talking about hasn't been brought before the court yet.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Hasn't been...? What?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But just because it hasn't been shown yet, doesn't mean that the evidence does not exist.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">This is absurd! The trial has run several hours already! And you say there's evidence yet to be brought forward? There can't be! I don't believe you have it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't! But there is someone who does have it! Someone in this very courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And if that person is willing to submit the piece of evidence I'm referring to... ...it will solve every remaining mystery about this case!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well... I have a feeling this will be my last request of the defence in this trial. Who possesses the conclusive evidence that will reveal the truth about this whole affair?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"> </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"> </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel... I'm disappointed. As this is likely your last chance, I would have expected you to be taking it more seriously.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems you need some waking up. Perhaps a penalty will help focus your mind!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Now we've come this far, there's nothing more to say. There's one person in particular who's provided us with various pieces of evidence already. You have plenty of clues that point to the right answer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">This is the last act in this trial. And you have centre stage, Ryunosuke!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The answer is obvious! It's Inspector Hosonaga!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">What?! I, I have it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">You, you think I've been withholding conclusive evidence? That's ridicul- Ahem! Ahem! Ahem, AHEM!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no no no! I'm not saying that! Everyone's attention has been focused on this steak with the teeth marks.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Now, earlier this afternoon, Sergeant Nosa told the court the following: 'I'd enjoy chomping my way through a good steak.' And as well as admitting to stealing Korekuta-san's coin, he told us that he 'slipped it under the steak.'</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">You, you watch it, cadet! I'm a superior officer!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sergeant Nosa, could you please confirm something for me? Was the steak that you put the coin under... in fact, your own steak?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">Teeen-shun! Affirmative, of course! I might be a soldier in the Imperial Nippon Army, but still... ...I'm not brave enough to ask a foreign gentlelady if she'd mind me manhandling her meal to hide something in it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In other words, the steak that the detective submitted as evidence earlier... ...was in fact Sergeant Nosa's meal.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Auchi">But...that makes no sense! That plate was taken from the victim's table.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yet the gentlewoman doesn't take bites out of her steak, nor did she have any opportunity to steal the coin.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Of course I didn't steal it! To even suggest such a thing would be...an affront to the entire British Empire!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then...how do you explain this paradox?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Exactly! Surely you're not going to suggest... ...that the sergeant switched the two steaks over?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">.........</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">......... You DID switch the plates?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">......... Well...after it happened... The, um...</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">When I saw the civilian had been murdered right in front of my eyes like that, I panicked. As I said, I immediately lifted my steak and hid the coin underneath it. But then when the waiter announced he was an undercover policeman, I thought I'd had it! If he decided to investigate my slab of meat, that'd be it. I'd be getting my marching orders! So when the cadet here was arrested and taken off to the kitchen, I seized my chance. With military precision and timing...I switched my steak with the one on the foreign lady's table!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">What?! You can't have! I, I never saw you do such a thing!</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">It was called 'Operation Lightning Bolt'. There was no time for strategic planning. It was do or die, I tell you! So yes! I did what had to be done!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Un... Unbelievableeeeeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">However! Fear not, Prosecutor-san!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">What now?</line>
<line speaker="Nosa">I swear on the brass buttons of my uniform... that is all I did! Sir!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">'All you did'?! That's plenty, Sergeant!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, that follows.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Inspector Hosonaga!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Earlier in this trial, you told the court this: You said that you had not only taken Miss Brett's steak after the incident, but also the sergeant's. That to preserve evidence, you had taken both.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">...!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">That's correct.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Then please present it to the court now. The plate that was actually on the victim's table at the precise moment he was shot!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Brett:</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">No! You're not wriggling your way out of it this time, lady!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">I, I beg your pardon...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Surely you're not that forgetful. Surely you remember the reason why this steak pan promises to prove such a problem for you...no?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Hmph! You're the ones who decided it was a problem, not me.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The reason the defence asked to see that plate was to confirm something the defendant remembers seeing.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Tsk! THINKS he remembers!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm quite sure of what I saw, Miss Brett. On the side of the plate that was on the table directly behind Dr Wilson... ...there was a clear spattering of blood from the gunshot wound to the victim's chest. </line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I believe the defendant's memory serves him well.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And now we have the evidence to prove it! The plate you were eating from, Miss Brett!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let us not prolong this any further. Inspector, you will show the evidence to the court. Present the beef steak and plate that was originally on the victim's table at the time of the incident!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Sorry for keeping you. Here is the other steak and its plate. Please, feel free to examine it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In other words! It's impossible for Naruhodo-san to have shot the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">It, it can't be...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In fact, there's only one person who could possibly have shot Dr Wilson from the front. I'm sure everyone knows by now who that person is.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">...Ugh...um...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right... Miss Jezaille Brett... It's you!</line>
<line speaker="Brett">......... Outdone...by a Japanese? Me? By a Japanese schoolboy? No... No... NO...</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Please excuse my...little outburst. I briefly lost my composure. Most unbecoming behaviour for an English gentlewoman. Forgive me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Miss Brett... ...I think it's time you told the court what actually happened that day. The truth, this time.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">......... Gladly, Your Excellency.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">...It was I who took the professor's life, using curare. As you surmised, I chose that particular day for one very important reason... The professor had a dental appointment for the extraction of one of his teeth in the morning.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So you planned to kill the professor, knowing that no trace of poison would be found in his water. Because curare is unheard of here in Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Yes. Of course, I never intended to remain at the restaurant for as long as I did. I only needed to see the professor take one tiny sip of his water, and it would be all over. I would place the steak I had ordered in front of him to make it appear as though he had been dining alone... ...and leave immediately. However... ...before any of that happened, there was an unexpected visitor at the professor's table.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That would be me...I suppose?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Yes, you. Who else? Such a trifling matter. But the fact that you'd decided to come over to greet the professor... ...meant that I had lost my chance to slip away unnoticed. In due course, the professor took a sip of his water and was paralysed. I made sure he was sitting in his chair such that he wouldn't fall.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">A plan to pin Dr Wilson's murder on this innocent man.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">......... I happened to know that the professor always carried a gun. I decided to use that fact to my advantage. I had the bottle of curare in my handbag. And...my own pistol concealed under my skirt.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">U-Under you [sic] skirt...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So I was right. There were two guns.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And then I finished my coffee and got up to leave. That's when I noticed the professor's gun, which you had presumably placed on the floor. Placed where you were sure that I would notice it.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">And everything went according to plan. You noticed the gun, as I'd intended. And then, just as you bent down to pick it up...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's when you shot the professor with your own gun. Even though at that point, he was already dead.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Naturally, the gunshot caused a commotion, at which point the waiter appeared.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Obviously, I assumed Naruhodo-san was the culprit and apprehended him. I took him to the pantry that adjoins the kitchen and locked him inside.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">That's when I took the opportunity to turn the professor and his chair around.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Because, of course... ...you needed to make it look like the defendant had shot Dr Wilson from where he'd picked up the gun.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">...So there you have it. That is the entirety of my...misdemeanour.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Your Excellency...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">I wonder... ...might I speak with you in private later?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I shall call on you.</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Thank you. Good day then, everyone. I hope you can forgive me...Naruhodo-san.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would seem... ...this trial has finally run its course. I presume the prosecution is in agreement?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">This, this can't be... Taketsuchi Auchi does not lose! Not to the likes of this, this...ROOKIE STUDENT!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You'd better start getting used to tough opposition.</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">ARRRRRRGH! Ryunosuke Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha- Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Auchi">This insult to the Auchi family name... will NEVER be forgotten!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You've become conceited with age, Counsel. But the old have to stand aside and make way for the new. It's the way of the world. ...May you never forget that! A thousand millenia may pass, and still the Auchi clan will never measure up to the Naruhodo clan!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This trial, in the Supreme Court of Japan... ...will, I believe, go down in history as the start of a new chapter in our country's judicial system. Despite being summoned as the accused, you, Ryunosuke Naruhodo, presented an excellent case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I... Thank you, Your Excellency!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The use of evidence and deduction to unravel the truth is a modern methodology. After all, it has only been a few short decades since our country opened its doors to the wider world. But the Western ideas of 'science' are rapidly gaining acceptance here. I feel sure that science will soon bring new methods of investigation, and new procedures of justice. A new future of law awaits. But what it will look like, I cannot begin to imagine. That is for the young to pursue. Kazuma Asogi...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">After this trial, you are set to embark on a journey of discovery, to the illustrious British Empire. Learn all you can. Absorb everything of the wider world that you are able to. And do not forget...to fulfil the mission imposed upon you.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... I understand...Your Excellency.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What was that about? Why do you look so grave all of a sudden?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ah... Never mind.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As for you, Ryunosuke Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In you, I sense - how can I put it? - unusual potential. I very much look forward to seeing how you carry that onwards.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you, Your Excellency!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is time to deliver the final verdict. I hereby find the defendant, Ryunosuke Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court is now adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I can't believe it. I can't believe what's happened. I made it! I defended myself and made it through that horrendous trial!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ryunosuke! You finally pulled it off! Congratulations!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I couldn't have done it without you. Thank you, Kazuma.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ha ha ha ha hah! No no, it was a pleasure to watch you at work. So, you owe me an extra large sukiyaki from the place on Yumei University Street. Don't forget!</line>
<line speaker="???">Good afternoon. All your hard work has certainly paid off.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Congratulations to both of you for proving Naruhodo-san's innocence.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ah, our trusty judicial assistant. You worked hard for that result, too, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no. I didn't do anythi-</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you so much! If we hadn't had that research paper of Miss Brett's, I don't know how things would have turned out.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Your kind words should really be for my father. I was simply doing as he asked. It was his idea for me to go to the university and investigate.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your father...? <thought>Ah yes, of course...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Forgive me for intruding on court proceedings, Your Excellency.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Susato Mikotoba, judicial assistant to the defence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Speaking of Mikotoba...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, there you are. I believe congratulations are in order!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Naruhodo... You did an excellent job.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Th-Thank you, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Oh no, it is I who should be thanking you. After all... ...your efforts exposed the true criminal that took the life of my good friend.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>'Good friend'?</thought> Oh yes, you mentioned that before. It was you who actually invited Dr Wilson to Yumei University, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Professor Mikotoba studied overseas himself. He went to study forensic medicine in Great Britain. Presumably that's when you met Dr Wilson?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Exactly. In those days, we worked together in the same hospital.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, you worked together?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I've never heard you mention that before.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well, it was a long time ago now. Besides... ...it's your turn, Asogi.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Great Britain is a magnificent country. It leads the world. In science, medicine, engineering, culture... And, of course, in law. Watch and learn, my boy. See what's happening in the world's largest melting pot!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I will. I'll learn all that I can. I swear on this, the spirit of the Asogi clan!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're not taking that sword to Great Britain, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Of course I am. A Japanese man's katana is his soul. This blade shows me where I need to go. And cuts down anything that's in my way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, I've definitely seen how sharp it is already with my own eyes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">That reminds me, what's happened to the woman? To Jezaille Brett, I mean. After all, she's guilty of murder.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Ah yes, her. It's not easy to tell you this, but...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean? Surely she's going to face trial herself now. She's the true culprit, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">She will be leaving Japan in the very near future. For Shanghai.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? Shanghai?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Jezaille Brett will not appear in court again in this country. I'm certain of that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? But why not?</line>
<line speaker="???">It's a matter of consular jurisdiction.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Inspector Hosonaga!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">It was a hard-fought battle in the courtroom today. Very impressive to watch. I must congratula-</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but what's all this about consular jurisdiction?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">We cannot try this particular foreigner for her crimes here in Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What...? We can't try her? But then, who? Who's going to bring her to justice?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">A British consular court will hear her case. Somewhere far away, where our voices can't be heard.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>But why a consular court...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Professor, I simply don't understand. I thought consular courts were a thing of the past now that we've signed the friendship treaty.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Yes, in normal circumstances, you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Then, so long as this is not a serious incident of a highly political nature to our respective governments... ...they can't invoke a consular court just like that!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh... Can't they?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, she's a student, but it doesn't justify our governments making secret agreements about her fate, does it? Something strange is going on!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So Miss Brett can't be held accountable for her actions here in Japan...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I'm afraid that for the young student... ...today's trial was nothing more than a game all along. There was never any danger of comeuppance for her.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't believe it...</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">The British government's foreign affairs ministry has demanded that we hand over custody of Miss Brett. They're obviously taking this case of a foreign student committing murder very seriously.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">......... But it's all going to change from now on. We can make it change. This is a time of great turmoil, this new era heralded by the start of the twentieth century. One day, I have no doubt... ...that woman will receive the judgment she deserves.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, change is coming. And we're the ones driving it.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well, I think that's enough seriousness for now. This evening calls for a celebratory drink!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But Professor...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You're right. This is no time for gloomy faces! We should be celebrating Ryunosuke's not guilty verdict! Let's start having some fun!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">In that case, might I suggest La Carneval? As the head waiter, I should be delighted to provide you with ample food and drink!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...you're a detective, Hosonaga-san. ...Aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Ahem! Ahem! Let's not worry about details for now. To La Carneval! Will you accompany us, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Of course! La Carneval's food is second to none!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I shall go and attend to the paperwork for Naruhodo-san's release.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, yes... Thank you. <thought>So Jezaille Brett won't be tried here. I, I suppose that means I'll never know. I'll never find out why she killed Dr Wilson...</thought> Kazuma...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, Ryunosuke?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I just wanted to say thanks again, that's all. You really saved my skin today.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ha ha ha ha hah! I didn't do a thing! You were the lawyer in there, weren't you? That defence was all your own work.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your skills made the difference, though. One day, I bet you'll be the best lawyer in the world.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Hm, I'm not so sure about that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">To be honest, something kept occurring to me over and over again during that trial. I couldn't help thinking that maybe you're the one destined to become a great lawyer, not me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...? Come on, be serious!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">If I helped you today, it was only right at the very start of the trial. But you have a natural talent for it. For being a defence lawyer, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh no! Not me! All that tense verbal combat? I never want to go through that ever again! I just... I did what you told me to do, that's all. Because I knew I could trust you.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">That's the point.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry? What do you mean, 'that's the point'?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Listen, Ryunosuke... Do you know what the most crucial weapon is that any lawyer needs in order to win?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...knowledge of the law?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">No. The ability to believe.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">To believe? To believe what?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">A defence lawyer has to fight for his clients. He has to believe in them at all times.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Like you believed in me when I said I didn't do it.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I'm human, just like you. I don't have some superhuman ability to know the truth. But you have to make a choice about what to believe in and stick to it when you're defending someone. Sometimes in the courtroom, you can really be backed into a corner. But being able to remain faithful to what you chose to believe in even then... Well, that's not something that anyone can do. It takes a special kind of person.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm, believing in your client...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Just look at today's trial. I'm a student lawyer with precious little real experience, but you never stopped believing in me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You faced seemingly hopeless situations time and again, but you never stopped looking for the truth. And in the end, you found it. Through your own efforts. And because you never stopped believing in me. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thanks, Kazuma.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... There's something I want to ask you, actually, Ryunosuke. Well, it's a favour, really. Something very important to me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It sounds serious. What is-</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Ah! You're still here, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Inspector Hosonaga!</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">I've arranged some rickshaws for us. Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Thank you. We'll be right there. Let's pick up this conversation again later. We should be celebrating right now. Your first court victory!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And YOUR study tour to Great Britain, don't forget!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ah yes. That too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What appears to be odd, is the way you're presenting yourself. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, um... Pay no attention, Your Excellency! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph, as you wish. Now kindly lower your hand!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Never! Not until I've proven that I'm innocent here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As far as I can tell, there is nothing untoward about this evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but that...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Pull yourself together! You look as though your eyes are about to pop out of your head!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh, I can't help that. It's just my look!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems perfectly reasonable to me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ex... Exactly! Perfectly reasonable in every way!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps you should take a leaf out of the witness's book, and learn to be more reasonable yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... Alright, I just need to calm down and think everything through again from the start.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't find anything out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you have anything to say about THAT, Miss Brett?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">No, nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah... So, nothing strikes you as odd having heard that last statement?</line>
<line speaker="Brett">Only your approach to this trial. Nothing else springs to mind.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh. </line>
<line speaker="Brett">You people are so uncivilised. It's unseemly to make idle conversation with a gentlewoman you don't know. Kindly refrain from talking to me again, please.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'll, I'll do my best.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You'll do your best to crush her!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you make of that, Inspector Hosonaga?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Ahem! ...Ahem!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm, I'm talking about that last statement.</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Ahem! ...Ahem! ...Ahem! ...Ahem!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What I mean is, does nothing strike you as unusual about it?</line>
<line speaker="Hosonaga">Ahem! ...Ahem! ...Ahem, ahem, ahem, AHEM!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This is hopeless! No matter how hard I try, I just can't get past that cough!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I don't think you need to push it, Ryunosuke. Give him some time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, alright. <thought>I'll leave it for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That will do! I am now satisfied that no reasonable doubt remains in this matter. The defence has consistently failed to refute adequately the assertions of the prosecution. Accordingly, I hereby announce this court's final verdict. I find the defendant, Ryunosuke Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Officer, restrain the accused, and send the telegraphic communication to Great Britain without delay. The accused will not be granted the right to appeal. That is all. Court adjourned!</line>
</xml>