
<xml>
<title>The Foreign Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the western edge of the Far East lies a peaceful country of spirit mediums and mystery -- the kingdom of Khura'in. But now, the flames of revolution are threatening to consume it whole. But things like "revolt" and "revolution" were the furthest things from my mind when I first arrived in this land.</line>
<line speaker="???">This blight on my soul... I'll have the child take the blame...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whew! I'm finally here. So this is the Kingdom of Khura'in, huh? What a long trip. I wonder how many hours I was in the air. But just look at this place! Get a load of this street! It really feels like I'm in another world here! And that gorgeous temple! I read that's the center of town. Wow! An ox right in the middle of the street! I have to get a picture of that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">E-Excuse me, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder what kind of bird that is. I've never seen anything like it. That's quite a crest it has on its head!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Excuse me, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? Oh! Yes?</line>
<line speaker="???">Pardon me, but are you Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, yes, that's right. <thought>Oops. Hope he hasn't been trying to get my attention all this time...</thought> Wait a minute. Are you...?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">That's right! Ahlbi Ur'gaid, at your service! I'm a monk-in-training at Tehm'pul Temple, and I'll be your guide around town. It's very nice to meet you. Hap'piraki!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"H-Happy" what, now...?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">"Hap'piraki"! That's how we greet people here in Khura'in. It's like "Hello!" or "How do you do?" It's a pretty handy expression to know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, let me give it a try. Hello. I'm Phoenix Wright. Hap'piraki!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>My name is Phoenix Wright. And I run a small law office. Well, that's what I do back home, anyway. Right now, I'm just a traveler; a stranger in a strange land.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Welcome to our country! Welcome to the Kingdom of Khura'in, land of spirit mediums and mystery! This is for you! To celebrate your arrival!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Speaking of mystery, what is this mysterious green lump, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Allow me to explain! This is a famous Khura'inese sweet bun. It's called a "magatah'man," or "soul bun"! It's shaped like a magatama. It's so yummy it'll send your soul right to the Twilight Realm!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That... doesn't exactly make me eager to try it...</thought> Th-Thanks. <thought>I think I'll indulge later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">That will be twenty dahmas. Thank you for your patronage!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to pay?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I always have plenty of those on hand, so just let me know if you ever want any more!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No wonder his bag looks so heavy. It's stuffed with all the tools of his trade.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Oops! I almost forgot to tell you something really important. It's about Miss Maya. She can't come to see you for a few days yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. When I called her from the airport, she said she was still training up in the mountains. I told her I'd wait for her here. Either way, I was glad to hear she's in good spirits. <thought>Maya Fey. She's a spirit medium who used to work as my assistant. I came all the way out here to celebrate the end of her ascetic training with her.</thought> Ahlbi, this is my first time in this country, so I'll be counting on you, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">You got it, sir! Please don't hesitate if you need anything at all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya was right when she told me I could leave everything in your capable hands.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Aww shucks, she said that? That sure was nice of her! I had a chance to show Miss Maya around a little bit, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If there's one person Maya WAS worried about, it's me. "Because we both know trouble likes to follow you wherever you go," she said. Hmph! That girl worries too much.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">But you sure came early to the party, Mr. Wright, sir! I mean, Miss Maya won't be done with her training for another two weeks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh. I hate to admit it, but I came early because I was worried about her, too...</thought> Oh, well, you know. Ha ha! I thought I'd get in a little sightseeing first.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Ooh, sightseeing?! Well, I'm your man for that! I'll show you all the best sights this country has to offer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-Thanks. That would be great. <thought>I guess Ahlbi takes his job very seriously.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Well?! What are we waiting for? Those sights aren't going to see themselves!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yikes! You don't have to shove!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">First stop, Tehm'pul Temple, right there in the center of town! There's something there I really want to show you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow! It's even more impressive up close!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Allow me to explain! This is the heart of our town, Tehm'pul Temple. It was created by the founder of Khura'inism, the Holy Mother, herself! I'm training right here at this temple to be a monk someday.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I read that the people of this country are all adherents of Khura'inism. According to my guidebook, it's a religion in which ancestral spirits are venerated.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">The Holy Mother was a great spirit medium who could commune with our ancestors' souls. And spirit mediums become queen to this day, direct descendants of the Holy Mother.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A spirit medium rules the entire country, huh. Talk about power and influence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">The main thing you'll want to see when you come to Tehm'pul Temple is... ...the Dance of Devotion rite! The Dance of Devotion takes place twice, one in the morning and once in the afternoon. This dance, along with the Song of Ceremony, is performed in offering to the Holy Mother! The Dance of Devotion has the power to summon forth souls from the Twilight Realm! In Khura'inism, we believe the soul is carried by the sacred Khura'inese butterfly! Its wings form a loop that wraps around the soul to transport it--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> Slow down! I can't remember all of that at once.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Oh! I'm sorry! I guess I got a little overexcited.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anyway, the main thing I got from all that is that you really, really love your country.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Heh heh. Well, that's sure true!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I like this kid. He pours his heart into everything he does.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Let's see. I guess I just explained about half of what I usually explain... so I'll give you a special discount and only charge you ten dahmas for the tour fee. Thank you for your patronage!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess he pours his heart into aggressive salesmanship, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Come to think of it, Miss Maya told me she could tell I love my country, too. We stood here for about an hour while I told her all about the Holy Mother.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really?! An hour?! <thought>Hope that counted as patience training...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">And she seemed really interested, too. She listened to my whole speech!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh. That doesn't sound like the Maya I know.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Miss Maya is so kind and nice! She treats me really well, like a little brother. She's kinda like a big sister to me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This IS Maya Fey you're talking about, right? Maybe she's grown up since I last saw her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Oh, nooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Is it that time already?! We have to hurry into the temple right away! But first... let me give you this lyrics card for the Song of Ceremony I told you about. There's an English translation of the lyrics there, too, so give it a read, okay? Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But why the big rush?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">If we don't hurry, we'll miss the beginning of Her Benevolence's Dance of Devotion!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Her Benevolence"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Singer">♪ When dragon and tiger battle ♪</line>
<line speaker="Guard">- Ahlbi Ur'gaid, you're under arrest for treason!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let me in! Why won't you let me in?!</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">'Cause you're a foreigner! What business could you have with this court?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I told you! My friend is on trial in there! <thought>The police raided the temple in the middle of the dance performance yesterday... and arrested Ahlbi on suspicion of treason. I was worried about Ahlbi, so I just had to come see his trial.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">A trial isn't a tourist attraction! So, clear off! If you want a picture for your scrapbook, take one of me, and get outta here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, you've got it all wrong! <thought>Just great... Well, I guess there's only one thing to do!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, I used to be Khura'inese.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I lived here when I was little.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Oh, really? What town are you from?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, well, um... <thought>*gulp*</thought> It was a tiny village called "Phoenixiah."</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">............ There's no such place! Did you really expect to get away with a barefaced lie like that?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Busted. Well, I guess that means there's only one thing left to say!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, I'm a foreigner, but I'm not your average foreigner.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm actually a lawyer! <thought>Back at home, anyway.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">What...? A... lawyer...? I can't... That's not possible...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's he so shocked about? Well, whatever... Now's my chance!</thought> Nothing wrong with a lawyer entering the courtroom, right?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Wait! Get back here, you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So this is a Khura'inese courtroom... Wait. Isn't that..."Her Benevolence"? What's she doing here in court?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The Divination Séance has been performed. I will now hand down my verdict against the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What? A verdict already? But the trial only just started!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">G-Guilty?! There's gotta be some kind of mistake! Please take another look!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Séances performed by Princess Rayfa are infallible. They show only the truth. What right do you have to question her abilities?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">But I... I didn't...!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Isn't it ironic that you, a devout adherent of Khura'inism, would dare doubt her Insight? Heh heh. Nonbelievers will only be met with suffering in the Twilight Realm, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">But... I didn't do it! Your Benevolence! Allow me to explain, I beg of you!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">......Be silent, impudent whelp! There is no merit to be had in indulging the ramblings born of a criminal's unclean soul.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">B-But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What in the world is going on here? The judge made his ruling based on something called a "Divination Séance"? What is Ahlbi's attorney doing? Wait a minute! Where IS Ahlbi's attorney?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Why is this happening...? I didn't do anything wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Foolish child. Doubting the Divination Séance is tantamount to doubting the Holy Mother herself. Your Magistry! As royal priestess and in the name of the Holy Mother, I command you! Impose the highest penalty against this unclean soul!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As you command, so shall it be done, Your Benevolence. May Her Holiness grant us her divine favor! Ur dihara Khura'in!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Ur dihara Khura'in! Ur dihara Khura'in! Ur dihara Khura'in!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait just one moment!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Y-You're...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh. Me and my big mouth. Now what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Mr. Wright...? What are you doing here, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I'm in it now! So I have to do this right!</thought> Your Honor! It's too soon to give your verdict! This trial has only been underway for a few minutes!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">E-Excuse me? Who on earth are you?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm... well... ...an ordinary tourist, Your Honor -- just passing through.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, a tourist, are you? Hap'piraki.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, more importantly, where is this boy's defense attorney?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defense... attorney...? Ha ha ha ha! What ever are you talking about? He doesn't need a defense attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait. What?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Of course you wouldn't be aware, being a foreigner and all... ...but we have no need for defense attorneys here in the Kingdom of Khura'in. We leave it all up to Her Benevolence's sacred power of Spirit Communion. Her Divination Séances determine all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! But surely you see how unfair that is! <thought>What kind of insane court system are they running here?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You would dare mock me, you barb-headed buffoon? If you value your life, you will leave posthaste... Or shall I summon the bailiff?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The bailiff is that big, scary dude with the big, scary gun, isn't he...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I'm sure he would be happy to oblige you with a bullet or two as a souvenir of your travels.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>At the cost of an arm and a leg, no doubt...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">N-Now, hold on! Mr. Wright has nothing to do with any of this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ahlbi!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I appreciate what you're trying to do, Mr. Wright, but never mind about me. You just go ahead and see Miss Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Forget about me! You have to go, now! I'm sure you can find another guide. There were lots more places I wanted to show you... ...but it looks like I won't get a chance now. I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>......The poor kid. He's trying to put on a brave face, but look how terrified he is. What can I do? What should I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The whole reason I came to this country was to see Maya. And I'm just an outsider here, with no knowledge of the way they do things... But I'm still a defense attorney, first and foremost.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't just let a verdict be handed down with nobody standing in Ahlbi's corner!</thought> If Ahlbi doesn't have a defense attorney, then I'll do it. I'll defend him!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">D-Defend him?! You can't be serious!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Did you hear that?! Is he out of his mind? Heaven forbid!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Defend me?! Mr. Wright! What are you saying? You can't do that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I most certainly can. Don't worry, I'm quite used to tackling all sorts of trials. Besides, can you imagine how furious Maya would be if I let anything happen to you?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You are but a naïve tourist, ignorant of our ways. But if you are smart, you will heed my advice. Do not pursue this matter any further.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like defending somebody is easier said than done in this country.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff, throw this man out!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You have something to say, Mr. Payne?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. Why not allow it, Your Magistry? Why not have him defend the accused? It could prove very interesting. Right, Mr. Phoenix Wright...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right... <thought>Mr. Whoever-You-Are...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor, are you acquainted with this traveler?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">That's "Chief Prosecutor"... Your Magistry. And yes, I am acquainted with him. He's a defense attorney from my native land. I've had dealings with him in the courtroom before.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Heavens to Betsy!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">What?! Mr. Wright! You're a... defense attorney?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A defense attorney! Well! This is a shock!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You may be surprised to hear that I have more than ten years of experience. <thought>I guess there aren't all that many lawyers around here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Magistry, would you kindly allow us to proceed in the manner of my old country?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But, Mr. Payne! I've already made a ruling in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. Call it nostalgia, if you will, but I am most eager to give it a try.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... But I have a previous engagement, you see. A class together with the missus.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Your Magistry, I agree we should have a whack at it. It sounds amusing. A score of years have passed since we last saw a defense attorney in this courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A score... As in twenty years?! What's the deal with this country?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Mr. Payne, I want that barbed head brought to me on a stick.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">As you wish, Your Benevolence! I, Chief Prosecutor Payne, will see to it myself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Payne. If that is what you and Her Benevolence want, I will acquiesce. As for the defense, I hope you are prepared for every eventuality.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Every eventuality"? What is he talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">There. Are you satisfied now, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. Thank you, Mr. Payne. <thought>And sorry for not remembering you earlier.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">That's "Chief Prosecutor"... or "The Incredible Payne" as I'm also known in this country. And you'll see soon enough just why that is... ...when you're forced to capitulate to me before this very court of law! Heh heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why is he so strangely confident? And not only that, but... ...what's with the gallery?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Just you watch! That defense attorney will try and twist the truth! You can bet on it! Get him, Chief Prosecutor! Crush that defense devil!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is way more lawyer hate than even back home.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, if you would please give your opening argument once again, Mr. Payne.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Certainly, Your Magistry. The accused is charged with two crimes: larceny... and murder. Yesterday, the Founder's Orb was stolen from the treasure room of Tehm'pul Temple. In addition to the theft, two other things were discovered in the treasure room: the dead body of Mr. Paht Rohl, temple security guard, and... ...the empty treasure box that housed the orb which Mr. Rohl was in charge of guarding. We believe that Mr. Rohl was murdered by the thief who stole the treasure.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">To kill a guard armed with a gun... What a terrifyingly bold act!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I couldn't agree more, Your Magistry. Please allow me to submit as evidence the victim's autopsy report and crime photo.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It's been a long time since we had evidence presented in court as well. It's kind of refreshing, actually. Ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">We may rely on the power of the Séances, but our police still carry out investigations. Thus, any proof I provide is indisputable!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, really? Well, forgive me if I don't just take your word for it. I can check the evidence out myself by looking at them in the Court Record. We'll see just how thorough you and your police were, Mr. Payne.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Such a deplorable crime! The audacity of stealing the sacred treasure of Her Holiness, our founding mother... It's a crime that strikes at the very heart of our nation!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Exactly, Your Magistry! We mustn't let the culprit get away with these heinous deeds. Indeed, such deeds are best described as "treason against the crown."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is this treasure really such a valuable object?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">H-How can you even ask such a thing?! Of course it is! Why, sealed within this treasure is the very soul -- the mitamah -- of the Holy Mother!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Her soul is sealed within the treasure? <thought>I think I'll take that with a grain of salt.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Grrr. You don't believe it, do you?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Of course I believe it! <thought>Something tells me I'd better play along.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. This kind of irreverence is exactly why I dislike defense attorneys so much.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor-- Er, Your Magistry?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This treasure... I've never seen it, so it's a little hard for me to imagine. Could I see a photo of it or something?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Of all the outlandish requests! You defense attorneys are truly beyond the pale!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's been getting awfully angry with me. And are those veins popping out of his forehead?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">It's forbidden for anyone outisde of the royal family to view the treasure itself. They say that anyone without the proper spiritual power would be blinded instantly. That is why the average person has never seen the treasure, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess there are national treasures that are off-limits to the public back home, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">For the benefit of the shamelessly uninformed defense, let me share this newspaper article. It includes photos taken about eight years ago when the treasure was unearthed. These are the only public photos of the outer box in existence. What's more, the treasure box only leaves the temple's treasure room but once a year... ...for a special New Year's rite that takes place at the palace. Therefore, this treasure box has only ever been seen by a handful of people.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hear there's been a string of thefts lately of historic artifacts from the temple.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Right, Your Magistry. Inexcusable thievery of precious national treasures for personal gain. And the culprit is the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So he used his position as monk-in-training to get his hands on the treasure, is that it?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The accused's family is by no means wealthy. To help with family finances, he works as a tour guide in addition to his ascetic training.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you for giving an excellent outline of the case, Mr. Payne. Now, then. No more questions from the defense, I presume?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? No, I DO have questions!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Even more? But you just asked a bunch. Well, make it snappy. My class starts in just a few short minutes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What?! He's still planning on going to that thing...? There's still a lot I don't know about the case. I should ask now while I have the chance. Let's see. What else do I need to know more about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Payne, where did the crime take place?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">What? As I already stated, it was in the treasure room of the temple.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oops! That's right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Have you even been paying attention? These lying lawyers! Not only do they lack morals, but memory, too?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">He apparently has all the brain power of a barnyard chicken, Your Magistry.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh ho ho! That explains why he has a crest like a rooster!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No matter where I go in the world, the insults are always the same...</thought> Your Magistry! Please let me try again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you claim was the defendant's motive?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Payne has already explained that. He wanted to sell the treasure in order to help his family with living expenses.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, yeah. Guess it slipped my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So it's true what they say about lawyers never listening to anyone but themselves.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My apologies, Your Magistry! Please let me give it one more try!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. If you must.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Payne, what was the murder weapon?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The murder weapon was... the treasure box itself. The empty treasure box left at the scene had a large bloodstain on it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How utterly reprehensible, using the sacred treasure box for murder!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The accused came to the treasure room with the express purpose of stealing the treasure. He climbed the altar stairs and snatched the box, ready to abscond with the treasure. But he was discovered by Mr. Rohl, who had come to the room in the course of his rounds. After walloping Mr. Rohl on the head with the treasure box... ...the accused forced the bloodied housing open and made off with the treasure inside.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the defendant is just a little boy. I hardly think he would be able to hit the victim -- a grown man -- on the head.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ah, a very good point, Mr. Wright... but I'm afraid that won't help you. At the time of the crime, the accused was on the stairs leading up to the altar. The accused's elevated position would more than make up for their difference in stature.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah... I guess that makes sense...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ha ha ha ha! Mr. Payne, your reasoning is flawless. What an elegant argument! Hats off to you, Chief Prosecutor! Your title is obviously well-earned! Well, the accused's guilt is certainly conclusive. Unless there is anything else, I am ready to announce my verdict. Very well. In that case, I find the accused...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">J-Just one moment, Your Magistry! Don't-- Don't you think you're rushing the verdict just a little bit?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I told you. I have plans to attend to, and... AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHH! I'm late! It's already started! How did the time fly by so fast?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's STILL stuck on that...?</thought> We haven't even heard the defendant's side of the story yet! Your Magistry, the defense asserts its right to cross-examine the defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? Did I say something funny?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Cross-examine the"...? What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! What do you mean, "what do I mean"?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I seem to have some dim recollection of the process, but I can't quite recall...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">And little wonder! A so called "defendant" hasn't been questioned in over twenty years.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Should I even be surprised anymore?</thought> Anyway, I demand we let the defendant -- or the "accused" -- tell his side of the story!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......Is that really necessary?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course it's necessary, Your Magistry!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. What harm could it do? I say we allow the boy to speak, Your Magistry. Though I doubt he'll have anything of relevance to say... Heh heh heh heh heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, how kind of you, Your Royal Payne-ness.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well. As long as it's okay with you, Mr. Payne. I'm already hopelessly late for my class, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">In that case, the prosecution calls the accused back to the witness stand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! But before we do, I'd better call my wife and apologize for missing that class. Any objections...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Go for it, Your Magistry.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Accused, state your name and occupation again, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Ahlbi Ur'gaid... I'm in training to be a monk... and I'm a tour guide, too.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*sigh*... Why me...? Now, where were we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Cross-examining the defendant, Your Magistry.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Right, right. Let's do that, then. At the defense attorney's insistence, I might add. *sigh*...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He sounds a little dispirited. His wife must've given him a piece of her mind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, the defense had better get to it. And make it quick, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">"Th-The defense"... Mr. Wright... I didn't know you were a lawyer...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I am, and I'm here to defend you, Ahlbi. Don't worry. All you have to do is tell the truth, and you'll be all right.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">You... You tricked me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">If I knew you were a lawyer, I wouldn't have given you that tour! Give back that magatah'man I gave you yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Ahlbi, what's gotten into you?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Don't talk to me. You... You disgust me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now even Ahlbi's against me! But why?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. This must be a new experience for you, Mr. Wright, being loathed by a client.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">............</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Now, then, accused, please give the court your testimony. The incident occurred around noon... ...during the break between the morning and afternoon Dances of Devotion. I want you to tell the court what you were doing around that time.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">All right...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I didn't kill Mr. Rohl, and I didn't steal the treasure.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Were you well-acquainted with the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Yes. He used to chat with me whenever we ran into each other in the temple. Mr. Rohl was a monk-in-training when he was a kid, too, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I bet Ahlbi looked up to him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">But he had to give that up and go work when his family needed money... That's why he became a guard. But at least that way, he could still stay on at the temple. He was so proud when he was put in charge of guarding the treasure box! He even got to carry the box to the palace for the New Year's rite!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The victim's parents apparently both died relatively young. So Mr. Rohl had to support his younger brothers and sisters as well. But even with his job as a security guard, I'm sure things couldn't have been easy for him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It sounds like his circumstances and Ahlbi's were very similar.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Mr. Rohl encouraged me to never give up. "Ahlbi, you train hard and make sure you become a monk one day! Don't end up like me," he'd say. He was always cheering me on, in my training, and in my tour guide business, too. Why in the world would I kill a nice man like that?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, yes. I see. You expressed yourself well. Defense, now that you've heard the accused's account, are you finally satisfied? If so, let's draw this to an expeditious conclusion...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, Your Magistry! I haven't even cross-examined the defendant yet!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm? That wasn't the end of it? It's been so long, I don't rightly recall what this "cross-examining" thing is all about.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A judge who doesn't know what a "cross-examination" is... What fresh hell is this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I really do wish I could remember how it works...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Should I give the judge a refresher on cross-examination?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I'd better, or we'll never get anywhere.</thought> Your Magistry, please allow me to explain the procedure. First, we lawyers listen carefully to a witness's testimony. Then we touch "Present" <thought>R</thought> to open the Court Record and examine the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And why would you do that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To find and "Present" <thought>X</thought> any evidence that's inconsistent with the statements given.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"P-Present"?! I certainly don't need any gifts from you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Clearly, something is getting lost in translation with His Magistry...</thought> The point is, it's possible that a statement could contain a lie or a mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... ...what do you do if you can't find any inconsistencies in a witness's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In that case, we may "Press" <thought>L</thought> the witness for more information. Pressing a statement might reveal new information or even entirely new statements.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. "Presenting" evidence is one thing, but "Pressing" witnesses? I'll have you know, defense, that I do not allow violence in my courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Rest assured! Only gentle verbal pressure is used. No physical force involved!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I'm not convinced... After all, who knows what sort of tactics an attorney will resort to? One false move and I'll call the bailiff!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah... Something's definitely getting lost in there... For now, I should just focus all of my energy on questioning Ahlbi... and comparing his statements with the information in the Court Record.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better save my breath. The judge doesn't exactly seem like a model student... He'll just have to watch and see how it's done.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I didn't kill Mr. Rohl, and I didn't steal the treasure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">............ You do? But you're a lawyer. Of course you'd say that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, now. There's no need for that.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">But he's right. Lawyers always claim their client is innocent, even if they have to lie. Just like you're doing right now, accused.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">D-Don't lump me in with that lawyer! I'm NOT lying! I didn't steal anything and I didn't kill anybody!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I'm not allowed to go anywhere near the treasure room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">It's a rule of the temple. They keep a lot of important things in that room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, like the Founder's Orb, in particular. Only the royal family may lay eyes on it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Didn't Mr. Payne say anyone without spiritual power would go blind?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I heard you wouldn't be blinded if you just looked at the outer treasure box. But I've never been anywhere near the treasure room. I'm too scared. You've gotta believe me...!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I've never even seen that treasure box with the green Khura'inese butterfly on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Yeah. You can see it in that newspaper article. Look! See? There's a relief of the Khura'inese butterfly on the treasure box.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, this design here carved on the back of the box. I see it now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">It's a sacred butterfly, said to carry the soul, or "mitamah," of the departed. Its wings form a loop that cradles the mitamah and carries it to the Twilight Realm.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As you can see, there's even one depicted here behind me at the judge's bench.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, what do you know? There it is. ...Though it kinda looks like he's about to be carried off to the Twilight Realm himself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Anyway, I've never even seen this treasure box. Besides...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">When the incident happened, I was in the hallway, planning out my tour route.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">............ Yes, I was planning out a tour for you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">For me? Well, thank you, Ahlbi.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">...I wouldn't have done it if I knew you were a lawyer. I wasted all that time on you! Give it back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sadly, I'm a lawyer, not a time lord... Actually... as soon as he heard that's what I am, he's been like a totally different person.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I certainly don't think Ahlbi committed murder. However...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Don't talk to me. You... You disgust me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...That outburst earlier makes me wonder if he'd willingly tell me the truth. I'd better compare his statements and the Court Record carefully. If I find an inconsistency, I can Present some evidence and maybe get him to open up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, Ahlbi... Why would you lie to me...?</thought> So, you say you've never laid eyes on the treasure box. Is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">That's right. It's forbidden, so I'd never do that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In that case... how did you know there was a green butterfly on it?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Huh? B-Because... I saw the picture of it... in that newspaper article.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nope. Take another look. These photos are in black and white. You couldn't possibly tell what color the butterfly is from these pictures!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Aaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hold on. His bag... Did it just... move?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">P-P-Pohlkunka!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I beg your pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">"Pohlkunka" is a word in Khura'inese that people use when they're surprised.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-You just exposed a lie! So this is the power of "cross-examination," is it?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should be the one shocked here by your shocking lack of understanding...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">But, just a moment. If the accused was lying...then that just makes him more suspicious than ever!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... And this just makes things worse for me than ever...</thought> Ahlbi, are you hiding something? Please give only true statements. I can't help you if you don't tell the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Darn. I just can't seem to get him to open up to me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. So, accused, you HAVE seen the treasure box with your own eyes after all, haven't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Well... Maybe I did take a peek one time a long time ago, when I was cleaning the treasure room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you weren't in the treasure room at the time of the incident, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">......O-Of course I wasn't.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He does?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">This was found on the floor of the treasure room. It's a scroll entitled "Notice," and contains a list of temple monk duties. These instructions pertain to the day of the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-And what exactly is that supposed to prove?!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The accused's fingerprints were found on the scroll.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-Whaaaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Oh, no! Where is it? It's not here! I must've dropped it somewhere...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Indeed. You must've dropped it when you were busy murdering the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Ngh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No, no, no, no, no... Then that means... ...Ahlbi was there on the day of the incident?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ha ha ha ha! So this is the power of "cross-examination"! The more the accused talks, the guiltier he paints himself.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes, it would seem so, Your Magistry. Heh heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! He predicted my argument and had evidence ready to refute it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gallery">How was any of that supposed to help the accused? See?! I told you you can't trust lawyers and their lies! Her Benevolence already said the kid's guilty! Just declare him guilty and get it over with!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Ngh... No... Everything's going all wrong... Shah'do... What do I do?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As I suspected, this "cross-examination" session has served no purpose whatsoever.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No...! You're wrong!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">But armed as we are with Her Benevolence's Insight, there's no reason to doubt his guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Then I guess I'll just have to poke holes in this "Insight" of hers!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">By the way, this didn't prove to be "very interesting" at all, Mr. Payne. Nevertheless, I will now finally announce my verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait just one moment, Your Magistry! I haven't seen this Divination Séance for myself yet. As the defense, I have the right to check it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Is that really necessary? I have to get home and apologize to my wife...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess she really did give him the business...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Magistry, I enthusiastically support having Mr. Wright see the Séance.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You do? And why is that, Mr. Payne?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Don't you want to see it? See the lawyer being utterly crushed by the power of the Séance... ...and then watch him tearfully beg for mercy?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, now!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I'm sure it'll make up for not getting to go to that class with your wife.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It certainly does sound worth seeing! And it'd give me a juicy tidbit to tell the missus. Ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've been reduced to a "juicy tidbit"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, foreign interloper, I imagine you do have to see it for yourself to be convinced. It's certainly unprecedented, but let's have the Divination Séance performed again. But, then, right after the tearful begging, I really do have to be going.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The only "tearful begging" is going to come from the prosecution when we're through!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. How pitiful the defense looks, still scrambling desperately for a foothold... ...blissfully unaware that defeat and despair are all that await him.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There she is: "Her Benevolence"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your Benevolence, Rayfa Padma Khura'in. Thank you for coming all this way once again.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Your gratitude is unnecessary. This is simply my duty. ......Barb-headed attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I am told you question the veracity of the sacred Divination Séance. It would seem the depths of your irreverence and blasphemy are lost on you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm just a foreigner, ignorant in the ways and customs of this country. I apologize in advance for anything rude I might say or do, Your Benevolence. All I want is a fair trial for Ahlbi.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You would imply that the trials of this country are unfair? Do explain, outsider... ...how verdicts founded on truths imparted by the very souls of the dead lack impartiality.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's fair about trials with no defense and no chance for the accused to tell their story?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">H-How dare you speak to Her Benevolence in that manner?!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Did you hear that?! Did you hear how he talked to Her Benevolence?! What does he know about anything?! Ignorant outsider! We won't stand for it! He must be punished!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yikes. Looks like I really stuck my foot in it this time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Punish him! Punish him! Punish him! Punish him!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Silence, one and all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is she... standing up for me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Be not disquieted, my people. He merely expresses his opinion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, well. Looks like "Her Benevolence" is going to be more reasonable than I thought.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Attorneys are ghastly creatures, with souls stained black by brazen untruths. The words of a lowly worm such as that are not worth troubling yourselves over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All right, I take that back...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">None of his prattling can sway the truth of my Insights. Rest assurred, he will soon see the error of his foolish ways!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Your Benevolence. The Divination Séance, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Certainly. Nayna, my robe... O Holy Mother! We hold this Divination Séance in your name! Let the eyes of everyone here be clear, and our ears be unstopped! O Dance of Devotion! Guide the victim's soul to me! So that we may receive their final memories in the Pool of Souls!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What just happened?! An image appeared in the pool!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">A final message from the victim's soul, the last communication of his mitamah... The Divination Séance has revealed this to us.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Her Benevolence can use her power of Spirit Communion... ...to project a victim's memories of the last few moments before their demise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So what we saw in the pool is what Mr. Rohl actually experienced?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">In the victim's memories, we see the accused raising a weapon up over his head. This is consistent with the findings of the police investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Th-There has to be some kind of mistake! I didn't do it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This looks bad for Ahlbi... Really, really bad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. Now do you see why I'm "The Incredible Payne"?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>More than I can express... But even if those are the victim's last memories, what can I do with them?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh! There it is! There's the face of a man being utterly crushed! Oh, how long I've waited to see it! Isn't it wonderfully gratifying, Your Magistry?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, yes. Very satisfying, indeed! Now are you finally convinced, traveler? The accused is most assuredly guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Am I really the only unbiased one here...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then, I think we've all been "amused" enough. If you give up now, I won't even invoke the Defense Culpability Act against you. You'd be free to slink back to your own country with your tail between your legs.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Defense Culpability Act? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?! You mean you honestly don't know?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, uh... No...? <thought>What's with all the hubbub?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Well, well. Not only is he a lying, black-hearted lawyer, he's also an imbecile. Your Magistry, I think you'd better explain the Defense Culpability Act to him.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I think I'd better. The Defense Culpability Act -- or "DC Act" for short -- is as follows. "In the name of Her Eminence, those who would support criminals... ...will be deemed just as guilty." In other words, if you help the accused by defending him and he is found guilty... ...you will receive the same sentence as he.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What?! What kind of insane law is that?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Under the DC Act, many an attorney has been convicted and met with a grim fate. Some went to prison. Others received the death penalty. That's why there are so few in our country today who admit to being an attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. That's as it should be. The history of our courts proves that... ...attorneys are black-souled creatures who will tell any lie to save the accused. Thus, attorneys deserve to be exterminated!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Exterminate! Annihilate!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've never felt so much hostility coming at me from so many sides! What could've happened to make everyone feel this way?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh... heh heh heh... Ha ha ha ha ha! You fell right into my trap, Phoenix Wright! Your win streak against me and my brother ends today! With the Séance and the DC Act on my side, I'll finally get my revenge!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's why he was so eager to have me defend Ahlbi!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Chased out and humiliated back home, fate brought me to the foothills of Khura'in. I thank my lucky stars that I'm chief prosecutor here now! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defense, know that if I rule the accused guilty, you will go to prison, too. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That explains Ahlbi's reaction earlier...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Defend me?! Mr. Wright! What are you saying? You can't do that!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Magistry, isn't a prison sentence a bit lenient? After all, we're talking about treason. One should pay for such a crime with one's life. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, yes. I believe the death penalty might be appropriate under these circumstances.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">TH-THE DEATH PENALTY?! <thought>N-No way...</thought> Y-You're k-kidding, right, Your Magistry...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ha ha ha ha! ...Do I look like I'm kidding? I'll have you put your life and your dark, tainted soul on the line here. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>D-Death...? This can't be happening...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">"The Courts of Resignation." Our courts are well-known as thus. In this land where my Séances provide the truth and no attorneys can intervene... ...criminals know that all they can do is resign themselves to their fate. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">O foreign lawyer, I ask you once more: Are you still sure you want to defend the accused?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*gulp* ...There's Maya to think of in all of this, too... I can't just lay down my life... What in the world should I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A trial I just happened to walk into, in a country I just happened to visit... How can I put my life on the line for something like this?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I appreciate what you're trying to do, Mr. Wright, but never mind about me. You just go ahead and see Miss Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But... What about Ahlbi...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">She's kinda like a big sister to me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Isn't this why I became a lawyer in the first place? To help those with no one on their side... I can't just abandon everything I believe in. All I can do now... is stand firm and fight!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Well? Don't hold your tears back on MY account, Phoenix Wright! Admit your defeat and grovel before me -- the chief prosecutor -- for your life!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-Whaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">B-But, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defendant insists he's innocent. And not even a Divination Séance should be accepted without examination.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">P-P...Pohlkunkaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">But if I'm found guilty, you'll get the death penalty, too... Even knowing that, you still want to defend me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know what happened in the past... ...but it looks like everyone in this country considers lawyers to be liars. So I can understand if you don't believe me. But... I still believe in you, and your innocence.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So all I have to do is keep believing, and find the truth. That's all there is to it.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">............</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hah hah hah. Barb-headed attorney, you continue to amuse me. Though your barbed jabs are proving to be more than mere jokes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Benevolence. Believe me when I say that this attorney will knock your Insights out.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That's enough!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Insolent, disrespectful attorney! You'll have plenty of time to regret your folly in the Twilight Realm!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not a wise move, traveler. Not wise at all... You should have taken the chance I offered to save your life. But you made your choice. The Defense Culpability Act will be applied in this case. And with this verdict, you'll both soon be parting with your heads!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Death! Death! Death! Death! Death! Death! Death! Death! Death! Death! Death! Death! Death! Death! Death! Death!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The souls of the departed speak only the truth, and I but give their messages a voice. If you think my Insights contain falsehood, I challenge you to prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The accused swung whatever he was holding down on the victim's head!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">These are the victim's experiences just before his death.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>As the victim's final memories, we can assume they aren't lies. So how do I break this down?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Allow me to relieve you of your ignorance, defense. Did you notice the words that appeared in the Séance vision?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come to think of it, I did see words... like "Song of Ceremony" and "Incense."</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The victim's final memories are not limited to sight alone. Sight, smell, taste, sound, touch -- all is laid bare in the Pool of Souls.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what Mr. Rohl experienced with his five senses appears in the vision as words, right?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Precisely. And by examining these sensations... ...we can perceive the victim's final moments with unparalleled clarity.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Works for me! I can use all the extra information I can get! Now, to find a contradiction between her Insights and the Séance vision!</thought> Your Benevolence, I ask that you please show me the Séance vision again!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait a minute. Her Benevolence said "after the morning Dance of Devotion" earlier, didn't she? Isn't there something off about that? I'll use these arrows (D-Pad or Circle Pad</thought> to select the Insight I think is off.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The accused swung whatever he was holding down on the victim's head!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yes, this is the Insight that sounded funny. Now I'll just carefully compare this Insight with the Séance vision. If I notice a sensation that seems contradictory, I'll tap "Select" (X</thought>!)</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... This part of the vision doesn't seem to really contradict the Insight. I'd better tap "Select" (X</thought> at some other point in the vision!)</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is it -- this is the part of the vision that contradicts the Insight. Now I just select the sensation I think is inconsistent and then "Present" (X</thought> it!)</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait just a moment!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes? What is it, Barbed Head?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're saying the incident occurred AFTER the morning Dance of Devotion, right?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That's right. What of it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then isn't it strange that Mr. Rohl could still hear the Song of Ceremony?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! You're absolutely right!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">............Hmph. Is that all that troubles you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What the victim heard was just a practice run of the Song of Ceremony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Practice run? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Mr. Payne, if you would?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Certainly! Allow me to explain. The incident occurred in the interval between the morning and afternoon Dances. During that time, the singers were practicing in the performance hall.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Precisely! I was there as well, so I can corroborate this statement.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. So what the victim hears was that practice session.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh. There goes my contradiction... Okay, so they were practicing in this "performance hall"... That must be the room where Ahlbi and I saw Her Benevolence dancing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">However, Mr. Payne, I admit one detail troubles me.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ask away, Your Magistry.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's a big temple. The performance hall and treasure room are quite far from eachother. Could the song really be heard all the way in the treasure room?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's right. It is a very big temple.</thought> Well? How about it, Mr. Payne?!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Magistry, have you forgotten? There are speakers in every room of Tehm'pul Temple, including the treasure room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, that's right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Speakers? For what purpose?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Are you serious, Mr. Wright? They're to broadcast the sacred music of the performance hall throughout the temple.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That's why the victim could hear the Song of Ceremony in the Séance vision. It was the practice run going on in the performance hall, heard over the speakers.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you for your explanation, You're Benevolence. That makes perfect sense even to a feeble-minded old man like me.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Think nothing of it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now if you wouldn't mind, could you please alter your Insights for us?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I'm getting the hang of this. If I point out an inconsistency, she'll update her Insights accordingly. So if I keep pointing things out, maybe I can knock all of her Insights out after all! I'd better find another inconsistency, no matter how small!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... It's a bit hard to focus on the Insights with the Séance vision going. I'll try using the "Pause" (L</thought> to temporarily stop the vision. There! I paused the vision! I think I can touch the flashing panels <thought>Y/A</thought> to jump to different parts of the vision. I'll try moving the mitamah mark to the flashing red panel there. Okay, now that I know how to get around in the Séance visions... ...it's time to find inconsistencies between the Insights and the vision!)</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The accused swung whatever he was holding down on the victim's head!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're saying the victim's field of vision went dark right after he was struck, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Of course, as anyone with eyes can see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, pardon me, but I must disagree.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Benevolence, please take another look at the exact moment the victim felt pain.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hm...? ......Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Everything goes black and then -- only after that -- the victim feels pain.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I-Inconceivable!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This places the order of events at odds with what you say happened!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">My word!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Pohlkunka! Your Benevolence! What is the meaning of this?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I c-cannot be wrong! My Insights are beyond fallacy!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If what the defense says is true, this is very grave matter indeed! Please forgive me, Your Benevolence, but... ...I'm afraid this contradiction is something we simply can't ignore!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You have something to add, Mr. Payne?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">A thousand apologies. It seems the prosecution has failed to make one tiny thing clear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that would be...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">On the day of the incident, there was a power outage -- a blackout in one part of the temple. And, as I recall, the crime scene was in that sector. The power outage must be why the victim's field of vision went dark. I apologize for neglecting to tell the court this detail. I'm afraid it slipped my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Or rather, you knew all along and are only letting it slip now that it's convenient, Payne!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">The power outage knocked out both the lights and the speakers.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Oh! There was a blackout there, was there?! Well now... That explains everything, does it not?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What do you men, Your Benevolence? Please share your thoughts with us, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The blackout occurred when the accused and the victim were faced with one another. Fearing the victim would flee under the cover of darkness... ...the accused swiftly brought his weapon down on the victim's head.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see! That makes perfect sense, Your Benevolence.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">So the victim was struck after the lights went out. The depth of your insight is awe-inspiring, Your Benevolence! Give her a hand, everyone!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Well done! Long may you live and prosper!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey! I want to live long and prosper, too!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Enough applause. You flatter me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............Now, Your Benevolence, in light of this new information...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, of course. I will alter my Insight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So much for my inconsistency. At least I was able to draw out some new info. And with new info comes a chance to find new inconsistencies. Now to compare the Insights with the vision again, and see what else I can dig up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The accused swung whatever he was holding down on the victim's head!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yes, I've finally found it! This is the gaping hole I've been looking for!</thought> Your Benevolence, as impressive as your Spirit Communion power is, it's not infallible.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You never know when to stop talking, do you? I hope you realize your words are an insult to all adherents of Khura'inism.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defense! Watch what you say! If you don't mind that tongue of yours, you won't have one left to mind!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's certainly not my intention to insult spirit mediums. But maybe I'm not the one who needs to learn when to stop talking.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What malarkey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe you said a few moments ago... ...that the victim could hear the Song of Ceremony thanks to the temple's speakers. But then, how do you explain... ...how the victim could still hear the Song of Ceremony, even after the power went out!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This contradiction of facts can only mean...  ...that the Song of Ceremony Mr. Rohl heard was NOT coming from the speakers!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">What?! Impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What are you saying?! That the song he heard was coming directly from the performance hall?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's exactly what I'm saying. It's the only possible explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But the scene of the crime was nowhere near the performance hall!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. The song couldn't make it all the way to the treasure room... Not unless...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Y-You mean to say...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, the treasure room was NOT the actual scene of the crime. It must have been somewhere else -- somewhere closer to the performance hall!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-Whaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-You can't be serious!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is a glaring contradiction in the claims of Her Benevolence and the prosecution. Therefore, the defense insists that this case be thoroughly re-examined!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What? N-No...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-This is completely unprecedented! An inconsistency in Her Benevolence's Insights...? Unbelievable...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">H-Head not his forked tongue, Your Magistry! These are but the claims of a corrupt lawyer! A feeble ruse from a feeble mind!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-B-But... But the contradiction revealed by the defense... is undeniable... I-I can't... We can't... We can't just turn a blind eye to it!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">B-But the defense's assertion is, in the end, meaningless! Even if the location of the murder turned out to be different... ...it doesn't change what we've seen of the moment of the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I-Indeed! The accused is standing right there in front of the victim! Furthermore, the murder weapon remains raised above his head! My Insights still stand!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I hate to admit it, but she's right. The Séance vision still makes the situation look really grim for Ahlbi.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. I doubt even the defense can dream up an explanation as to why... ...the accused had his hands up over his head.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, this defense dares to dream! <thought>Of making it out of this nightmare alive...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">You what?!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You still insist on trying to tear down my Insights, do you? You'd better be prepared to back up your claim. Remember what will happen to that tongue of yours if we find you are just wagging it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course I can back up my claim! <thought>Just as soon as I think of something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ You appear to be fully prepared, defense. As the embodiment of this court, I give you permission to try and prove your claim. As long as you're willing to stake your life on it.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I concur, Your Magistry. Prepare the tongue shears! Chop-chop!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ch-Chop-chop?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, let's have the bailiff fetch them. I think I saw a suitable pair in the basement. Chop, chop.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Stop, stop...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. I hear that lying lawyers have several tongues to spare. I'm sure he won't miss one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yikes! These people are actually serious! I'm rather attached to my tongue... Think, Phoenix! Think! Other than to raise a weapon, why would Ahlbi have held his hands up like that? Aha! So that's why!</thought> The reason the defendant had his hands up over his head... ...can be explained by something in the crime photo! <thought>What explains why Ahlbi had his hands raised above his head?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Excuse me? What exactly are you pointing at?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This! Er, this general area here...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......I have no idea what you're talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oops! Looks like I was too vague.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Magistry, I believe a vague answer like that deserves a clear penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ooh, goody! It's been so hard to dish out a proper lawyer penalty these days. This brings back such fond memories!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Fire when ready, Your Magistry.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, to savor this rare opportunity... A penalty for the defense!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eeeyowch! <thought>Are you done savoring my savory tears, too? Anyway... let's try that one again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As in the Séance vision... ...I witnessed the defendant raise both of his hands over his head yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You did? Where did you see such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When the police had their guns trained on him as they made their arrest.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! Are you saying...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim was a security guard, and an armed one at that. The defense proposes that the victim had pointed his firearm at Ahlbi. And that's why the defendant's hands were raised in the air!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">P-P-Pohlkunkaaaaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Who would have thought that the Séance vision could be interpreted that way...!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">This is not possible! I-It... can't be!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not bad for a total knockout!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gallery">How dare that lawyer-devil go against Her Benevolence?! He's no better than that traitorous snake, Dhurke!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Traitorous snake? Dhurke? Who's that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">N-No... I can't believe it... A contradiction in one of my Insights...? There has to be some kind of mistake... I... I won't accept it...!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">That's right, Your Benevolence! And I won't accept it, either! It goes against all we hold sacred! Throw him in jail immediately for lese-majesty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Yeah! You said it! Throw him in jail! Yes! Make him pay for the way he disrespected Her Benevolence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... These people are definitely NOT my fans right now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gallery">That's right! Exterminate him! Exterminate! Annihilate!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Peace! Give me peace! I said peeeeeeaaace! Now, everyone, please calm down.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hm...? Is he...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Magistry, please assign this black-hearted attorney a suitable punishment.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ No. I can't charge him with lese-majesty.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-What?! But, why not, Your Magistry?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He was simply following the proper procedure for defending the accused. There's nothing unlawful about that.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">B-But, Your Magistry... Don't you want to wrap this trial up quickly? Why not just give your verdict? Then you can go home and make it up to your wife...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We can't end the trial now, not when we just learned new information about the case.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-Whaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Your Magistry! Not you, too! You would honestly entertain the idea that my Insight contains a contradiction?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Truly, it is shocking. In the twenty-plus years since the DC Act went into effect, such a thing has never occurred. To be honest... I didn't want to believe it, either. But with his life on the line, the defense pointed out an inconsistency. And it is our duty to scrutinize it to the satisfaction of the law.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You dare go against the royal priestess, you... NON-BELIEVER?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, my faith is as strong as ever. But I have a duty to make a fair ruling in this trial. If you insist on interfering with that process, Your Benevolence... ...I'm afraid I must request your removal from this courtroom, royal priestess or not.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">WHAAAT? I'll have you know--!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your Benevolence!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please acquiesce in this, Your Benevolence.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Nngh... Grrrrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If looks could kill...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I won't forget this offense, Barbed Head! I do not admit defeat! I won't!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff, please see Her Benevolence out.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Y-Your mitamah will face due retribution in the Twilight Realm! The demons there will... They'll pluck the barbs right off your stupid head! Ha ha ha ha ha! I hope your suffering will be super-duper painful! And, and! I hope they throw you into a lake of burning fire, yeah! And then, and then...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess she's still just a teenager after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, defense. Mister... Light, was it...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's "Wright," Your Magistry. Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Of course. Mr. Wright. My apologies. Well, now that we have this newly uncovered fact, I suggest we proceed with arguments.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Your Magistry.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, yes... But do not misunderstand me. This doesn't mean I trust you completely. I'll be keeping a close eye on you, so don't even think about lying to this court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I understand, Your Magistry. <thought>Whew! Maybe NOW we can finally run a real trial!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. Arguments, Your Magistry? Very well. I accept your challenge.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? What's with him?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hee hee hee! Oh, the look on your face, Mr. Wright! It's just... Heh heh! It's just too hilarious!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's so funny, Mr. Payne?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The defense still doesn't get it. The "truth" he unearthed is going to bury him and his case instead.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean by that, prosecutor?!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I told you! It's "Chief Prosecutor"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yes... Because that's the point to focus on right now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">The defense is digging its own grave. Consider this, Your Magistry. Why would the victim -- a security guard -- point a gun at the accused?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">"Oh," indeed! Because the accused was about to commit a theft. It's the only logical explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaaaaaa?! <thought>That... does sound pretty logical, actually...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">It doesn't help the accused's situation at all! If anything, it makes him look even more guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I have to agree.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Allow me spell out this "truth" the defense didn't bother to think through. Mr. Rohl came across the accused, just as he was trying to steal the treasure. The guard pointed his gun at the accused, and, just when the power went out... ...the accused murdered the victim and hid his body in the treasure room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gnrk!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">A hand truck for moving heavy treasure around is stored in the treasure room. The accused could have easily moved the body with that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And after all that hard work to knock down those Insights... Ahh, backed into the ol' familiar corner once more...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, do you have a rebuttal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>Ugh. I'm drawing a total blank here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. I hope you're ready to climb that scaffold...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I asked you a question, defense!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>......I've got nothing. I can't think of any grounds for an objection... The only thing to do at this point is ask the defendant himself what happened. But I don't know if Ahlbi will cooperate with me or not...</thought> Ahlbi?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Will you tell us what really happened?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">............</line>
<line speaker="Payne">You don't have to say anything, accused. Fall for his evil trap and you'll only dirty your own soul.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ahlbi, you have to tell me the truth! I can't help you unless you do!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Ungh...... Nngh... Mr. Wright... I'm sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why?! Why won't he trust me?! Is this it? Is this the end... for both of us...? Maya... I'm sorry...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Everybody always told me they're bad, bad people who help dirty criminals go free. I never thought a lawyer would actually try to help me... would actually believe in me... Would risk his own life for me... I never would've even imagined it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Ahlbi...!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">So... that's why I lied. To try and save myself. But I'm not going to lie anymore! If you believe in me enough to put your life on the line... then I'm going to believe in you, too!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-Whaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Allow me... Allow me to explaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaain!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now we're talking! Time to finally get to the bottom of things!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">To be honest, I went into the treasure room lots of times to look at the treasure box.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Even though the temple told you you weren't allowed to go anywhere near it?!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Yes. I'm sorry... Mr. Rohl even saw me once and scolded me. But that box is so beautiful! The way it glows in the dark... I couldn't help myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait. It glows in the dark?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">That's right. It's covered in this special mineral called "fluorenite" that makes it glow. It's absolutely breathtaking. It's really a shame they don't put it on display for the public! Can't you imagine how many people would go on night tours if they did?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If only he applied such passion to telling me the truth earlier...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">On the day of the incident, I was on my way to the treasure room again... ...when I ran into Mr. Rohl on the great stairs.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So those were not the treasure room stairs in the Séance vision...?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">No, they were the great stairs that connect the hallway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Makes sense. The vision wasn't clear enough to show us what was at the top of those stairs...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">All of a sudden, Mr. Rohl drew his gun and threatened me with it. I quickly put my hands up. Mr. Rohl... He acted so scary... For some reason, he had his scarf over his mouth. I couldn't read his expression at all. Just then, the power went out. So I took that chance to hightail it out of there! I ran for my life! Even now, when I try to think back on it... ...all I can remember are the gun and the piercing look in Mr. Rohl's eyes... That must've been when I dropped the notice scroll.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix *incorrectly identified as Ahlbi in-game"><thought>Which means someone else brought it to the treasure room, along with Mr. Rohl's body.</thought> Did Mr. Rohl say anything to you when you ran into him on on the stairs?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is it, Ahlbi...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I have no idea why, but... ...he asked me a strange question. "Did you steal it?" he said.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I'm sorry... I'm sorry I didn't say all this before. I didn't think anybody would believe me.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. A grand speech. One that confirmed my suspicions that... you were the thief!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Nnnnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why does every new piece of information have to seem so incriminating...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Nnngh... Shah'do... What do I do, Shah'do...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">And what better reason to suspect the boy than seeing the treasure box in his hands? In the course of his rounds, the victim must've noticed that the treasure had been stolen. And then, just after that... ...he ran into the accused, Ahlbi Ur'gaid.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Nnngh... No... Th-That's not what happened...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Therefore, the one who stole the treasure and killed the victim... ...can be none other than the accused!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Nnngh... Aaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-What now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">Rrr... Ruff, ruff! Ruff, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">H-Hey! Shah'do! Down, boy!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well! What do we have here?!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I-I'm sorry about this. This is my dog, Shah'do.</line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">Ruff, ruff, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You nearly gave me a heart attack!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's what was making his bag move...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">Ruff, ruff! Ruff, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Can't you quiet that yappy mutt down?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Shah'do says that Mr. Rohl made a mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You can understand him?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh! Don't tell me this a surprise witness for the defense?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I beg your your pardon? You're not thinking of cross-examining an animal, are you?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Of course not, Your Magistry! <thought>Not this time, anyway...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Phew. Well, I'm glad to hear that. I thought I'd have to reassess my assessment of your sanity for a second there...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I'D better reassess my strategy... and fast! I have to somehow show that somebody else could've struck the victim, or we're sunk.</thought> Wh-While it's true that the defendant was standing in front of the victim when he died... ...it doesn't mean somebody else couldn't have struck the victim at that time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you're going to go that far... ...then I hope this means you have another angle of approach ready.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Exactly! I mean, who but the accused -- standing front and center -- could've done it? Unless you can back up your claim, it's nothing more than conjecture.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay... Come on, Phoenix! I know I can think up something convincing... Where else could the victim have been struck from?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Payne">From there? Using the treasure box as the murder weapon?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... <thought>I guess nobody could reach that far...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Nothing but lies and claptrap every time you open your mouth. How very lawyer-like.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Magistry, it would be very judge-like of you to give him a penalty at this time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ack! Come on, Phoenix! There's gotta be something more convincing than that... With the treasure box as the murder weapon, the culprit had to have been nearby.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">With the defendant standing in front of the victim... ...isn't it possible that the victim could've been struck from behind?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">From behind, you say? Hmm... I see. Yes, I suppose it's not outside the realm of possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Good. Now at least I have some breathing room.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">But who do you suppose it could have been?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, uh... The true culprit, naturally -- the one who actually committed the theft and murder!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The true culprit? And I suppose you have a true timeline of events to go along with that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should've known I'd have to explain everything... All right. If we assume the true culprit struck the victim from behind, then that means...</thought> After going to the treasure room and stealing the treasure, the true culprit tried to escape. But then Mr. Rohl appeared, making his rounds. I imagine the culprit then quickly hid in the storeroom at the other end of the hallway.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. You're grasping at straws, Mr. Wright. Admit it. You have nothing but baseless conjecture.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm going to look for something to base it on right now! Ahlbi? When you ran into Mr. Rohl in the hallway, was there anyone around the storeroom area?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">...I don't know. There might've been somebody there, but I couldn't see... I was only halfway down the stairs, so I couldn't see the ends of that hallway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... <thought>Swing and a miss.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">Ruff, ruff! Ruff, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Oh! Shah'do says that someone was there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I see. Thank you for that. <thought>Too bad his testimony is inadmissible...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You think this is a joke?</thought> Maybe the defendant didn't happen to see this other person... ...but that doesn't mean the true culprit couldn't have been there in the hallway!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Unfortunately for you... ...only the accused and the victim were there in that hallway at the time of the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How can you continue to make that assertion?!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Because there was a witness. A very reliable eyewitness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What?!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Magistry, the prosecution would like to call its witness to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Calling an eyewitness to the stand, hm? It's been decades since that's happened.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">And unlike the defense's witness, you can rest assured that there are no pets involved.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That was a low blow...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">Rrr... Ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. I'll allow it. And now, for something we've not heard in quite some time: Bring the witness to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Witness, please state your name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Pees'lubn Andistan'dhin's the name. I'm, like, Tehm'pul Temple's head monk. Can ya dig?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! If it isn't Instructor Andistan'dhin! You're the eyewitness?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Instructor"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Not only is Mr. Andistan'dhin Tehm'pul Temple's head monk... ...but he's also a renowned dahmalan expert.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry to have to ask, but what's a "dahmalan"?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Check it! Here she is, my sweet serenader, my one and only. Groovy, right? But you heard our sultry sounds once before, brother... When dragon and tiger battle...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's the song from the Dance of Devotion!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Right on, brother. The Song of Ceremony. Playing this tune together is a precious gig for me and my girl here, ya dig?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The Song of Ceremony, the song that was playing at the time of the murder...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">O Holy Mother! May the righteous sounds of my dahmalan serve as my offering to you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wonderful! A great performance, as always!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">This is my thing, ya know? My bag. I make instruments speak, baby. By the by, Magistry Pops... ...no dahmalan class today?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No. I'm afraid this trial has gone into overtime... thanks to this lawyer over there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The class the judge wanted to attend was a dahmalan lesson?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Well, ya know what they say, baby. Never trust the lawyer-man! But transgressors against the Holy Mother have to be brought to justice.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Thank you for your cooperation, Mr. Andistan'dhin. As the treasure's keeper... ...you must've been shocked to learn that it had been stolen.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Yeah, man... That was not cool.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Keeping the treasure safe is one of your duties, Mr. Andistan'dhin?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">That's right, brother. This here's the one and only treasure box key... ...and I keep it on me at all times. Can ya dig? But the sneaky thief went and cracked open that sucker anyway... Total bummer, man.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that's the key to the treasure box, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">You know it, baby! It's called the "Magatama Key," and it's a historical artifact, to boot. It's been passed down from head monk to head monk at Tehm'pul Temple.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The Magatama Key, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">And now someone's jacked the treasure, on my watch... It's a real buzzkill, man... How am I ever gonna face Her Holiness again! O Holy Mother! Please find it in your infinite mercy to forgive me! Please guide this lost and humble lamb!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I always get the faaaaar out ones...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Mr. Andistan'dhin, you witnessed the accused and the victim heading to the treasure room?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">You know it, baby! Best believe I scoped that tiny transgressor...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Would you please give the court your testimony regarding what you saw?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">To bring justice against the transgressor, man, yes, of course, I'll do all I can. In the name of Her Holiness, I vow to sing, naught but the truth, I swear to bring! Hit me!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">After morning Dance of Devotion, to go back to my chamber, I got the notion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Tell me I was hallucinating just now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Like, can you believe Mr. Rohl bit the big one after that? Harsh, man.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I share your sentiments. You were the one who discovered the victim's body, weren't you, Mr. Andistan'dhin?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? You found the body as well? <thought>He really is a key witness, then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">That's right, brother. After the blackout, I went to reset the breaker and give power back to the people. The circuit box is near my chamber, so I'm always the man for the job, ya feel me?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The breakers are in the first floor hallway, in front of the storeroom.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">On the way, I got a whiff of something funky -- blood, man. Really harsher my mellow. I knew something wasn't kosher, so I swung by the treasure room to see what's what. And it was like, whoa, man! There was poor Mr. Rohl, dead as a doornail!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">In the interval between the end of the Dance of Devotion and the blackout... ...the only ones who went to the scene of the crime were the victim and the accused. So you see, Mr. Andistan'dhin's unassailable account is what led to the accused's arrest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> Isn't it possible that the murder took place before the end of the Dance of Devotion?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. I'm afraid that's not possible. The victim was in the performance hall until the very end of the dance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He was?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Would you like some proof? How's this -- a photo, taken by a tourist, of the morning Dance of Devotion.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">My! What graceful dancing! I can almost hear the sound of Mr. Andistan'dhin's dahmalan now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Payne's right. There's Mr. Rohl, on duty.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. Never underestimate The Incredible Payne!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nrgh. So in addition to Rayfa's Insights, he had backup evidence lined up, too, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">As head monk, my monks-in-training are like my own kids -- like family -- can ya dig it? I should've taught Ahlbi better, man... Before Her Holiness, the Holy Mother, O Ahlbi, confess your sins, my young brother.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">H-Head Monk Andistan'dhin... I-I didn't kill Mr. Rohl... So I don't have anything to confess to the Holy Mother...</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">What?! ...Bogus, little man. Your faith is weak, like a wet paper bag. Are ya feeling me? Spare the rod, hey baby, Spoil the child, not maybe. Her Holiness is magnanimous, son. If you confess your guilt... ...she'll forgive you in the Twilight Realm.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't suppose she could forgive him in this realm first...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defense, please begin your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">After morning Dance of Devotion, to go back to my chamber, I got the notion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Lay it on me, man.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How dare you interrupt the performance of the great Pees'lubn Andistan'dhin?! I was really enjoying that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry... But, you know... there's something about that name I can't put my finger on...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's so funny about "Pees'lubn Andistan'dhin"?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">You had a question for me, brother?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were playing something during the Dance of Devotion, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">You know it, baby. I was playing my beautiful girl here, this dahmalan. In offering to Her Holiness, I play the music, and the singers sing the Song of Ceremony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Andistan'dhin's playing is the best in the kingdom. It must please Her Holiness greatly. Now, then. Could you continue with your testimony, Mr. Andistan'dhin?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">For the Holy Mother, I keep on truckin'! This dahmalan still needs some plucking!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Don't you know my chamber's on the way, to the temple's treasure room, hey, hey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Yeah, man. No sweat. My chamber is on the way from the performance hall to the treasure room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So anyone going to the treasure room would have to pass by Andistan'dhin's chamber...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Give Pees'lubn a chance...</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Any small footsteps I can quite clearly hear, if anyone to the treasure room goes near.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Tehm'pul Temple is a groovy old building, built from Mother Nature's finest. You can hear a pin drop through the wooden walls, ya dig?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>In an old building like that, I guess the walls must be pretty thin.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">And that's how Mr. Andistan'dhin could know the culprit's movements. It's all thanks to the Holy Mother's divine protection.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Right on, my man! I dedicate this testimony to Her Holiness!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Through the window, I did spy, little Ahlbi with my own eye.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">That's right, brother. There's a courtyard outside the window of my chamber. Across the courtyard, I can see the window of the hallway to the treasure room, man.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Judging from the diagram, I guess that's plausible.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">A view of the courtyard your chamber? How nice that must be! I bet it's beautiful at this time of year, what with Khura'inese butterflies flittering about.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">You know it, Pops! I often look out into the courtyard while playing my dahmalan. And it goes a little something like this...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Ahlbi was the only one. Ahlbi was the only one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Ahlbi is practically family, man. The smooth groove of his shoes are easy to pick out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But how do you know he went to the treasure room? Didn't you think it was possible he went to the storeroom at the other end of the hall?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">No way, man. I saw him with my own two eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You saw him?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">In the treasure room, this you can believe. My peepers peeped this sneaky sneak Ahlbi.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">And tell us where, where it is you stood, when you saw the accused, if you would?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">When I heard the footsteps, I looked out the window. From my window, I can see... ...the window of the first-floor hallway, across the courtyard, ya dig? And, through that window, I saw Ahlbi walking into the treasure room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Should I have him add this statement to his testimony?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you please add that statement to your testimony, Mr. Andistan'dhin?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">You got it, brother.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"Through the window, I did spy, little Ahlbi with my own eye."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... That statement doesn't sound very relevant. No need to add it to the testimony.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Mind if I sing, sing my song, brother?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Before the blackout, one other than Rohl, only Ahlbi to the treasure room did stroll.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Whoa, man. You lawyers are as uptight as they say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't it possible that someone else could have snuck past?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">The answer, my friend, is... squeaky wooden floorboards, baby. They make such a racket, not even the quietest cat could sneak by me, ya dig?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, that makes sense. And all of that just now was simply more of the attorney's unfounded suspicions, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">That's the truth, baby. It's all that I sing. The truth is all, it's everything.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Words of wisdom! Words of truth! Erm... Baby tooth, forsooth, phone booth!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Much thanks to Mr. Andistan'dhin. Let's bring an end to defense grandstandin'.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're not stopping me until my client goes free! <thought>Wait a minute! Why am I singing?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Right on! Even the lawyer is joining in, baby! Everybody's starting to feel the groovy vibe of my far-out rhythm.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I refuse to let him run this show!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I didn't notice any inconsistencies in his testimony... Looks like I'm going to have to Press his statements to draw out more information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I found the flaw I've been looking for. Andistan'dhin was in his chamber on the second floor... ...but there was something that definitely should've been blocking his view...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's something off about that, Mr. Andistan'dhin.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">My music is off? I'm sorry ya feel that way, man. Maybe this vibe ain't topping the charts where you're from. What's your poison? Orchestra? Jazz Soul?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's nothing wrong with my ears, witness. But something's not quite right with your eyes. Mr. Andistan'dhin, you've been lying to this court.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Now why would I lie? I got nothing to hide. Truth and truth alone is all I sing. Lying, y'all? Now, lying ain't my thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I contend otherwise. Do you recognize this object, Mr. Andistan'dhin?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">It's a temple notice, man. What of it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In this notice, the following instruction to the temple monks is written: "...all of the hallway shutters will remain shut for today's Dance of Devotion."</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Whatchoo talkin' bout, Phoenix?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm talkin' about the fact that from your chamber... ...you couldn't have seen ANYONE going into the treasure room through those shutters!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Gaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like you didn't get the memo.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">...No way! I don't believe it, man!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you don't believe it, why don't you read the notice for yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Umm... Let's see... Something, something, "will," something, "for," something, something...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that your idea of "reading"?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">I'm not so hot at reading Khura'inese, man. I usually get one of the other monks to read stuff for me, ya know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Doesn't that make your duties as head monk a little difficult?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Hey, cut me some slack, man! I only moved to this country six months ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's quite recent, isn't it? So... how did someone who's only been here six months become head monk of a temple?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">How little you understand. Religious faith can't be measured in months or years. I've only been an adherent of Khura'inism for three months, myself. The Holy Mother's teachings really spoke to me, prompting me to stay in this country.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Or was it the fact that there are no lawyers here that spoke to you, hm?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Mr. Payne, I know just how you feel, my man. Her Holiness's teachings spoke to me, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ladies and gentlemen, I present: Brother Dumb, and Brother Dumber... Well, I know why Payne suddenly became a believer in Khura'inism... ...but could Andistan'dhin have had an ulterior motive for becoming a believer, too?</thought> Mr. Andistan'dhin. Were you really in your chamber as you claim?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Wh-What? Hey, be chill, brother...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Weren't you, instead, somewhere else?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to Mr. Andistan'dhin's testimony, he saw Ahlbi with his own eyes. Therefore, is it really "nonsense" to suggest he could've seen Ahlbi from somewhere else?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">W-Well...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you have a theory, defense? Do you know where Mr. Andistan'dhin was, if not in his chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If he wasn't in his room, then... If Ahlbi had gone down the hallway towards the treasure room... ...there are only a few places he could've seen Ahlbi from.</thought> I do have a theory, Your Magistry. Let's say the witness really did see Ahlbi going towards the treasure room. What then? The defense proposes this is the only place he could've been to see Ahlbi go down that hall!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">What you're saying, Mr. Defense, doesn't make an honest lick of sense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">According to the assertions you yourself made earlier, had the witness been standing there... ...he wouldn't have been able to see the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wasting time so contemptuously, I believe the defense deserves a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Yeah Pops, I agree, most readily!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sooo NOT groovy... I'd better think this through a little bit more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-There?! But you just suggested earlier... ...that that's where the true culprit might have been!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>True. But, no matter how I look at it, this is the only place Andistan'dhin could've been.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Foreign Lawyer... D-Don't tell me... Are you accusing Mr. Andistan'dhin of being the true culprit in this case?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Accuse Andistan'dhin...? Is that really what I want to do here...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, defense?! Speak up, now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The only place Andistan'dhin could've been is where the true culprit most likely was. Well, I've come this far. There's no turning back now! Here goes!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Magistry. I contend there's a strong possibility this witness is the murderer.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Th-That's nothing but groundless conjecture!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And there's one more thing. Do you remember what was said in the opening argument?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The opening argument?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">During that argument, it was suggested that Ahlbi... ..."used his position as monk-in-training to get his hands on the treasure."</line>
<line speaker="Payne">That's right! And what of it?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, why don't we try this twist on for size? The thief used his position as head monk of the temple to get a hold of the treasure!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WH-WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Y-You joshin' me, man...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The key to the treasure box has been passed down from head monk to head monk. What better position to be in if you want to steal the treasure?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Y-Y-You can't possibly be serious!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Does this mean you're claiming that Mr. Andistan'dhin's oath of faith... ...is nothing but a lie designed to get him close to the treasure?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness hasn't been truthful in his testimony to this court. So clearly, he isn't above lying!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Nnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Didn't you swear to the Holy Mother that "naught but the truth" would you bring?! In light of that, I don't think it's unfair to call your faith into question!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Nnnghaaaaaaagh...!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="???">Andistan'dhin:</line>
<line speaker="Payne">What?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What was that, Mr. Andistan'dhin...?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Lawyer-man... You really are the lowest of the low. You've gone and said something I can't forgive... You called my belief into question, my faith in the Holy Mother... And nobody... NOBODY gets away with that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What on earth?! That music! It's making my ears bleed!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">This is the music of my SOUL! DEATH TO THE LAWYER! I'm the twilight messenger. Can't ya tell?! Gonna take this lying lawyer straight to hell! He's drippin' with lies, runnin' with philistines. I'm gonna send that lawyer to the guillotines!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And now for something completely different...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">That plinkity-plunk music just wouldn't let me express my RAGE!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your rage, huh? Isn't the real source of your anger having your lie exposed?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">You just don't get it. If I lied, it's 'cause you drove me to it! All sniffin' around and suspicious and throwin' out false accusations!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but as a lawyer, I'm afraid that's my job.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Yeah, well, lawyers are crap! Keep making noise and I'll have to use my partner on you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'M the one making noise...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Hey! So you wanna know the truth, huh? Think you can handle the truth, do ya? Fine. Let's see you try! Feel the heat of my brutal death beat! Savage, right? Sweatin' bullets, ain'tcha? The screams of my soul are gonna make a mosh pit outta this peanut gallery!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Did he really just win the court over with that performance...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Yo, geezer! I got something to testify! Get ready for the howling of my SOUL! I call this chart-topper: Soul-Screaming Truth!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">The priestess's dance had come to an end. To the music storeroom my way I did wend.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is that music? I've never heard anything like it! And it's so fast, it's making my head spin!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">THIS IS DAHMALAN METAL! Hey yo, geezer, how're those ears ringin'?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't know much about music... ...but I've got chills, and they're multiplying...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Hey, you scared, lawyer-man? Run away, run away, fast as ya can!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">What a wonderful rhythm! The perfect accompaniment for further deliberations! Now, Mr. Andistan'dhin, what did you go to the music storeroom for?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Hey, I went to put my dahmalan away. She's my precious partner. Gotta give her a good rest after playin' in the rite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But then why did you lie before?!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">BECAUSE YOU'D SEND ME TO HELL!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">We all know about lawyers and their lying, lawyerly ways! Am I right, people?! If I admitted I went to the storeroom, he'd have drummed up a false charge on me! I didn't want to get sent to hell. Whadaya say?</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">He's right! That sooo would've happened!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Now I see why that Defense Culpability Act was passed! You feel me, Khura'in?!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Yeah! You said it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is it too much to ask for a low-key trial...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Now, are you punks ready to rock or what?!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Yeaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">I can't hear you! I said, ya ready to teach this lying lawyer how we do things around here?!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yeaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">All right! Then I'm gonna lay it on ya one more time! The screaming truth of my SOUL!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">The priestess's dance had come to an end. To the music storeroom my way I did wend.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">And on what grounds would you base that accusation? Got anything to show for it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's right. I don't really have any proof... And yet...</thought> Well, you can't prove that you DIDN'T go to the treasure room either!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You stole the treasure and were ready to make your getaway when you saw Mr. Rohl. So you panicked and ran into the music storeroom. Isn't that right?!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I feel like I'm being stabbed by icy stares from every direction...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">The silence is your answer, lawyer-man. This audience knows the score. Just what we needed! A moment of silence to bid this lawyer's baseless claim goodbye.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do they have to hate lawyers so much in this country...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">I said it before and I'll say it again, lawyer-man. After the priestess's dance, I went to the music storeroom.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Death truth is what you DREAD! Hear me shred!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">It's the blade of truth that's gonna send your lawyer soul to HELL! A sea of blood will be the last thing you ever see!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not sure I want to get what he's saying...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">I don't expect a bobblehead like you to understand. Either you get it and you feel it, or ya don't, simple as that!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">From my spot in front of the storeroom, I saw Ahlbi creep to the treasure room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Come to think of it, he was glancin' around all shifty-like. You could tell he was up to no good. Shady, I tell ya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's that saying about people who live in glass houses...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Well, he was about to steal the treasure, so it only stands to reason he'd look furtive.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">What's that, people? "Only the Holy Mother knows the truth," you say? Bzzt! Wrong! Pees'lubn knows the score, baby! From my lips to our Holy Mother's ear, an artist only sings what he saw there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>In other words... ...my reasoning isn't good enough for god-boy here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">And what did you see next, Mr. Andistan'dhin?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">And trailing from behind, hound on the scent, I saw Paht Rohl. After Ahlbi he went.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">What?! You don't get it?! "It's always the same, y'all. Lyrics questioned without mercy. The more famous the song, the greater the controversy."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It wasn't your lyrical sense I was questioning...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">I say "hound on the scent," like a hunting dog, 'cause, you know, Rohl was a guard, and...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh-oh. Here we go...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">...The inspiration came to me suddenly, like a flash, and--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Hey! You're the one who asked!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I knew I shouldn't have asked...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Andistan'dhin, you're still on the stand, so please stick to your testimony. You can explain your lyrics to me alter in dahmalan class.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Fine. Have it your way, geezer. The show must go on! Slash an' thrash!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Me and my girl here, innocent and sweet, back by the storeroom. Can't be beat!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">............ There! Get the picture?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Picture"?! What picture?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Andistan'dhin is requesting that you do not ask him the same thing over and over.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Hey, geezer! You got it in one! Take a bow, baby!</line>
<line speaker="Judge"><thought>How the heck did he understand that?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">What was I doing in the music storeroom, you ask? I already told you. I was taking care of my partner in crime, here, getting ready to put her away. But see... would you believe it...</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Then out went the power. Ticket to the midnight. Blacker than blackest black, robbing all sight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Like I said, I was in the music storeroom. My girl had been sounding a little off, so I had to get her back in tune.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't it true that you were actually in the hallway at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">The hallway, you say? Why would I be in the hallway?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were waiting for Mr. Rohl to come back from his patrol of the treasure room. Now that he'd discovered that the treasure had been stolen, you were going to kill him!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Lawyer-man, just as always, so full of bull, spewing noxious lies and pullin' the wool. Filthy liar, through and through. And I ain't never, ever gonna forgive you!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Utter lies with no evidence. As always, his claims are just tenuous.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Hey, nice, prosecutor! I'm picking up what you're throwing down!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Someone stop their jam session... Please...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I only understood about half of what this guy's saying... I suppose I should press his statements, but I'm not really looking forward to it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's not good...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Heh heh heh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's so funny, Pees'lubn Andistan'dhin?</thought> Nevertheless, the possibility is still there! You can't deny the witness could have killed the victim under cover of darkness!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. It seems you've forgotten that the outage happened by chance, not design.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, that's right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, that's right... <thought>I did forget about that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">It's not like the witness planned the outage so he could take advantage of the darkness. And, without darkness, it would've been hard to sneak up behind Mr. Rohl and kill him.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're right. Even I would notice someone coming up behind me. Well, defense? What do you have to say about that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What CAN I say about that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Mr. Wright, your claim is completely without merit... ...unless you want to argue that the witness somehow magically made the outage happen!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, maybe not "magically," but... Wait, that's it!</thought> I contend the witness could have made the power outage happen... ...with no magic necessary.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">What?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You have a theory, defense?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All he had to do was make use of something shown on this diagram. <thought>What did the witness use to make the power outage happen?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's with the silent treatment?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness used that to cause the blackout? I would love to see you show us how that would be possible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like I got it wrong.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">It seems there's been a blackout in the defense's brain!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nngh... Come on. Think, Phoenix! There must've been some way for Andistan'dhin to cause the outage...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness was in the storeroom. The circuit box is on the storeroom end of the hallway. There's nothing really magical about turning off the breaker, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Gnrk!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Nice try, but that theory doesn't hold water, lawyer-man.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And why not?!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">You're saying I turned the breaker off, and then snuck up on Mr. Rohl and hit him? In pitch-black darkness, with no source of light whatsoever? That what you're saying?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Ha ha ha! With the lights off, that hallway is blacker than a hundred midnights. You can't see the hand in front of your face! How could anybody commit murder like that? Unless it was somebody standing right in front of the victim -- like the accused!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I hate when he's right... But I can't just let his point stand!</thought> W-Well, maybe the victim was holding something that served as a guide?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A guide through the darkness?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">"Something"? That's more than a little vague, wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">You ain't gonna move this room with a half-baked hunch like that, bro! You gotta hit 'em hard, really make 'em feel it, you hear me?! Just like my verse, baby! Woo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, I'm afraid I don't understand the witness's lyrics very well, either... But, in a trial, your arguments have to be clear and precise. Let's see some of that clarity and precision now, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh-oh. What do I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Can you present to us something that could have served as a guide through the darkness?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I can't very well come right out and say "No, I can't." Even if I wanted to. The whole trial would be over if I did that. I have to say something -- anything -- even if it's just a bluff!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, I can! <thought>Because there HAS to be something!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right. Let's see what you have, defense. What could the victim have been holding that served as a guide through the darkness?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Is NOT what I mean to say...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You changed your answer based on my reaction, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ohh, he's good...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Hmph. Lawyers! Sad, pathetic creatures...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Time for a sad, pathetic penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Nice pitch on that scream, man. Rock those pipes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Magistry, please let me try again!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Yeah! Let us hear that sick crescendo one more time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. I'll allow you to give it another try.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe the victim was holding... the treasure box.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Huuuh?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Have you gone mad?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, the box glows in the dark, so you could use it as a sort of beacon.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well. I guess you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">But why in the world would the victim be holding the treasure box?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh, well... because... <thought>Your guess is as good as mine...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gallery">What is this lawyer talking about? Nonsense and lies yet again! Just give him the death penalty already!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is there no way to win them over...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defense... ...are we going to be needing those tongue shears after all?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, You're Magistry...</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Yeah, man! Do it, do it! Then we can jam out to this lawyer's shrieks of pain! Ha ha ha! Better get those screams of agony out now, lawyer-man... ...while you still have a tongue to scream with!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I, uh, guess I'd better come up with a reason. No pressure or anything...</thought> A-As to why the victim was holding the treasure box... ...it can easily be explained as thus! <thought>Brain, don't fail me now. What reason could the victim possibly have had to be holding that treasure box?</thought> The victim was holding the treasure box because he was...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because he was a security guard.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I beg your pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rohl removed the treasure from the treasure room in order to protect it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What on earth are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He must have known that the treasure would be stolen on that day. Maybe he'd received a warning from the culprit...? And, so, before the treasure could be stolen, Mr. Rohl decided to take it somewhere safe!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! How thrilling...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Oh! You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">He never mentioned a word of anything like that to me, and I'm the head monk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm... suddenly not so confident about that answer...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whew! I just came dangerously close to having my soul sullied by this lawyer's lies!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But I'm not lying! <thought>Guess I'd better try again! What reason could the victim possibly have had for holding that treasure box...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because he was a devout believer.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">What's this, now?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If he was such a devout believer... ...he would have upheld the rule of forbidding anyone from even looking at the treasure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, you certainly have a very good point there...</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">That's...! Why...! I...! Say...! ...he's just making up a bunch of random nonsense as he goes along!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can't say I disagree.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not nonsense! I have a proper theory! <thought>What reason could the victim possibly have had for holding that treasure box...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's an idea I just happened to stumble upon... ...but I think it might just be the answer. And... it would turn this whole trial upside-down!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hello? Defense? Are you still with us? Let's hear this "easy explanation" you promised!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't it possible that it was because the victim himself was the thief?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The victim?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The thief...?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Ha ha ha ha! What kind of bull are you spewing now?! Your Magistry, this guy's off his rocker.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If the victim was the thief, everything we've learned so far would all make sense. And it would give us a completely new way to interpret the victim's actions! After the morning Dance of Devotion, Mr. Rohl went to the treasure room. He grabbed the box that contained the treasure and started to take off with it. But then he ran into Ahlbi on the great stairs. That's why Mr. Rohl pulled his gun on Ahlbi. Then, when the blackout occurred... ...Mr. Rohl was bludgeoned to death in the darkness. This explains why the victim would be holding the glowing treasure box in the dark. And how it would've been possible for someone other than the accused to kill him!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Do you have any idea what you're saying?!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">You're unbelievable, lawyer-man! I think you've lost it! Ha ha! That's the craziest thing I've ever heard! Rohl, trying to roll the temple?! That devout believer?! That pious Khura'inist?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I won't allow you to disparage the victim's departed soul with unfounded allegations. I hope you're prepared to back up your claim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Of course, Your Magistry.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Oh, really? In that case, can we assume you have proof?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh-oh. Proof, huh? Do I have any proof? But I can't back down now!</thought> Yes, I have proof! <thought>In my dreams...</thought> The proof that Mr. Rohl was the thief... ...may have been left behind on a certain piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Let's see your evidence, and be ready to stand behind it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Footprints, fingerprints -- I'll take anything at this point! I need proof... something that would've been involved with the theft... ...and that might still have some trace evidence on it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What proof do you have that the victim might have been the thief?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Would you, now? I don't think that piece of evidence will give us any answers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops. Looks like I got it wrong.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps you would like to examine this penalty instead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH! <thought>Nnngh... Okay, don't overthink this, Phoenix. It's gotta be something that might still hold some trace of it being touched... And if the victim was the thief, what's something he would have touched?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'll give you another chance, defense. And this time, show me evidence you can stand behind!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense would like to examine the treasure box! There might be trace evidence on it that would show that the victim had held it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Might"? You'd better hope you turn up something more definitive than that, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, sir, Your Magistry!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well... Bailiff! Bring the treasure box!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There you are, defense. You're free to examine it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I don't find something now, my entire argument up to this point will be blown. Plus... there's that little matter of the ol' tongue shears... I have to find something! I just have to!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now, to make sure I remember how to do this... I can rotate the evidence by sliding the Touch Screen. I can zoom in and out with the slider on the left, too, to get a better look. And if I ever get too turned around... ...I can always touch "Reset" to return things to this initial state. I'd better search every inch of this box carefully... ...and touch anything of interest to check it out in detail.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is the lock. It was forced open. I don't really see anything else of note about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's a butterfly relief here. I've seen this same butterfly shape here and there all over Khura'in. Interesting, but I guess it doesn't really help me prove anything...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So this is where the Founder's Orb was, huh? I doubt there's any trace of the orb left here now... Although, I don't really know anything about the orb, so who knows?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... The lid of the box was forced open... But while the victim was holding the box, the lid must've been closed. I'll try closing the lid, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Hey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What?!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">You son of a-- You locked it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So? <thought>What's the big deal?</thought> I thought you can open it with that key you're wearing.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">...Y-Yeah, I can, no sweat...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Then why is there a bucketload dripping off of you over there?</thought> I think I'd like to open this box back up again. Could you lend me your Magatama Key?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">...Sure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, let's see. Where's the keyhole...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, it's the "Magatama Key"... ...so wouldn't it go in the hole above the magatama mark?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? It won't open.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">...Hmph. W-Would ya look at that! The thief must've busted the lock when they forced the box open!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Really...? 'Cause I'm not so sure about that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>In any case, I'd better take another good look. I have to find proof that the victim was holding this box!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This lid is really shut tight! Hrrrrrnh! Huuunh! *huff, huff, huff, huff* I can't budge it, no matter how hard I try.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Th-This bloodstain...! It shows the outline of a hand! Could the be what I've been looking for...?</thought> Your Magistry, take a look at this! There's a bloodstain here that outlines the shape of a hand!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Really? Let me see that... Oh, my! Y-You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now I'm getting somewhere!</thought> I believe the bloodstain is an outline of the victim's hand as he was holding the box.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even as he was being struck, he held on tight to the precious treasure box. After all, he'd gone through a lot of trouble to steal it. The blood from his head wound splattered across his hand and onto the box.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. Mr. Wright, where is your proof that the outline is that of the victim's hand?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What...? <thought>I should've seen this coming.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Either show proof, or prepare to meet the shears. Or you could save us all some time and bite your tongue out now and submit it instead.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That... I did NOT see coming...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, defense? How about it? Do you have proof that the outline is of the victim's hand?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Where would proof of something like that even be?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please submit your evidence at this time. What evidence shows that the outline on the treasure box is that of the victim's hand?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. What connection does that have to the victim's hand?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...W-Well, we can't unequivocally say that it DOESN'T have a connection... can we?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ Bailiff! Bring the shears!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No! Wait! Please give me another chance!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...*sigh* Very well. But, Bailiff, do bring those shears anyway. Just in case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess I'd better come up with some proof -- and fast!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've got it! This is the evidence that's going to save my beloved tongue!</thought> Mr. Payne, despite your claims about my "forked tongue"... ...it just so happens I have the proof you require.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">You do?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's right here in this crime photo.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is? Where? Defense, please point it out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What proves that the bloodstain outline on the box is that of the victim's hand, you ask?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Payne">What am I supposed to be looking at, exactly? I don't see anything of interest there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look closer! Just give your eyes a second to adjust! Wait for it... Waaait for it...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...I'm waiting, and I still don't see anything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well, if you'd take off those ridiculous sunglasses... This is a court of law, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">What?! These are my lucky sunglasses! You take that back!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Covering up one's own mistake by tearing down others... How uncalled for. Penalty! For being a sore loser, defense!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeowch! <thought>Nnngh... Let's try that again -- minus the mistakes this time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Payne, take a good look at the victim's hand. See this? That's blood.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If we place Mr. Rohl's hand inside the bloody outline...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Y-You think the blood on his hand would complete the splatter?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly! <thought>Here goes nothing...</thought> And if they do form one complete splatter, it would prove my theory correct!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then... Then... the victim really was holding the box...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm willing to bet my life on it. The defense reasserts that the victim was the thief who stole the treasure box!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Y-You can't be serious! I-I protest! There's... There's no way they would ever match up! I assert that it's patently impossible for-- --OWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWW!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Talk about tongue karma... Sounds like he just bit his.</thought> What's the matter, Mr. Payne? Did your forked tongue get tangled up in there? Or were you trying to submit your own tongue to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Whai, yuuuu...! Nnnnnnnnnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can hardly believe it. Apparently, not everything out of the defense's mouth is a bluff.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course not, Your Magistry. This tongue doesn't lie. And I'd like to continue to use my tongue in the future, too, if you wouldn't mind. <thought>He never has to know it really WAS a bluff...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">No! Not Mr. Rohl! I can't believe it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, Ahlbi. I know it's upsetting news... He must've needed the money badly, probably to support his family. After all, he even gave up his dream of becoming a monk to help them...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Oh! So that thing Mr. Rohl would say to me...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">"Ahlbi, you train hard and make sure you become a monk one day! Don't end up like me," he'd say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, he was probably warning you not to end up like a thief...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">*sniffle*... Mr. Rohl...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Oh! That's a very good point. It doesn't make much sense, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The real murder weapon...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...Was something else...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The blood was thought to have gotten on the box when the box was used as a weapon. But it turns out that wasn't the case. The blood splattered onto the treasure box the victim was holding... ...when he was struck with the real weapon. THAT'S what really happened! Isn't that right, Mr. Andistan'dhin?!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">............ Are you insinuating I'm the one who used this "real weapon"?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you saying I'm wrong in my "Andistan'dhin"?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Ha ha ha ha ha ha! You got me riled up, lawyer-man! I feel a song comin' on! Looking for a weapon that just don't exist. Pathetic lawyer-man, drop into the abyss! Despicable lawyer-man, yo you make me sick! You can disappear, just like a magic trick! Worthless lawyer-man, done in by a weapon. For you, miserable wretch, hell doth beckon! Yeaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I know I don't need to remind you, defense... ...that your life is on the line.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know, You're Magistry.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yet you're prepared to risk it on this mere idea of a "real murder weapon"?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">DEATH TO THE LAWYER!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is it! The moment of truth... I can't back down! Not now!</thought> Yes, Your Magistry, I am. I'm confident the real murder weapon does indeed exist!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">That's a bold claim, Mr. Wright. Now let's see you back it up. Show us which piece of evidence points to this "real murder weapon!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gladly! <thought>...If I knew which one it was... What would somebody like Andistan'dhin use to bludgeon someone...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then, defense. Please submit your evidence to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Heh heh heh! Yeah! Let's see it, lawyer-man! Let's see this thing that shows the "real murder weapon" you say I used!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Andistan'dhin:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hardly think that piece of evidence has any connection to a murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And I contend that it does, Your Magistry! ...At least, that was my impression. I don't know, though. Your mileage may vary...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. Our lying lawyer here appears to be confused. His forked tongue has gotten so tangled, even HE doesn't know what he's saying anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh... I definitely should have thought that through a little better...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps it would be better for everyone if he were too tongue-tied to speak at all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nngh...</thought> I can do better, Your Magistry! Please give me another chance!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, but you'd better come up with something compelling this time!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Heh heh heh! Yeah! Let's see it, lawyer-man!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What I'm about to present is really nothing more than a possibility... But this thin thread is all I've got!</thought> Allow me to direct the court's attention to this photo of the morning Dance of Devotion.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">That photo? How is that going to help you, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's something about it that doesn't sit right with me.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">............Oh, yeah? And what's this "something," hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This thing here is odd, to say the least.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't find it odd, You're Magistry?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not in the least.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Looks like the only thing "odd" here is this lawyer's crazy babbling!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh... <thought>I blew it... But I can't give up now!</thought> Look, forget what I said just now... but I swear there's something about this photo.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Andistan'dhin. Why is the instrument you're holding different from the one you're playing in the photo?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Would you look at that? They're completely different shapes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe you said your dahmalan was your "one and only"...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Andistan'dhin? What do you have to say to that?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">...Heh heh. I got nothin' to say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then allow me to answer for you. They're different because the one in the photo is no longer in playable condition. Not after you used it to bludgeon Mr. Rohl to death!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">............ Ha ha ha ha! My old partner wasn't doing so hot, so I brought her sister along. That's all! Not a big deal, lawyer-man.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In that case, please submit your old dahmalan to this court as evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Too bad. You're too late. I got rid of her yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You what?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Burned her up with the rest of the trash! Ashes to ashes, baby! Ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO! <thought>He's already destroyed the evidence...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">And I see more trash right here in this court that needs to burn in the fires of hell! Lawyer-trash! Ha ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nnnrgh... <thought>Now there's no proof to show...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Oh, come on! That was pathetic. Your agony can sound better than that! Where's that great scream of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This... This can't be how it ends!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think I've heard enough. It seems the defense is unable to produce the evidence it needs to prove its assertion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But, Your Magistry! That's only because the witness destroyed it!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">"Evidence is everything in court." Don't tell me you've forgotten this most fundamental principle of our profession?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Without sufficient proof... ...your claim that Mr. Andistan'dhin is the murderer is no more than conjecture.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaarrrgghh!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. There's the pained expression I've been looking for. By the way, there seems to be one more thing you're forgetting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it now?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">You accused Mr. Andistan'dhin of being the thief. But the real thief turned out to be the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh-oh...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">And, with that, Mr. Andistan'dhin's purported motive for murder goes out the window.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Great point, Prosecutor! You tell 'im! If I had been there, I would've just collared Rohl and gotten the treasure back. There wasn't any reason for me to kill him, now, was there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-- <thought>There's no good counterargument to that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It sounds to me like Mr. Andistan'dhin has been completely wrongfully accused. Unfortunate as it may be, I think it's time to hand down the verdict in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not good! Not good!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defense, I trust you understand what you yourself will receive for taking on this case.</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Death! Death! Death! Death! Death! Death! Death! Death!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Aaaaagh... Wh-What do I do? The murder weapon's been destroyed, and now I've got no motive... Poor Ahlbi will be convicted, and I'll lose my life, too!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Mr. Wright, you've wasted this court's time and disparaged everything we hold sacred. We should charge you with lese-majesty, in addition to the crime of abetting the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">......Yeah. You should pay for desecrating my good name! Buh-bye, lawyer-man. Time for you to do some repentin'... in the Twilight Realm!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This guy is guilty as sin. I just know it! He must've had SOME reason to kill Mr. Rohl... but what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">C'mon, people! Lemme hear ya scream and shout! Time to take this lawyer-trash OUT!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Exterminate! Annihilate! Exterminate! Annihilate!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The thing to do at a time like this to turn my thinking around! I shouldn't be trying to figure out what Andistan'dhin's motive was. I should be thinking about what kind of situation would GIVE him a motive!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">"Did you steal it?" he said.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We know that Mr. Rohl was the thief, and that he had gotten his hands on the box. So then, why... Why in the world did he ask Ahlbi that question? What about the treasure box would've prompted him to...</thought> ......AAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defense! What's gotten into you?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now I get it! Now it all makes sense!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Like, Pohlkunka, man! Whatcha tryin' to say?! Mutterin' and squealing' to yourself! Sounds like you knocked something loose upstairs!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Magistry! Please hold off on your ruling for just a little while longer!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Don't tell me you're going to start begging for your life now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, You're Magistry. That's not it. It's just that I realized something more important. We've been operating under a serious misconception this whole time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A misconception, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. A mistaken notion about the treasure box. <thought>But could this really be true? If so, there's still a lot to figure out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ Very well. Let's hear what you have to say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Your Magistry!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Magistry! This is just more of his nonsense! He's just stalling for time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is your last chance, defense. The second I find it really IS nothing but nonsense... ...no amount of begging will stay my hand. Understand?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Magistry.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hmph...! We all know this is just going to be another one of your stupid bluffs...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then, defense. What is this misconception you mentioned?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The thing we didn't realize about the treasure box was that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I would like to suggest that the treasure box wouldn't open.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We were under the impression that the lock had been forced open. But would such a precious treasure really be kept in such a flimsy box?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If the treasure box wouldn't open, then how did the thief manage to steal the treasure? Because, as you know, the treasure was, in fact, stolen!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">G-Good question, Your Magistry...! It's a point to ponder, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes... Though not nearly as good a point to ponder as this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ngah... Please allow me to revise my statement! The REAL misconception we've been operating under...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I would like to suggest that the treasure box was already gone.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Huh? What about the treasure box that was found beside the body?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It must've been a fake!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA?!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Unfortunately for you, we're positive that that box is the genuine article. We even got an expert to authenticate it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is that all you have to say?! You nearly gave me a heart attack with that false revelation! This is for shaving a few years off of my life!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH! <thought>You didn't need to shave a few off of mine! But I can't lose heart now!</thought> Your Magistry! Please let me clear up our big misconception!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What if the treasure box was already empty from the start?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">What?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please recall... ...that when Mr. Rohl ran into Ahlbi on the great stairs, he asked the boy a question.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">"Did you steal it?" he said.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Also recall that Mr. Rohl was holding the treasure box at the time. So why, then, did he ask Ahlbi the question that he did?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That IS a bit peculiar, isn't it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not at all, Your Magistry. Not once you realize that... ...by the time Mr. Rohl got to the treasure room... the treasure box was already empty.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I beg your pardon?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rohl suspected that Ahlbi had gotten to it first... ...which is why he confronted Ahlbi when he ran into to the boy on the stairs.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">He was so proud when he was put in charge of guarding the treasure box! He even got to carry the box to the palace for the New Year's rite!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He would've been able to tell by the weight when he lifted it that the box was empty!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, I see! I suppose he would've been able to tell, wouldn't he!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rohl most likely decided to at least steal the empty box. It's an important historical artifact in and of itself, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Gah... But what's your point, Mr. Wright? What does any of this have to do with Mr. Andistan'dhin?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My point is this. It gave Mr. Andistan'dhin a motive to murder the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">A motive?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Andistan'dhin, keeping the treasure safe is one of your duties, isn't it? So if anyone had found out that the treasure was missing... ...you would've been accused of incompetence.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">From the moment Mr. Rohl discovered that the treasure was gone, his fate was sealed. Because you decided then that he had to be silenced forever!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">But that's absurd!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Aha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Can ya believe the stuff that comes outta this guy's mouth?! This is all just a colossal joke!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So then, what really happened to the treasure?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It had been stolen long before this incident occurred.. ...by Mr. Pees'lubn Andistan'dhin himself!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">............</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Mr. Wright, will you stop at nothing to accuse Mr. Andistan'dhin?! Your Magistry, please don't listen to these trumped-up charges. The defense is grasping!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ I'm not ready to give my verdict yet.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense has successfully presented a new possibility in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yes! Finally, a tiny shred of hope!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Andistan'dhin... Would you care to make any statements in response to the defense's claims?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">............ GRAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH! This is all BULL! My noggin's a rage cage and it's ready to EXPLODE, baby!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Instructor Andistan'dhin! Please calm yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">I'm not gonna take it! No, I ain't gonna take it! I dutifully watched over that treasure with pride... ...and now I'm getting accused of stealin' it?! THIS LAWYER IS A LYING SCUMBAG!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Eep!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">You better believe I got something to say! Open up your ear holes, sheeple! LET'S ROCK! DEATH TO THE LYING LAWYER!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Steal the Founder's Orb? Me?! I did it?! This lying lawyer's insults know no limit!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right. We've now heard from both sides. Either the treasure box was forced open by the accused, as the witness claims... ...or, Mr. Andistan'dhin opened it... ...as the defense claims. Defense. This is your last chance to cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Magistry.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you are unsable to prove your assertions by the end of this cross-examination...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...Then the DC Act will come into play, and both you and the accused will lose your lives.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I understand. <thought>Life or death! It all comes down to this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry, Ahlbi. I'm here to defend you! I promise it'll be all right.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Thank you. I believe in you, Mr. Wright! I know you can win this for us! And, after we win... we can go see Miss Maya... together!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a deal! <thought>I can't let Ahlbi down. I have to win this trial! Somehow, I have to prove that only Andistan'dhin could've stolen the treasure!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Do your worst, lawyer-trash! This is your requiem! The last song you'll ever hear on this mortal coil!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Steal the Founder's Orb? Me?! I did it?! This lying lawyer's insults know no limit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Hmph! It's no use even talkin' to you! Where's your proof that I stole the orb? Huh, lawyer-trash?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's right. I don't have any proof... yet. But I'll find some!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">The real method to open the lock, you say?! Delusional, man! There ain't no other way!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Wild ideas: that's called delusion. Mixed-up lawyer: drownin' in confusion.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Indeed, the defense's sinful wrongdoing has made him lose touch with reality!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Let's hear it: what'll it be? For this sinner's flight of fancy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nothing, because I'm not the delusional one. I just know there's gotta be some secret trick to opening the treasure box!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Oh, really? And where exactly is this secret hidden?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The secret is obviously hidden in...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The treasure box!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Yeah? And where on the box is this secret, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... It's... <thought>I hadn't thought that far ahead.</thought> I-It's the carvings! There's definitely something going on there!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you sure? You're sounding a little desperate, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Desperate? Not at all, Your Magistry!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The carvings the accused snuck in to see, even though it's forbidden, I might add.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, can you tell us anything about these carvings on the box?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Of course! As head monk, I know all about them! THe carvings depict a Khura'inese butterfly as it carries a soul to the Twilight Realm. They were made in around the seventh century.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Could you please add that information to your testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Fine... Listen up, lawyer-trash! Khura'inese butterfly from the 7th century, Carries the mitamah -- so elementary. Yeaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's obviously some secret hidden in the key! I'd like to examine it, if you please!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Ha ha ha ha. You don't know when to quit, do ya? Here. Go ahead. Examine it all ya like!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... ............ <thought>Nothing. I don't see a thing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, defense? What have you discovered?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm afraid I haven't discovered anything, Your Magistry. Here. I'll return it now.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">I told ya! Didn't I tell ya?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, yes... You told me...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">There's just no reasoning with this man. The accused forced the lock open. There's no other explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">That's right! He desecrated the box by opening it without using this Mitamah Key!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait. What did he just say?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">I'll sing it as many times as I have to, to get it through your thick lawyer skull! Only the Mitamah Key unlocks the treasure. Force it, and reap the founder's displeasure! Yeaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">For the forgetful defense's sake, could you please add that to your testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">If I have to... Carve it into your brain, lawyer-man!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">All this time, I guarded the orb faithfully. Sacred duty to the Holy Mother, easy to see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Why, you...! How dare you question my faith?! It's downright insulting!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not trying to insult you. But I can't suspend logic, either. You wormed your way into the temple with the intent of stealing the treasure, didn't you?!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">I've had all the insults I can take outta you, lawyer-trash!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you're the only one who can open the treasure box!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">You just keep on arguin' the same ol' lie! I sing the truth! Hear my battle cry!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Hands unclean, the accused did the deed. Forced the box open. No key did he need.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Hmph. Come on. You just saw for yourself, didn't ya? The lock was busted on account of the box bein' forced open!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh. Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Well, there's your proof right there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh... <thought>Score one for the metalhead...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Look, if the accused really didn't try to force his way into the box... ...then how do you explain why the lock was busted and wouldn't open up for you earlier?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... How DO I explain why the box wouldn't unlock earlier? Maybe there's...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd like to suggest that a different key is required to open it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A different key...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...To open the box?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As we saw earlier, the box wouldn't open with Mr. Andistan'dhin's key. Which means that a different key -- the true key -- must exist!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Ha ha ha! Are you kiddin' me?! Of course not!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can't prove that it doesn't exist!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Just calm down a second and think about it, lawyer-man! Why in the world would I bring a fake key here with me?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why, you ask? Well... because... Hmm. ...Well, I guess you got me there.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Looks like that babbling brook you call a mouth has dried up at the source, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Darn. I messed that one up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-There's a different way to open the box!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Huh? What are you talkin' about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a secret trick to opening it, to protect its contents from being stolen. And you're the only one who knows how it works, isn't that right?!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Are you for real? You've been watchin' too many movies, lawyer-man.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ahh... So you're one of THOSE tourists. Honestly, Mr. Wright. Did you come expecting magic and mystery around every corner?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'll have you know, defense, the Kingdom of Khura'in is not some sort of Fantasy Funland.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... It's true I don't have any real grounds to make that assertion... And yet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Oh, yeah! I feel another song comin' on! A little number about a crazy lawyer with wild, fantastic ideas! The real method to open the lock, you say?! Delusional, man! There ain't no other way!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahh, a new verse... Please do add it to your testimony, Mr. Andistan'dhin.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Khura'inese butterfly from the 7th century, Carries the mitamah -- so elementary.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Oh, yeah? Why don't you check it out for yourself, then?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? What's with the smug look on his face?</thought> I think I'll do just that! Your Magistry, if I could? Hmm... ............ <thought>Nothing unusual here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, defense? What have you discovered?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm afraid I haven't discovered anything, Your Magistry. Here. I'll return it now.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">I told ya! Didn't I tell ya?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh...</thought> Th-Then, in that case, there must be some secret trick to the key!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Ha ha ha. Now you're suspicious of the key, are ya?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">There's just no reasoning with this man. The accused forced the lock open. There's no other explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">That's right! He desecrated the box by opening it without using this Mitamah Key!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait. What did he just say?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">I'll sing it as many times as I have to, to get it through your thick lawyer skull! Only the Mitamah Key unlocks the treasure. Force it, and reap the founder's displeasure! Yeaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">For the forgetful defense's sake, could you please add that to your testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Oh, so you like this little number better, do ya?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Let's see. Should I have him swap in this statement?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe the witness just made - er, sang -- a very important statement. I would like it switched into his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Witness, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">If I have to... Carve it into your brain, lawyer-man!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm okay without it. Thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Oh, you're digging the lyrics as-is, are ya? Fine! Kick back and listen to the rest of your requiem in peace, then!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Only the Mitamah Key unlocks the treasure. Force it, and reap the founder's displeasure!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Oh, yeah? And what exactly is this "secret trick"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? What's that smug look for?</thought> Umm... Maybe something like... it can change shapes?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Wow, man! That's some wild imagination you got there! I'll give credit where credit's due. You can daydream like a champ!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Just like any magatama, this key is made of a translucent material. One look and it's pretty obvious it can't change shapes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah... I wasn't really sold on that one myself... But I felt like there was something odd about Andistan'dhin's testimony just now... I think I'd better take another look through the evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Lying lawyer! Condemn him to hell! Kick him, throw him, into a prison cell!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">You think so, huh? Hey, what do YOU think, people?! It's not just me this lawyer is puttin' down. He's insulting Khura'inism and the Khura'inese people, too! If he thinks he can get away with that, he's got another thing coming! Right, people?!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh heh heh! That's right! Disrespectful lawyers deserve to be removed posthaste!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Exterminate! Annihilate!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yikes. The gallery's getting really whipped up over this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">You're goin' to jail. YOU! Not me. If ya don't believe me, just wait 'n' see! It's too late, no forgiveness for you. Not from me, the judge, or Her Holiness, too. You'll rue the day you set foot in this court! To the gallows, lawyer, you will report!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is it! My last chance! The thing is... ...even though our lives are on the line, I feel strangely calm. I think it's because I know, as a lawyer, I just have to do what I do best. All I have to do is believe in my client's -- in Ahlbi's -- innocence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! I can't seem to find an inconsistency in his testimony! Come on, Phoenix! I can't give up now! I just have to keep chipping away at him. If I can't find a contradiction, then I'll keep pressing him. I'm bound to find something, as long as I just keep at it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What was that just now? It's like there was something odd about his testimony...? I can't afford to ignore any inconsistency, no matter how small. The smallest detail could blow this case wide open! I've got to use the evidence to unlock a path to the truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just a minute, Mr. Andistan'dhin. You just called your key the "Mitamah Key," didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But didn't you originally say it's called the "Magatama Key"?!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Gaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The Mitamah Key? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know, Your Magistry. But, apparently, it's a rather crucial question.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Wh-What? What's the big deal? S-So I said the wrong thing. So what? Simple slip of the tongue!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">An "A" for effort, Mr. Wright, but your grandstanding betrays your desperation. I'm afraid a small slip of the tongue like that adds absolutely nothing to your argument.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What say you, defense? Is it an important detail?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Judging by Andistan'dhin's reaction... ...I'd say it's everything my argument needs!</thought> Yes, Your Magistry. It's very important. This key is apparently not the "Magatama Key," but rather, the "Mitamah Key." And I believe this discrepancy holds great significance for the defense!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Naw, man. Just a meaningless mistake. Insignificant! Hmph. You're riding the crazy train to nowhere, lawyer-man!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Magistry, please don't pay the defense any heed. It's all nonsense.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... To tell the truth, I'm not really clear on what the defense is driving at myself. However... I am eager to find out.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defense, you will explain yourself like your life literally depends on it... because it does. Now, then. Is the name of the key an important detail?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, it's an absolutely important detail! <thought>...I think.</thought> Because the Mitamah Key is connected to the Founder's Orb!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Very well. In that case... ...please show the court the grounds on which you are basing this claim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-The grounds, Your Magistry...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You can of course show grounds, can you not, defense?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Of course! <thought>What else can I say? Nngh... I have to come up with something! Anything! Even if it's just a bluff... The Mitamah Key... "Mitamah"... Hmm... There has to be something somewhere that ties "mitamah" and the orb together...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Don't keep me waiting, defense. What evidence shows a connection between the Mitamah Key and the Founder's Orb?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't you see it, Your Magistry? A subtle, but very significant connection?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, I'm afraid I don't see it.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Neither do I.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Ha! Nothin' there to see!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then... I guess there's no connection, huh. In that case, allow me to present a different piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your feeble attempt to gloss over your mistake won't work with me, defense!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ouch... This guy's good... I'd better think this through a little better.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's that? The Song of Ceremony...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All this time... The answer was right there in front of me! It's right there in the Song of Ceremony performed during the Dance of Devotion!</thought> Your Magistry! The Song of Ceremony tells of the treasure of the founder of Khura'inism. But hidden within its lyrics... ...is the secret behind how to really open the treasure box!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Holy...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">MOTHEEEEEERRRR!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But how can that be, defense?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Song of Ceremony contains the following lyrics: "When the butterfly embraces the mitamah The favor of the orb is bestowed." I believe the "mitamah" here refers to the "Mitamah Key."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Well, yes, it is the same word, but that doesn't mean...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We've been calling this key the "Magatama Key." And that's why I inserted the key into the lock with the magatama design on it. But that was obviously not the right way to use it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And I suppose you know the "right" way?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I do, Your Magistry. To use this key properly, you have to first...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You have to first flip the key horizontally.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Flip it horizontally...? A-And what good would that do, exactly?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It would turn the Magatama Key into the Amatagam Key!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Payne">............</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But haven't you been trying to argue that it's the "Mitamah" Key?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oops. <thought>That's right...</thought> M-My apologies, Your Magistry. Please disregard all of that. What you really have to do is flip it vertically!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If we turn the magatama shape upside-down like this... ...it becomes the Khura'inese symbol of the soul -- in other words, a mitamah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! You're absolutely right! But now what? What do you do with it? It's too big to fit into the lock that way!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... Um...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. I knew he was just bluffing. Bluffs and lies are the only tools of his trade after all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There must be some other place this key fits... but where? Let's see... What were the words to the Song of Ceremony again? "When the butterfly embraces the mitamah The favor of the orb is bestowed."</thought> Where should the Mitamah Key actually be used?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right here! This is where the key should be used!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There? How on earth could you possibly use the key there?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Allow me to demonstrate! Let's see... <thought>Huh? How DOES this work...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gallery">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......Well? We're waiting, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Brr... All those icy cold glares are giving me chills...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Flying by the seat of your pants yet again, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Penalty! For raising our expectations in vain!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh...</thought> My apologies, Your Magistry. I was wrong about where to use the key. But I won't make the same mistake twice!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-My goodness! The treasure box! It really opened!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">No way, man!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-What?! NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that, ladies and gentlemen, is the real secret behind the Song of Ceremony. It's the true key to opening the treasure box! It's all over, Mr. Payne.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">H-How so...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's say someone was fooled into trying to force the front-facing lock open. Sadly for them, it won't budge. That's because the lock is, after all, just a decoy.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-Then, what you're saying is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Neither the victim nor the defendant would've been able to open the box! They therefore had no way of stealing the treasure. The only one who could have stolen it is the one man who knew about the Mitamah Key: Pees'lubn Andistan'dhin!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I'm not done yet! Please recall the scene of the crime! On the floor by Mr. Rohl's body... ...was the very unlocked, and very open treasure box! Only someone who knew how to open the box could've left it in that state.</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Mmmrrrrrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And so! There can only be one true culprit. Admit it, Mr. Andistan'dhin! You're the one who killed Mr. Rohl!</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">I-I... Uh... AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH! GAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH! Hah! Yah! Gragh! ...Huh? Cuckoo... Cuckoo...</line>
<line speaker="Andistan'dhin">Curse him... It's all his fault! Why'd he have to try and steal the treasure...?! Why'd I have to spot him with that box... ...on my way to the storeroom after the morning dance? It's his fault I had to cause that blackout and clock him good! I couldn't let my secret get out! Nobody could know the treasure box was empty! I'd lose my position as head monk... Who knows what else they'd do to me?! I couldn't let...! I had to... I had to stop him...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ What a shocking development... I can scarcely believe it... Nothing like this has ever happened since the DC Act was enacted twenty-three years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Nngh... No... My perfect, unblemished record... destroyed... ...The Incredible Payne... ruined... NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Did that lawyer really win? I can't believe it! No way! This can't be happening!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Peace! I said peace! Honestly speaking, I'm just as shocked as everyone else. But the truth has been made known, so it's time for me to give my verdict. In the name of the Holy Mother... ...this court finds the accused, Ahlbi Ur'gaid...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... There's still quite a commotion... The people in the gallery show no sign of clearing out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gallery">I can't believe it... "Not guilty"! I'm still in shock... Can you believe that guy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can feel everybody's eyes on me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gallery">This can't be happening! It's impossible! O Holy Mother, preserve us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've never been in a defendant lobby quite this uncomfortable...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, Ahlbi!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Thank you! Thank you so much for what you did for me!</line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">Ruff! Ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm just glad it turned out okay! <thought>It was touch and go there for a while...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I'm really sorry, Mr. Wright. I... I had a really hard time trusting you at first...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's okay, Ahlbi. I know how unpopular lawyers are in this country. But how did it ever get this way in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Allow me to explain...! At least, I wish I could explain... But I don't really know why. I never even questioned it before today. By the time I was born, all the lawyers were already gone. As far back as I can remember, verdicts have been based on Her Benevolence's Insights.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right... Rayfa... the royal priestess...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You would imply that the trials of this country are unfair? Do explain, outsider... ...how verdicts founded on truths imparted by the very souls of the dead lack impartiality.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>For her part, I'm sure she really believes in what she says, but...</thought> Even with Her Benevolence's Divination Séances, lawyers are still necessary. Without proper defense, people could easily wind up receiving wrongful convictions.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Mr. Wright! Shhhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Don't say that so loud! People might think you're a rebel! You could be arrested!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A rebel?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">That's right. One of those people going against our queen and the court system! They call themselves the Defiant Dragons. And they're led by a scary guy named Dhurke. They'll do anything to overthrow Her Eminence -- even commit crimes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Dhurke... I remember people in the gallery mentioning that name...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">The things you're saying sound a lot like the stuff they say. But you're not scary like that Dhurke guy!</line>
<line speaker="???">Pardon the intrusion. You. Yeah, you. I wanna talk to you, see? Flight, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wright, sir, Phoenix Wright. And you are...?</line>
<line speaker="???">I'm the Khura'inese Minister of Justice. The name's Inga Karkhuul Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Inga">I oversee the whole legal shebang. I was watching that three-ring circus in there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were? <thought>Wow. The Minister of Justice... So he's in charge of the entire court system -- Defense Culpability Act and all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">M-Minister Inga... How are you, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Run along, mini-monk. Grownups are talking here.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Y-Yes, sir. Very sorry, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-May I help you with something?</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Just wanted a good look at you. Guys like you aren't exactly a dime-a-dozen around here! Huh... Well, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's eyeing me like I'm some kind of exotic creature in a cage...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Inga">Oh yeah, might as well share this little morsel with you. Turns out Rohl was a seasoned thief -- a repeat offender, see. Had my men look into it, and they found all the booty he'd pilfered right there in his digs.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">But he seemed like such a nice man... Why, Mr. Rohl, why...?</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Guess he was doing it for the family. What a mook.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">A-A "mook"?! How can you say that...?!</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Hmph. Guess that kind of sob story gets you common folk all misty-eyed, huh. Anyway, another thing... I had my men check out that Andistan'dhin fella, too. He wasn't the one with the sticky fingers. It's the insurgents.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Inga">They put the squeeze on our head monk, apparently. So he gave up the Founder's Orb and tried to keep it hush-hush.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow. I see. Thank you for letting me know.</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Yeahhhh... Say, White. That was a cute li'l number you pulled in my courtroom today, wasn't it? First "not guilty" ruling in twenty-three years... You're making waves, see? Stirring the pot. Catch my drift?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... Well, I... <thought>Yikes! I'm in for it now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Inga">Hmph. But thanks to that song and dance, we know our precious national treasure got nicked. So I'm gonna call it a wash, and let it slide this time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But all I did was defend the accused...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Inga">You'd do best to read between the lines here, chump... Yer standing on thin ice, you get my drift? Even a dirty, no-goodnik punk knows to cash in his chips before the house steps in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">!</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Do us both a favor, and keep an eye on the path you're walking down... You never know whose toes you might be steppin' on. This ain't your turf, buddy. Never forget whose soil it is you're standin' on.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Yikes! He was kind of scary, wasn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, well, no use worrying about it. We have more important things to think about. Such as when can we continue the sightseeing tour?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Tour?! Ooh, anytime, sir! We still have plenty of time until Miss Maya's training ends! And there are still lots more temples to see, and all kinds of local foods to eat! I can show you the natural beauty of the area, and the waterfalls used for training! And I haven't shown you the breathtaking mountain view from the Plaza of Devotion yet! And there's this place where they dangle you off a really steep cliff that offers your soul a great view of the Twilight Realm! And walking on a bed of nails doubles as a foot massage!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right! All right! Slow down, Ahlbi! There's plenty of time!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">And when we're done with all that, we can go see Miss Maya together!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, you bet! <thought>Maya... I wonder how she's doing. Hope she's okay...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Man">So, how about that "not guilty," Dhurke?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I heard. Sounds like the winds of change are beginning to stir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No... The only thing "odd" I find here... ...is your objection. I hope this will help you change your ways.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That didn't go very well... Actually... I guess I wasn't even remotely close on that one... I'd better take another good look at Ahlbi's statements and the evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're laying your life on the line on THAT...? And what exactly about the testimony is inconsistent with that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... <thought>Urk. Suddenly, I'm not so sure...</thought> I apologize, Your Magistry. May I try again?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">By all means... But know this: You just drove a nail into your own coffin!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gaaaaagh... But I just KNOW something's off about this statement. Guess I should search the Court Record again for something that contradicts it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! Guess that's not it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">More of your defense attorney shenanigans, is it? Well, I won't stand for it. In the name of the Holy Mother, I give you a penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Urk! <thought>I'm SURE this is the piece of evidence I need, though. I guess I'd better take another look at Ahlbi's statements...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait... No, that's not it. This sensation isn't really inconsistent with the Insight. I'd better find the sensation that IS, and "Present" (X</thought> that!)</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">An inconsistency, you say? And where exactly do you see this supposed "inconsistency"?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, defense, please be specific.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I don't know how specific I can be, exactly, but... ...I just get the vague feeling that something doesn't quite add up... you know?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, I don't know. But I DO know you're skating on thin ice, defense. By your leave, Your Benevolence...?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Do it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh... <thought>And here I thought I was skating so gracefully on that ice, too... I get the feeling I was way off the mark with that one... I'd better take another good look at the Insights and the sensations... I doubt there are any mistakes in the victim's last memories... So that must mean one of Her Benevolence's Insights is off! I'll use these buttons (D-Pad or Circle Pad</thought> to cycle through the Insights and check each one carefully. And then I'll compare the Insights with the sensations and look for an inconsistency!)</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! Guess that's not it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">More of your defense attorney shenanigans, is it? Well, I won't stand for it. In the name of the Holy Mother, I give you a penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're laying your life on the line on THAT...? And what exactly about the testimony is inconsistent with that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... <thought>Urk. Suddenly, I'm not so sure...</thought> I apologize, Your Magistry. May I try again?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">By all means... But know this: You just drove a nail into your own coffin!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gaaaaagh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! I could really use a partner to consult with right about now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh. You seem to be having a hard time. Can't do anything without your little friends? I feel bad for your poor subordinates, having to always pick up your slack and all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Pick up my--"?! I'll show him! Get your head back in it, Phoenix! You can do this! If I think back on everything I've heard... Yes, that one statement is definitely fishy!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">O foreign lawyer, you aren't looking very well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's because I couldn't find a foothold in that testimony just now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see the defense has turned a lovely shade of blue to match his suit.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I believe you're right, Your Magistry. Very resourceful, these foreigners.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey, buddy. Aren't you a foreigner, too? I can't let my face give me away. I have to look confident! Maybe I should give the ol' "pressing statements" tactic a try.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Agh. I can't seem to find any inconsistencies... But something's been nagging at me. I think it has something to do with the sensation of pain... Although, I shouldn't overlook the moment the victim was struck either. I think I'll take another look at the Insights with these things in mind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I have heard enough! This trial need not be drawn out any longer. The defense has failed to counter the charges filed by the prosecution. In accordance to the law, I invoke the Defense</line>
</xml>