
<xml>
<title>The Monstrous Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is back in session for the trial of Damian Tenma.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo Justice, defense team leader, is ready, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena Cykes, assistant defender, is ready, too, Your Honor. Je suis prêt!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As chipper as ever, I see. And in French, no less! ...And the prosecution?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, then. By the way, I asked Detective Fulbright to provide sturdier shackles today. There will be no more of your funny business this time, Prosecutor Blackquill!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, your opening statement, if you would. I believe it's standard procedure for the prosecution to handle it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Looks like the judge is really bringing it today.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He probably realized how Blackquill played him. That was one mean game of Simon Says.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, His Honor has to fight to defend his honor today.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........Your Baldness... It's plain to see that you've always dreamed of delivering an epic opening statement.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I have? Hmm... I don't know if I'd say that.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Why, of course you have. I saw it in your eyes the last time you gave the opening statement. That was the look of one who yearns deeply for the thrill of an epic opening statement. For decades now, you have been watching opening statements from your bench. They were the crown jewels of the court -- the one thing you could not possess!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The crown jewels... of the court?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Now, at long last, they are within your grasp. How could you possibly refuse?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......Oh, uh, so you don't mind if I do it, then?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I'll make a special exception, just this once.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Here we go again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yep, more of Blackquill's mind games.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, in that case, I think I might go ahead and make the opening statement myself. *ahem* In yesterday's session, we learned the shocking truth that... ...the victim Alderman Rex Kyubi was The Amazing Nine-Tails. We also learned that... ...The Amazing Nine-Tails was a key figure in the yokai craze and anti-merger protests. It was further revealed that upon learning Rex Kyubi's secret identity... ...Mayor Damian Tenma murdered him. The fact that the crime took place in a tightly locked room was also brought to light. And the only people in that tightly locked room were the defendant and victim. The defense proposed the existence of a hypothetical third party... ...but further investigation revealed no proof of a third party who had escaped the room.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Ergo?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We must conclude that the evidence against the defendant is... well... conclusive. Eek! D-Did I say something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...That was quite astonishing. You've truly outdone yourself this time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, heh heh. One more thing to boast about to my grandchild!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Well, this was not an unexpected turn of events...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, it seems the prosecution has called a new witness to testify.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The inexplicable yokai evidence left at the scene of the crime... Well, does that not demand some sort of explanation?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The feathers and tracks? Weren't those left by the mayor while he was possessed?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">That was but an act to protect his daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! Uh... yes, of course! I had suspected as much.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait, did he actually believe the mayor's "award-winning" performance?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">His daughter was the one who planted the yokai evidence. Ergo, the true identity of the yokai in the manor was the manor's maid, Jinxie Tenma.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Would you care for some witness testimony, then? For I am ready to prove that the little scamp is the one behind the Tenma Taro farce.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Witness testimony? I'll bet he means Filch and that creep L'Belle.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, then. Bailiff, would you bring in the first witness?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Filch, you made quite the hasty exit yesterday. See that it doesn't happen again today.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Eh heh heh. Been known for my hasty retreats since I was a kid. Bit of a trademark o' mine.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. You managed to give a total of five bailiffs the slip.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Like those amateurs could ever nab me, eh heh heh. Yiiipes!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Perhaps we should shackle you by the neck. That would keep you in place.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yipes! No, please, I'm liable to rip my own head off if I start running!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........Your statement. Now.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yes, sir, Mr. Blackhead, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He may beat a hasty retreat, but there's no escaping Prosecutor Blackquill.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, Blackquill doesn't strike me as the give-up-easy type.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Filch, your testimony please. Specifically, the true nature of the yokai you saw in the manor shortly after the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Tenma Taro's really that little maid gal. Ain't no doubt about it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, Tenma Taro was short in stature. And that's because it was Ms. Jinxie Tenma all along?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">You betcha! Besides, all the rest in the manor were way taller than her.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Feigning height is but an easy thing... ...but a big ox like the defendant could never pass for short.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What if the Tenma Taro impersonator was walking on their knees?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Weren't no knee walking. I seen it myself!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Then perhaps that yokai really was Ms. Tenma, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">All monsters are naught but tricks, either of the mind or the cheap parlor variety.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, you're saying she created an illusion like one of those magical eye things?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Precisely. Human senses are easily deceived. Take the fellow in the cell next to me. Each night, he cries and screams about some ghost he thinks he sees. But in truth, it was simply the janitor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho ho. Prosecutor Blackquill just gave up the ghost, literally!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The janitor's deathly complexion and all-white attire are, no doubt, partially to blame. That and the fact that he constantly mutters about taking vengeance for this or that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That...... actually sounds like a real ghost to me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense may now cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Tenma Taro's really that little maid gal. Ain't no doubt about it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">N-No, ya got it all wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then could you tell the court exactly what sort of lesson it was?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Oh, um... it was... Uh... it was... What was it again? Yiiipes! Ah, now I remember! Math! Ya know, numbers 'n' stuff!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He's completely under Blackquill's control, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Filch">Anyway, that Tenma Taro was that little maid gal, so what's the difference?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">I mean, the Tenma Taro I saw was just a lil' thing 'bout her size!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Eh heh heh, you betcha. I got a habit o' sizing people up. I can even give ya a primer on how to pull it off. All under the table, natch. I got a knack for figuring out where people's pockets are and how much money they have. I size 'em real good before I relieve them of their valuables!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He just admitted to being a pickpocket right here in court.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Does the witness hold that this Tenma Taro entered the foyer?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Darn right I do.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">But the little runt had a big ol' staff. I seen it when she came into the foyer!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Eh heh heh. Musta hit a raw nerve 'cause ya ain't that tall yerself!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Look who's talking, Mr. I've-got-to-stand-on-a-box-just-to-testify!</thought> Anyway, Mr. Filch, correct me if I'm wrong... ...but didn't you say the Tenma Taro you saw had a staff?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Cross my heart, hope to die! I know 'cause it went a jingle and a jangle.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And where do you suppose that staff came from?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Errr... The staff, ya say? Well, I uh...</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Betcha she stole it from the Forbidden Chamber after stumbling on the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Well, I ain't never seen a staff like that in the manor! So it had to be the Forbidden Chamber!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, really? The stench of L'Belle is thick in the air today.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Jinxie entered the Forbidden Chamber after the incident... ...then she took the staff and tried to cover up her actions by pretending to be Tenma Taro. I guess that's what Filch is trying to say...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Could Jinxie have even entered the Forbidden Chamber if she wanted to...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">There IS one thing I was wondering about. Why did that yokai have a staff in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Eh heh heh. Well, I've got my hunches about that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">She was gonna use it to wallop me on account o' my fierce reputation, I just know it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">That little maid gal never did like me! She always high tails it when I come 'round or she sticks these weird papers on my noggin!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She probably thinks of him as the dreaded tanuki monster of Kyubi Manor or something.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">We need to prove that Jinxie isn't Tenma Taro. But I've no idea how we're going to do that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All we have to do is prove that it was impossible for Jinxie to turn into Tenma Taro. And that might be easier than you think.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Now's our chance. Our chance to expose the real Tenma Taro for all to see!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It would seem that Tenma Taro was, in fact, not this innocent little girl.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Huh? How you figure that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You claim the Tenma Taro you saw had one of those staves from the Forbidden Chamber. But it would've been impossible for Ms. Tenma to get a hold of one!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Care to elaborate, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The mayor swallowed this key shortly after the murder. He wanted to keep the killer out of the Forbidden Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This key was deep in the mayor's stomach when Ms. Tenma discovered the crime scene. So you see, it would've been impossible for her to get into the Forbidden Chamber. In short, the Tenma Taro seen holding that staff... ...could not have been Jinxie Tenma!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Aaaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Whaaaaaat?! B-But...! Then who does the defense believe was impersonating Tenma Taro?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Our Tenma Taro impersonator is none other than Mayor Tenma's aide--</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, in fact, I can.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well, let's see where the defense is going with this. Mr. Justice, please show us proof as to the true identity of the Tenma Taro impersonator.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, uh... good question.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Way to walk down a one-way street to a dead end.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court doesn't need more questions, Mr. Justice. The defense will present evidence that provides answers, and only answers. A penalty for our questionable attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I know we have evidence that can prove who was in the Forbidden Chamber.</thought> The killer was the only one who could've entered the Forbidden Chamber. The question before us is simply the "who" part of this equation.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We found this hand cream in the Forbidden Chamber. And we know that whoever was Tenma Taro took one of the staves out of there. In short... ....I believe whoever this hand cream belongs to is the yokai impersonator we're looking for.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... But Mr. Justice... ...how do you propose to identity the hand cream's owner?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm glad you asked, Your Honor. The defense requests a fingerprint analysis on this piece of evidence! It might tell us who it belongs to!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Interesting... So, you expect to find the yokai's prints there? Very well, I hereby call a short recess while we wait for the fingerprint results.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">No need for that, Your Baldness. We have the prints of everyone at the manor that day.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">You called, Prosecutor Blackquill?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>.........Could anyone be more whipped?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Fool Bright! Analyze this for prints. You have three minutes.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Your wish is my command!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, then. I guess we'll just wait right here.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">......It would seem the fingerprint analysis is complete.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do the results show?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What in the world...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They're Florent L'Belle's prints, aren't they?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">This... This is absurd!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... Prosecutor Blackquill? <thought>I'm not going to like this, am I...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">D-Don't tell me... they're Tenma Taro's prints?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Fingerprint analysis has revealed that the prints belong to... ............Phineas Filch.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The Mr. L'Belle wasn't the one who entered the Forbidden Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">S-S-Sure, th-them prints are mine! I mean, I did pilfer that hand cream from Mr. L'Belle, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-So you're the one who entered the Forbidden Chamber?!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">S-So what if I did! G-G-Got a problem with it?! Yiiiiiipes!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You...... fool of a tanuki!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Mr. Justice, care to explain what this could mean?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Excellent question... Um, the fact that Mr. Filch was in the Forbidden Chamber... Wait a second... Does this mean the Tenma Taro holding that staff was... Phineas Filch?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yiiiiiipes! Another cat outta the baaaaaag!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Filch is Tenma Taro?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't understand. Does this mean... Mr. Filch is the real killer?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness will explain himself this instant!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Begging your pardon, Your Honorship, but I was just doing what the alderman told me. He wanted me to be Tenma Taro in the village exorcism ritual.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, you mean that event at the Nine-Tails Vale festival. So, that was you inside the Tenma Taro costume.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yep. And after the event, I went to watch that pro wrestling program... ...but it bored me to tears on account o' the wrestlers being complete jobbers.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So, he didn't actually watch the entire wrestling match.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Filch">That's when I looked at the Tenma Taro costume and got a great idea! Nobody can tell it's me while I'm wearing it... ...and 'cause o' them superstitions, no matter what I do, the villages [sic] won't say a word!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In other words, you used the superstitions to effectively render yourself invisible.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why did you want to enter the Forbidden Chamber in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">'Cause o' the treasure there! Thought that was my big chance to sneak on in 'n' nab it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Treasure?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Eh heh heh. Only that it's the greatest get-rich-quick chance in the universe. Grandpappy told me all about it. Said there's an amazing treasure in there!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He went in there not knowing his grandfather had already pilfered it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Guess this is one tale that didn't get passed down from grandpappy to grandson.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, how exactly did you get into the Forbidden Chamber? There was a meeting in the Fox Chamber that day. Plus, the mayor swallowed the only key that could open the Forbidden Chamber's door. You couldn't have possibly gotten in!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">I could through the air vent in the foyer! The vent's left o' the alderman's picture. I went on in and made a nice little hole. Used that to get into the air duct that leads to the Forbidden Chamber, I did!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You what?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-But how's that even possible? ...Wait a sec...! Remember that air vent in the Forbidden Chamber? So, Mr. Filch found a way to get into that air duct... ...and that's how he got from the foyer vent to the Forbidden Chamber vent?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So, Tenma Taro was nothing more than a cat burglar -- or rather, a tanuki burglar. And we're back to being without anyone to charge for the alderman's murder.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Looks like our so-called yokai is nothing more than one big troublemaker.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tell me, Mr. Filch, what did you do after fleeing to the foyer?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">I got outta that costume real quick. Woulda just caused trouble at that point!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And where is that costume now?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Heck if I know. And it ain't my fault if ya never find it.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The police searched every nook and cranny. No yokai costume was left in that manor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What if it was tossed outside the manor? ...Ah!</thought> No way! But maybe, just maybe...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense seems to have hit upon an idea. Well, go on, Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, here's what I think... Mr. Filch! Did you get rid of the costume here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense will remember to pay attention from now on!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack. <thought>If the costume wasn't in the manor, then maybe it was thrown out somewhere.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you toss it out the window? Because that would certainly explain why it didn't turn up inside the manor!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">You think I tossed it out the window? That costume cost me a pretty penny! So why would I go do something like that?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I can think of a few reasons...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Any bright ideas, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, assuming the costume really was tossed out from the window... ...then the next question would be, what happened to it after that? <thought>And if I'm right, I might have just the thing to prove what happened to the costume.</thought> Phineas Filch......... I have just the evidence for you!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Ya do?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This evidence proves you got rid of your Tenma Taro costume through the window!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It doesn't, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, it does not.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack. <thought>Back to the drawing board. What would happen if the costume was tossed out the window? I must have some sort of evidence that can show what would happen!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Filch">Ah, that's... ...Tenma Taro flying through the sky?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And just how does that prove Mr. Filch threw his costume out the window?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's quite simple. That's not Tenma Taro in the photo. It's the costume Mr. Filch threw out.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Aw, that's crazy talk! You ain't serious, are ya?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a steep cliff right outside the foyer window, meaning the manor is pretty high up. The costume flew through the air after it was tossed out. That's when the photo was taken. In other words, the photo of Tenma Taro really was a flight of fancy!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Whaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yiiiiiiiiiiikes!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! So there really never was a yokai.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Aw, I can't keep any o' them cats bagged! Can I still file a claim for the lost costume?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This more than proves the defense's position. Jinxie Tenma had nothing to do with staging the yokai sighting.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Care to raise any objections, Prosecutor Blackquill?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............None whatsoever. I'll deal with that tricksy tanuki after I've dealt with this case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>We... We did it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Good going! Now all we have to do is make Florent L'Belle take the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Nothing has been proved beyond a doubt. Take this tricksy little tanuki for instance. How do you suppose he was able to exit the Forbidden Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh... Probably the same way he got in -- through the chamber's air vent!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">And what of the feathers and tracks at the scene of the crime? They would suggest that the tanuki exited through the chamber door, not the air vent.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">......Hmph. Someone on the outside opened the door for you, isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yep, that's right, Mr. Blackjack! The door suddenly sprung right open!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Didn't get a good look on account o' the sudden glare.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Like how the reflection from my head blinds fellow moviegoers emerging from the dark.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">That's when I snatched that staff and made my daring escape! And then that lil' maid gal spotted me as I high-tailed it down the hall!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That means the Forbidden Chamber wasn't opened until after the crime was discovered.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But wait... We still don't know who opened it. Maybe there really was a third person in the Fox Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Nope. Only one there was the alderman, and he was dead as a doornail.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. If the accused wasn't there, what do you suppose he was up to?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh-oh. I don't like where this is going.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah! Don't tell me--!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Plainly, the only one who could have opened the Forbidden Chamber was... ...the accused Damian Tenma!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Arrrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Really? And who might that be?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, well, that would be...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I didn't forget...! I was just... testing your attention to details...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Cykes! You can't prove your point without proof of some sort! It's a proven fact!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sorry... Guess I put my foot in my mouth again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, Athena. We're definitely on to something here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We are?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Think about it. If Filch was stuck inside the Forbidden Chamber... ...one of the alibis we heard would no longer hold any water! The defense would like to call a new witness to the stand! Someone who knew Mr. Filch was stuck in the Forbidden Chamber! And by virtue of knowing this, has an alibi that no longer adds up!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ah! Not that insufferable--!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court will hear what Mr. Justice has to say. Whose alibi no longer adds up?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Really?! Please explain, Mr. Justice. How does this person's alibi has vanish [sic] in this case?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Err... You know how your hand vanishes when you stick it into a dark room? Kinda like that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ Keep making half-baked statements like that... ...and it'll be the court's trust in you that will vanish!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, uh... just kidding, heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A penalty to dissuade the very unfunny Mr. Justice from pursuing a career in comedy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>We know Filch was in the Forbidden Chamber at the time of the murder. Which means...</thought> Your Honor! There IS someone whose alibi no longer adds up!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. You may try once again.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, that's... that's the defendant's aide, Florent L'Belle. Didn't he claim to be in the foyer at the time of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">True, but in his alibi, he also claimed Mr. Filch was in the foyer, too. However, as we all know now, Mr. Filch was NOT there with Mr. L'Belle at that time. In short, Mr. L'Belle's alibi has disappeared!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Argh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Florent L'Belle's alibi was one big lie! Isn't that right, Mr. Filch!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">I reckon there ain't no keepin' that cat in the bag here, neither. It was all Mr. L'Belle's idea. He told me he'd button his lip about me breaking into the Forbidden Chamber. And in return, he said we'd vouch for each other's alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Shame on you, Mr. Filch! Perjury is a serious crime, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Aw, shucks... Mercy, Your Honorship, mercy! Aaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I also assert that the person who opened the Forbidden Chamber for Mr. Filch... ...was none other than Florent L'Belle! After all, his alibi has just been proven to be a complete fabrication!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I see. We will take a twenty-minute recess... ...after which time we will see what Mr. L'Belle has to say for himself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yes! We're finally going to drag that slippery snake onto the stand!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In the meantime, the prosecution will question Mr. L'Belle about these new allegations!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We did it, Apollo! We finally dragged Mr. L'Belle into court!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, why the long face?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I can't help but feel I'm missing something important. Plus, Prosecutor Blackquill's bound to mount a counterattack.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You really are a worrywart, aren't you? It'll be fine! That mystery figure who opened the Forbidden Chamber for Mr. Filch... ...had to have been Florent L'Belle!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know. But that's not what's bugging me. I wish I could put my finger on it, though...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">At any rate, the big showdown with Mr. L'Belle is up next, so chin up, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is back in session. Our next witness is--</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">...Yes. I'm ACTING on behalf of the mayor in this VERY important matter.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems the witness is predisposed at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! SURELY you jest! I will hold you to your promise, remember that. Oh, my DEEPEST apologies. This is Florent L'Belle, PERSONAL aide to Mayor Tenma -- or should I say -- the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ouch, like the poor mayor hasn't suffered enough...</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Well, what business do YOU have with ME? I'm a VERY busy man, so let's make this as BRIEF as possible.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">......Your Baldness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, right. *ahem* Mr. Filch's testimony has revealed a hole in your alibi. And for this reason... ...you are suspected of having some sort of connection with the case at hand.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Pffft. To think I'D be associated with this entirely lurid affair. Well, I'm NOT, so may I go now? I have VERY important matters to attend to.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, you are being accused of perjury. This is your chance to clear the air.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Fine. The truth is I faked my alibi for a VERY good reason. The mayor was OBVIOUSLY the killer, so I created a fake alibi to confuse the matter. You see, as his PERSONAL aide, I felt I HAD to protect him. SORRY! Ah ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You think this is funny?! Without your alibi, you're a suspect, too! What were you really doing at the time of the crime?!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Pffft, PEASANT! How dare YOU accuse ME, one of the BEAUTIFUL people, of being--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">.........</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........Enough jabbering. Swords have been drawn. The time for talk is past.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Swords? What swords?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">This is a duel to the death. The fate of the accused rests in our hands. Be gone, ye of cowardly heart! The battlefield hath no place for ye!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Again...?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Oh, my.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Spare me, pleeeeease!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So much for sturdier shackles. Aagh!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Those chains hindered my vow that heads would roll this day.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This gives "keeping your head on in court" a whole new meaning!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Will the witness please deliver the accused's death knell? You know of what I speak.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! Most CERTAINLY. His GOOSE is already COOKED. Time to stick a fork in him!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Whatever he has to say can't be good.</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">As I TOLD Prosecutor Blackquill during the recess... ...I RUSHED right over to the Fox Chamber when I heard little Jinxie scream.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">THEN -- drum roll please... ...I saw Mayor Tenma OPENING the Forbidden Chamber doors.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-B-But...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">There you have it. The mystery man who opened the chamber door -- as witnessed by one Phineas Filch... It was the accused. There was never any third party.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">......Oh, and THAT'S not all! I heard something QUITE startling there at the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Startling sounds bad...</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">The mayor, who was barely conscious, muttered this... "Forgive me, Jinxie. I killed the alderman." That's right! The mayor ACTUALLY confessed to the murder right then and there!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">H-H-He confessed?! Order! Order in the court! This is quite conclusive testimony if it stands!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Just so. And quite astonishing, I might add. I only learned of this fact during the recess.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! I just LOVE surprises, don't you? That's why I saved the best for last. Consider it a gift from ME to YOU!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No way. I don't believe Mr. L'Belle heard the mayor confess.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... but is this really true? Did Mayor Tenma really confess?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It is, indeed. During that last recess, I confirmed it with the mayor's daughter. It would seem Mayor Tenma actually did confess.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That testimony is quite favorable to the prosecution's--</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">This is L'Belle. Yes, I called earlier about the PARTY reservations. That's right. And I'll be calling MY little shindig "Mayor Tenma's Conviction Gala." A SPLENDID time is guaranteed for all -- all but the mayor and his defense, ah ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, as it seems our witness is a very busy man, let's get right to his testimony. Mr. L'Belle, please tell us what you saw when you came upon the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">I was in the hallway, HIDING in the shadows. THAT'S when I heard the confession.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I must say... this is a shocking revelation... Quite unexpected. To think the defendant actually confessed then and there to his crime!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Perhaps the guilt was TOO much to bear, so he confided in his daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You do realize you should not have withheld such crucial testimony from the court!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! Once again, SORRY! It's just, I feared being accused if I mentioned coming upon that MOST unpleasant scene.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Argh. Why did the mayor's confession have to be brought up by THIS guy...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We better do something before the judge declares the mayor guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. As a death row inmate once told me in years gone by... "There is a time to fight and a time to yield. A time to live, and a time to die."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Arrrgh! <thought>He's laying it on real thick now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense may now cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">I was in the hallway, HIDING in the shadows. THAT'S when I heard the confession.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">PEASANT! You wouldn't DARE ask such a question if you truly understood. TRUE beauty is never wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's not?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">No, beauty is carved DEEP in the DNA. That means I'M programmed to ALWAYS be right, EVEN when I'm wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm not following.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">These exquisite ears like flowers abloom... These eyes that shine like pearls... This hair like the finest silk... Nothing can corrupt the truth they hold!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh... right...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... The witness will hurry up and explain this truth of his. Specifically, what did Jinxie Tenma do upon hearing the confession?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Upon LEARNING of her father's crime, little Jinxie fled without EVER noticing me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Oh, the poor little thing seemed POSITIVELY heartbroken -- all teary eyed and whatnot. I couldn't help but shed a few tears myself after seeing her like that.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He actually sympathized with Jinxie? Seems like an overly human emotion for him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, because he's the only real monster we've seen so far -- in looks and in character.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">The NEXT thing I did was check my face in the mirror.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Checked your face? Why?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Pffft! To behold the beauty that is my sadness, why else!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Apollo, I'm starting to lose all faith in humanity.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know the feeling, but hang in there. At least keep faith in our client.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's keep moving, shall we? So what happened next?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Immediately AFTER that, the mayor came to, stood up and opened the Forbidden Chamber!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Who knows? MAYBE he wanted to free the demon, Tenma Taro?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Hello? L'Belle speaking. ...Yes, I will CERTAINLY explore the matter. Toodles! Now, WHERE were we again?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were going to tell us the real reason why the mayor opened the Forbidden Chamber!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Oh, yes! Of course. Hello? This is L'Belle. ...A ha ha ha! Good one, sir! You're an ABSOLUTE riot. ...Okay, bye. You were saying?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Never mind. <thought>This is a waste of time. He's just going to tell more lies.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness will focus on his testimony, not his phone calls. Now, tell the court what you did after you saw the mayor open the Forbidden Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Well, after THAT...</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">As I ran in TERROR, the demon emerged from his prison!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">He was shouting, "I can't see! I can't see! It's the curse o' Tenma Taro!" THEN, he took off running like a MADMAN.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He must've been blinded by the sudden light flooding in.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">He set EYES upon me... ...and was thus BLINDED by my radiant beauty!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...So, it was the curse of Florent L'Belle, rather than Tenma Taro?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Yes, I'm afraid such beauty can be a curse. It's almost criminal.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...The only thing criminal here... is your ceaseless jabbering. Now, get on with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Oh, forgive me, Your Darkness. Let's see... Oh, yes. I FLED for dear life from Tenma Taro, and...</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">In shock, I FLED down the hallway to my right -- the one with the PHONE at the end.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">PRECISELY.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Notice any inconsistencies, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, Jinxie also saw Tenma Taro, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">She did. She said they passed each other in the hall after she made that call to the police.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, if L'Belle had fled down the hall where that phone is... ...Jinxie would've seen him when she was returning from making her call.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, right. And if she saw him, she would've definitely asked him for help.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. It just doesn't make any sense. <thought>Time to review the evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If we don't find some way to poke a hole in his testimony... ...Mayor Tenma is as good as guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is bad, very bad.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We need to find an inconsistency, a mistake, some kind of conflict!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's all over if we can't find a flaw in the prosecution's case!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Florent L'Belle, you're lying about having witnessed those events from the hallway!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! What on EARTH do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, care to fill the rest of us in, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If Mr. L'Belle had really fled down into the hall with the phone in it... ...he would've crossed paths with Ms. Tenma.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">...What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">After she discovered the crime scene, she immediately went to call the police. Then, after making her call, she went back to the main hallway... ...whereupon she encountered the demon, yokai, or whatever you want to call it. As for me, I call it Phineas Filch in a Tenma Taro costume! The encounter happened right there, where the hallways meet. As for Mr. L'Belle, if he had fled here, feigning escape from the yokai imposter...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, yes! The two would've crossed paths!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. Except Ms. Tenma told us that "there was no one else in the hall." In short, Ms. Tenma did not see you in the hall because you were never really there!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Aaaaaah! My eyes! My beautiful eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hah! Not such a FABULOUS scent now, is it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">But Mr. Justice, the witness also stated that he heard the mayor confess. If he was lying about hearing the confession from the hall... ...then where was he when he heard it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Inside the Fox Chamber, where else?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... But isn't that within the very crime scene?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It is, Your Honor. And that means he's not really a witness. Rather, he's the third party I've been alleging this whole time!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">What?! You think I'M the killer? How DARE you!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Foolish fop. A true man knows when he is beaten. A shield of lies comes to naught before a foe with the sword of truth bared.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">P-Prosecutor Blackquill, what ARE you...? I thought WE were on the SAME side?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You are mistaken. There are no sides here, save for my cold, steely edge of judgment. You are alone upon this battlefield, with naught but your lies and sickly sweet perfume.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Whoa, what just happened? Blackquill's really tearing into him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You heard the mayor's confession from the inside, did you not, you deviant dandy? For the sole location from which you could've seen and heard the mayor and the tanuki... ...without either of them noticing you was right there in the Fox Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">.........Oh, my. So THAT'S how it's going to be? Fine, I'll come clean, then.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Seriously? You admit to being there in the Fox Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">I do! I DID enter the room AFTER the murder. But I was afraid of being FALSELY accused, so I lied about it. I feel TERRIBLE about lying like that. But it's a verbal cologne I use to PROTECT myself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You'd better explain yourself, Mr. L'Belle!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Yes, of course! I was JUST about to get to that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness is skating on thin ice. I'll remind you that perjury is a very serious crime. Now, let's hear your testimony again, this time without your perfume of lies.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">I DID enter the Fox Chamber after the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">From behind the screen? Why, yes, I believe you wouldn't be spotted if you were there.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Just so. He could see everything without being spotted by the victim or that tanuki Filch. Suffice to say, he was mere witness to the events, rather than an actual third party.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>This guy's as slippery as an eel.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, you think he's telling the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, he WAS in the Fox Chamber, so at least that much must be true.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense may cross-examine our slightly voyeuristic witness.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">I DID enter the Fox Chamber after the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">WHY? Because I was WORRIED sick. Mayor Tenma's suit, it...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It what?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">It was designed PERSONALLY by me. I was WORRIED my work of art might get blood on it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This man clearly has his priorities in order...</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Okay, let's get this over with, SHALL WE? Now, where was I? Oh, yes, so I ENTERED the Fox Chamber almost WITHOUT thinking.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">But I DIDN'T enter until AFTER Jinxie had heard the confession and left.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">And RUIN my designer shoes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your shoes?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Even now, just THINKING about getting blood on my FABULOUS footwear... It sends CHILLS down my spine. That's why I hesitated.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Need I remind you, this is a court of law. We are not teaching morality here. We have schools of etiquette and such for trivial pursuits.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Gah.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Now, you listen to me, you deceptive dandy. Get to the point and be quick about it.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">...Yes, well, I WAS there in the Fox Chamber, BUT...</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">I HEARD the mayor groan and hid behind the folding screen there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Oh, my. So you DO understand!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I do?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">By hiding, I was concealing my FABULOUS beauty, which, for the sake of the universe... ...is something I should NEVER EVER do! THAT'S what you were thinking, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm sensing a black hole of egocentricity forming around the witness stand.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">We can deliberate his mental process another time. Get on with the testimony. Now!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Well, regarding the murder scene...</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">What I saw there up close... It was absolutely HORRIFYING!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Hm? And WHAT exactly would you like DETAILS about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, what I'd like to ask you about is...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you remember about the yokai feathers and tracks?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">They RESULTED when Tenma Taro EXITED the Forbidden Chamber. He came out in QUITE a rush, scattering feathers THIS way and THAT.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you immediately know it was Mr. Filch?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">I did. And THAT'S why I suggested we cook up our alibis together.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And how did those practice sessions go?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">They were NEARLY the death of me. Filchy has to be the WORST STUDENT EVER.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He really doesn't think he's done anything wrong, does he?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? Do you consider his statement to be of any importance?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is it important?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, I believe it is, Your Honor. I request that it be added to the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"The yokai feathers and tracks weren't there before the Fox Chamber was opened."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's probably not particularly important.</thought> No, Your Honor. The witness may proceed.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">All right, then. I would JUST like to add that it was a TERRIBLY grisly scene, as I have described.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you remember about the yokai feathers and tracks?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">They RESULTED when Tenma Taro EXITED the Forbidden Chamber. He came out in QUITE a rush, scattering feathers THIS way and THAT.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you immediately know it was Mr. Filch?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">I did. And THAT'S why I suggested we cook up our alibis together.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And how did those practice sessions go?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">They were NEARLY the death of me. Filchy has to be the WORST STUDENT EVER.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He really doesn't think he's done anything wrong, does he?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I've already had him add this statement to his testimony... ...but is there really anything there? Maybe I should try reviewing the evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could you please describe the Forbidden Chamber at the time?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">It was SHUT tight until the MAYOR opened it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He's really trying to stress that it was the mayor who opened the Forbidden Chamber.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Tsk, that big liar! He opened it himself!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Whoa. If looks could kill, L'Belle would be toast!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? Do you consider his statement to be of any importance?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is it important?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I have a feeling it is. Let's add it to the testimony, just in case.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"The Forbidden Chamber was shut tight until the mayor opened it."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's probably not particularly important.</thought> No, Your Honor. The witness may proceed.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">All right, then. I would JUST like to add that it was a TERRIBLY grisly scene, as I have described.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could you please describe the Forbidden Chamber at the time?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">It was SHUT tight until the MAYOR opened it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He's really trying to stress that it was the mayor who opened the Forbidden Chamber.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Tsk, that big liar! He opened it himself!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Whoa. If looks could kill, L'Belle would be toast! I've already had him add this statement to his testimony... ...but is there really anything there? Maybe I should try reviewing the evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could you describe the state of the weapons that had been used at the scene?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">The spear had been thrust ALL the way through Alderman Kyubi. Then there was that STATUE the alderman used to BLUDGEON Mayor Tenma. That INCREDIBLY inspiring symbol had fallen to the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, right, the statue... But why would he find it inspiring?</thought> Why exactly did you find the statue inspiring?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! Well! When I saw THAT statue... I felt as if the MERGER had been realized! It was like... ...a celebration of union between town and village -- an INSPIRING symbol of goodwill!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A broken statue next to a bloody corpse... Real inspiring...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? Do you consider his statement to be of any importance?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is it important?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's probably not particularly important.</thought> No, Your Honor. The witness may proceed.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">All right, then. I would JUST like to add that it was a TERRIBLY grisly scene, as I have described.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I believe that to be extremely importantly [sic]! I request that it be added to the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"A statue had fallen to the floor. It was a token of goodwill celebrating the municipal merger."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could you describe the state of the weapons that had been used at the scene?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">The spear had been thrust ALL the way through Alderman Kyubi. Then there was that STATUE the alderman used to BLUDGEON Mayor Tenma. That INCREDIBLY inspiring symbol had fallen to the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, right, the statue... But why would he find it inspiring?</thought> Why exactly did you find the statue inspiring?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! Well! When I saw THAT statue... I felt as if the MERGER had been realized! It was like... ...a celebration of union between town and village -- an INSPIRING symbol of goodwill!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A broken statue next to a bloody corpse... Real inspiring... I've already had him add this statement to his testimony... ...but is there really anything there? Maybe I should try reviewing the evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">The yokai feathers and tracks weren't there before the Fox Chamber was opened.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">They WERE, indeed. And it was QUITE a shock when I saw that yokai.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can't imagine how terrifying it must've been to see this face emerging from the darkness.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Okay, so he's not even reality TV-grade handsome. Can we move on now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, you think that statement's important?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't think there's anything particularly unusual there, so let's keep going.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">The Forbidden Chamber was shut tight until the mayor opened it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">In a SENSE, yes, it COULD be seen as a lie.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, so you admit it?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">In this world RIDDLED with deceit, my beauty is the ONLY self-evident truth! That is to say, all else except me is but fiction and lies.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The nerve of this guy! His testimony is riddled with lies! Looks like I won't be getting anything useful out of this statement.</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">A statue had fallen to the floor. It was a token of goodwill celebrating the municipal merger.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Yes, the STATUE the alderman allegedly use to STRIKE BACK at Mayor Tenma. The mayor TRAMPLED down municipal goodwill only to be CLOBBERED by its symbol! It's QUITE ironic, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And that's when that symbol of goodwill was transformed into a symbol of conflict.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">So you SEE, I was THERE, but merely watching from behind the screen.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Well, it DID seem difficult. He was ALL woozy and stumbling around as he opened it. It was SUCH a heroic effort that I NEARLY started to cheer him on despite myself!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think the mayor needed medical attention more than a cheerleader.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">You think he's telling the truth about being there in that room?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I believe he was there... The question is, when did he enter?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You mean, did he enter after Jinxie fled... ...or was he there before the murder? If it's the latter, that would change everything.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. If he was there before the murder, that would make him a suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But how do we go about proving that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well... I guess we ask him about what happened there. Anyway, let's press him and see what kind of info we can extract from him.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's cross our fingers that he says or reveals something incriminating.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your lies have finally betrayed you, Mr. L'Belle!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">What POSSIBLY could you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You said this statue was "like a celebration of union between town and village." Isn't that correct?!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">It is indeed! But WHAT of it? The two yokai ARE joining hands in goodwill... ...as if they were CELEBRATING the municipal merger!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">.........Something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, how did you really know that this statue was meant to be a symbol of goodwill again?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">What?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........Justice-dono, explain yourself. And make it quick.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This statue WAS meant to symbolize goodwill in its original form, but that was a secret.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">A secret? What EVER do you mean?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What I mean is that it broke when someone used it to strike Mayor Tenma on the head. What's left clearly makes it look like the two yokai are battling it out!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Eep!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The statue's secret and its true form were lost inside that locked room. For Ms. Tenma is the only living soul who should know what it once looked like. So, Mr. L'Belle, where could you have possibly seen the statue in its original form?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">! P-Pffft! What do you mean, WHERE?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The only possible answer is this! You saw the statue in its original form... ...right there in the room where the alderman was murdered before it was broken!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">How DARE you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Justice! Are you accusing the witness with some sort of crime?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yes. Yes I am. Florent L'Belle! I accuse you of the murder of Alderman Rex Kyubi!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Mr. L'Belle! You've been accused of murder. Do you have anything to say in your defense?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">...Arrrrrrgh! How could YOU possibly accuse ME -- the EMBODIMENT of BEAUTY!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Way to go, Apollo! This is the conclusive evidence we needed! Magnifico!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We've got you now! We know you killed the alderman. Now, admit it!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">I-I... I... Aaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Enough of your silly games, Justice-dono. This prancing peacock could not possibly be the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Why could he have not seen the statue in its true form before the murder? After all, he was close friends with the alderman. Ergo...</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Y-Yes, th-that's right! I CLEARLY remember it now! Alderman Kyubi TOLD me about it. ...About what the statue ACTUALLY looked like! I mean, he WAS a good friend of mine, ah ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Moreover, it has already been proven that he was not present at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It has?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Forgotten, have we? Recall the little scamp's statement if you will. When Jinxie Tenma unlocked the Fox Chamber... ...she saw the alderman and the mayor collapsed therein -- and no one else.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dangit.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The fact is, it was you two who made that apparent in yesterday's court session. Thus, Florent L'Belle could not possibly have been in that locked room!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urrrrghhnnn...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nooooooooo...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh! <thought>I just don't get it. How could Jinxie not have seen L'Belle?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........The proof is incontrovertible. No room for debate exists. Am I not right, Your Baldness?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It does seem awfully conclusive. The facts point to the defendant and victim being the only people in that locked room. Moreover, the defendant has already confessed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You cannot defend the indefensible. Your role in this charade is over, Justice-dono.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-B-But...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Your Baldness... This trial would last an eternity if we were to keep crossing blades with these simpletons. It is high time you brought down the hammer of justice.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...A point well made. I believe it's time to declare a verdict. This court finds the defendant, Damian Tenma...</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Tenma:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">M-Mayor Tenma?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Counselor! There is a matter to which I must testify! I recall it now only for your good graces.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">C-Counselor? Oh, right, he must mean me. <thought>Has he finally remembered what happened before that blow to his head?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Bailiff! Don't just stand there! Seize him!</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">It's no good! I can't restrain him!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Caw caw-caw-caw! Know me and despair! For I am Tenma Taro, demon lord of the yokai!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Justice! Do something!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Since when am I responsible for court security?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, this is our chance! We might get some new information out of him!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Your Honor! Seeing as our client has something new to say... ...I believe due process demands that we hear him out, even if he is a yokai!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... When you put it that way... .........Still, I believe testimony by a yokai is unprecedented in the legal world.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Unprecedented in absurdity more like.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right then, Mr. Damian Tenma -- or should I say, Mr. Tenma Taro. Your testimony, please.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">I shall now speak of recollections most real, courtesy of my host Damian Tenma. Heed these words, mortals, for hear them but once you shall! Caw caw-caw-caw!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Barely conscious was Damian there amid the darkness.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............Umm... So, is the defendant asserting that the room he was in was very dark at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Hrmm. Strange as it may be, yes, indeed, all was in darkness.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And the part about Tenma Taro and the Nine-Tailed Fox being there?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Yes, that, too! Tenma Taro towered overhead and the Nine-Tailed Fox glittered gold!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Aaaaah! I call animal abuse, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. It would seem the defendant's recollections are not to be trusted.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Yes, well, truth be told, my host's recollections are still a bit fuzzy. As if half dreamt, that happening lingers in his mind.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Apollo. Maybe I can help here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? Oh, you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, I can hear it. The discord in his heart. I sense an unusual emotion in the mayor's memory of the event.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, I just hope our findings don't come back to haunt us... again.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Barely conscious was Damian there amid the darkness.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Suddenly, two yokai did appear!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">On, one side, I, Tenma Taro, ruler of demonkind!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">And on the other, my mortal enemy, the Nine-Tailed Fox!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It sounds like the mayor saw the same thing as what's shown on that scroll.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's with those Tenmas and their yokai vision?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think it's sweet how father and daughter can share something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't think a shared nightmare really qualifies as sweet.</thought> Anyway, all I need to do is point out an unnatural reaction like last time?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right. Look for places where an emotion conflicts with the testimony. That conflict usually indicates a thought or emotion that is being suppressed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When the Nine-Tailed Fox appeared, you not only experienced shock and sadness... ...but also, something like joy as well.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Joy? Hmm... Perhaps it was joy at the light coming to my eyes at long last. A long and terrible creaking did pierce the silence... ...and then there was light! On reflection, it was a door that did produce that infernal racket.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A creaking door? Oh, you must be talking about the Forbidden Chamber door. It does make a lot of noise.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, this means the Forbidden Chamber really was opened. But what about the sudden light he described?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think I know! He mentioned darkness and Tenma Taro towering overhead. Maybe the mayor wasn't really in the Fox Chamber at the time of the crime! Mr. Mayor! Did the darkness that you were in happen to be here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Hrrrm? You claim I was there? No such recollections do I possess.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's just because your memory is still hazy!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Hrmm... On further reflection, I believe that... ...you are gravely misguided!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He means you got that one wrong, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Counselor! I expect attempts of a more serious nature from you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All right, let's think that one over again.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">The Forbidden Chamber?! Was it not the Fox Chamber where the murder did occur?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, but it all makes sense if you were in the Forbidden Chamber! That terrible creaking sound was probably the Forbidden Chamber's door opening. And the towering Tenma Taro you saw? Most likely the Forbidden Chamber's statue!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Why, yes! That would explain it! The darkness and the staff in the demon's grasp!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But even if all that's true, then what about the Nine-Tailed Fox?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Umm... Maybe he was seeing things, just like Jinxie and her imaginary yokai.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Fantástico, Apollo! It's entirely possible! In a groggy, dream-like state, people can misremember things and events.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Misremember, you say? Hrmm. Let me think. ...Ah! I do believe... I remember now! That... that was not the Nine-Tailed Fox. It was... ...The Amazing Nine-Tails!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Wh-Whaaaaaat! Th-The Amazing Nine-Tails?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">At first, this is but a dream, I thought. Now, however, most clearly do I recall it. Twas The Amazing Nine-Tails who did open the Forbidden Chamber's door!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ <thought>I'm sorry I asked.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">The Amazing Nine-Tails? But that was the victim, Alderman Kyubi, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. Why would he open the Forbidden Chamber? Wasn't he trying to keep it sealed?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Never mind that! This is completely new information! Let me enter it and run an update!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Barely conscious was Damian there in the Forbidden Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Amid the darkness, a mighty statue of Tenma Taro loomed overhead.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Suddenly, the door did open, and a shaft of light did pierce the gloom!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">The Amazing Nine-Tails had come to the rescue!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What do you suppose The Amazing Nine-Tails was up to?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Good question. Could he have been trying to free the mayor from the Forbidden Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But why help an enemy like that? Wasn't he opposed to the mayor's merger plan?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... Well, at least now we know why the room suddenly lit up.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Must've been a huge relief for the mayor. I mean, just thinking about being trapped in that pitch-black room freaks me out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When The Amazing Nine-Tails opened the chamber, banishing the darkness within... ...you felt joy, but didn't you also feel shock and sadness?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Hrmmm... Yes, in the hazy depths of my mind, I do recollect something of that nature. I believe it was the fiend's cape of red. For when I did behold it, a great wave of sadness did inexplicitly wash over me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A cape... of red?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! We've reduced the noise level! Oh, but there's still a little left.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mayor Tenma, why were you sad when you saw the red cape?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Hrmmm... Why indeed...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What could this mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess his memory is still a little spotty. I know because his latest recollection contradicts the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, it's one of those contradictions that slaps you right across the face.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... Something this obvious could arise... ...when someone is trying to force a fuzzy memory into a definitive shape. Apollo, I know what you have to do! You need to present evidence that contradicts the image you see!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, so it's basically the same as the usual cross-examination process. <thought>Okay, time to review the evidence. Look out contradiction, here comes Justice!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Barely conscious was Damian there in the Forbidden Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Amid the darkness, a mighty statue of Tenma Taro loomed overhead.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Suddenly, the door did open, and a shaft of light did pierce the gloom!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">The Amazing Nine-Tails had come to the rescue!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It still seems like his memory is really confused.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, that's because unlike data, memories are living, breathing things. Preconception, illusion, memory overlap, memory repression... Our memories are intimately tied to our psychology and emotions.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, this contradiction is somehow caused by an emotion?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I believe so. There's some deeper meaning here. Let's present some evidence. Maybe it will help jog his memory!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You said The Amazing Nine-Tails's cape was red. Are you sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Yes, well, I do believe it was a red cape I saw, but...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mayor Tenma! Does this cape look red to you?!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Ohhhh! That certainly does NOT look red! Not even scarlet or crimson, either! Nevertheless! Upon my liberation something red did fill my as yet hazy field of view... ...and I thought to myself, "Ah! The Amazing Nine-Tails is arrayed in a cape of red!"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you mistook that red something for his cape, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Apparently so. And remembering it now, brings a great sadness upon me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So the red something probably wasn't a cape after all. Maybe that great sadness he mentioned is what's interfering with his memory.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, he would've seen the Fox Chamber behind The Amazing Nine-Tails. What red object could he have seen there that would've been that shocking? Hmm... I know! Could it have been...! Mr. Mayor, was the red thing you saw this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tenma:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa! Sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">I'm afraid I have no recollection of seeing such an item. You must cease this practice of leaping before looking!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-Sorry! Sorry! <thought>Youch! That was a human/demon double punch!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, think of something that's red and could produce a feeling of sadness... And take a good look at the evidence again!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Something red that could produce a deep sadness... Could it be, Mr. Tenma, that what you saw... was the alderman's blood?!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Blood?! Why, yes! It was blood! Arrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrgh! Oooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooh! Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh! It's all coming back to me now! It wasn't a red cape that I saw... It was, lying behind The Amazing Nine-Tails, the alderman's bloody body!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">His noise level is down to zero! I think he's remembered everything now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Does this mean The Amazing Nine-Tails killed Alderman Kyubi?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But the alderman WAS The Amazing Nine-Tails, so how exactly would that work?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey! I asked you first!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice, you sure know how to make a complicated matter even more complicated.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">True, but at the time of the crime, out client was in the Forbidden Chamber. Moreover--</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hoy! Don't you think this strange? The little scamp has already confirmed her father to be in the Fox Chamber. But she said naught about seeing The Amazing Nine-Tails there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack. <thought>You just had to bring that up, didn't you...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Jinxie didn't see L'Belle there, either. It's so weird. Who really was in that room, then?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Would the defense care to share any theories with the court? Can you explain the inconsistency between the defendant's testimony and his daughter's?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, o-of course, I can explain it! <thought>Because if I don't, we're in serious trouble!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Explaining something like that would be completely--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I am?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Even if you can't explain it, you can't let them know that! Just make something up!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't hear YOU helping!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Not with more of your bluffs and fairy tales, I trust? Fair warning, Justice-dono. I shall have your head if you fail to explain this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eep! <thought>What about a good old-fashion penalty?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice, let's see if you have a head worth keeping on your shoulders.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">First of all, Mr. L'Belle was definitely in the Fox Chamber while it was locked. We also know that Mayor Tenma was in the Forbidden Chamber based on his testimony. These two facts are crucial to my explanation. So, let us consider the following question. If the facts point to Florent L'Belle and the victim being there at the scene... ...why did Jinxie Tenma see her father Mayor Tenma and the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... A very good question, indeed. And I suppose you have an answer for us?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>Sadly, you would be supposing wrong...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Umm... You think she could've mistaken L'Belle for the mayor?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, if she did, then the question is, why did she do that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, how about that explanation, Mr. Justice? I believe the time for questions is over. The defense asserts that Florent L'Belle was at the scene of the crime. However, Jinxie Tenma has testified that she saw her father collapsed there. If she has, in fact, misremembered the event, what could've made her do so?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ms. Tenma was in a state of confusion at the time. That's how she mistook Mr. L'Belle for Mayor Tenma there in the Fox Chamber. After all, they both look kind of like yokai.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid I don't follow you, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, can I have a do-over on that one?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She only thought she was in the Fox Chamber because she got the rooms mixed up!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... When I'm in a big rush, I may make an unintended detour or two through the building... ...but I never end up in the wrong courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Even if she was confused, I think she'd notice if she entered the Forbidden Chamber. There is that massive barred door to deal with, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right. Eh heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A penalty for our spatially challenged attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Let's try that one again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The figure Ms. Tenma saw was not her father. It was Florent L'Belle disguised as Damian Tenma.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">That is a complete impossibility. Their faces are utterly unalike. How could you explain that away with a mere disguise?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, they both DO have incredibly distinctive faces.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">M-Maybe the disguise completely hid his face?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think Jinxie would've mentioned if she couldn't see her father's face.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">And if it was that sort of disguise, wouldn't she have removed it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Your sword is as dull as your mind, Justice-dono. Shall I show you what a truly sharp blade is capable of?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aha ha ha... I think I'll pass--ack! Aaaaaaaaaaaaaah!!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Are you okay, Apollo?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm... I'm... not fine, am I?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Well, now that we have that little fairytale out of the way... Your Baldness, your verdict if you will.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice, I believe it's time for a verdict if you have no further arguments.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uhh... <thought>What's even left for me to do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! Remember what Mr. Wright always says? When you're stuck in a tight spot, turn the case upside down.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Turn the case upside down? Hmm... He does say that, doesn't he? But I don't quite see how it applies here. <thought>Still, never hurts to give it a try, I guess. Let's see... Rather than "Jinxie didn't remove the disguise," maybe "she couldn't remove it." And rather than "she didn't tell anyone about the disguise"... maybe it was "she couldn't talk about it."</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">A wrestler's mask is more precious than his own life! He'd never unmask himself in front of others. But there ARE matches where wrestlers battle for the right to remove each other's masks. To have your mask torn off is the worst humiliation a wrestler could suffer! That's why their masks are more important to them than life itself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And what about the fact that it was The Amazing Nine-Tails who opened the door? A mask that can't be removed in front of others? Can these facts turn things around?</thought> Ah! Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh! <thought>We... We got it all backwards!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think... I think we might've made a huge mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Your Baldness, I see no need to further indulge them in their silly little farce. The defense has no proof. They never did and they never will.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Then it seems I must announce my verdict--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........Do you, now?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right, but this better be good, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We can solve the remaining riddles by turning all of our assumptions upside down. Why Jinxie Tenma mistook Mr. L'Belle for her father... ...why she couldn't remove the costume, or tell anyone about it in the first place... These riddles are inextricably linked to Mayor Tenma's secret identity! A shocking secret identity that will turn the entire premise of this case upside down! This piece of evidence clearly reveals Mayor Tenma's secret identity!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Isn't it obvious?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, it isn't.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I, too, fail to see your point.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, I guess we're all in the same boat, then.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice! The only revelation here is your shocking desperation.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Okay, time to find something that doesn't stink of desperation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Gah! Wh-What absolute claptrap! Poppycock! Balderdash!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We thought the alderman was The Amazing Nine-Tails and the mayor was Tenma Taro. That's why we believed the mayor killed the alderman in his lust for Nine-Tails Vale. And it was the basis for the prosecution's entire case against our client. However... We got the whole thing backwards. Mayor Tenma wasn't Tenma Taro at all. He was The Amazing Nine-Tails!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What's thiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You... You'd best explain yourself, Justice-dono... And from where you derived such a farfetched conclusion!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Jinxie, no doubt, knew the true identity of The Amazing Nine-Tails. But she couldn't tell anyone no matter what. That's why she didn't say it was The Amazing Nine-Tails she saw passed out! Even though, unbeknownst to her, it was really Florent L'Belle in disguise!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The accused and that deceitful dandy are utterly dissimilar in physical build and voice. The little scamp would have seen the difference!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Why did she not simply pull the mask off?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Gah! Uuuwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This case of mistaken identity also explains the riddle of the locked room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then by all means, Mr. Justice, answer it for us already!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">First, Mr. L'Belle entered the room where the mayor and the alderman were talking. I suspect he brought with him coffee laced with some sort of sedative. Once the alderman was out cold... ...that's when Mr. L'Belle killed him! Next, he took the mayor, who he had also drugged, into the Forbidden Chamber. Then he returned to the Fox Chamber, slipped into some of the mayor's spare clothes... ...and completed the disguise by donning The Amazing Nine-Tails's mask! With his entire charade in place, Mr. L'Belle then let out a scream... ...the scream that led Jinxie Tenma to the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ah! So then... ...the person who said, "I killed Alderman Kyubi" was...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yep, that was Florent L'Belle in disguise. The mayor never actually confessed.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. This is no more than guesswork and speculation. Now, stop your jabbering and--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Argh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Once Ms. Tenma left the scene... ...Mr. L'Belle, still wearing the mayor's clothes and mask, opened the Forbidden Chamber... ...so he could drag the mayor back out into the Fox Chamber!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, so The Amazing Nine-Tails the mayor saw was...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right, it was L'Belle opening the Forbidden Chamber. The second time Mr. L'Belle opened the door to the Forbidden Chamber... ...he happened to catch the thieving Mr. Filch by surprise. Startled, Mr. Filch in his Tenma Taro disguise ran as fast as he could away from the room. As he did, he left behind him a trail of feathers and tracks... ...and gave Ms. Tenma the scare of her life in the hallway. With no one left to witness the events that had occurred... ...Mr. L'Belle then proceeded to drag the sleeping mayor back into the Fox Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Well, that all certainly does make sense.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then, after dragging the mayor back into the Fox Chamber... ...Mr. L'Belle threw the mask out the window and fled the room!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">For this absurd theory to work, it requires that the defendant be The Amazing Nine-Tails. However, he was the one pushing for the municipal merger. That such an individual could possibly be The Amazing Nine-Tails is preposterous!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Gah! This is madness! No one could possibly hatch such an insane plot!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No one except a killer as insane as his plot, and I'd say Florent L'Belle more than qualifies.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Foolish mortal! It is at your own peril that you forget who I am!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">M-Mayor Tenma! It's okay now! Jinxie will be safe just as soon as Mr. L'Belle is arrested! You ARE The Amazing Nine-Tails, aren't you?!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">I-I...! .........Hrmmmm.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! You have QUITE the active imagination! Mayor Tenma is NOT The Amazing Nine-Tails.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">WELL, has the mayor ADMITTED to it yet?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But that's just--</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">And even if he DID admit to such nonsense... ...I would reveal the TRUTH behind Tenma Taro right here and now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Why you--! You would dare reveal the secret?!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">A ha ha ha! My GOOD FRIEND the alderman told me ALL about it. But it WOULDN'T be good to expose the truth, what with the superstitions, now would it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The truth behind Tenma Taro? What's he talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">So, go ahead, SAY it! Say, "I AM The Amazing Nine-Tails!" I DARE you!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Arrrrrrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Mayor Tenma will do ANYTHING to keep the truth behind Tenma Taro a secret. A dark, TERRIBLE truth that has been kept SECRET by the village superstitions.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And if the mayor admits to being The Amazing Nine-Tails, you'll expose the truth?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Right! I WON'T have him walking free because of some NONSENSE you made up.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........Hmph. So, what now, Justice-dono? Without the mayor's admission, your theory is as useless as you are in battle.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'll show YOU who's useless!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! Don't you dare give up now!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I know, I know. Your Honor! I believe Mr. L'Belle's statements warrant a thorough cross-examination! After all, the true identity of The Amazing Nine-Tails is the cornerstone of this case!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... You do have a point there. Please answer this court, Mr. L'Belle: Is the defendant The Amazing Nine-Tails or not?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">The Amazing Nine-Tails's TRUE identity is NOT Mayor Tenma.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Talk about out of the pot and into the fire... At this rate, the mayor will be found guilty for sure...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Honestly speaking, if Mayor Damian Tenma is not The Amazing Nine-Tails... ...I'm afraid I don't see how the defense has much of a case here.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! And LET'S just leave it at that, shall we? We ALL know Alderman Kyubi was The Amazing Nine-Tails, anyway. I mean, THAT'S how Nine-Tails Vale made a comeback -- the alderman was SO popular.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's... gotta be a hole in that testimony somewhere... But I don't even know where to start.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Since we don't have any proof that the mayor is The Amazing Nine-Tails... ...then we'll just have to get him to admit it himself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But if he admits it, L'Belle's going to expose the secret behind Tenma Taro. <thought>Argh! We are so close! I know it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">The Amazing Nine-Tails's TRUE identity is NOT Mayor Tenma.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Nothing more than idle speculation. You've no evidence, now, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! Sorry, but I HEARD about the statue from Alderman Kyubi. If you DON'T believe me, just ASK him. Oh, but what's that? The ALDERMAN'S dead? Ah ha ha ha! LOOKS like the joke's on YOU, my sweaty little friend!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! You mind if I wring his neck?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait in line, 'cause I'm going first!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Temper, temper... ANYWAY...</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">The mayor would NEVER admit to such UTTER nonsense.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Tsk tsk. Such anger is TERRIBLE for the skin, you know. BEAUTY is like a FLOWER that blooms forth from a serene heart.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Pffft. I wouldn't EXPECT a wilted peasant like you to understand. Perhaps this fragrance will help the BLOSSOM within you BLOOM!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! You liked that, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Enough jabbering about blossoms and whatnot. Get on with your testimony before I slice you into a bouquet of cut flowers.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Oh, dear, please excuse me. As I was saying, the ASSERTION of our wilted attorney here is UTTER NONSENSE.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">But if he DID admit to such nonsense...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Yes, it's true. I would be SACRIFICED upon the altar of justice DESPITE my innocence. But what a TERRIBLE loss that would be for the FUTURE of humankind's cosmetic needs! It is a TRAGEDY that MUST be averted! Defend me if you UNDERSTAND this!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The only terrible loss is the time wasted by your ceaseless yammering. If you would avert the tragedy awaiting you and that vexing visage of yours, then--</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Yes, yes, I know. Get on with my testimony. Anyhow, suffice to say... ...should the mayor ADMIT to the defense's nonsense, I will make good on my threat and...</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">...I will EXPOSE the TRUTH behind Tenma Taro right here and now...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Alderman Kyubi told me all about it. The SECRET of the Forbidden Chamber AND the TRUTH behind Tenma Taro!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why would he share a secret like that with you, Mr. L'Belle?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Because of the alderman's wife. I was looking AFTER her while she was hospitalized. He appreciated it SO much, he shared the SECRETS with me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, did he threaten the alderman in addition to the mayor?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Don't tell me THAT'S how he learned how to open the Forbidden Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Needless to say, I'm NOT above revealing the TRUTH behind Tenma Taro...</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">...and THAT would bring RUIN upon Nine-Tails Vale, just as the superstitions say.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">EXACTLY. Telling others what Tenma Taro LOOKS like would REVEAL the truth. THAT'S why the superstitions were written down in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And ruin coming to the village if you free him? Is that a warning not to expose the truth?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! Bingo! And that truth is, Tenma Taro is a great, greed-inspiring fortune! That's what the whole battle over Nine-Tails Vale is all about!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Tenma Taro is.. a great fortune? Come to think of it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Filch">Eh heh heh. Only that it's the greatest get-rich-quick chance in the universe. Grandpappy told me all about it. Said there's an amazing treasure in there!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could Tenma Taro actually be...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mayor Tenma just has to be Tenma Taro... right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Telling the villagers that Tenma Taro is a terrifying yokai... ...is what has scared them away from the Forbidden Chamber and the treasure within. That's how the treasure has been kept secret all this time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! Well, well, well... It seems our ace attorney here has uncovered the truth that MUST NOT be revealed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Mayor Tenma looks like he wants to keep the truth hidden as much as I do...</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">TRAGEDY is DOOMED to repeat itself as long as Tenma Taro exists. THAT'S why the secret MUST BE protected!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>As long as Tenma Taro exists, huh...</thought> Mr. L'Belle, please add that statement to your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"TRAGEDY is DOOMED to repeat as long as Tenma Taro exists."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">EXACTLY. Telling others what Tenma Taro LOOKS like would REVEAL the truth. THAT'S why the superstitions were written down in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Telling the villagers that Tenma Taro is a terrifying yokai... ...is what has scared them away from the Forbidden Chamber and the treasure within. That's how the treasure has been kept secret all this time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! Does your hopelessness have you at a LOSS for WORDS? Well, your case IS hopeless, so I'd say that's MORE than appropriate.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">TRAGEDY is DOOMED to repeat as long as Tenma Taro exists.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Yes, I SUPPOSE so, but THAT'S wishful-- This is L'Belle. ...Yes. ...Mm-hm. ...You don't say?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... As long as Tenma Taro exists, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">How's the mayor supposed to admit to his secret identity now?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, we have to find a way to make him say it, or our entire case unravels. There must be a hole in L'Belle's testimony somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. L'Belle, what if Tenma Taro no longer existed? Revealing the truth would no longer be an issue, would it?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">...If Tenma Taro no longer existed? Ah ha ha ha! What on EARTH are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, apparently you haven't heard. Tenma Taro no longer exists. But I guess you didn't get to do a thorough search after the key was taken from you... ...because when we searched the Forbidden Chamber, there wasn't any treasure there!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Really? Well, MAYBE you weren't looking in the RIGHT place.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sorry, but I have proof that Tenma Taro no longer exists. Take a look at this figure.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do we have here? It looks like some sort of creature.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We found this in the Forbidden Chamber. It's an Azuki Kozo figure. The great thief Azuki Kozo used to leave them at the scene of his crimes.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Are YOU suggesting that... that Tenma Taro has been STOLEN?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yep. Phineas Filch's grandfather, a master thief, was the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">And by that hideous, moronic caretaker's grandfather, no less?! ...You! I-- Nooooooooooooooooooo! M-My beautiful golden, Tenma Taro was...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The greed inspired by Tenma Taro can no longer bring ruin upon Nine-Tails Vale. Isn't that right, Mayor Tenma?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">The root of tragedy would indeed seem to be gone. In fact, I now recall the alderman revealing the secret to me on the day of our meeting. He must have been speaking of Tenma Taro. For he said to me, the gold ingot was gone.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The gold ingot? You mean the treasure that is Tenma Taro's true form...?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Recall, if you will, the scroll in the Forbidden Chamber. Tenma Taro is the yellowish object shown there... ...a giant gold ingot that my nomadic ancestors bestowed upon Nine-Tales [sic] Vale. In return for that gold, my ancestors did receive from Nine-Tails Vale... ...land that would become Tenma Town. But drive the villagers mad with greed did that great fortune! Bitter was their greed-fueled battle. It was as if they were possessed. My ancestor's gold became as a curse upon their village -- a curse of ruin. Thus it was that the yokai Tenma Taro came to be.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, Tenma Taro and the village superstitions were merely fairytales to scare people away.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. Fairytale or not, Tenma Taro made quite the mess of things.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Yes, indeed, for there is no greater monster than a mortal man's lust for gold.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, you know what they say, "The love of money is the root of all evil."</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">My ancestors did bring a terrible thing here to Nine-Tails Vale. A thing so terrible that... ...Tenma Taro, a monster just as terrible, had to be created to keep it a secret. Yet we have naught but love for the little village to which we owe our very existence. Tenma Town would never seek to take over Nine-Tails Vale in a merger!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh my. That was quite a shocking lesson in history.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Mayor. Now that we know Tenma Taro no longer exists... ...are you ready to admit YOUR secret? You ARE The Amazing Nine-Tails, aren't you?!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">L'Belle:</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Be gone, you demented demon! Ahem. Now, where was I... The golden lord of yokai, The Amazing Nine-Tails is, indeed, me! Ah-ha ha ha ha ha! Ah-ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Ah-ha ha ha ha ha! Ah-ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And that means...! Jinxie!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">.........Y-Yes?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The man wearing the mayor's clothes who you saw collapsed in the Fox Chamber... Was he wearing The Amazing Nine-Tails's mask?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">...Uh-huh. That's what made me think it was Papa. He said he was going to reveal his secret identity to Alderman Kyubi that day, so... So... it wasn't really Papa I saw there, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">It was Florent's idea from the start. He advised me to reveal my secret identity to the alderman.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yeesh, Rube Goldberg machines have less elaborate setups than L'Belle's scheme...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tenma">You may rest easy now, Jinxie. That monster's deception is through! Caw caw-caw-caw!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The true facts behind this case have finally come to light! Mayor Tenma did not kill Alderman Kyubi! But Florent L'Belle DID!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">How... dare you... PEASANT! Gnrk! Uwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah! Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh! NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!!!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...............Hmph! Justice-dono... You should at least have a real blade in your hands if you desire to cross swords with me. Or have you mistaken this battlefield for a training ground?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>What's this guy want now?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Evidence is like a razor-sharp blade that cuts through bone as though it were butter. But you have only blind guesses -- a dull blade incapable of cutting even a cake.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He has you there, Mr. Justice. After all, evidence is everything in a court of law.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-B-But!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">They're right! Let's see some EVIDENCE! Of course, a PERFECT being like me wouldn't leave ANY incriminating evidence behind. Ah ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">This is the final battle. Just as a samurai must live and die by the sword... ...you will live or die by the evidence you hold. My swift blade of judgment awaits. Now, present your conclusive evidence, or don't you have any?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, crud... Do I have anything conclusive?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Evidence? Oh, I have evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-You do?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of course! It's just the conclusive evidence we need, too! <thought>I'm going to finally prove Mayor Tenma innocent! Here comes Justice!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh. I can't think of anything. But there has to be some kind of evidence I can present.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't give up now, Apollo! Let's try reviewing the case again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm... I'm... I'm......... ...I'M FINE, I'M FINE, I'M FINE, I'M FINE! <thought>She's right. I can't give up now. This whole trial would've been for nothing! I know there has to be some conclusive evidence somewhere!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's review the facts. The most damning evidence against the mayor was the crime scene itself. The mayor and the victim were the only two people found in the room. Also, we all though [sic] the alderman was killed because he was The Amazing Nine-Tails. But as we know now, of course, we were way off. The Amazing Nine-Tails is really Mayor Damian Tenma! That's why when his daughter Jinxie saw The Amazing Nine-Tails collapsed at the scene... ...she mistook him for her father. Those are the facts we have revealed. However, Mr. L'Belle asserts that he did not leave any evidence at the scene of the crime. But he didn't say anything about evidence outside the crime scene. Maybe he isn't as clever as he thinks he is! Does any of the evidence found outside the crime scene provide any clues?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, that's not it. The hand cream had Phineas Filch's prints on it... ...because Filch had stolen it from L'Belle. That's not going to help us nab the real killer, though. Maybe I should study the evidence again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, I know. The Amazing Nine-Tails's mask! It was found washed up along the river. What sort of clue does that mask hold?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The patch of golden animal fur... It was found caught in the window at the crime scene. Oh, but that's evidence from inside the Fox Chamber. I should be thinking about evidence that was found outside of the crime scene right now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And what about the hair left in the mask? Who does it belong to?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The hair in the mask belonged to the alderman. So, the true identity of The Amazing Nine-Tails is... the alderman? No, of course it isn't! What am I thinking?! Someone had been wearing that mask at the crime scene. That's what I should focus on! Let's think about that again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right! That hair is Florent L'Belle's! Yes! Now that's what I call conclusive evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? Do you have any conclusive evidence to present to this court?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of course, I do! Observe this mask, if you will.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That mask? How is that conclusive evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's not the mask itself, but the white hair inside it. We originally thought it belonged to Alderman Rex Kyubi.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, but The Amazing Nine-Tails, as we now know, is Mayor Tenma, so...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That is correct. So, the question is, whose hair could this be? And the answer to that is the last person to have worn it before it was discarded. That would be you, Mr. Florent L'Belle!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">What ARE you talking about?! I NEVER had hideous white hair like that!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It would appear your coup de grâce failed to hit its mark. This freakish fop is not the white-hair type. Because he's busy being one ludicrously garish color or another.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Remember where this mask was found? Washed up by the side of the river? With that in mind... This last piece of evidence will solve all of the remaining riddles!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right. It solves all of the riddles that have been plaguing this case!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! You're presenting the wrong piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oops. <thought>What a place to slip up...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Think about L'Belle's real hair color. Given what it is, there's only one piece of evidence that really stands out in this case!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I know! But in my case, I've got a case of the end-of-case jitters! Sorry, Your Honor. I was way off on that one.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That was an eleventh-hour blunder, and it clearly reveals your attention deficiency. A penalty for our attention-deficient lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm gonna nail it next time. You'll see.</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Argh! Th-That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm? What is that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is Mr. L'Belle's own private brand of hair color. It washes out with just water. The court will also recall that The Amazing Nine-Tails's mask... ...washed up along the side of the village river with white hair inside it.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What's this?! Are you saying that preening peacock's hair color is...?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's exactly what I'm saying. Mr. L'Belle's hair color is a freaky work of fiction. But thanks to the river flowing through Nine-Tails Vale, we now have a real life exposé.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Aaah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The white hair in this mask is conclusive evidence proving you're the real killer! A DNA test is all we need to prove it, and we both know we'll get a match! Admit it! Florent L'Belle, you were the one who killed Alderman Rex Kyubi!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Y-You... You......... Peasant... How DARE yooooooooooooooooou! Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah! You profane MY beauty, like a bug on a roooooooooose. I'm going to exterminate you, like I did the aldermaaaaaaaaaaaaaan! Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah! Aah! Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah! N-Noooooooooooooo! M-M-My makeuuuuuup!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">............... ............... Hello, this is L'Belle! ...What? The project... is off? This is L'Belle! ...The sponsors have pulled out? L'Belle speaking! ...I'm fired? You mean I'm no longer Mayor Tenma's aide?! Hello, this is L'Belle! ...What? There's a stratospheric damages claim against me? ...One hundred m-m-million dollars? Heh heh heh. Hee hee hee! Ah ha ha ha ha! I'm FINISHED, WASHED UP! Stick a fork in me, I'm DOOOOOOOOOONE! A-ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! A-ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...This is preposterous. I, Simon Blackquill, defeated?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order in the court!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well...! This is quite the unexpected outcome. I must hand it to you, Mr. Justice... ...you really turned this case on its head, just like that other lawyer, Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ha ha ha. <thought>Wait, that was a compliment, right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor Blackquill, what have you done with Florent L'Belle?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The defaced man has withered like a flower without water. One of the officers is currently tending to him with a sprinkler.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Um, wouldn't that just wash even MORE of his makeup off?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Allow me to explain the actions of the guilty party in detail. The motive, of course, was to steal the gold ingot known as "Tenma Taro." However, few are allowed into the manor due to its cultural ties to Nine-Tails Vale. L'Belle set in motion plans to gain access to the manor and the gold within via the merger. But the efforts of The Amazing Nine Tails saw those plans come to a halt. And thus, L'Belle murdered the alderman and attempted to pin the blame on Mayor Tenma.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. But what I still can't comprehend is why would he go after the gold in the first place? Mr. L'Belle doesn't look like someone who is in need of financial aid.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">L'Belle hid his past well, much like he hid his "beauty" with makeup. He's mired in debt. Debt due to pouring money into a brand only he could love... ...which is why he sought the gold with such voracity.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Too bad for him, someone else had gotten to it first anyway.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Very well, then. I believe it's time I declared a verdict. This court finds the defendant, Damian Tenma...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was some seriously good lawyering, Apollo. Even I didn't see that coming.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Heh heh. Just got lucky, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You banished Tenma Taro from Nine-Tails Vale like you were some kind of exorcist.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Um, there's one thing I still don't understand. How come Mr. L'Belle didn't kill Mayor Tenma, too? He could've set it up so the mayor murdered the alderman, then died from a counterattack. That would've removed at least one possible fly from the ointment.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was wondering about that, too. But I have a hunch L'Belle was biding his time. He was planning on exposing The Amazing Nine-Tails's true identity himself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? But why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because the mayor was The Amazing Nine-Tails. Had L'Belle succeeded in framing Mayor Tenma for the alderman's murder... ...the wrestler's popularity would've plummeted once his identity was revealed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, I get it! If The Amazing Nine-Tails was just killed, he'd die a hero. But if he was proved a villain... ...his fans would abandon him, making the merger that much easier.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. Then when the merger was complete and everything cooled down... He'd be able to search the Forbidden Chamber at his leisure.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What an insanely intricate plot.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Caw caw-caw-caw! A most excellent job clearing my name! A feat worthy of the demon lord's approval!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, why are you acting like Tenma Taro again?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Let this be of no concern to you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>How could it not concern me?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Tenma Taro, be gone!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Gaaaaah! J-Jinxie... Seems like ages since I've laid eyes on you.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Papa! You're finally back!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Yes, it would seem Tenma Taro is no match for you. Ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">I'm not scared of that silly yokai anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Your father's a free man now, Jinxie! Isn't that great?!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Thank you for all you've done! Seeing you guys in action, it... ...it made me feel like I don't have to be afraid anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait, is Jinxie actually... smiling?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tenma">This is all thanks to you two. Too bad The Amazing Nine-Tails will have to retire, though.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aww, how come?!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Once everyone hears I'm The Amazing Nine-Tails, my fan base will nosedive. After all, I'm not the most popular of people -- another reason for my secret identity. I don't see how I could possibly continue.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hee hee, I think you've misjudged yourself. Take a look outside!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Say, now that you mention it, what's all that noise out there?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A big crowd gathered outside the courthouse once the news broke. Seems they want to get a glimpse of Mayor Damian Tenma, the man behind the mask. And to root for your return to the wrestling ring!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Rooting? For me? But I thought I was nothing more than a malefactor in their eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The only one who really matters is Jinxie. Show her how cool you really are!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Yeah, you're the coolest when you're out there fighting in the ring, Papa!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Jinxie...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Here, I think you'll be needing this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tenma:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Because if you wear it, your fans will come flocking to see you in action!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! That's not what you're supposed to return to him!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? ...Oh, right! <thought>Could I have been any less cool?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">This is what we have to give back to Mayor Tenma!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right, The Amazing Nine-Tails's mask. Here you go, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Thank you. Now, if you would excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">I don't want to keep my fans waiting!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Nine-Tails Vale, forever!</line>
<line speaker="Crowd">Nine-Tails! Nine-Tails! Nine-Tails! Nine-Tails! Nine-Tails!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I sure hope they can settle the problems between Tenma Town and Nine-Tails Vale.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Me, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure they'll be fine. After all... ...the blackmailer-slash-killer is behind bars and the merger's no longer an issue. Plus, The Amazing Nine-Tails is obviously still a hit, and I suspect Nine-Tails Vale will be too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And it's all because we believed in our client, just like you said.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, people. Now that we've got that one in the bag, let's go get something to eat! I'm starving!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sounds good. I've been so nervous I haven't eaten since yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Better keep eating, Apollo! Or you might have to start looking up at me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? I'm definitely past my growth phase, and you should be about past yours, too!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Are you kidding me? I'm just getting started! Ready or not... it's face-stuffing time!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Keep eating like that and the only direction you'll grow is sideways.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Very funny! But I've got a hollow leg! I can eat as much as I want without gaining an ounce!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? Wow, I can't wait to see this.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Calories? Ha! Just let 'em try to stick on me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, already, you two. Let's get going before the old man closes shop. Eldoon's Noodles isn't an all-night stand, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm with Mr. Wright! Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I've been waiting to have a bowl from there ever since Mr. Wright told me about them! Well, what are we waiting for?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The noodles are on me today, so I expect some serious eating from you two.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yay! Thanks, Boss! I won't let you down!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Athena has no idea what she's getting into. Mr. Eldoon's noodles are so hot and salty... ...two bowls would kill a man.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">That was our first case together, and it felt like nothing could bring us down after that. The dark age of the law seemed so distant, so irrelevant to our small, cozy office... But little did I know that it had been lurking all along, right there behind us. The first time it made itself known was during the murder at Themis Legal Academy. That case would mark the twilight before the dark, cold night that was to come.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. I object to you on personal grounds. The sole contradiction lies in what your faulty logic dreamt up just now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. The defense will think twice before making such erroneous statements!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It seems that statement didn't particularly conflict with the evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Your gall knows no bounds. It's shocking, really.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's that supposed to mean?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You stand there, brazenly objecting to perfectly factual statements... One does not see such shameless behavior that often.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A penalty for our shameless attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, no. Looks like Blackquill is turning the judge against me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...........................Your Baldness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Who, me?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What do you make of this objection of his?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, I don't know if I should, um, well...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I've no patience for vagaries. Now, answer my question.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes, sir! The defense's objection was clearly misguided!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Bravo. Nicely done.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho ho. It seems our misguided attorney has earned himself a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Erk... I better look before I leap next time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... There has to be a contradiction here somewhere. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Too bad I'm drawing a blank.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">There was a statement that I thought was a little strange, but... ...I wouldn't bet my life on it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........And which statement would that be? Since I'm the one betting my life on it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hee hee hee. Okay, if you must know, I'll show you the one I'm thinking of.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Time to swallow my pride and let her lend a hand. There must be an inconsistency in the testimony Athena's pointing out!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... I can't flag any inconsistencies.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So there haven't been any contradictions in the testimony so far... That can mean only one thing...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Time to press the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. We'll have to work to get the testimony we need. Let's press the heck out of any statements that stick out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The unexpected emotion is right... here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really? You sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, can't you see it? Maybe if you look really hard? Just keep staring, and maybe--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, this isn't a game of "Where's Emo"...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, I'm way off?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">At least make an effort next time!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, okay. Let me try that again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Hrmm? Where is this contradiction of which you speak?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oops, looks like I got that one wrong.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Judge">The contradiction-challenged Mr. Justice just earned himself a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Time to compare the testimony and evidence again.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The defense's argument is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims! This court finds the defendant, Damian Tenma...</line>
</xml>