<xml>
<title>The Kidnapped Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...It's time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't worry, Mr. Edgeworth! I'll be following your every movement with my binoculars!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Good to hear. Now make sure you don't lose sight of me. I'm counting on you for backup.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You can count on me, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have to go. The kidnapper is supposed to contact me soon. <thought>Who would've thought that upon my return, I'd be thrust into a kidnapping case. And that I would be the one who would have to make the ransom drop-off...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Let's see... I checked that the money is all there, safe inside this suitcase... Now all I have to do is await further instructions from the kidnapper... ...which I'm expecting to be transferred to my cell phone. I wonder who else is around? This is meeting place, after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Welcome to Gatewater Land!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? Oh, thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Proto B.">And a big hello to you! I'm the Proto Badger! Nice to meet you! ............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............</line>
<line speaker="Proto B.">Excuse me, but were you perhaps thinking of taking a picture of me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A picture...? Of you...? Sorry, but I'm not interested.</line>
<line speaker="Proto B.">Aww, that's too bad. Well, have a good day!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hello?</line>
<line speaker="???">...Who aRE yOu? YoU'Re nOt ERNesT AmaNo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It sounds like the kidnapper is using some sort of voice alteration device...</thought> I'm his representative, Miles Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="???">...ARE YoU a cOP?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, I'm......... a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="???">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............ I know what you're wondering, and yes, I have brought the ransom money with me.</line>
<line speaker="???">I SeE... In THAt caSe, bRIng thE mOnEy wiTh You to tHe StaDIum.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So this person intends to see if I'm being followed, huh. Please, Detective Gumshoe... I really need you to come through for me this one time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Edgeworth speaking.</line>
<line speaker="???">NeXT, ComE to THe HaUNteD HOUsE.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And just how long do you intend to have me wander around for?</line>
<line speaker="???">ThAt'S fOr mE To dECIdE. YoU dON't hAVE MucH of A cHOIce hERe, mY fRIeNd.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose not.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I've arrived.</line>
<line speaker="???">...Go iNsIDe.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmph. What a dismal place...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">ThaT'S IT. GO thROuGh tHOsE DooRs...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Am I being watched from somewhere?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">LeAVe tHe MoNEy aND GO. NoW.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnngh............ .................. <thought>I was hoping for an exchange, but maybe I should do as they say for now and not push it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I couldn't catch even a glimpse of the kidnapper. Perhaps I should keep an eye on this haunted house until police backup arrives. Agh! It was a trap!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This badge's design is said to reflect the relentlessness and discipline of law enforcement. It comes from the authority vested in us as strict protectors of the law... ...and executors of sentences, much like harsh winter frosts and blazing summer days. To wear it is to identify oneself as a prosecutor, but I have no interest in doing so.</line>
<line speaker="???">That guy... betrayed...</line>
<line speaker="???">No.. can't be... Then the deal...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Who is that...? And what are they talking about...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...split... police...</line>
<line speaker="???">...Alright...</line>
<line speaker="???">...in front of... meet up...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I can't move my body... ...I-I fear I may faint again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Where am I...? <thought>How long was I out...? It wasn't raining like it is now when I made the drop-off... This was supposed to be a simple affair... ...so why have I been taken hostage as well!? I can only assume Detective Gumshoe lost sight of me at some point.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The only reason I agreed to be the drop-off man was because of that phone call. It was from Mr. Ernesst Amano, the director of the powerful zaibatsu, the Amano Group. But aside from that, I also owe him a great debt of gratitude. His only son, Lance, had been kidnapped. I know that Lance is already in his twenties, but I guess some things you never grow out of.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.................. <thought>I can't sit around waiting for someone to come help me! I must escape somehow...</thought> ...Nnnnnggghhhhoooooooooooh!!</line>
<line speaker="???">Hahaha! Was that you making that funny sound!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............Who's there!? And how dare you laugh at a gentleman's plight!? ...Who are you? Are you one of the kidnappers?</line>
<line speaker="???">A kidnapper? Me? No way! I'm not into such petty crimes. Nope! I'm after something much, much bigger!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.................. <thought>Argh! I must be worn out from today's ordeal. Focus, Miles!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, I forgot to introduce myself! Sorry about that! Ahem! Even in the depths of night, when no other bird dares to take flight... ...one alone soars to shine the light of righteousness on the world's blight! And that one is me! For I am the Great Thief, Yatagarasu!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Great Thief? <thought>And did she really just claim to be the Yatagarasu?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, but my real name is Kay Faraday. You can call me "Kay", 'kay!? Good! Glad that's settled!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.................. Not quite. I have a mountain of questions for you... ...but first, if you would be so kind as to remove these ropes.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmm... I wonder... Should I remove them? I was actually having a lot of fun watching you make those silly faces...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! There's no need to get all mad and icy glare-y on me, you know! This rope goes through here, and... there you go!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What a relief. I owe you my thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah, it's OK. You can pay me back in full later!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Now then... What question should I start with? Unfortunately, I can already tell nothing is going to be easy with this cheeky girl...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You call yourself a Great Thief, yet are you really a thief at all?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You doubt me? I get it! You think that a young lady like me couldn't possibly be such a big-time thief, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's not the part I have a tough time believing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">I am the real, genuine Yatagarasu, you know. Yup! I'm a pure-blooded Great Thief! It's a little something I inherited from my predecessor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In that case... you wouldn't mind if I arrested you then, right?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What!? Of course I'd mind! I haven't stolen anything yet! Seriously, I don't know how can you say such a horrible thing to your savior!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's true. Technically, she hasn't stolen anything in front of me... yet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">When you say you're the "Yatagarasu", do you mean you are THE Yatagarasu...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yup! The most righteous of the righteous! The legendary Great Thief! But the title was only recently succeeded to me... ...so I haven't had a chance to steal anything yet as the second Yatagarasu.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I was not aware that thieves could pass down their titles like that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">But don't worry! I've got some big plans in the works!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Big plans, huh? They wouldn't happen to lead to a big arrest, would they?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I knew it! There's just no reasoning with a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm not the problem here!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'll have you know that the Yatagarasu has no interest in stealing petty trinkets! There's one thing and only one thing I want to steal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Only one thing? And what would that be?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">But that's going to have to wait until we find our way out of here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, at least there is one thing we agree on. I'm sure I'll have plenty of time later to learn more about you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Don't surprise me like that! I can't believe you're just shoving things in my face! I mean, aren't there more pressing things you'd rather ask little ol' me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She has a point... I should probably find out more about my mysterious savior first.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">So, you never told me what your name is, Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, I guess not. I'm Miles Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aha! Now I remember!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...How can you "remember" something I just told you...? But she sure is cheery.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Alright, then Mr. Edgeworth, let's get outta here! ............Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It would seem that we are locked in from the other side.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What!? No way! I don't hear you! La la la!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, you do remember where you came in from, right...? It looks like that might be our only way out of this room...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Whoops, slight miscalculation. That's a good height to make an entrance from, but I can't jump that high to make an exit!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...*sigh* I suppose we have no choice but to look around and see if we can't find another way out.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you know where the person who kidnapped me went?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, after they locked you up in here... ...it sounded like they went into the nest room, and started talking to someone.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I feel like I heard something as well, but it's all a haze in my mind. However, I do recall that the kidnapper was talking with someone... I was just a guess before, but I guess I really AM dealing with two kidnappers here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">After that, they left. It almost seemed as if they were done with you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose that is the case, as my kidnapping seems like an afterthought to the $1 million. Well, if they went into the next room, let's see what we can find out through the slot.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnrgh... It seems that we won't be able to open this by ourselves. It also seems quite thick, so we can't just break it down. <thought>There must be another way out of here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ooh, we can peer into the room the kidnappers were in from there!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is a beam in the next room identical to the one in this room. There's even a hook on it to hold a propped-up floor panel in place. Which reminds me...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Did you find something useful, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm, perhaps. I may have found a very handy hint to how we'll get out of here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is that what I think it is?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It looks like the kidnappers had an escape tunnel prepared just in case. That's awesome! They're like a bunch of Great Thieves themselves!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, they're not, because I highly doubt they made the tunnel themselves. The floor panel was removed and propped up <thought>Open floor panel - The panel is held in place by a hook. The entrance to an underground room perhaps?</thought> against the beam in a very specific way. I think this building was originally built with a basement or underground area.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's a door on the opposite side that appears to be the same as this one. Which would mean... ...that I can probably assume that these two rooms are very similar in structure. <thought>I believe I may have just found our ticket out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is this...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Looks like the Bad Badger, and it's looking as bad as ever!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Looks like a costume head to me.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I guess the Bad Badger's costume is, at the very least, a two-piece, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The real question is, why is only the head sitting out here on the floor?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the beam I was tied to. ............</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hm? What's up?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was pondering if perhaps we could make it over to and out the window if we climbed this.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Good thinking! And if it's climbing action you need, just leave it to me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thanks. This little hook looks like it might make for a good foothold. Up you go, Kay, and good luck!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Count on it! The Great Thief Yatagarasu spreads her mighty wings, and takes to the skies! Here I go!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As I thought, this beam <thought>The beam I was tied to - There is a hook on this beam, but it's not enough of a foothold to climb out with.</thought> was definitely not made for climbing.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What do you mean, "As I thought"!? I'm not your guinea pig, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the beam I was tied to. ............ Just maybe, we can use this to climb up to and out the window.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Leave it to me! ...............Wait. Didn't I just try this!? I can't climb this thing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I suppose we'll just have to find another way to escape.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm? Isn't this my phone? It looks like it made it through the ordeal intact.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">If only there was a way for us to contact someone on the outside...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, but we do have a way... right here.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! There was a cell phone here this whole time!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If I'm right, Detective Gumshoe should have contacted the precinct for backup by now.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth, sir! Are you OK!? I was so worried, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm fine. I was knocked unconscious for a spell by the kidnapper, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm sorry, sir! I'm such a failure! If only I hadn't lost sight of you...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective, we don't have time for this. Have the police set up a perimeter right now!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You don't have to worry about that, sir! I already got the boys working on that! But in doing that... I sorta... Aaah...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's wrong, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="???">...Sorry to butt in, but I'm afraid you're going to have to make due with me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Who is this?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Shi-Long Lang of Interpol. A pleasure to speak with you, Mr. Edgeworth. I've heard a great deal about you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So why exactly is an Interpol agent like yourself involved in a domestic kidnapping case?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Don's sweat the details. A crime's a crime whether it's on local or a global scale. Besides... ...you're the one who's in a world of trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A-And why would you say that!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Lang Zi says: "The pack that runs together, stays together." You catch my drift? You caused quite a ruckus by running blindly into a situation and then getting caught.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tsk...!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You should've contacted the police from the very beginning.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sorry that this happened because of a lapse in judgement. However, I humbly request that you please help me out of here posthaste.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">......Sorry, no can do.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">We're hunting the kidnapper now, and I haven't got any hands to spare. As I said, my pack moves as one. You're the one who wanted to go it alone, so good luck to you... Mr. Prosecutor. Oh, and once we do catch the kidnapper, rest assured we'll come find you... eventually.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You... You...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What's wrong? Did you get cut off!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No... My phone ran out of power.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">No way!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It doesn't matter anyway. We should try to get out of here through our own means.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah! I have a name to live up to, after all! If we put our heads together, we're sure to find a way out!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They're holding a Blue Badger photo rally?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You didn't know? Plus, it's not just the Blue Badger, it's his whole family, too. If you manage to snap a shot of every member of the family, you get a really posh prize.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, there's a costume head sitting over there. Why not start with a picture of that?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You can't do that! That's cheating! There's only one of each Badger in the park, so you have to work for it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Speaking of Badgers, there was one sitting against a wall in the haunted house.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Seriously? But somehow, I don't think that one counts, Mr. Edgeworth! You have to take pictures of the costumed ones walking around the park!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... So these are the rules of this game? How quaint...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Maybe we can use this paint to help us escape...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what exactly do you have in mind?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, we could paint "HELP" in really giant letters!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And who, pray tell, would see these giant letters? We're inside a building.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK, then how about we light the paint on fire and send out colored smoke signals! Anyone who saw it would think some crazy arsonist was about, and call the cops! Hmm... Actually, that may not be all that great for me, seeing as I'm a thief and all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Let's try to find something other than this paint to use, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! There's something inside the bottom-right box. Oh, I think it's a Pink Badger costume!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Pink Badger...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You don't keep up with what's going on in the world, do you? In that case, you'd better study up on the whole Badger clan with this!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is this thing?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Think of it as a bible of all the things you'll ever need to know about the clan!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Whatever. I suppose I can keep it as a reference guide or something.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose this means that this is where they keep all the costumes?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It certainly looks that way! It's like the Badger family's home!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There are eight boxes, but seven of them are empty. Which means that seven of the costumes (Costumes - It seems that the costumes of the Badger family are kept in the Isolation Room.</thought> are in use right now.) But aren't these Badgers the mascots of the police force?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, I heard that the police had a hand in sponsoring this theme park. Probably because the Gatewater Group owes the police from all those cases they solved.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They have all the power of the state, and they used it to make a theme park!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's not just any theme park! They have a handcuff-shaped, double-looping roller coaster...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's quite enough. I'm feeling woozy from just the thought of such a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I've already finished examining this area, but it never hurts to look again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what have we here...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! ..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why do I feel a laser-like stare aimed right at me?</thought> D-Did you want to take a look?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, don't mind if I do! Ooh! I see! Yes, this is definitely...! A key <thought>Tiny key - I may be able to open something, somewhere in this room with this key.</thought>! I'm sure it's a key to something!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The "something" is what is relevant to my interest...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Look! It's the Blue Badger!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I suppose even this thing can be popular with women.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">I can't stand him!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What in the...!? <thought>Why is she suddenly beating the Blue Badger's image up!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">He's got the word "badge" right in his name! How bad is that for a girl like me!? And to think he's out there wandering around in this park... I'd better be careful, or he's going to arrest me by the power of his name alone!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I somehow doubt that the Blue Badger has the power to arrest anyone.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So this is the Blue Badger's rival, the Bad Badger, huh. Do you feel some sort of reverence towards this Badger, Kay?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Hah! I can't believe you would be so stereotypical when it comes to thieves! Surely you must also think there are much cooler, and cuter ones out there, right? That's it! I've decided that thieves and thievery need an image makeover!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Good luck with that one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the Blue Badger I met at the main gate.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Excuse me, but his name is "Proto Badger", not "Blue Badger"! He's based off of the very fisrt design created by the local police chief. You know, when you compare the two, the Blue Badger looks a bit cuter!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose as he continued to redesign him, the chief managed to make him cuter and cuter. Even humanity has come a long way when you think about how much we've evolved.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Are we comparing the Blue Badger to humans now...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose this is the Pink Badger? But since it has the same design, doesn't it seem forced to call this one a female?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You think so? I mean, just look at how long her eyelashes are!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's the only difference.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And the fact that she's pink.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And her lips are red! See, lipstick!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.................. <thought>What? She has nothing to say about the giant pink ribbon, or is that too obvious?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Man! Why did they have to put the windows so high up, anyway!? How is a thief supposed to make her daring escape!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose we could make our way out if we were able to climb on top of these lockers.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Haha! That's pretty clever! You'd make a good thief yet, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please don't ever place my name and the word "thief" in the same sentence again.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Let's see... I wonder if I can jump and grab the top of the locker here... Man! Why did they have to make such ginormous lockers, anyway!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Even if we wanted to use these lockers, we'd need some sort of foothold (Lockers - If we can get to the top, then we can escape. If only there were some footholds...</thought>...)</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This hook on this beam...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You know I already tried, and there's no way I can jump from this hook to the window! Come on, even you have to admit when something's just not possible.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hah, I wasn't about to suggest that again. Rather, that it's here for a different purpose.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Really!? Like what!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As you saw in the adjacent room, it's clearly for keeping a floor panel propped up. Which means that there should be a panel in this room that we can open as well.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh! I get it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We didn't notice its existence all this time because it was being hidden by this tarp.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Alright then! Let's fold this thing up and see what's underneath!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Now THIS is what I call a treasure!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow, this must be another entrance to the secret, hidden basement! I totally smell treasure!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The scent I wish to smell is the sweet fragrance of freedom.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Then what are you waiting for!? Hurry up and open the hatch!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Alright. .........Mmnph. This thing is locked down tight <thought>Underground entrance - We might be able to escape through here, but the door is locked.</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aww! Fiddlesticks!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe you're up, Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh? Why me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Because we need to use the tiny key that you've taken quite a liking to.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, gotcha! Just leave it to me! I love the tense feeling of these moments when you're about to uncover something big!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe the feeling of freedom would be much more satisfying right about now.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Alright! I got the secret door open! And now...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ack! Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wha--!? Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you alright!? Kay!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'm fine. The ladder just slipped is all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Thank goodness she's alright. I about had a coronary...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">There's a lot of really large machinery down here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What about an exit?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Umm... It's really dark and cramped down there, so I really doubt there's an exit. Argh, I can't believe that happened!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You have only yourself to blame for leaping before you looked, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">No way! I mean, how was I supposed to know that the ladder is removable <thought>Underground ladder - It looks as though it can be easily removed, but is it really safe to use...?</thought>!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I finally got the door to the underground area open...</thought> Kay, I just want to confirm with you that there wasn't an exit down there.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, it was really cramped, and there was a lot of really large machinery.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. Are you hurt at all?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'm perfectly fine! I was just a little surprised when the ladder suddenly slipped out from under me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I wonder if this ladder can be put to some use...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've figured out how we will escape this prison, Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh? So, how are we going to bust out?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems that your reckless actions were of use after all.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Are you actually praising me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">More of a "thank you" for giving me an idea regarding this ladder.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The underground ladder? What about it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This ladder isn't just for those who wish to go down...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh! I see! If we use this...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I believe it's long enough to reach the top of those lockers.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, then what are we waiting for!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Alright! Now we can get out of here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... We spent entirely too much time in here. <thought>Kidnappers who held me hostage, and a mysterious Interpol agent... This case is only getting started, and I'll be the one to bring it to a resounding end!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It looks like it's stopped raining for now.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, and thank goodness! You have no idea how hard it was raining earlier!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! I'm so glad to see you managed to escape, sir! I was so stressed that I thought my heart was gonna give out!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe, may I ask what in the world that is?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, that's... um...</line>
<line speaker="MIB">Count off!</line>
<line speaker="MIB">Shifu! All 99 members are here and accounted for, sir!</line>
<line speaker="???">Heh... What the heck do you think you're doing counting my cubs off like that!? Every person is a valuable human being, you get me? And everyone has a name that their parents gave to them. No one is a 2 or a 3... Everyone, regardless of age or rank, is number 1! Got it!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You're Agent Lang, I take it?</line>
<line speaker="MIB">You infidel! How dare you address our Shifu so rudely!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Grr! Lang Zi says: "A cub who disrespects others soon feels the disciplinary bite of an elder." So don't you ever forget to show the proper respect towards another person! Shih-na. This isn't much, but please accept my card.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh, thank you. ...Please, accept mine in return.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You all see that just now!? That is the proper way for two people to show their respect! Keep that in mind and you'll get far in life, got it!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ah, that's right... Franziska did warn me... Something about an elite Interpol Agent from the Republic of Zheng Fa. Apparently, this man has the highest successful arrest rate in the organization.</thought> Agent Lang, why exactly is an Interpol agent involved with this clearly domestic case?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">That's none of your business, Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How is it not!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I've heard a rumor or two about you. You solved a murder that occurred during your flight home recently, right? Hah! But you sure took a while just to arrest one little flight attendant. How pathetic.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-How dare you say that about Mr. Edgeworth!? Are you saying you could've solved it faster, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">The comedic relief jumps to the aide of his master... How cliché. Look, what I'm getting at is that if I had been there, no one would've died.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I would've solved the entire case and Agent Hicks would still be with us here today.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Agent Lang knew yesterday's victim, Agent Hicks...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hicks was like a brother to me, so now, I'm out to take my revenge!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Agent Hicks was investigating a smuggling ring with Franziska and a third person... This must be the man she was talking about.</thought> In that case, you should understand how I feel, as the kidnapped is someone I know. So I ask that you please allow me to participate in the investigation...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">This isn't your neatly trimmed Courtroom of Eden, you know. You're out in the wilderness now, Mr. Prosecutor, and way out of your league. No hard feelings, but why don't you go on back to your courtroom now, pretty boy?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You...! You dare to mock the court!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I do... And I don't need the help of a filthy "prosecutor". Sorry, but the truth doesn't need the likes of you to distort it today!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Who uses the adjective "filthy" to describe a prosecutor...!? And why...? Why do I feel such intense loathing emanating from him!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Alright, men! Good job on the perimeter around Gatewater Land. Now just find me the kidnapper, and bring the punk to me! Dismissed!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Now then, Mr. Prosecutor, you just sit tight here and don't cause any trouble, understand?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">M-Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's been a while since I last met someone so disagreeable.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why of all places did he show up here? And completely out of the blue at that! I suppose I'll have to ask Detective Gumshoe to fill me in on that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Excuse me, but if you could just let me through here...</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Sorry, I can't let anyone through. Agent Lang's orders.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnngh... <thought>I suppose I'll have to deal with this impasse for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I highly doubt I'll find a clue in here, but I might as well check, just to be sure. ...Mnngh. This barrel sure is heavy. You there! Do you know what's inside of this thing?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">It's the emergency water supply for putting out fires.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I see. Well, they certainly are well prepared.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This horizontal bar is used... for tying up horses. Apparently, you can ride real horses at the Cowboy's Ranch area just up ahead. Is it possible that the culprits have already escaped with the help of a stolen horse or two?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Under Agent Lang's orders, we already rounded up all the horses... ...and every last one has been accounted for.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Agent Lang is good, although, I won't go so far as to say I'm impressed just yet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Maaaan... I can't calmly do any stealing at all with that detective around.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose it's not easy when there's this many members of law enforcement in the vicinity.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's alright! It's not like I'm in a hurry to steal just any ol' thing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Which is it? Do you plan to steal something or not? Quite the mystery, this one. Maybe I should talk with her a bit more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">So what are you going to do about your investigation into the kidnapping?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Good question. Since Agent Lang holds the authority to investigate this case now... ...this makes things a bit more complicated.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, come on, you can't let that stop you! I'll even lend you a hand, so let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But you're a self-purported "Great Thief", are you not? I don't believe I can let someone of an unlawful nature participate in an investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You don't like to listen, do you? I'm not just any ordinary Great Thief; I'm the Yatagarasu! And as I said earlier... ...the Yatagarasu is after one and only one thing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is the "one and only one" thing you're after?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The Yatagarasu is only interested in one thing... ...and that is the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... It was seven years ago... There was a vigilante who threw the business world into a panic. Labeled "mysterious" and "phantom-like", the Yatagarasu appeared and vanished at will. Though we still don't know much about this thief's ultimate goal, we do know the targets. The Yatagarasu liked to find and make public, evidence of corrupt dealings of all sorts. Once a target was chosen, no dramatic calling card or announcement was sent forth. Instead, the chosen corporation was infiltrated without even the target noticing. Some days later, the evidence that was found was sent out to the mass media... ...along with a card with the mark of a three-legged raven. Looking back, I suppose you could call what the Yatagarasu was stealing the "truth". <thought>Could this child really be the successor to the Original Yatagarasu? But that can't be... can it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">If I had one of these, I could be a prosecutor, too, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't even think of stealing this from me.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">If it's that important to you, then why don't you wear it on your lapel?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why should I have to label myself as a prosecutor everywhere I go? And why does everyone ask that question of me? That's what I'D like to know.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">I really love theme parks! Too bad we're not here to have a fun time...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So why did you choose this one, and why choose to show yourself to me of all people?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Because I was tailing you, silly! Duh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You were following me!? <thought>But why?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's a book of information about my arch-enemy, the Blue Badger. But I won't lose to the likes of him! You just wait and see. I'm going to write a "Tome of Thievery"! How's that, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...The information that winds up on your wanted poster will suffice in this competition.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Come on! The Badger family is waiting for us to find and take pictures of them! And remember, you have to yell, "Badger GET!" each time, or it doesn't count!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They even have a rule for when you take their pictures...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Tell me about it! I was planning to steal all of my shots, as any proper Great Thief should!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Does the concept of stealing permeate every aspect of this girl's life...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">What do you think about this?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you're going to steal anything, at least keep your hands off of my lines.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Alright, alright. I'll return it to you. Here you go!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I was hoping for some information in return, but my line will do for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Great job, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For losing sight of me and the kidnapper, and allowing my investigation to be hijacked.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I... Sir...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I look forward to your next month's salary assessment.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But... But the case isn't lose yet, sir! I'm gonna show you just how much of a man Dick Gumshoe can be!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Shall I prepare the 21-gun salute now or later?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective, are you sure it was the precinct you called for backup?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">O-Of course, sir! I think I would know the number to my own precinct like back of my hand!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then why did an Interpol agent show up instead, with an army of his own agents?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That, I have no idea... About five minutes after I made the call, that wolf-man showed up out of nowhere, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Agent Lang definitely has an agenda, so the question is, "What is he after?"</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! I was wondering if I may ask about one thing, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um... Who is that? The girl over there, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'm Mr. Edgeworth's assistant, Kay Faraday!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-Whaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Funny, I don't recall making you my assistant, Kay...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah! I'M Mr. Edgeworth's assistant! ME! It's been like that since... forever!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Sorry, but I just stole your supporting role.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">How can you say something so serious with that giant grin on your face, pal!? Mr. Edgeworth! We've got a thief on our hands, sir! She stole my role, sir! I'm taking her in, getting her convicted, and making sure she serves out her sentence!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, come on, it'll be fun! Like musical chairs! You'd better stay fast on your feet!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No way! I won't... I will not lose the spotlight to you, little girl!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If you're going to show me your Prosecutor's Badge, then I'll show you my police badge!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Your wallet is looking rather thin, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? Oh, whoops. I must've left my badge at home. I always get the two mixed up.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's not a laughing matter, Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Gatewater Land... Who would have guessed this place would be such a success. But the Gatewater Group and I go way back, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... Same here. I handled two murder cases that took place at two of their hotels. And it was you who headed the investigation in each case.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, I remember that, sir! I was 16 back then, standing in front of the hotel in the snow...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Clearly, we are not on the same page here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You actually got a copy, Mr. Edgeworth!? Ooh! Can you show me the very last page!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The last page? Very well... Let's see here... ...Interesting. Why is your name listed here under "Special Thanks"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's it, sir! You found it! Oh... Um... That's because I did the choreography for the "Dance, Dance, Blue Badger" song!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I suspect that no one entrusts him with any real responsibilities at work...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, are you participating in the photo rally, too, Mr. Edgeworth!? Um... I mean, I'm only doing it as part of my duties! Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I see. In that case, keep up the good work. So, how many have you found so far?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I've been sorta busy with the investigation, so I haven't really found any yet, but...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Something tells me finding the Badgers isn't really a part of his duties.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm sorry, sir! Absolutely nothing is coming to mind right now! As a man, the only thing I can attest to is this: "To be a man, I, Dick Gumshoe, will tell no lie!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>His heart's in the right place... Now to work on his deduction skills.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's an old-fashioned rocking chair, the kind that makes you feel instantly at ease. There's something written here... "A soothing 10-minute sitting for only $100"...!? I see. Reverse psychology. Make it so expensive that no one would dare sit on it...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's an empty barrel. I'd venture to guess that its only purpose is to set the mood.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a cactus... and there's something written here on this sign... "This cactus is a very gracious gift to Gatewater Land from the local police precinct." <thought>I can't believe the police went so far as to even donate a cactus to this place.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Horses are painted on this garage door to complete the Wild West theme. They almost look like they're ready to jump out into the real world and gallop away. ...Almost, being the key word.</line>
<line speaker="Blue Badger">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That wriggling... I just can't bring myself to call it "dancing"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Some sort of tracks were left in the mud here thanks to the rain. They look like tire tracks. Too bad they're destroying the Wild West atmosphere they worked so hard to create. <thought>The tires on whatever made these probably got pretty muddy, as well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Laaaaaaance! Laaaaaaaaaaaance! Where are you, son!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Amano?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Oh! Miles, my boy! I'm sorry to involve you in such an affair just after you've returned.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For you, Mr. Amano, I gladly offer my assistance. After all, I have you to thank for how well things turned out during my time abroad. If it wasn't for you, I might not have been introduced to that law office... ...and had the chance to study the inner workings of another country's judicial system.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">No, no, no. Think nothing of it. As you know, Manfred and I go way back. I consider a beloved disciple of his to be like one of my own blood.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">If you ever want to go overseas again, you need only to ask. I can use my company's vast network to send you anywhere at any time.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So who's the old man?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He is the father of the currently kidnapped Lance Amano, Ernest Amano.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Now then, have you found Lance yet, Miles? Please... I miss my poor boy dearly!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm terribly sorry, but your son's whereabouts remain unknown, Mr. Amano.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Wh-- Hold on there! Then, what happened to all that money!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........I believe the $1 million has been stolen, and that the culprits are now on the run.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Whaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Poor old man... Don't you have anything you could give him to cheer him up, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Forgive me, Mr. Amano...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was wondering if you could please tell me the details of the kidnapping one more time?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Oh. It was yesterday... A call came to the house. From the receiver came the sound of my son... "Help me, Daddy!"... *sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know this is tough, but please stay with me here, Mr. Amano...</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">You don't understand. He hasn't called me "Daddy" in ages... It was incerdibly moving... I wish I had recorded him saying that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He definitely should have recorded that conversation... ...but not for the foolish sentimentalities of an old man.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Refresh my memory, what kind of person is Lance again?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">How will telling you about Lance help you get him back?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Surprisingly, a lot can be deduced from a person's relationships and behavior.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Very well, then. Lance is my one and only son, and he turned 21 this year. He is very much like me when I was his age -- kind and very attractive. I'm sure women simply can't keep their hands off of him.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is there anything else about him you noticed of late?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Now that you mention it, I haven't been able to get in contact with our butler, Oliver.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your butler...?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Yes, his name is Oilver Deacon. He's been with our family for years now. He gets along so well with Lance, so I thought maybe he would know where my son is...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Amano, could you please tell me a little more about your butler, Mr. Deacon?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">As a butler, he's outstanding. He even serves as Lance's personal private tutor. He took a brief leave recently, but even after it was over, I haven't been able to reach him.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you still haven't spoken with him since his leave? What about his family and friends?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">They said they hadn't seen him. I've tried everything I could think of, Miles. ...Do you think this could have something to do with Lance's kidnapping?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's possible, but I can't say anything for sure quite yet. <thought>So even the person closet to the victim has gone missing... Oliver Deacon... Sounds like one name I had better keep in mind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Ah... Seeing that badge reminds me of Manfred. Now HE was one fine prosecutor, the best of the best.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes, I can't disagree with you there.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Hmm... I sense that you don't really want to talk about them.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How I feel about him... It's hard for me to be truthful about that with another person.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Your hard countenance... I don't know what you're thinking or feeling... ...but mark my words, I think you are Manfred's true successor. I really do.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Ho, ho! That looks to be something with quite a bit of value. But then, all things have some value attached to them. Only by probing deep into the unknown can we become true winners in this world, Miles.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Thanks, but knowledge isn't what's going to make me a winner here; it's information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.................. Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's begin our investigation. Even if that Interpol agent holds the authority to head this investigation... ...we can't allow ourselves to stand idly by, twiddling our thumbs.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm with you 100%, Mr. Edgeworth, sir! I, Dick Gumshoe, pledge to stick by your side through thick and thin!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Amano, it was my fault that the culprits escaped. Which is why, with your blessing, I vow to return Lance to you myself.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Oh! I've never seen you so passionate before, Miles. Good luck to you, my boy.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Alright! Well, what are you waiting for!? Let's do some investigating!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If you think I'm losing to you, pal, forget it!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So what should we examine first!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... Thanks to Agent Lang, we can't leave this area. But the culprits were here until only very recently. Which means we may be able to find some clues that will tell us how they escaped.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OK! Let's get looking!</line>
<line speaker="Detective">Hey! You there!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Who, me!?</line>
<line speaker="Detective">What are you doing goofing off in a place like this!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I wasn't goofing off! I was about to help Mr. Edgeworth kick off his investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Detective">You imbecile! All precinct detectives are now under Agent Lang's direct command!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">N-No way! I am NOT working for Wolf-boy! Mr. Edgeworth! Can't you do something...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.................. I'm not exactly in a position to argue, seeing as how you ARE a member of the police.</line>
<line speaker="Detective">Good, now let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nooooooooooooooooooooooo!!!</line>
<line speaker="Detective">Boy, have I got just the job for someone of your talents!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, that was exciting.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............ Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What? Can't you tell I'm all ready to get down to some detective work!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You should go home. Your parents must be worried about you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, come on! I finally get to be your assistant and you try to ditch me!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I don't recall offering you the position.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmmmph. Why do you have to be so difficult? Besides, it's already too late, you know! Like I said, I've already stolen the position of "assistant" a while back!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hah. You're the only one asserting that.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well! By the time everyone notices, it's already gone! That's the Yatagarasu way!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You shouldn't speak so lightly of things you know nothing about!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Fine. Whatever, you win. Go ahead and do your little investigation. But the talented assistant Kay, is going to tag along to matter what you say!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Even if she turns out to be useless, she's not going to listen to me. I might as well surrender and let her come along for the ride...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A second Blue Badger that shouldn't exist... Clearly, the true identity of the person underneath is...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, I know! It's one of the kidnappers, right!? The person wore a costume to get away <thought>Costumed escape - The identity of the second Blue Badger was probably the kidnapper in disguise.</thought>!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely. After all, the costumes that went missing from the storage area are...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...A Blue Badger, a Proto Badger, and a Bad Badger.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, those three.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So there are three phony Badgers running around in the park somewhere, huh!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, what do you think about the kidnapping?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, I don't know anything about the victim... ...so actually, I was hoping you could tell me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, that's right. I never did explain the situation to you. I got involved because of a phone call I received. It was none other than the director of the Amano Group, Mr. Ernest Amano. His only son, Lance, had been kidnapped, and he wanted me to be the drop-off man. Little did I suspect that I would be abducted myself.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And that's when I found you tied to a pole screaming, "Nnnnnggghhhhoooooooooooh!!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Can you please drop that already!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Looks like there's another thief afoot!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Only if we assume that this is not your handwork.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Are you kidding!? You know that the Blue Badger is enemy number one to me! Can you imagine me ever being on good terms with that thing!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.................. Actually, it's surprisingly easy.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hah! I've got you now, you vile criminals!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'd think the kidnappers would have better sense than to try hiding in these.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, come on! Lighten up, will ya? I was only joking! I don't REALLY think that the criminals would be hiding here, right in front of two officers!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I-I certainly hope not.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! There's a bunch of footprints in the mud over here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I remember hearing rain fall out here while I was being held in there.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yup, it was just a passing rain. That's why the ground has already pretty much dried up.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I should be thankful. It left us with some nice footprint samples.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You know what? I bet if we followed them, we can find out where the kidnappers went! Plus, we'd be able to spot them because of their muddy shoes!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I don't think it will be that easy.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Look carefully. There are quite a few different sets here. And we don't know which ones belong to the kidnappers.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, that's true... We don't know what kind of shoes <thought>What kind of shoes? - If only we knew, we'd be able to track the kidnappers from the footprints.</thought> they were wearing.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, Mr. Edgeworth, isn't this one of those things you tie horses to?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, although the horses are in another location at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aww... And here I was hoping I would get to ride one.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You know how to ride a horse?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Nope! Never rode one in my life! But I have an Asian friend who was born in the year of the horse!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>"Non sequitur" is the only way to describe your logic...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">If these were real, I wonder what you'd put in them.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Water would be the obvious answer...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But if you stored water in a barrel under the blazing hot sun, wouldn't it go bad?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">People of that period probably didn't care about how it tasted.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Sorry, but I can't let you get away with making fun of our forefathers! I mean, maybe they really liked the strange taste!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Look who's making fun of them now.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Just what sort of operation is this, that they would allow their valuables to be stolen!? It's a disgrace to the way businesses are run everywhere!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, thieves, by nature. generally tend to target these types.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Stealing is an abominable behavior, don't you agree, little miss!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Y-Yeah, the worst!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Am I going to have to add "hypocrite" to the list of things you are, missy?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Look! There's a blurb about the cactus here! "This cactus is a very gracious gift to Gatewater Land from the local police precinct."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't believe the police went so far as to even donate a cactus to this place.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">So, is the police department running a cactus farm on the side? Ha ha, just kidding! They wouldn't do something so silly!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Actually, I have the vague impression I've seen a cactus farm at the precinct before.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Horses are painted on this garage door to complete the Wild West theme.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">They look so life-like, don't you think!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you thinking of wrangling, or rather, stealing them?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">If you can coax them out of there, sure! Come on, I know you can sweet-talk them out!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I could be holding a cube of sugar in my hand and they wouldn't budge, Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Blue Badger">..................</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! It's the Blue Badger! Badger GET!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I really don't understand why she is so excited over this badger hunt. Speaking of Badgers, there's a person inside of there...</thought> Mr. Badger, I wonder if you might share with me what you saw?</line>
<line speaker="Blue Badger">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He's doing that contorted wriggling "dance" again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">............ Aha!</line>
<line speaker="???">Aaaah! You've uncovered my undercover identity, sir! I was to remain under that head, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Aren't you Officer Meekins?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">SIR! Mike Meekins, reporting for duty, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This man was a witness in one of the cases I headed two years ago. About the only thing I remember about this officer is that... ...he often spoke and acted before he thought, which gave me a great deal of headaches.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Is he a friend of yours, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've met him in the courtroom once before. <thought>Hmm... Why was he so upset when we unmasked him? Does he have something to hide?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Officer Meekins, why are you standing here wasting time?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">SIR! Because I'm not a police officer right now, sir! I'm the Blue Badger! And I'm creating memories and dreams for the kids! That's never a waste of time, sir! I have a dream to become as big as Detective Gumshoe, sir! I was patrolling the scorchingly boring beat until a little while ago... ...when the dispatch radio on my shoulder crackled that the kidnappers had escaped, sir! I thought maybe this was my shot at making Detective, sir! I rushed on over to join in, but when I got here, there was a sea of people already... ...and I couldn't spread my trademark friendliness and joy on to anyone...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It would seem that some people never change...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So why exactly are you in that ridiculous outfit?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir! That's because, sir! I'm here to keep the visitors in good spirits, sir! But it's also to hide the fact that I'm an officer on the trail of a kidnapper, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. Agent Lang is very wise to employ this sort of diversionary tactics.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">To be handed the role of THE Blue Badger out of all the different disguises, sir... It's... It's such an honor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How long have you been standing here, Officer?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">SIR! For about one little hour, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... That's around the time I woke up from being knocked unconscious...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">And I've been here even since, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If that's true, then it's possible Officer Meekins saw the kidnappers escaping!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">B-B-B-However, sir! I must tell you I didn't see a thiiiiiiing, sir!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I haven't asked you anything yet, Officer.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">No no no no no! B-But I know you will, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He's hiding something from me.</thought> Officer Meekins, I insist that you tell me more about your recent movements!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir! I've been playing the Blue Badger this whole time, sir! And getting into it, too! I patrolled the park, all while wearing this costume! And about one hour ago, I came over here, sir! I haven't seen any suspicious-looking people this whole time, sir! But! I did see a Badger, sir! A lone Blue Badger!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What you said just now is contradictory to the facts.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">How so, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is what Officer Meekins's testimony contradicts!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your testimony contradicts this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I'm just a little patrolman, so I don't understand what you're talking about, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I can't say I get it, either.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Gnnnrk! This isn't what I was looking for!</thought> I'm sorry, Officer, but you could you please repeat what you said once more time?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Of course, sir! I'd be honored to repeat myself as many times as needed, sir! For almost a whole little hour, I didn't see any suspicious-looking people around, sir! But! I did see a Badger, sir! A lone Blue Badger!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As I thought, what you said just now is contradictory to the facts.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK, so what exactly is so contradictory, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Officer Meekins, let's back things up. I'd like to ask you about your last statement.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir! Of course, sir! If that's your wish, Mr. Prosecutor! This little patrolman will wait as long as I am commanded to wait!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You said that you saw a Blue Badger, correct? And yet, if you take a look at this, what you saw was not supposed to happen. This park is supposed to have only one of each Badger in it at any given time. Which means that as long as you are the Blue Badger, Officer Meekins... ...you should not have seen another Blue Badger wandering the premises!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Wh-Whaaaaaaaaaat!? SIIIIIIIIIIIIIIR!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Then, that would mean that there are two Blue Badgers <thought>A 2nd Blue Badger - There's only supposed to be 1 Blue Badger in the park, but a second was spotted.</thought> walking around!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How long have you been standing here, Officer?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">SIR! For about one little hour, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... That's around the time I woke up from being knocked unconscious...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">And I've been here even since, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If that's true, then it's possible Officer Meekins saw the kidnappers escaping!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yup, I've been hanging around in this area ever since then, sir! But! I did see a Badger, sir! A lone Blue Badger!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And yet, if you take a look at this, what you saw was not supposed to happen. This park is supposed to have only one of each Badger in it at any given time. Which means that as long as you are the Blue Badger, Officer Meekins... ...you should not have seen another Blue Badger wandering the premises!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Wh-Whaaaaaaaaaat!? SIIIIIIIIIIIIIIR!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But then, that would mean that there are two Blue Badgers walking around the park!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir! It's so incredibly shiny, but it has a really ugly shape! I knew it! I was right to go for the much more manly police badge, sir! But I lost it alot, and I just know I'm going to lose it for real one of these days, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Mr. Edgeworth, I think this cop is one donut short of a baker's dozen.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know. Believe me, I know.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir! You have a copy of the Blue Badger Bible, too, sir!? That was written by experts on the Badger family, sir! And it's very, very thorough! It doesn't matter that I was made the Blue Badger only a little while ago, sir! That book helped me memorize every name of every Badger, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's not that hard to remember four incredibly obvious names...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Drip, drop, little by little our privacy is being sold off to the public through this, sir! But that means I need to work extra hard on my cute poses!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ooh, like what?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Like thiiiiiiiiiiis!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Great! Now I know what your new pose will beeeeeeeeeee! Look, sir! I've successfully stolen his pose and speaking styyyyyyyyyyyyyle, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*sigh* That's nice, Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir! I'm undercover as the Blue Badger now, sir! I must pretend to not know anything about anything, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I mustn't respond to that. It would be like shooting fish in a barrel...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a set of tire tracks originating from the garage.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aha! So that means a car left from the garage at some time, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correct. But for the car to leave these tracks... ...it would mean that it left during the passing rain. <thought>That's the only explanation as to why these tracks are made of mud.</thought> Hmm, three treads... I think we can also safely it's a special type of car.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now that we know that the kidnappers were wearing Badger costumes... ...those footprints from earlier take on new, and very significant meaning.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, you mean now we know which tracks belong to the kidnappers, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. More than shoe prints, we need to follow the paw prints of Badgers.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK, Mr. Edgeworth! It's time to use those footprints and go Badger hunting!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmm... So we're looking for footprints made by a costume... Hey! I think I found them! There are two sets here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They both do look like possible candidates.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">This set is walking off to the west... Argh! It just stops! I can't make heads or tails of where it's headed from here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think we can assume it's headed towards the stadium...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmm... I wonder where the other set leads? This one seems to be headed east... Huh? Quick, Mr. Edgeworth! I've got him! I got one of the culprits!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Aaaah! Nooooo! I'm not a kidnapper, sir!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Down, Kay. Clearly, those footprints belong to Officer Meekins. But our criminals were each wearing a costume.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aha! Maybe they came over to this garage for something?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's what I would suppose. Officer Meekins, if you could step aside for a moment. We need to examine the garage.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">SIR! Roger Wilco, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It appears that this case has taken a turn for the unexpected.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'll say! I was shocked to open that shutter and find a dead body inside!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose most people would be, since the average person rarely runs across a corpse.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wait! You just compared me to a "normal person", didn't you!? I'll have you know that I'm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry. I suppose I should recognized that you're a... thief, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">No! I'm a GREAT Thief! And a GREAT Thief is not surprised by anything! Got it!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Apparently, with GREAT thievery comes GREAT loss of short-term memory.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">This horse is really pretty...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't even think about it.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK, I'll just hold onto it then! Don't worry, it's safe with me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Just so we're clear, Kay, a five-finger discount is not part of the bargain.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There are two sets of prints that could be from the kidnappers...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">One set is headed off to the west...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To the stadium, I would suppose...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And the other set heads to the east...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We should follow these prints to their conclusion and investigate the garage.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ooh, did you know? I really love this kind of chair, the way it rocks back and forth! When I grow old, I plan to sit in one of these and rock the day away every day! But you don't have to wait, Mr. Edgeworth! You're at just the right age for one!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Do I really project myself as someone of that age?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Amano... This body...</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Yes... That's my butler, Oliver... How could something like this have happened!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Indeed. And why was Mr. Deacon here to begin with?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">And the other set heads to the east...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We should follow these prints to their conclusion and investigate the garage.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What a peculiar car...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah. From the look of it, it must be the Blue Badgermobile. And it has three tires... So maybe it left those tire tracks behind!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*sigh* That's simply not possible.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Take a look at the tires. There's no mud stuck to them. Therefore, it must have been here since before it started to rain.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, gotcha! Good bye!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's a shame I don't see any other clues around...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's open this shutter and see what we find.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Maybe we'll find the kidnappers hiding inside!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What in the--!? <thought>We seem to have stumbled across a dead body...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She must be in severe shock to have been the first to find it... Now then, who is this man?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ernest">I-It's Oliver!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! Mr. Amano, are you saying that this man is...</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Yes... He's my butler... How could something like this have happened!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Indeed. And why was Mr. Deacon here to begin with? I'd better investigate this crime scene quickly, before Agent Lang or his men return. The kidnapper's footprints lead right to this garage... ...and right to a dead body. Is it possible one of the kidnappers is now a murder victim (Victim was kidnapper? - Following a kidnapper's prints lead us to a body. Was the victim in a costume?</thought>...?) From my cursory examination, I believe this man died of a fatal bullet wound.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You sure are calm for someone who just found a body.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's surprising what one can become accustomed to in the span of two days...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This is an unusually-shaped pendant...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">What is it? Is it something valuable?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She seems to have regained some of her composure...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">It looks like a horse pendant! It's got an antique feel about it, and it's really pretty... Hold on... This is made of platinum silver! Nice! It IS worth something after all! Ooh! and look! There's something written on the back. "Colin Devorae"... It's a name.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Colin Devorae"...? <thought>But this man's name is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>As long as that Interpol agent has control of this case... ...I'm not going to be able to have real autopsy done on the victim. I'm no doctor, but let's see what I can piece together myself.</thought> Hmm, there are two gunshot wounds one in his abdomen and one in his shoulder.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So that means he was shot twice...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, I don't think so. I think the abdominal one is an entry wound, and the one near his shoulder is the exit wound.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Nice! I knew you could figure out!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It comes with experience, and I've seen my share of crime scenes. <thought>Speaking of experience... ...this crime scene seems a bit too clean for a murder where the bullet went clean through. I should make a note of this oddity.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this spot somehow connected to any of the evidence I hold...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's something not right about the name on the pendant. The victim is the Amano family butler, and his name is "Oliver Deacon". But the name on the pendant is "Colin Devorae".</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I wonder what's up with that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't know, but... ...I think we've hit upon an important piece of information.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence alone solves this whole case!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Really!? You think so!? Because to be honest, I don't really see how it solves anything... You must be confused jumping from a kidnapping to a murder. Yeah, that's it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh! I can't believe I made such a large blunder... ...that even this little girl could point it out!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the victim's pendant, which is shaped like a horse.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's got a real dignified look on its face. That makes it worth all the more...&#160;! Oh no, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What? Did you find an important piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">This... is made of platinum silver! That makes this thing super-valuable! I've seen this type of jewelry at a lot of stores before, so I know it when I see it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............Kay, if you ever laid so much as a finger on those pieces of jewelry...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wh-What? Me? I-I'd never do something like that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>......Is it possible that she has never wanted to steal from a jewelry store before?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The name "Colin Devorae" is engraved here.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I really admire people who carve their own names into a pendant.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? And why would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You have no imagination, Mr. Edgeworth. Did you ever think that maybe people want to have their loved ones always nearby?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's not as if I have a wedding band, and I have no interest in accessorizing.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">*sigh* I suppose. Anyway, you know what? More than wearing flashy accessories... ...I'd rather be engraving my name into every treasure I can find all around the world!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A sign of affection is one thing, but blant vandalizing is just a bit different.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Laaaaaance! Laaaaaaaaaance! Where are you, sweetie!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Excuse me, but you are...?</line>
<line speaker="???">*ba-dump*</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">?</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, this is bad... He's really good looking! Ack! Stop it, Lauren! You can't let yourself fall for a playboy like him! You're in love with...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Sounds like someone doesn't know the meaning of the phrase "inner monologue", huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry to interrupt your... conversation, but might you be friend of Lance?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Yes, I'm Lance's girlfriend... My name is Lauren Paups.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">His girlfriend...?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Oh, it's not like that! We're more like friends... and, um... We're not lovers or anything! We! Well, we haven't gotten that far yet! But... I guess that's how people are going to see it, so I should just accept it... I even got this ring as a present from Lance... *swoon*</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ha ha, you know what she reminds of? A cartoon character!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N...Nnnnrrrghn... May I inquire as to why you are here?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">I haven't been able to get in contact with Lance lately... ...and I began to get really worried. *sob* I looked everywhere for him, and then I heard about the kidnapping, so I came here.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow, you're really strong for having made it through all this by yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Um! Is it true!? Has Lance really been kidnapped!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...No one is supposed to know, but yes, it's true.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Oh, Lance...! I can't believe you've been spirited away... I wonder how you're doing right now...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Looks like she's gonna back to the "fair maiden in love" routine... So, Mr. Edgeworth, where do we go from here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, we found a body, so we should look into the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">My men brought me up to speed over the radio. And I have to say, you really should've called. I heard you found something very intriguing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have nothing to hide, Agent Lang. It's exactly what you see before you.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I'll take it from here. Yeah, that guy's really dead. Hey! You waiting for an invitation? Hurry up and detain the suspect, now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Suspect? Who...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Officer Meekins, is it? You're coming with us.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">What!? SIR! I had nothing to do with it, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang! Don't you think you're being a bit rash!? Do you even have a good reason to suspect Officer Meekins!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah, I leave that kind of stuff to you prosecutors. It's your job, after all. Like I said earlier, the crime scene isn't as forgiving as your precious courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's your answer!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I know you like your logic and reasoning... ...but that sort of impractical fluff is not needed out here in the field.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">All you have to do is arrest suspicious person after suspicious person. That's how you eliminate crime from the streets!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But that's also precisely how you unnecessarily arrest innocent people by mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">"Innocent people"? Nonsense! There's no such thing as an innocent person. We've all got a blemish or two in our hearts.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's tyranny! I won't allow such a thing to go on unchecked before my eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Heh! Too bad you don't call the shots around here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As I have sworn to uphold the laws of this land, I cannot allow you to take this man in. That you would arrest a man on false charges without even conducting an investigation... ...have you no honor as a member of law enforcement!?</line>
<line speaker="MIB">You! How dare you speak so disrespectfully to our Shifu!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> .................. Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! You amuse me, Mr. Prosecutor. Lang Zi says: "Every pack has its own rules." If you can play by their rules and come out on top, that is a true victory. Alright, I'll give your beloved laws a fair shake. I'll show you just how much investigating I've done... ...through my line of logic!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I've seen a lot of bodies like the one being carted off in my time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That is your reasoning...?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Solid as a rock! It's based on the philosophy of detainment!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Um... What's this "philosophy of detainment"?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah! You don't know!? In that case, pay attention, girlie. In my country, the criminals have a saying: "Beware of the wolf."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why the wolf...?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Because in my language, "lang" means "wolf", and you don't mess with me or my pack. And as for the detainment philosophy, its father is my honorable ancestor, Lang Zi.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... You'd think I'd have heard of him and his teachings if he is that famous...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Lang Zi developed it as he worked to lock criminals away thousands of years ago. To this day, the Zheng Fa police still trains its recruits using his philosophies.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But "thousands of years ago"? That makes your story about as believable as a fairy tale!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Anything wears down and breaks over time. Do you really something as ancient as that can be applied to today's world?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">......You want to put it to a test?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I've seen a lot of bodies like the one being carted off in my time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So what can you tell me about the body?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">A lot. Even without an autopsy, I have my eyes. They teach you the basics of forensics along with the detention philosophy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? Then you wouldn't mind telling me a little of what you've figured out, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I can say he was shot in a single glance, but even you figured that much out, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I think anyone who saw the bullet wounds would come to the same conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Heh, don't pat yourself on the back yet!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Lang Zi says: "Search where the water is deepest." You have to keep your eyes on the big fish that lurks in the depths, which is the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is that right? And what would you know about the killer?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">With your current gun laws, it's not exactly easy to get your hands on a gun.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would appear you've studied a little of our laws.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Studied? Who needs to study what every child on any street corner already knows? It's that... that......... Shih-na!</line>
<line speaker="Shih-na">The "Federal Firearms Restriction Act".</line>
<line speaker="Lang">That's it. The Federal Firearms Restriction Act. I hear it's not easy to get a gun these days.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Interesting. That woman is the one in charge of keeping track of the information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not unless you're a member of law enforcement like Officer Meekins, isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that's the case, there are plenty of other officers who might be potential suspects. You're not seriously going to arrest each and every one of them, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">As if I would need to! I've already looked into everyone else here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Other than Officer Meekins. I know no one else's weapon has been fired.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! H-How did you check every single person's weapon in such a short span of time!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">That's because each and every one of my subordinates is extremely capable. It didn't take more than a few minutes to conduct the entire investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The power of sheer numbers...</thought> But you have yet to check Officer Meekins's weapon, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Thanks for reminding me. Hey, you! Show me your gun.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">..................Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What's wrong...? Why does he look so sicky pale all of a sudden?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">............Gun!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What did you say? I can't hear you. Stop mumbling and spit it out already!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir, sir... I LOST MY GUN, SIIIIIIIIIIR!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How could you be so irresponsible!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha ha ha ha ha ha! In the end, it looks like you're still the only suspect we've got. You're the one who waited here outside this garage to ambush and kill the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So you think that Officer Meekins waited here to kill the victim, do you, Lang? I think this little accusation deserves a lot more scrutiny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"Officer Meekins ambushed the victim in this garage and killed him here with his gun!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you are implying that the murder weapon in this case is a policeman's service revolver?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I don't know for sure just yet, but it's entirely possible. After all, Officer Meekins did just admit that he "lost his gun". Ha ha ha ha! You'd think he could come up with a better lie than that!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Officer Meekins ambushed the victim in this garage and killed him here with his gun!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You mean to tell me that the murder occurred here, in this garage?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">From the fact that the suspect was found almost next to where the body was found... ...I'd say that it's pretty obvious that this is the crime scene. Lang Zi says: "A criminal always returns to the scene of the crime."</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! Finally, a quote even I've heard of before!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Furthermore, Lang Zi says: "Successful investigations are the result of multiple returns to a crime scene."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Looks like neither detectives nor criminals have changed their ways over the millenniums.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So this is the kind of conclusion the philosophy of detainment can lead you to...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">I don't get it, Mr. Edgeworth. Why are you putting yourself on the line for Mr. Meekins?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's not that I particularly care about what happens to Officer Meekins.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Whaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, I can't simply stand by while Agent Lang ignores our country's laws. <thought>Shi-Long Lang... Just what sort of investigator are you?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unfortunately for you, Agent Lang, that is simply not possible.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You've seen the crime scene for yourself. And while you were looking, did you not think to yourself that it was a little to clean?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Aiya!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you did notice that there was too little blood. Do you still wish to claim that Officer Meekins committed the murder here? Because this isn't the crime scene. And if it was your men who led you to think it was... ...then I suggest you leave this case to the local police to set the record straight!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Grr! Ha ha ha ha ha ha! Not bad. I see your logic can be just as sound as mine. In that case, let me ask you this: Don't you think it's weird that officer was hanging out around here in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Weird? How so?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey, you! Your squad's not even supposed to be in this area, right? What were you doinㅎ neglecting your duties and loafing around here?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I-I...!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Don't you dare give me some lame excuse like, "I found myself taking a walk."</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">But sir... I really did take a walk, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You're a disgrace. How dare you take your pack obligations so lightly?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Officer Meekins is looking extra meek. Is he hiding something...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Mr. Edgeworth! Please! Sir! Save me the way you did earlier, please, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Officer Meekins. Please give is a detailed account of what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">SIR! Not you, too!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">It's true, sir! I wasn't assigned to this area, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is this "Blue Badgermobile"?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">It's a moving store on wheels that sells sweet dreams and merchandise, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So the Blue Badgermobile is just a roaming souvenir shop?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">SIR! I swear I was chasing the kidnappers down while I was being a good dream merchant!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He seems rather worked up... Even more than his usual hyperactive self.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">He sure seems sure of what he's saying.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Can you try to calm down and lower your voice to a more reasonable level, Officer?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">SIR! Roger, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">It's true, sir! I wasn't assigned to this area, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Alright then, where were you assigned to?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I-I was assigned to the main gate, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He must mean the area with the bridge and the outrageous fountain.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK, then why are you here in the Wild, Wild West area?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">That's because! It's because of a very deep reason, ma'am!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I was told to check every square inch of the main gate area, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Describe for me how you conducted your investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir! Well! First, I made sure there were no suspicious-looking people in the area, sir! But! The only people that seemed to gather around me... ...were little girls, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, what did you expect when you're dressed like the Blue Badger?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I thought I had no choice at that point, sir, so...</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I also went looking for the kidnappers while selling dreams in the Blue Badgermobile, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What exactly do you mean by "selling dreams"?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">SIR! The Blue Badgermobile is where dreams are collected!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Um, what?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sweetness like you've never known except in dreams, ma'am, like "Innocence Drops". And bitterness found only in nightmares, ma'am, like "Guilty Jawbreakers". Selling those as I pushed the Blue Badgermobile along is my sworn duty, ma'am!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">But! I got completely caught up in my role, selling dreams to the children! SIR!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You completely forgot to look for the kidnappers?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">NO, SIR! OF COURSE NOT, SIR! I! I would never do something like that, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">..................Umm... You're absolutely riiiiiiiight!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow, you're good at this forcing-people-to-confess thing, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">To be frank, I'm just a little man, sir... I'm better at selling kids a few small dreams than looking for a big crook, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Enough wallowing in your own self-pity. Let's return to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Before I knew it, I found myself in this area, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How did you wind up all the way over here?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I was in the middle of a sea of kids, sir... But one of the kids decided to challenge me to a fight, sir! I had to run away from the child's painful dropkicks, and before I knew it...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ha ha, the good ol' dropkick! I dished out my fair share of those when I was a kid! It was always the best when you felt one really connect with your opponent!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In any case, you wound up here for a reason completely unrelated to the investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">SIR! That's right, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That's not something you should be admitting to with your head held high, Officer.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It sounds like he simply forgot about his real job and became the Blue Badger... However, there is one flaw in Officer Meekins's story. But I have the feeling that he'll need some prodding before he'll spill the beans.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Officer Meekins, I would appreciate it if you didn't tell such transparent lies.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">SIR!? I'm lying, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, you are. If you were really out there selling dreams with the Blue Badgermobile until recently... ...then what is it doing here inside the garage?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Aaaaaaah! A-Actually, I had just lost track, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Lost track of what?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">By the time I realized it, the Blue Badgermobile was nowhere to be found, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Which would mean it was perhaps... stolen?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">And that's when I came back to this area, thinking maybe it was in the garage, sir! But that's when you found me, Mr. Edgeworth! Sir!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">A likely story! Who do you think is going to buy such a convenient tale as that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what exactly is so convenient about his story?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">The car getting stolen; it's completely unbelievable, even for a cover story! But I think we can assume the car was used alright. To move the dead body!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Wh-Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You killed the victim at some distant location, Officer Meekins. And then you used the Blue Badgermobile to transport it all the way here.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Now then, you're coming with me.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">But it wasn't meeeee! SIR! THE KILLER, SIR! It wasn't meeeeee, sir!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang! Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hm? What do you want now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We still don't know where the real scene of the crime is. You can't say we know all the facts of this case, let alone the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I told you! Truth, schmuth, I couldn't care less!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Our job is to catch the crook. You'll find out your precious truth after we arrest this guy and take him in. That's the job of you prosecutors in your fancy courts with your "logic". As for us, we don't have that kind of time to waste.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You boorish buffoon!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I think you need to leave.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">We need to get the body to autopsy, and you guys are getting in the way.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You...! You would interfere with another one of my investigations!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey now, let's not forget who holds the actual authority to conduct investigations here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I'm afraid the one doing the interrupting is you, my ignorant little pretty boy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnn...Ngwooooooh!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Now be a good fancy boy and get out of my sight. If you don't... ...I'll arrest you for obstruction of justice.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnngh... Chased out like a pair of peasants.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes, Kay?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">There's something even thieves should never steal. Do you know what that is?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You really shouldn't steal anything, however, I'll bite. What shouldn't a thief steal?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">A life. It's too heavy of a burden on your soul to get away with, ever.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's something we can agree on. Well said, Kay. No matter what we may try, murder is the one crime that can never truly be hidden. And I intend to prove that by my own hands... ...when I apprehend the murderer myself.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Alright. And I'm going to work extra hard to be a good assistant! Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I still never said she could be my assistant... *sigh* 'm just going to drop the issue.</thought> The first thing we should do is locate the real scene of murder.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! The stadium! Hurry, sir! This is supposed to be hush-hush, but they found witness at the stadium!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A witness!?</line>
<line speaker="Detective">You! What did we tell about leaving your assigned post!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aaah! The jig is up! Mr. Edgeworth! Remember that I'm always rooting for you, so go get 'em, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Those detectives sure look loke they're enjoying themselves.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's not all fun and games, Kay. Now then, let's head to the stadium and meet this witness.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I thought there was a witness here...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, I don't see anyone...</line>
<line speaker="???">Mr. Edgeworth! Long time no see!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You are... Ms. Ema Skye, correct? <thought>This girl is the younger sister of my former superior, Lana Skye. Two years ago, we stood in the same courtroom together as witness and prosecutor. But I thought she had gone to Europe to study forensics...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I can't believe you remember me, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course I do. How have you been? You look to be in good spirits. Are you still studying abroad?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You bet! More than anything, I want to investigate crime scenes, scientifically! I've been studying non-stop every day to become a top-notch forensic scientist! But it's spring break now, so I thought I'd come back for a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You look deep in thought. Care to share, Kay?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">With all that's happened, I'm getting a little confused. Umm... For example, what that detective said earlier...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">About how we must look for the witness at the stadium...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">No, not that. The "I'm always rooting for you" bit. I was thinking how sweet that is! It's like you two are best friends!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think you're a little confused alright, Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Where are you going, Mr. Edgeworth!? We have to find the witness before that mean ol' werewolf does!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're right. The witness is supposed to be here in this stadium, but where?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I assume this is another Badgermobile?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, but it's a different color than the Blue Badger's car.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, this is the retina-searing pink model.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I almost didn't recognize you. You've really grown in these past few years.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Please don't tease me, Mr. Edgeworth! I know I still have a long way to go. But I'm going to be a super forensic scientist someday! You'll see!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You seem to know Mr. Edgeworth really well. Are you two acquaintances?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh! I forgot to introduce myself! I'm Ema Skye. Nice to meet you! I'm studying abroad now to be a forensic scientist! How about you?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow, that's a great dream! My name's Kay Faraday! And I'm training to become an unstoppable Great Thief!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A-A Great Thief...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Don't think too hard on it, Ema. It's not worth the trouble. In any case, we have much to catch up on.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You bet we do!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, why are you here, Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, I just happened to decide to come back home for spring break... ...and then I heard that you'd come back, too, so I raced on over here! I had really wanted to welcome you back at the airport, but I had just missed you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And how exactly did you know I was here?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Through the power of science, naturally! Never underestimate what science can do for you! I used these to track your footprints, and I followed them straight to you! This set is the greatest! It's so wonderfully scientific! You spray this chemical on the ground, and when you shine the special light on it... ...Zing! The footprints light up like an electrified noble gas in a glass tube! It's almost like magic, scientifically speaking!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Forensic science has never seemed more ominous to me than at this very moment.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ema, I'd like to ask you about what you witnessed...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you not the witness Detective Gumshoe told us about?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, I did get a call from Detective Gumshoe earlier. He was practically yelling at me! "Mr. Edgeworth needs your scientific doohickeys right now, pal!" he said.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What was that man thinking? ...Or rather, not thinking?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So let me guess, there's been a murder, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... Unfortunately. <thought>There's a sudden glint in her eyes... But I need to keep my mind focused on the witness. Now, where did that person go?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">This is the symbol of a prosecutor, right? But I don't think I've ever seen you wear it, though.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, I'm not as enthusiastic about wearing it as you are with your pin badges.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I know, right!? I mean, I really wanted to put even a few more on today! Oh, hey! I like yours, Kay! Do you have any estras?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Sorry, but there's only one of these in the world, and it's proof that I am a Great Thief!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Now, if I calculate this out scientifically using my time scheduler... Aha! I can definitely see all of the attractions before the park closes!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Science sure is useful, huh, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'm not even going to bother asking Ema how she calculated that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Seeing the Blue Badger sure brings back memories...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I remember it like it was yesterday! That was really something, huh -- the red-hot courtroom battle between the two of us!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I don't think it was quite as dramatic as that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Scientifically calculating and think critically about this... ...then putting it in a way that transmits the feeling that I understand... Whew! Done!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">She makes it sound like she knows what she's talking about, but she really has no idea.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Admittedly, I am slightly confused by what she just rattled off...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I assume this is another Badgermobile?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, but it's a different color than the Blue Badger's car.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, this is the retina-searing pink model. <thought>Hm? What's that off in the distance...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, hey! It's the Pink Badger! Badger GET!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Badger, badger, badger, badger... Just what does she see in these silly things?</thought> ..................</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I think this Badger has something to say to you, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you, by chance, the witness I've been searching for? <thought>Sorry, but I don't speak Badger Dance.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pink Badger">..................</line>
<line speaker="???">Aaaargh! I can't take bring inside that stuffy head anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-You're--!!! <thought>Nooooo! Why HER!? Why HERE!? Why NOW!? I first met this woman three years ago. She was a witness in one fo my cases. She has since gone out of her way to pop up unexpectedly, and cause me great thief--</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Edgey-pooooooooooo! Why couldn't you understand what I was trying to tell you!? I mean, really! I was trying so hard to keep the kids' dream alive by staying in character! But you couldn't pick up on what I was trying to convey to you! I'm sick and tired of that roundabout way of talking, so I'm going to just be direct!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I had a bad feeling before, but this just made it official. Today has gone beyond the typical "not my day" into the realm of "waking nightmare"!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">So you're a friend of Mr. Edgeworth, too, Ms. Pink Badger?</line>
<line speaker="???">You could say that. But right now, I'm just the Pink Badger, dearie.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She may look the part, but I know better than to trust my eyes around this woman...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">My name is Wendy Oldbag. But you can call me "Wendy", or "Granny", or whatever suits your fancy.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Nice to meet you, Ms. Oldbag! I'm Kay Faraday.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hmph! What do I care about young whippersnapper like you!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeesh, I was just trying to be polite...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Weren't you a security guard at one of the Gatewater hotels the last time we met?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hmph! I go where I'm needed! I'm very good at what I do, unlike the youth of today! I get called in all the time to fill in when there aren't enough hands. But enough about me, Edgey-poo! I'm thoroughly dejected right now! I finally get the chance to see you again, and here you are, talking with two young girls! Men are all the same! It doesn't matter how old they get, they continue to shamelessly flirt with young girls! Why, just the other day, it happened with my Yun, who I had finally gotten to notice me. He went and got into an arranged marriage with a 16-year-old! I don't see what he sees in her at all! As they say, the permission takes three years to ripen! That girl</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You seem to attract all sorts of interesting people, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, please, I'm begging you. By all means, do not provoke her any further...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">It's like a line-up of ugly thugs.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You cut to the quick.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Only behind the scenes. I'm the Pink Badger right now to the kids. But don't you think I'd even more lovable if I kept this head piece off?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Think of the children! You're the one who wants to keep their sweet dreams alive, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Yet another Blue Badger? I've had my fill of these things for a lifetime!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thank you for the extra commentary, but all I wanted was for you to take a look...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, alright. I guess I can do that... But only because it's you, Edgey-poo! .................. What is wrong with this thing!? Why is this Blue badger wearing sunglasses!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...How could she have not noticed all this time?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Thanks to this, people have been taking my picture all day. It's like I'm one of the mascot characters of this park.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's not "like"; you ARE the mascot character. Well, one of them, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">But you have no idea how hard it is to be one. You're not allowed to talk at all! Taking away my ability to talk halves my effectiveness as a human being!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You have a hard time not talking? But it seems like such an easy thing to do!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What do you know, young'un!? Just wait until you're my age and then we'll see!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is it possible this loud, old lady was once a quiet, fair maiden? ...Hah, impossible.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Go on, Edgey-poo! Show me anything, and I'll tell you all about it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very well. What do you think about this?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">...It's nothing special.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Somehow, I figured she'd say as much.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aren't you forgetting about something, Mr. Edgeworth? This person could be the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Honestly, I hope she isn't, but I don't think fate is going to be so kind today...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I saw what happened! I even saw the exact moment it happened! How's that!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So it's true! She is the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>*sigh* I don't suppose I can afford to ignore the old bag...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Yes, it was just a little while ago! I saw it happen right in front of me! The moment of the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You mean to say that you witnessed someone being killed right before your eyes?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Sounds like a pretty important piece of testimony to me!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I came to this stadium to take a short break.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Looks like we hit the jackpot, huh, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I can't afford to ignore what she has to say. ...Unfortunately.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What's that "unfortunately" you tacked on at the end supposed to mean, Edgey-poo!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, anyway! Let's see what we can find out from this little ol' lady!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I came to this stadium to take a short break.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You mean you took a break from being the Pink Badger?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">You may not think it, but it's hard work keeping kids' dream alive. You smell of sweet, your hip creaks with pain -- you even begin to dream about work.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's the kind of story that would scar a child for life, you know...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, that's why I chose to come take my break here, whippersnapper! I don't plan on playing the part of the Dead Badger in front of a bunch of kids!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So what did you see while you, the Pink Badger, were resting?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, yes, that! Well!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">As I was resting, I happened to glance over and I saw two men facing each other in that area.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You saw two men...? Can you describe them for me?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">They looked like your average Joes, completely uninteresting and not worth fawning over. I'm telling you, they were so boring that I don't even remember much beyond that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But did they have any special features? Anything you can recall would be very helpful.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, my! Don't tell me you're jealous of those two men!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, she's right. You do seem pretty worked-up over them, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I'm not worked up over anyone! A-And not jealous!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">It's alright, Edgey-poo. Those two were just foals compared to a stallion like you. I thought so little of them that I lost interest the instant I laid eyes on them.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Suddenly, there was a loud gunshot, and the person who was shot fell to the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're claiming to have seen the exact moment in which the murder took place?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Absolutely! That gun made a terrible racket when it was fired.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You didn't try to go help the person that got shot?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I'm only one person, you smart-alecky brat! What could I have done!? But I took off as soon as I could to find someone who could help.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">It was a very terrifying experience, let me tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">.................. Well, don't you have anything to say to me!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, not especially.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">You're so cold, Edgey-poo. But... that is exactly what I like about you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You sure are one tough cookie! One part unshakable, and one part scary...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Watch that smart mouth of yours, missy! What do you know about my fragile heart!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can tell this is an important piece of testimony, but she's rather vague in a few spots. *sigh* I suppose this means I'm going to have to talk with her some more...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Two men, one bullet... It's all consistent with that we found out from the body.</thought> Sadly, there wasn't exactly a lot of new information to go on in your testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, if I saw the guy again, I'm sure I could identify him for you! I mean, how do you expect me to remember anything without something to jog my memory!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Self-centered, aren't we?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">While it was somewhat useful, her testimony also presents us with a new problem...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So, about this new problem...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is that giant grin on your face for?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Do you want me to show you something really nice?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...No, thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Don't be so mean! I swear it's something you're going to like!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is that gadget you're holding?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What you see before you is the secret weapon of a Great Thief!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Ahh, I should have known it would be worthless.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aww, don't be like that! Tee hee. *ahem!* What do you think now!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is it doing...? It's projecting something into the air...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'm going to input the necessary information to run the simulation now. Once I'm done, I'll increase the size of the projection to its maximum size... Dark skies of evening, when no other bird dares take wing, one alone remains all-seeing! Now, witness the true power of a real, modern-day Robin Hood!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What is this!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">This is a re-creation of the murder based on the info I inputted into Little Thief!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">L-Little Thief? I dare say I think you're taking Robin Hood a bit too far...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Little Thief is actually meant to be a simulator for me to plan my thefts. But I suppose if I used it like this... Let's see... Ms. Oldbag said that the two men were facing each other. And then, a gunshot rang out, and the victim fell to the ground...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah... So with this, we can inspect the crime scene as it was in the past.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">See! So, what do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have to say, I'm impressed by the technology thieves have access to these days.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, it IS the super-secret weapon of the mighty Yatagarasu!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, but if there isn't enough information, or if something is out of place... ...the re-creation could come out a little strange.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In other words, I can use this to authenticate the validity of a witness's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You got it! You really catch on quick, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Right now, this simulation is a re-creation of that witness's testimony... So for now, I should re-examine everything... ...and if I find anything illogical or strange, I can then ask for clarification.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Feel free to examine anything in this simulation in the way you always do! You even present evidence when you find a contradiction! And if you find something, I've got Little Thief with me, so you just let me know, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, you believe that this gadger will provide us with the proof we need?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, of course! Pretty neat, huh? By inputting info like this, it can re-create the crime scene exactly as it was. Although, Little Thief was originally intended to be a training sim for heists...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A training sim for thievery!? I don't believe I can turn a deaf ear to that, Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Bah, it's for practice! Practice! It's not like I've actually stolen anything yet! Besides, we're in the middle of an investigation! So stop nit-picking!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even if it is just "practice", I can't exactly endorse the act of stealing. Although, admittedly, this device is rather useful in an investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, how am I supposed to use this to aid my investigation...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh! That's right! I guess I should explain how to use it, huh? Objects outlined in yellow are things that are not present in our time, but were in the past. Things outlined in a dotted line are things that exist now, but didn't in the past.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You can examine and interact with replicated people and objects as you normally do. You can even present evidence whenever you find an inconsistency. Oh, and be sure to point out mistakes in the re-creation with evidence, too!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... Very well, let's continue with the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">If there's something you don't get about Little Thief, feel free to ask anytime, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This is amazing! Just FEEL the power of science!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What is this? Some sort of new attraction?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's the silhouette of the killer with his gun at the ready.</thought> Kay, is it not possible to re-create the face of the killer?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, I can't exactly input what we don't know into Little Thief.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She has a point...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It looks like they broke the stage down <thought>Stage was packed up - The stage I saw this morning in the center of this stadium has been packed away.</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I guess this means they're done for the day...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Or maybe it's because a different show is scheduled to start its run tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">According to the testimony, the victim fell to the ground here...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's right. But...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But, if that's the case, then we've already found our first contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh? What? Where!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If this is the real scene of the crime, there's something missing that should be here. Which piece of evidence shows the missing item?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Kay">.................. Maybe you're still adjusting to the simulation...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Y-Yes, that's it. Allow me to find my bearings, and I'll present the contradiction again. <thought>Maybe I need to review the evidence again. It should go without saying that the truth lies in what is missing from this scene!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eh? Is something wrong with my re-creation?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If this is the real scene of the crime, something specific should be here. If you think back, how did we deduce that the other crime scene was not the real one?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh! I get what's missing now! There's no blood on the ground here either, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Right. The fact that there is no blood here casts doubt on the witness's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Edgey-poooooooo! How can you doubt me like that!? Are you calling me a liar!? I know what I saw! And I saw the victim get shot down!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You know, I don't think she's lying, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>To be honest, I can't think of a reason why she would lie to me. In that case, maybe there is another explanation for the distinct lack of blood (Why is there no blood? - Why is there no blood around the victim's prone body?</thought>.)</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Now I'm fairly convinced that the victim was killed here. But then why is there no blood? There must be some explanation for this contradiction! Perhaps I should go over all of the information I've gathered one more time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is it not possible that the victim was wearing a costume?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So you really think that Mr. Deacon was one of the kidnappers?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think we can reasonably assume there is a very good chance that he was. And that if he was shot while he was inside one of those stolen costumes...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Then Mr. Deacon's blood would be inside the costume instead of on the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely. Now, if only we could prove that the victim was wearing a costume...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You'd think it'd be pretty easy if we could find some footprints... ...but the problem is FINDING them, since there doesn't seem to be any around.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Footprints, huh...? I wonder how we can go about finding some of those...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">This is amazing! Just FEEL the power of science!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ema, about that method you were talking about for finding footprints...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah, finally my expert knowledge in forensics is needed!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, well... Can you detect and trace even partial footprints?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Leave it to me! My cutting-edge detection kit can find anything!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very well. If you could please analyse the footprints in this area...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">OK! Stand back now, and witness the power of science at work!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey! I found something! Look, right here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">? I don't see anything...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, that's right! Here, put these special glasses on, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! These footprints here were definitely left by a Badger costume!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Judging by the way the prints are layered, those seems to be the newest.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Then... we can conclude that the victim was definitely wearing a costume at the time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK! In that case, I'll update Little Thief's simulation parameters! I can't wait to see what we find out from this new info!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So the victim was wearing a costume when he died.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And with that, we should be one step closet to the truth, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... I see the re-creation has changed in accordance with the new information.</thought> We may be closer, but now, something else has caught my attention.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What do you want?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your testimony, naturally. I'd like to hear it one more time, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I came to this stadium to take a short break.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So! Does this mean that Ms. Oldbag's testimony has a contradiction in it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and I believe our best course of action is to compare it with your re-creation.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">See! I just KNEW Little Thief would be of help! Now let's see if we can pull more info from Ms. Oldbag to put into the re-creation!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For that, we must first find the contradiction in her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I came to this stadium to take a short break.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You mean you took a break from being the Pink Badger?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">You may not think it, but it's hard work keeping kids' dream alive. You smell of sweet, your hip creaks with pain -- you even begin to dream about work.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's the kind of story that would scar a child for life, you know...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, that's why I chose to come take my break here, whippersnapper! I don't plan on playing the part of the Dead Badger in front of a bunch of kids!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So what did you see while you, the Pink Badger, were resting?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, yes, that! Well!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">As I was resting, I happened to glance over and I saw two men facing each other in that area.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You saw two men...? Can you describe them for me?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">They looked like your average Joes, completely uninteresting and not worth fawning over. I'm telling you, they were so boring that I don't even remember much beyond that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But did they have any special features? Anything you can recall would be very helpful.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, my! Don't tell me you're jealous of those two men!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, she's right. You do seem pretty worked-up over them, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I'm not worked up over anyone! A-And not jealous!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">It's alright, Edgey-poo. Those two were just foals compared to a stallion like you. I thought so little of them that I lost interest the instant I laid eyes on them.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Suddenly, there was a loud gunshot, and the person who was shot fell to the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're claiming to have seen the exact moment in which the murder took place?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Absolutely! That gun made a terrible racket when it was fired.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You didn't try to go help the person that got shot?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I'm only one person, you smart-alecky brat! What could I have done!? But I took off as soon as I could to find someone who could help.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">It was a very terrifying experience, let me tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">.................. Well, don't you have anything to say to me!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, not especially.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">You're so cold, Edgey-poo. But... that is exactly what I like about you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You sure are one tough cookie! One part unshakable, and one part scary...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Watch that smart mouth of yours, missy! What do you know about my fragile heart!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Knowing what we know now, thanks to your re-creation...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...The contradiction stands out like a giant sore thumb!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely. It's all becoming clear to me. Let's clear up this issue with some well-presented evidence, and get this over with.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Two men? How did you know the gender of the two people involved... ...seeing as how the victim was wearing a costume at the time!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Furthermore, I have another matter I'd like to inquire about! I'd very much like to know... ...why you failed to mention the costume in your testimony!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Uwah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm beginning to doubt if you really witnessed the murder at all.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">But I'm telling you, I really did see it! I saw it with my very own eyes! ...From a seat in the second tier.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The second tier...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, didn't you say you saw it "right in front of you" earlier?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That was... you know... I was using the phrase in the metaphorical sense...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>*sigh* I see our witness still has a screw loose, in the metaphorical sense.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">The cushy seats in the second tier are reserved for hot-shot VIPs. Which is exactly why I go there now and again to take a nap!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I can't see how you could've gotten a good look from there. It's so high up!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Were you able to see even the victim's costume from way up there?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, I know I saw two people. But I couldn't really see what they looked like because they were in the stage's shadow <thought>In the shadow of the stage - It was hard to make out the killer and victim that Oldbag saw in the stage's window.</thought>. My sight isn't what it used to be, you know. Not like when I was young. Ah, people used to call me "Eagle-Eyed Wendy" back then! could spot a good man from 100 paces away as I walked down the street, just like that! Of course, they also noticed me in a flash and tried to make their move. But I'm not that easy! I was a careful girl with a judgmental eye! Bu</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*sigh* Let's return to our investigation, shall we, Kay?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You got it!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This is amazing! Just FEEL the power of science!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thanks to you, I'm able to proceed with my investigation once again. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah, it was nothing! i'm just glad that science and I could be of service!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Pretty amazing how we could see the footprints. So what's the secret behind that thing?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, you want to know? Um... here, you can read the manual!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aha... Very interesting... So if I do this, I can avoid leaving footprints...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She can't seriously be trying to use the information to her advantage as a thief... Wait...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This new silhouette of the victim is in a costume.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">This silhouette can change depending on the information I input. But Little Thief can re-create mroe than just people... So investigate away! We may even find more info with which to make a more accurate sim!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Alright. Sounds like a plan.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, there's a mic up there! What kind of ninja is the Jammin' Ninja? He's no slouch, no way, you batcha!♪ You're the best, Jammin' Ninja! Everyone's always trying to thank ya!♪ How was that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How was what?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You know what would be really awesome? If we put a band together! I can see it now! A Great Thief and a Prosecutor, stealing the hearts of millions around the world!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The only instruments I can play are the flute and the piano...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You can play the flute while playing the piano!? That's really fresh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How many hands to you think I have!? Besides, I haven't even agreed to anything yet!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that woman's testimony is to be believed... ...the murder occurred before the stage was broken down.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Do you want me to input that bit of info into Little Thief?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Battle of the Magicians: Max Galactica versus Troupe Gramarye"... And tomorrow, there will be a concert by the "hip" new rock band, the Gavinners. Not that either of these stage shows interest me in the least.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is clearly...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...A contradiction here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please stop stealing my lines!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, come on. It wasn't that hard to see it coming, even for a layman like me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose. In any case, it's not possible for the killer to have stood here in that way... ...because there was a very real stage set up in this spot at that time.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeesh, I told you I got it! Do you feel the need to explain everything!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, well... In any case, we still need to resolve this unusual situation.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Isn't it obvious? The killer was on top of the stage, naturally. Right, Ms. Oldbag!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Yes! I remember now! The killer was standing on top of the stage!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">See! Now let me update the info in the simulation.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Well, well, what have we here? A bunch of hooligans running amok, I see!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang, how nice of you to join us.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Well, I can't have you going around messing up my crime scenes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang, we've discovered that the real scene of the murder is here, the stadium.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I see. Thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For what?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I'm just trying to show you my appreciation for all the time you saved me. Who knew that such a strange little toy could re-create a crime scene like that.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Little Thief is NOT a toy!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">...You two!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">And there you have it. You see? Big boys like me don't need silly toys, little girl.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">*sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Now THIS is a re-creation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So what? Do you still intend to assert that Officer Meekins is the killer?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Of course. Even knowing that the crime took place here doesn't let him off the hook.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">This is the real scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How far will you go to accuse Officer Meekins of the crime...?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">He's the most likely suspect we've got, especially given the situation with his gun.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, even if he is the killer, at least my re-creation was on the mark.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You see? Thank you for understanding, my little crow-girl.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Grr... I'm not some common crow! I'm the Yatagarasu! The raven of legend!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unfortunately, your conclusion has yet to be tested, so let's see how well it holds up.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">This is the real scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Looks like we found the real crime scene first.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha! Brag all you want, but we don't have all that free time, unlike the two of you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Heh heh. You know what you remind me of? A dog licking his wounds as he whimpers home!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Well, I guess I should be thankful for all the time you saved me. Xie xie. That's how we say "thanks" in my country.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-You're welcome. <thought>I hope he realizes we didn't do all of this for him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">But I'm here now, so I'll be taking over! As I was saying, this is where the crime took place.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Officer Meekins lay in wait for the victim on top of the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Lying in wait? How did Officer Meekins even know the victim was going to come here?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Simple. He was investigating the kidnappers, right? And while he was doing so, he came to understand the victim, Mr. Deacon's movements.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hah! And why would the good officer want to ambush and kill a kidnapper?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You mean his motive? Who knows, and who cares. You can find that out for yourself when you talk to him in jail.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. You have no respect for the order of law.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Don't got me wrong, but I need more than "There's no motive!" to convince me otherwise.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He's right. The lack of a motive is rather weak argument by itself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">So, the officer lay in wait on top of the stage...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">And when the victim finally showed, he shot him from on high!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you agree with how our re-creation turned out...?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Like I said, I'm grateful that you were able to save me some time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Alright, but we still don't know why he chose to wait on top of the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Who cares. Maybe he wanted to become the Blue Badger. Who's to say he didn't see the stage and decided to put on a Badger stage show of his own?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Or maybe there's a completely different reason...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">What does it matter!? It still doesn't change the fact that Officer Meekins... ...stood up on that stage and shot the victim on the ground below.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Lang">That's the truth your little re-creation showed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you honestly believe that what you're saying is what really occurred?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey, you're the ones who came up with this scenario. Are you saying you doubt yourselves?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnngh... Touché...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unfortunately, Agent Lang's conclusions do not contradict with our re-creation.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmm... Then, does that mean it all went down just as he says?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, not quite. <thought>I wonder if what we had re-created earlier was the whole-truth?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm terribly sorry, Agent Lang.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I should have you warned you that our re-creation is incomplete. You cut in quite unexpectedly, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You said that the victim was shot by the killer from up above, correct? I hate to break it to you, but that's not possible.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh? Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Recall Mr. Deacon's body, specifically, where the gunshot wounds were located.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">.................. Actually, I didn't get that good of a look.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh. Well then. The bullet entered Mr. Deacon in his abdominal region, and exited his right shoulder. This is more consistent with an angled shot from beneath the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Kngh!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Then...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, our re-creation had the victim being shot at an angle from above.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">A clear contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You're discounting your own conclusions!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, this one point is the only flaw. This was the mistaken parameter in our re-creation:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's right. The location of the stage was wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You mean the stage was in a totally different spot than where it is now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, the stage was situated where the victim was standing in our simulation.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah! Are you out of your mind, Mr. Prosecutor!? I've never heard of a stage show where the stage actually blocks the audience's view!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I suppose not... But I swear I know the reason for the error!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The location of witness was our mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Edgey-poo! How can you betray me like this!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your testimony was riddled with vague statements.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey, now. I can't let you get away with bad-mouthing a very valuable witness! Besides, if you're saying that it was wrong for you to think she saw it from far away... ...then, perhaps she saw it from up close? That'd make her story even more trustworthy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I didn't mean it that way...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Edgey-poo! You can do it! Hang in there!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So the wrong parameter was not where the witness was... In that case...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, the locations of the killer and the victim were wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ah, I get it. I see what you're trying to say!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe the killer and the victim were standing opposite to what we initially thought. It was the victim who was on top of the stage as he as being shot by the killer!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If this is what happened, it'd also explain the positioning of the gunshot wounds.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But then, what about the footprints?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Since footprints don't lie, we can assume then, that the killer also wore a costume.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK! I'll try using that data instead!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Judging by the fact that both the killer and the victim were wearing costumes... ...I'd say it was a killing between the two kidnappers. That would be the most natural conclusion. Wouldn't you agree, Agent Lang?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hmph. Well done, Mr. Prosecutor! But that alone doesn't clear Officer Meekins of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I ask that you take another good look at the tire marks over there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You believe he moved the body with the car?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">That's right. It was Officer Meekins himself who pointed us to the way he did it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The three-tired tread marks are very telling, however... ...is the Blue Badgermobile the only thing capable of creating such a pattern?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">I ask that you take another good look at the tire marks over there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The tire marks...?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Yes, the tire marks. The one there behind the stage. They were hidden up until now by the various pieces of stage equipment. As for when they were made...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...They must have been made after the rain had begun to fall, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Yes, and probably around the same time as when the killer's footprints were made. The tires on that Blue Badgermobile probably got pretty muddy because of that. I say it's the Blue Badgermobile because, well, that's pretty obvious, too.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">The three marks are indicative of the Blue Badgermobile.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Three tire marks... I have to agree that the Blue Badgermobile has three tires.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Of course! The only thing in this park that could make those marks is that roving shop.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you forgetting that there are, in fact, three of them? You can't simply ignore the Pink and the Proto Badgermobiles, Agent Lang.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Of course. I didn't say it couldn't be either of the other two... ...but I see no reason to drag them into this just to complicate things!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Lang">That story Officer Meekins told about that shop on wheels getting stolen was just a lie.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course, you have some sort of proof that it was all a lie, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Of course not.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, that was blunt.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">But, suppose it is a lie. It would explain a lot of things. Like his movements and his whereabouts.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">He drove the Blue Badgermobile here and committed the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you still claim that the tire marks belonged to the Blue Badgermobile?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">It must have arrived on the scene after the ground had become wet with rain. Officer Meekins committed the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Then, he used the car to move the body to the garage in the Wild, Wild West Area.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Besides the Blue Badgermobile, there are other ways the body could've been moved.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Recall what the Wild, Wild West Area looked like. Only the Blue Badgermobile and Mr. Deacon's body were in the garage. I'd say that's proof.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I suppose if one were to look at that place, that would be the only logical conclusion. However, my experience tells me that the truth is usually not so easily found. Is there some sort of problem with Agent Lang's statement with regard to that scene?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Looks like the only thing that car was selling was death, not dreams.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Only if what Agent Lang believes turn out to be true. <thought>The three-tired tread marks are very telling, however... ...is the Blue Badgermobile the only thing capable of creating such a pattern?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry, Agent Lang, but that's an impossible tale.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">And why is that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Those tire marks could not have been left by Officer Meekins's Blue Badgermobile! One look at the car would've told you so! What proves that the Blue Badgermobile had never been to this stadium?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The reason I believe this car never came to the stadium is the car itself!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Pink Badgermobile was here from the beginning. And there is no need for two Badgermobiles to be at any one location at the same time.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You sure like to give random answers to things, don't you? But I'm not so easily sidetracked by such weak logic!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arrnnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Now then, tell me why you believe that car was never at this stadium!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The victim's body tells the true tale behind it all!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What's wrong with you, Mr. Prosecutor? We're talking about the Blue Badgermobile! What does the body have to do with anything? Unless it's hiding some sort of secret...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Well, I believe we should investigate this next is all...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah! Looks like you're no match for my wits after all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait, please allow me to take another good look.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is where we should be focusing our attention!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I have no idea what I'm supposed to be looking at. Perhaps you're a bit worn down by all this excitement, Mr. Prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's none of your business. Just allow me to explain it once again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Take a good look at the tires. There's not a single dollop of mud to be found on it.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Nngh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If this car had come to the backstage area and left those tire tracks... ...then the lack of mud on these tires stands out as very peculiar indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Then, how do you explain the tire tracks, genius?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! I've got it! What about Ms. Oldbag's Pink Badgermobile!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Don't be ridiculous! I was sleeping the entire time in the second tier seats!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed, I believe we can rule her out as someone related to the crime. However, there is yet one more roving store, as I recall.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh! You mean the Proto Badger!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's right. There was one more parking space inside that garage. And it proves the existence of a Proto Badgermobile.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Agent Lang, I suggest you find this Proto Badgermobile posthaste. There must still be some sort of incriminating evidence in it.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Nngh.........</line>
<line speaker="???">H.........</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, did you hear something?</line>
<line speaker="???">H.........Hel...... ...Help... me...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Are you alright!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Well, this is something! Looks like we've found our kidnapping victim. Where were you all this time?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Wild West... With kidnappers...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He was in the room next to the one I was held in!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lance">Ran away using underground... and get lost... Th-The kidnappers...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hm? What is it!? I can't understand what you're trying to say!</line>
<line speaker="Lance">Th-The kidnappers... escaped... wearing costumes...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Did you see the faces of your kidnappers!?</line>
<line speaker="Lance">No... I didn't see their faces... but... two... One was a w-woman...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A woman...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Quite an important piece of testimony. Hey, what are you guys doing!? Stop standing there and get your cops on this already. I'll even let you guys have what the kid said just now. Consider it a gift. Now, are you going to get out of my crime scene, or am I going to have to get rough?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Akgn... <thought>Again...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">You're nothing but a big bully! Come on, Mr. Edgeworth! Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Oh, no, no, no. Not you. You're a very important witness for my case. I'm not about to let you get away that easily.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Don't count on me to testify, because I won't. Not for you!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That's right! I won't either! You hear me, you young whippersnapper!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey, calm down. There's no need for all this hostility. I just want to take a statement from each of you. I'm not going to rough either of you up. I give you my word. Come now, fair maidens. What do you say? Will you cooperate?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">"Fair maidens"...? My, you little rascal! You sure know the way into a woman's heart.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Lang Zi says: "The passage of time is but a fleeting moment," and a lady is young forever.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">..Hmph! Trying to outdo my Edgey-poo with your fancy-schmancy sayings. Let's get this over with. So we're clear, I'm only interested in giving you my statement.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Sure, just as soon as Mr. Prosecutor leaves us be.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Edgeworth...!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Looks like we got the boot again...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">With Lance safe, the focus of the investigation will shift solely onto the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You mean the in-fighting between the kidnappers?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and also the identity of the remaining kidnapper...</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Miles, my boy! Tell me it's true! Tell me that you've really found my boy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, Mr. Amano. We found him earlier in the stadium.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Then... my little Lance is unhurt!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He's not exactly the picture of perfect health, but his life is not in danger. He's being questioned right now by Agent Lang.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Poor Lance.. It must've been so horrible for him... Locked up like a... *sob*</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Mr. Edgeworth, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">G-Good work, officer...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, Mr. Edgeworth! I thought you wanted to talk with Mr. Amano and Ms. Paups?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I do... Perhaps I should start with them before I do anything else.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So this must be the Blue Badgemobile that Officer Meekins was driving...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He said it was stolen, didn't he...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't tell me that you were the one who stole it.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What the heck are you talking about!? I don't even have a license! It's illegal to drive a car without a license! A Great Thief doesn't break the law!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This little girl has a very odd understanding of the word "law".</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This man looks suspiciously like the precinct...</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Look at that lovely smile on the Blue Badger's face!</line>
<line speaker="Daughter">Aaaah! It's looking at me! Make it stooooooooooop! It's scaaaaaaaaryyyyyy!</line>
<line speaker="Chief">It's alright, dear. You want to know something? I was the one who created the Blue Badger! See, look at his eyes. Don't they look just like daddy's?</line>
<line speaker="Daughter">It's scaryyyyyyyy! It's scary because they do look like yooooooours, daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Chief">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, that was rather depressing. I think I'd better leave the two of them alone.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Why is there a Blue Badger here, too!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you deathly allergic to him or something?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Um... It's not that. It's more the half-smile on his face; it's really unsettling.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She's disturbed by the half-smile? I'm more disturbed by its movements and how it managed to obstruct an investigation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To think they were but a hotel, now they have their own safari park attraction. Talk about a veritable goulash of rides and attractions.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">With so many of them, you'd think they would have a ninja house! Like one of those buildings with a zillion secret places to hide in! Those are fun!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, they don't.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! How can you be so sure!? Oh, I know! I bet they really do have one, but it's hidden in real ninja fashion! Come on out, ninja house! I know you're around here somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A hidden ninja house... Next she'll be looking for a lost pirate ship!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">That lamp looks like it's got a lot of good stories to tell about the olden days!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? It looks like incredibly new to me.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Argh! Mr. Edgeworth, you need to lighten up and get a sense of humor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That was rather rude! But just this once, I'll look the other way.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...On second thought, maybe the first thing you need to work on is tact.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They say that couples who cross this bridge together will find happiness. Or so the Gatewater Land pamphlet says.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But you'd think that they'd already be happy because they were able to come together.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Logistics aside, I wonder who came up with this tale and when? This bridge doesn't look old enough to be the stuff of legends.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, some things are better left uninvestigated, don't you think? Ignorance is bliss!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is it, Kay? You look like you've stumbled upon something.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'm kind of confused by all of the different events going on. First, there's the kidnapping, and then the co-conspirators of that end up in a murder. And Ms. Oldbag saw the crucial moment, but you and Ms. Oldbag are kinda...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We do NOT need to investigate further into that last statement! <thought>Disregarding the fact of who it came from, the witness's testimony was a mess. However, it did shed some light on the truth behind this case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, let's keep investigating and see what other types of people we run into, shall we!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I guess it's a love letter...? It reads kind of bitter-sweet.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that was all, I'd say it was nothing more than someone pining for Lance. However, the sender is the loan company "Tender Lender".</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Aaaaand the story takes a super-bitter downturn.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Miles, my boy, I can't think you enough.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">I'm still in shock over what happened to Oliver... ...but I have to say I'm relieved that Lance is alright. Oh, that's right! I mustn't forget to pass this on to Lance as soon as the police are finished with him.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A letter?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Ah, the way Lance is being chased after by woman reminds me of someone I know. I almost can't believe he received yet another love letter, you know. Here! Take a look for yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Isn't this a breach of confidentiality?</thought> It's a very simple love letter.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh? Hey, let me see! Hm? That's really weird. It's from a loan company, "Tender Lender". Looks more like a collection bill to me.</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Oliver... *sigh* He served me well for such a long time. What am I going to do without him...? I'm afraid my money will continue to be dampened by my tears in the long nights ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This was found on the body of your butler...</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Oliver...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But what strikes me as odd is the name engraved on the back, "Colin Devorae"...</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Oh...Coden Livorea? ...Veldor Dalein...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He's so sad that he's got it all mixed up in his mind.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I understand, but that last one wasn't even close.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">He loves me, he loves me not. He loves me, He loves me not... Aww, that's the 12th one! No, you can't give up, Lauren! Just one more try!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Excuse me, but I can't help but feel a bit sorry for all the flowers you've gone through...</line>
<line speaker="Paups">I suppose... If they were me, then... *blush*</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe you said that you are Lance's girlfriend when we first met, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Yes, I am, but... Oh! It's not like we both think of each other as lovers! But he DID give me this ring, so I guess we're not just "friends" either...? I mean, because! This isn't just any ordinary ring! It tastes so sweet when you lick it! Ah! It's so wonderful!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>You mean to tell me that he gave you a lollypop ring...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">So which is it!? Have you guys not decided if you're going out, or is it just one-sided?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Decided"...? Shouldn't the parties involved naturally just know...?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">My father used to work for Mr. Amano. And so, Lance and I grew up together. ...*gasp!* I said it out loud!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I don't see how that's anything to be embarrassed about...</thought> So your father was an employee of the Amano Group? What did he do?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">I heard his job was to fly around the world... ...on Pegasus...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">P-Pegasus!?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Oh, Pegasus was the name of the airplane. The airplane belonged to the company.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Y-You had me there for a second...!</line>
<line speaker="Paups">But now... It's all changed. My father... He isn't around anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Paups">About 10 years ago, he rode in Pegasus off to somewhere, and never returned.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Riding Pegasus to whereabouts unknown... Sounds like the stuff legends are made off.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Paups">It's been so long... I don't think I'd recognize him if we were to ever meet again...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'm so sorry, Lauren...</line>
<line speaker="Paups">But I won't give in to the sadness! I have to live! Yes, Lauren! Live!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">About this incident...</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Incident? But isn't the kidnapping already over and dealt with? I've been here the whole time, so I'm afraid I don't know much about any other incident.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How did you come to know that Lance had been kidnapped?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Oh! Ummm... That's because... of my woman's intuition!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You based everything on that?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">I know everything when it comes to my Lance! It's really strange! It really must be destiny...! *blush*</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Argh. She's started fantasizing again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you know what this is? It's a Prosecutor's Badge. I'm not a bad person, and I'm not out to seduce you. Come now, won't you talk...</line>
<line speaker="Paups">No! You're showing that to me to lord over me with how much authority you have. Well, I will not bullied! You should be ashamed of yourself, you evil man!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...How should I repent in order for this woman talk to me!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Paups">This right here is Lance's and my "Castle of Love"! It's the perfect new house for us made out of candies and sweets... But I can't seem to get the door open... Why?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Because this is a theme park, and I highly doubt they would let you live here for real.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">You won't let me in my own house...? You truly are a terrible man, you know that!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-- But I have nothing to do with that!</line>
<line speaker="Paups">...Aaaah! It's a monster! A hideous monster!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know that it may look like a monster, however, I'd like to ask you about it...</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Oh, Lance up in heaven, lend your little Lolli your strength!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But he's not dead.</line>
<line speaker="Paups">If you lend me your strength, I can defeat the bad monster and live a long and happy life!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'm beginning to suspect that you are not very good at this listening business.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">About what we found when we examined the victim...</line>
<line speaker="Paups">AaaaAAaaaaAAAAAaaAaAAah!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh--!?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">You big bully! I can't believe you'd show me something so gruesome! But, but, I have to admit I kind of like that mavericky aura around him... Oh, Lauren... Are you becoming "bad" as well...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She's off in La-La Land again, I see...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If I show this to her, she'll probably just go on about another one of her fantasies.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">If you're not going to show it to her, then why not give it to me for safe-keeping?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why would I do anything of the sort!?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">?</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Lance and I met on a street corner by the crosswalk... I was so busy eating a loaf of bread that I ran right into him! It was destiny, as people like to say...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'll take that as she's not interested in this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">So what are you going to do now, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We already established that there's a good chance that the killer is the other kidnapper. It's my duty to figure out who this other person is. I believe there is one location that might hold a clue or two.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The place where we were held as prisoners!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hoooold it! Don't lump me in with you! I can't allow you to slander my good name as a Great Thief by saying I was "captured"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Not being able to escape from somewhere qualifies you as a caged bird, Kay.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Besides, we checked that place out pretty well while we were there, remember!? Don't you think it'd be an even better idea to check somewhere else?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps you're right. <thought>What I really need right now are leads to the killer's identity...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's often the case that some clues are overlooked at the crime scene itself. Which means we should give the stadium another sweep.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's pretty good! Very "professional prosecutor"-like of you! And of course we'd go investigate if we hadn't just been tossed from there!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...True, and Agent Lang is still conducting his investigation there.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, now get it together, will you, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Alright, then. To do our part, we should leave them alone and investigate somewhere else.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The obvious location is the kidnappers' hideout.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But we're still not allowed in, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang and his men should be done with this area. In that case, there is no harm in asking that officer over there to let us in.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The next place to investigate...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">... Is the kidnappers' hideout, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Yes. And their hideout is ...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">... That room next to the one we were stuck in!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Kay! I would appreciate it if you didn't steal the words from my mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ha ha! But I can't help it, you know! I'm a Great Thief, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So the best that the "Great" Thief can do is petty theft of other people's words, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you have to report?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Sir! Nothing unusual or out of the ordinary, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>? Where have I heard such redundancy before...?</thought> Hmm... is it possible for you to let us take a look around inside?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Sir! Roger, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That was surprisingly hassle-free.</thought> Are you certain? Didn't Agent Lang order you not to allow me in?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Sir! That's true, sir, but... ...Detective Gumshoe asked me personally to let you in, sir! And I couldn't refuse a request from him!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow, looks like Detective Gumshoe has a following!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Furthermore! I was asked to give this document to you, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is this? The man in this picture... Isn't this Mr. Oliver Deacon?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But the name here says "Colin Devorae"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's the same name as the one on the back of the pendant.</thought> It appears that "Colin Devorae" was his real name... What's this? He was convicted in a case 10 years ago and sent to prison.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What!? Then what was he doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Apparently, he broke out of jail... and then just vanished. He must have become "Oliver Deacon" to cover up the fact that he was an escaped felon.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Now I'm not sure what's going on anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is there sort of link between the victim's past and this current case? These police documents are rather detailed. I should take the time to give them a thorough read eventually.</thought> It's fine. Let's focus on one thing at a time, starting with the kidnapper's hideout.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, I agree! We should investigate first, think later!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">More than thinking things through, I think you should try remembering things first. Now then, if you could please unlock the door, officer.</line>
<line speaker="Officer">It was locked up until a little while ago, but... ...since then, the door's been wide open, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm not sure I follow what it is you're saying. Care to explain in a bit more detail?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Sir! The door was locked down tight when they went to check out the room... ...so they got about ten officers to help out and break the door down, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. <thought>I guess that means I get Agent Lang's left-overs. Well, let's see what we find.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So ths is where the kidnappers planned their foul deed...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">While you were tied up for a while in the room next door, hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, please. Must you bring that up again? Now then, down to business. There might still be some clues left in this room. Let's try to find out what we can of the other kidnapper's identity.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This common denominator between the cups and folding chairs... ...is the number three. Speaking of which... ...the number of missing costumes is also three.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wait. But I thought there were only two kidnappers...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. Something isn't adding up... Literally. Is it possible there is a third kidnapper that Lance didn't see?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a bit strange that the police had to force their way into an unlocked room. One look at the pristine door lock, and anyone can see that it was not in use at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But the policeman outside said that it took 10 men to get it open!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... A door that was locked tight, despite it being not locked at all... It can only because of this.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh! You mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, it was used to jam the door. Here, take a look at the door handle. Do you see how the handle is completely destroyed?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So that's how the sword broke!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So this is the room next to the one we were held prisoners in...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You know, I took a peek in here through the door from the other room.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As did I, Kay. Anyway, if this room was truly the kidnappers' hideout...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Then that means there should be some clues to their identities here, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't know if there are, however, the probability is quite high. I believe a through combing of this room is necessary.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">In a way, you can think of it as he stole and hid himself away.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This man was a fugitive. I imagine that was the only way he could live on the outside.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, people who do bad things don't deserve to be respected. The best way to live life is to follow the straight and narrow!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>How ironic that I'm getting a lecture on morals from a thief...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">This reminds me of a saying, "Till one's sword breaks and one's arrows run out."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Except that we are not dealing with any arrows.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I guess not. I wonder where they went? Oh, I know! I bet it's because I already stole them!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I sincerely hope that she is kidding...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This door is thoroughly broken thanks to the police who forced it open.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The panel that hid the entrance to the underground is propped up and wide open. Be careful of where you step, Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I only fell into that other opening once, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Looks like a sword. A broken sword.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Strange. Why would it be broken <thought>Broken prop sword - Found lying next to the door. Broken cleanly in half.</thought> like that? Swords don't usually break on their own.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's true.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Alright then, let's think about it in this way: Maybe it broke when someone was trying to use it for or on something.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hypotheticals aren't going to get us anywhere. Perhaps we should think more on this later.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That doorknob handle-thingy is looking pretty beat up.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose that's what happens when ten officers break their way in with brute force.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, that's odd... The lock on this is completely fine. Look, not a single dent!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But how is that possible after what that officer told us?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah! If the lock had been in use when the door was busted down... ...then the lock itself should be completely wrecked!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, the lock on the door leading to the outside <thought>The door leading outside - The door had to be forced open, yet the lock is intact. Was it not locked?</thought> is undamaged... How can that be?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, there's a trapdoor in this room, too!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's not a trapdoor; it's an entrance to an underground passage, Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I know that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The door leading to the outside world was locked... ...so Lance must have escaped his prison through here.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ooh, they have barrels like these just outside.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, I know I already asked you when we were out there, but... ...if these were real, what would you put in them?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's an expectant gleam in her eyes that I'm about to dash...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unused folding chairs lean against the wall in their folded state.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow, whoever lined these up did it perfectly! They're not even a single hair off! I'd feel bad using these because it'd be like stealing the perfection away!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I suspect it's more like you wouldn't want to be the one to put them away.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This must be where they dispose of old and worn-out costumes.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's so sad...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would seem that they trow the costumes away in pieces <thought>Costume pieces - In the hideout, there is a trash bin for old and useless costumes.</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Watch out, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a broken mirror... It probably came from the haunted house. <thought>Why is this there? Are they planning to repair it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A sign advertising the photo rally, something I have absolutely no interest in.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, but I do! And I'm going to get my hands on the rest of the Badger family! You'll see!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She definitely brings a decidedly different atmosphere to a criminal investigation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Folding chairs, and by the looks of it, they were probably used by the kidnappers.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmm... There are three chairs <thought>Folding chairs - Three of them were set up. It's very likely that the kidnappers sat in these.</thought> set around the table.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A poster of Gatewater Land is stuck on this wall. "Intrigue! Fun! Prestige! Gatewater Land has it all, and it's waiting for you!" ...It's not especially catchy, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? I wonder what this key is to...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmm... You got me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It reminds me of the key we found in the other room.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's it! This must be the key for one of those trapdoors!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That wasn't a trapdoor. You only call it one because you quite literally jumped into it.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, but isn't that what you're supposed to do when you see one?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I am not having this conversation with you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Cheap, styrofoam cups.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmm... Looks like only three cups <thought>3 cups - They were on top of the table. The coffee looks like it was poured today.</thought> was used.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Beyond this door...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Is where the kidnappers held you after getting the jump on you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Must you keep reminding me?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But it's the room where I got to see your awesome "Nnnghhhoooh!!" face!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You didn't need to remind me of that mortifying moment either...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I thought that we might uncover the true identity of the kidnappers... ...but instead, we've only uncovered more questions that need to be answered.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Proto B.">Well, well! Mr. Edgeworth, am I correct?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What are you doing, suddenly popping out of the secret entrance like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Proto B.">This is an underground passage used by staff members, sir. We Badgers also make use of it in our duties.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Look, why don't you get out of there first, and then we'll talk, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Proto B.">Ah, I beg your pardon, miss.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Proto Badger GET! Alright! Only one more to go!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What are you getting all excited about?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">*gasp!* Did you forget!? The photo rally, duh! See, look! Now, all I have to do is get a picture of the Bad Badger and I'm done!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ah, yes. I vaguely recall a contest or something of that sort...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Proto B.">Wh-What--!? It's gone! But where did it go!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm? What happened?</thought> What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Proto B.">A Bad Badger costume is missing, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, is that all! Well, it's missing because the kidnappers stole it.</line>
<line speaker="Proto B.">I heard about how they were stolen... ...but they said that only three of the costumes had been taken.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What? <thought>Is he saying that more than three of them are gone?</thought> Mr. Proto Badger, please tell me a little more about these costumes you use.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, are you participating in that Blue Badger Photo Rally?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah. I figure since I came all this way, I might as well. Plus, I want the prize.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prize?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's a handcuff-shaped notepad! Wait, or is it a notepad-shaped set of handcuffs?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Either way, they both sound incredibly useless.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! You don't know that! And I'm sure I can figure out what to use it for... Whichever it is.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A notepad might be useful, but I don't see when she will ever need a set of handcuffs...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What did you mean by "a Bad Badger costume is missing"?</line>
<line speaker="Proto B.">Why, just what I said, sir. We are one Bad Badger short. Counting the spares, we have two of each costume on hand at all time.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK, so because one of them is walking around in the park...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...The other should be in that room.</line>
<line speaker="Proto B.">Ah, actually, both of them should be in that room.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Proto B.">Normally, we don't use the Bad Badger costumes. In fact, we only use them during a certain event at a set time each day. It's the stage show where the Bad Badger wreaks havoc around the park... ...and the other Badgers must work together to apprehend him, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'm speechless that such a show exists.</line>
<line speaker="Proto B.">Well, sir, I was just trying to explain to you the only time we use that costume.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Then doesn't that make it near-impossble to take a picture of the Bad Badger!?</line>
<line speaker="Proto B.">Personally, I can't believe that it's this close to show time and there's no costume! Oh, dear. What am I to do, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">All this is basically means is that the kidnappers stole four costumes in total.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Then, are you saying that there are four kidnappers?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, I don't think that's very likely.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Recall the costumes for a minute.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The stolen ones, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What proves that a fourth kidnapper does not exist?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Looking here, you can plainly see that a fourth kidnapper is out of the question...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Look where? Do you know what he's trying to say, Mr. Proto Badger?</line>
<line speaker="Proto B.">N-No... I'm very sorry, sir, however, I must have missed something myself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's alright. I zigged when a zag was more appropriate... <thought>It's as simple as it appears. All I have to do is think a little to find the answer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you had four people, and you had wanted to steal a fourth costume... ...wouldn't you naturally go for the full set and steal a Pink Badger costume instead?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, that makes sense!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And yet, the kidnappers decided to steal another Bad Badger. I believe the culprits needed two Bad Badger <thought>Unaccounted for Bad Badger - A 4th stolen costume by the 3-person kidnapping group. Where's the other costume?</thought> costumes, but the question is, "Why?"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was wondering, if you don't mind... ...Mr. Proto Badger, how did you know my name?</line>
<line speaker="Proto B.">You're pretty famous, sir. I would think that most people would know who you are.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Famous? Me?</line>
<line speaker="Proto B.">Ab-SO-lutely, sir. You're always very active in the community, I hear.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow, I didn't know you were such a celebrity, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I feel like I've met this person before... Maybe it's just my imagination...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The second Bad Badger costume... I believe it may be closer at hand than we think.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hm? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That costume in the trash... Wouldn't you say that it's wearing some very telltale pants?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, you're right! Let's get it out of there and take a look!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As I suspected, it's a Bad Badger costume.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, minus the head.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There are three folding chairs over on this side. I can't say they were arranged nearly as nicely as their siblings to the right.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You think so? I think they're just fine, like a bunch of used chairs ought to be.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...*sigh* I'm beginning to think you just keep a most chaotic room.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! Don't slander and sigh at me all in one shot!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">L-Look! Its hand is hurt!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm? It looks more like something was ripped off of it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wonder why this Bad Badger costume's right hand is torn up like that?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmm... Maybe it's a flesh wound from a fight with the Blue Badger! I always knew the Blue Badger was one ferocious beast!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I somehow doubt that even real badgers are as blood-thirsty as that, Kay.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unused folding chairs lean against the wall in their folded state. The ones over by the table probably came from this stack.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this spot somehow connected to any of the evidence I hold...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is a clear contradiction of the facts!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh? What are you talking about!? Are you going to fill me in or not!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait, maybe it's not quite so clear...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Even so, it's still a contradiction, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Or it might not be.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You're acting really weird, Mr. Edgeworth. Just tell me if it's a contradiction or not.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mnngh! My apologies... <thought>There is definitely something off about this costume. If only I could envision the truth in my head, I'd be one step closer to it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe what we have here is an inconsistency.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hm? Between what?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Look carefully. Our costume is not holding something in its right hand that it should be.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmm... Oh, the gun!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely. The Bad Badger was designed to always hold a gun in his right hand. However... You there! Did you remove the gun from this Bad Badger's right hand?</line>
<line speaker="Proto B.">No, I did not, sir. The gun is supposed to be securely attached to the costume.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As I thought. The rip itself confirms my hypothesis that the gun was forcibly removed. Mr. Proto Badger, the gun is, of course, not a functioning weapon, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Proto B.">Ab-SO-lutely not, sir. It's just a model gun. However, it can fire blanks. We need to use them for the stage show.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems that our kidnappers also had a need for the model gun, my dear costumed friend.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think we're about done with this room.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So, what's next?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, we found new answers... ...but there are still a few things left that we have to ask a certain person about. Let's go, Kay!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth, sir! You've gotta hurry, sir! Come on!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is it, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">They found a Blue Badger costume down in front of the main gate, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Isn't that what one of the kidnappers was wearing!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Bingo! That's why you've gotta come to the main gate with me right now! If we hurry, we still might be able to get there before Wolf-boy does, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Alright. Let's make haste to the main gate!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, the pieces don't fit together quite right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't see a clear connection between these two pieces of information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Not exactly a shining example of the perfect line of logic.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang, about this piece of evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Lang Zi says: "Confidence is like a soul, and words without confidence are but empty shells." You shouldn't waste your breath on words you have no confidence in, Mr. Prosecutor. Although, it's just as bad to say something in full confidence and be wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arghn!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Are you going to let him lecture you about your self-confidence like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I don't need to be overflowing with self-confidence; I just need to think rationally. After all, I only need to be confident in the facts!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang, if you could take a look at this piece of evidence... ...you'd see that there is a very big flaw in your logic.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Flaw? Are you sure it's not your eyes that are flawed? Talk to me again when you can see straight!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Gnnrk! Maybe this wasn't the piece I was looking for after all!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That statement just now stands in contradiction to this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">That thing has nothing to do with what I was saying. Now, put it away! And your logic is so badly in need of repair that you might as well throw it out, too! This is the real deal here. Your courtroom mannerisms are worthless at a crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnrk...! You dare to insult the courts!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Officer Meekins, your statement contradicts this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">SIR! Permission to say that I don't think it does, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha ha! It's not looking good for you when even the culprit's doubting you, Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnngh... <thought>He must be lying, or there wouldn't be that unnatural spot in his testimony. I just have to present some evidence to prove my point!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That statement just now stands in direct contradiction to this piece of evidence. What do you think, Agent Lang?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Are you trying to buy yourself some time? Because I don't see what you're talking about. If you're going to start going on about unrelated matters, I'll just take my suspect and go!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Mr. Edgeworth, sir! Is this it, sir!? Am I under arrest now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait, please allow me to hear his testimony once more.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This evidence contradicts your statement just now...</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">...So what if it does?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Wait up, there, Junior. Where is this contradiction you speak of, Mr. Prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnngh! <thought>There must be something wrong with the way I'm approaching this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Maybe, in reality, you doubt me, too, Mr. Edgeworth, sir. B-B-But, sir! I'm telling you, I don't know anythiiiiiiiiing, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Now I KNOW something is wrong. Officer Meekins is definitely hiding something!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence says otherwise...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">............</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Great job, Mr. Edgeworth! She's so lost, she's just staring blankly at you now!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aaaangh! <thought>Then this piece must not be what I'm looking for... I can't let my guard down. I must stay focused or I'm done for.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That statement just now conflicts with this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That's not fair, Edgey-poo! I didn't have a chance to prepare myself for your...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just be quiet and listen!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I don't think you're going to get much out of her with the evidence you just presented. I mean, I don't think it even contradicts anything anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Since when did she become Ms. Law Expert!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hold on for a second. What you said just now and this piece of evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What is it now!? If you have something to say, then out with it already!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I...I... Never mind.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I admit defeat. I can't seem to find a way out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Looks like our only choice is to wait, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh! But we were so close!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A few hours later, Kay and I were freed by the police. Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I thought I told you to behave! Look, Mr. Prosecutor. I'm the one in charge here, and you're getting in the way, so get out!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm involved in this case just as much as the victim, so I insist that I also be allo...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Go back to running trials in your precious courtroom, Mr. Prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Looks like you found something interesting. I'm done being one step behind, so if you would kindly remove yourself...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But it was I who discovered the body first! I should be allowed to participate in...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I'm the one with the authority to investigate, so go back to the courtroom, Mr. Prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">End of the line for you and your logic, Mr. Prosecutor! We're leaving now, with Officer Meekins.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Mr. Edgeworth! Sir! What's going to happen to this little patrolman, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you intend to do to him, Agent Lang!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What else!? I'm going to arrest him!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Mr. Edgewoooooooooooorth!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I thought I'd drop by and see how you were doing. And fill you in on some details.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">D-Details? Concerning what?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Officer Meekins. I've officially placed him under arrest for kidnapping and murder.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">H-Hold on! That's not...!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Too late! I've already made up my mind!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is there really nothing I can do...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I think it's time we wrap up your pointless quibbling!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Quibbling"!? A man's life is at stake, Agent Lang!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I leave it up to you to reason through this mess later, in court! You guys! Place Officer Meekins under arrest, now!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh...! Is this it!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's nothing unusual about this area.</line>
</xml>