<xml>
<title>The Memoirs of the Clouded Kokoro</title>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Whew. We made it back in one piece...just. To be perfectly honest, I thought we were finished there for a while.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, I know. What a lot of close shaves. There are so many carriages on the streets of London, you were very nearly flattened several times.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...no...I didn't mean that.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I know. It was a marvellous defence, Naruhodo-san, it really was. I was in awe of you!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Um...thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And now that your fervent exploits have won us some more precious investigation time... ...let's see if we can't find some new clues for court tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. Let's do that! .........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Everything alright?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I suppose...I still can't quite believe it, that's all. That I'm here in England working as a lawyer, I mean. In the Old Bailey, no less.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The truth is, it shouldn't be me, should it? It should be him standing in my shoes. It should be Kazuma.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">...It was Kazuma-sama's wish that you follow him to Great Britain and work alongside him.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. I mean, I never had the chance to ask him exactly why, but...he clearly had a plan. I wouldn't be here today if it wasn't for him.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And you're doing wonderfully, Naruhodo-san! I've no doubt that Kazuma-sama would say exactly the same if he were here with us.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Thank you, Susato-san. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It was quite a shock earlier today, wasn't it? When the victim himself turned up in court and took the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I know...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Not only that, but then finding out that he is actually a barefaced gas thief as well!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes...that was certainly a surprise to us all. For a while, it seemed as though everyone had quite forgotten about Soseki-san poisoning the tea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Careful of your phrasing, Susato-san! He didn't poison anything! <thought>And there's more to this Mr Shamspeare than we yet know, I'm sure of it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Shamspeare certainly wasn't the noble, upstanding man everyone thought he was at first.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's become of him, actually?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I was told that he'd be returning to the hospital ward where he was receiving treatment.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, which one is that?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Let me see... Ah yes, he's at St Bartholomew's. Or Barts as Londoners call it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We know that place, don't we?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, we visited Miss Green there yesterday. It's the same hospital to which she was taken.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah yes, after Soseki-san stabbed her in the back.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Do be careful of your phrasing, Naruhodo-san! He didn't stab anyone!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Perhaps we both owe Soseki-san an apology. <thought>St Bartholomew's... Yes, we should probably visit the hospital later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...we know that Soseki-san took tea to the victim on the night in question. But as he isn't the culprit, then obviously...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes. The poison surely wasn't in the tea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But if that's the case... <thought>...how on earth did the poison get into Mr Shamspeare's body?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm sure we'll find a clue at the scene. There must be something in Mr Shamspeare's room that will help solve the mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, naturally Scotland Yard detectives have been over the place already. But it couldn't hurt for us to have another look around, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Definitely! And I'm desperate to know the outcome of the investigation into the tea left in the bar of soap.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well, if we run into Inspector Gregson, we could ask him about that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Kazuma Asogi... The best friend I ever had... And a lawyer with such promise. He really saved my bacon in that horrible incident just before we left Japan. I can still picture him now, looking so fierce and determined in court. And then after the trial, that crazy idea he came up with...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As a stowaway?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, you can fit inside my trunk if you curl up small enough, I'm sure. No one will know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma...won't you tell me why? Why go to these lengths so that I can accompany you to Great Britain?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well, it's been on my mind ever since we got through that trial. That you really ought to go into law. Be a defence lawyer. You've got a natural talent for it. Believe me. I guarantee it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But I've never even thought about becoming a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well...I can't force you, obviously. You'll have to decide for yourself. But anyway, London is the cultural capital of the world. The city at the forefront of everything. It can't hurt for you to see it with your own eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I suppose, though... ...if you were to become a lawyer, then one day... .........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">One day what?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...Oh, no, never mind.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Naruhodo-san?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, sorry. I was just thinking about Kazuma.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes... He's forever in my thoughts, too. To change the Japanese judicial system for the better... That was his dream. And that's why he so desperately wanted to come to Great Britain to study, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's right. But...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...? Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I do wonder if his true intentions lay elsewhere sometimes. I don't know. The thought just takes hold of me every now and then, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Naruhodo-san, what do you mean by Kazuma-sama's 'true intentions'?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I mean this.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...His katana?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I never expected to inherit this sword after Kazuma passed away of course.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, I know. It was because I asked you to take it...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When I have it at my side in court, I feel as though...it gives me courage.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Actually, the night before he died, he told me a little about the sword.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...'Karuma'?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">That's right. It's a prized sword that's been passed down through generations of the Asogi clan. A Japanese man's sword is his soul, Ryunosuke. I can't be parted from my katana. Karuma guides me. I truly believe that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So its name compels its wielder to slice evil in two? Not that you would need much compelling...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">On that subject... ...there's something very important that I have to do in Great Britain.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Something you have to do?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...Yes. I'd appreciate you seeing it through with me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of, of course I will. Whatever it is, I'll see it through to the end with you.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...I knew you wouldn't let me down.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What did he mean by 'something very important that I have to do'?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I had hoped that the answer to that question would become apparent when we arrived here, but... ...as yet I've not found a single clue.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Unless you put coins in this meter, of course, it won't give you any gas.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The British have some really chilling inventions, don't they?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, you could die on a cold winter's night if you weren't able to light your stove.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I suppose in a way, one little coin could be the difference between life and death...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Personally, I'd break the meter and find a way to light the stove somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no! The meter might explode if you were to tamper with it, Naruhodo-san!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... The gas companies have it all buttoned up, don't they?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Garrideb appears to be out.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm, oh well. I suppose we'll just have to come back again later.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...We probably shouldn't poke around in here whilst Mr Garrideb is out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">...What do you suppose is happening? It sounds like some sort of disturbance...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I hear angry voices...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Be not angry, o ample lady! Verily, thou art mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Mistaken, my foot! You were looking! You were looking at my painting!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'The eye of man hath not heard, the ear of man hath not seen...' 'Twas foul indeed, the poison that moustached villain gaveth me! Forgive me, lady!</line>
<line speaker="Green">I wish that you'd died from that poison!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">God-a-mercy, ample lady! But thou seest, I have vigour still! Behold, my Shamspeare dance!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...This looks rather ominous, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Ah... Lo, 'tis the lawyer from the land whence riseth the sun! How now?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, what are you doing here, Mr Shamspeare?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Marry, I do believe I am return'd unto another ward!</line>
<line speaker="Green">He was looking, that's what he was doing! Looking at my terrible work!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">......... Eastern fellow, so dark yclad... ...faith, thy work in court this morning was wonderful. I do applaud thee!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, well...thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">But! That doesn't mean things will go so wonderfully for you tomorrow, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">...Anon, exeunt!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Mr Shamspeare might technically be the victim in this case... ...but there's definitely a lot more to it than that. It's very hard to pin the man down.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Green">I'm so sorry. I'm such an awful person.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, Miss Green. Is everything alright?</line>
<line speaker="Green">Oh...yes...I mean, don't worry about me. They're about to discharge me, so...I must get ready to leave now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We're delighted that you'll soon be well enough to go home, Miss Green.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Oh dear, you're too kind. I, I don't deserve it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So, are you feeling more like yourself today, Miss Green?</line>
<line speaker="Green">I am. ...Thank you. I mean, people do recover from ordeals like this, don't they? Even people like me...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, yes...it really was an ordeal, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Green">As far as I'm concerned, I was just walking along in the snow one evening, minding my own business. And then, completely out of the blue, I was struck in the back by a knife and collapsed unconscious for days. Of course, when I finally woke up again yesterday, the whole business had been cleared up already.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What a terrible week it's been for you.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Oh no. I'm sure I'm very lucky, really. I'll look back on this fondly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Really?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Green">Anyway, I must be getting my things together now so I'm ready to be discharged.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes, of course. Sorry to take up your time when you're obviously busy.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, Runo! And Susie! Hurray! You're back!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Hello, Iris. You're in fine spirits as always, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I am! And you look as immaculately presented as ever, Susie!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! You flatter me!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, you couldn't have come at a better time! I've just made a pot of tea. I'll set some cups.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? Thanks, Iris. <thought>But actually... ...what is that foul smell?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah-ha! The wanderers return at last! Where on earth have the pair of you been?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...we've been in court?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Oh! For Mr Moustache's case? That was today, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm sure I mentioned it only yesterday, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm sure you think you did. Ah ha ha ha ha hah! ...Well, we can laugh about it now! So tell me...how did the trial go?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Reasonably well so far. We've managed to escape without a guilty verdict at least.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Really? I would have liked to see it. And I must pass the time of day with Mr Reaper again. It's been too long.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is Lord van Zieks an acquaintance, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Naturally. There's not a person in the world who doesn't know my name, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Not quite what I asked, but still...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes...whatever is that odour?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, what is it? It's faint, but...absolutely awful!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, indeed! That's the scent of victory, my dear fellows! Victory in science!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Alright, I'll bite. What's he up to now...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Lord Barok van Zieks... Yes, it's an interesting sobriquet he has, isn't it? The Reaper of the Bailey. Once the legendary prosecutor has fought for someone's conviction, that person is doomed. Even if he or she is found not guilty by the courts, sooner or later the hapless soul will vanish from the capital.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But vanish how exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">By falling under a passing carriage, or drowning in the Thames... ...or succumbing to a sudden fever, or, quite out of the blue, being set upon by a highwayman. There are numerous routes to one's final terminus, my dear fellow.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...It all seems a little far-fetched, really.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, on the bright side, Mr Moustache is fighting fit...for the time being, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That's not overly reassuring.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">If the rumours are true, though, the obvious conclusion... ...would surely be that those acquitted are, well...by Lord van Zieks's own hand...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As it happens, Miss Susato, that is quite impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Naturally, the man very quickly came under such suspicion. However, whenever these incidents occurred, the Reaper always had a cast-iron alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">R-Really?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And so his reign continued. But five years ago... ...he vanished from the courts, never to appear as a prosecutor again. That is, until you arrived in the country, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, so I've heard. <thought>In fact, it was the very day I arrived, when I was thrust into that trial at the Old Bailey. That bitter fight to the death coincided with the Reaper's resurrection... ...and really did end bitterly indeed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And here you are, facing Mr Reaper again.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Poor Runo. I don't know if you're just incredibly unlucky... ...or incredibly unlikeable.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I think it goes deeper than just me. I sense a general loathing... ...of all Japanese people.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...what is that...indescribably foul smell?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, well... Most probably this, I would say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...What is that?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow! It is, of course, my latest invention! A chemical test that can identify whether or not a tea is genuine at the drop of...some tea.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">There are some unscrupulous sorts manning the stalls along some of London's less-frequented streets. They regularly sell what purports to be high-quality tea, but is in fact merely dyed leaves of drab flavour.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...that's certainly unsavoury behaviour.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So...when one is presented with what appears to be black tea, one must be careful. ...Iris!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">At the ready, Hurley!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Let us add a drop of my chemical to this cup of tea here. ...Do you see what happens?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's turned completely black!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And what a foul odour it's giving off!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed. The blacker the tea becomes, and the more foul the odour...the better the tea is! It would appear that this cup was a particularly fine Darjeeling.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's...very ingenious. ...But what do you do with that black liquid now?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Why, dispose of it, naturally. Surely you wouldn't like to drink it...would you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">There...does seem to be a rather obvious problem with your new invention, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hence why this chemical test is merely a 'test', my dear madam.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Riiight...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The point is, we are entering a new era of science. In the world of criminal investigation, also.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! Forensic science! Oh, these are such exciting times!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I regularly engage in this scientific experimentation alongside my unofficial consulting detective work. The 'Herlock Sholmes Method' will be the foundation upon which modern investigative technique is based. This little tea indicant was a happy by-product of my ongoing forensic science research.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Forensic science...? I suppose I should find out more about that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">With Mr Natsume, who I'm currently defending, being Japanese as well as Miss Susato and myself... ...I felt it even more keenly in court today. For some reason, Lord van Zieks seems to have...an inherent disdain of the Japanese.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed... It is an interesting observation.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Do you know something about it? Do you, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... It was about ten years ago that Barok van Zieks chose to enter the legal profession. However...before that time... ...the young man's closest companion... ...hailed from the Empire of Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What the...?! Tell us more, Mr Sholmes! What happened?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... I believe I've made it clear before... I'm unable to tell you anything about the affair.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, but...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... The veil will be lifted on the events of the past in due course, I have no doubt. For now, however, it is Mr Moustache who is most deserving of your attention, I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So, your 'tea test'... Is that an example of forensic science?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed it is. An essential tool in cases that hinge on the knowledge of whether some tea is of high or inferior quality.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Not a huge number of cases, then.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Perhaps a more practical example is required. ...Fingerprints? Not yet accepted in our courts as evidence, I might add! Really, we are dragging our heels there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I hadn't even heard of them until recently...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Which is partly why I undertake research in this field myself, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Does that mean you're studying fingerprints, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">There are others in that field already. And I abhor the company of inferior minds. No, what I am researching is skin prints!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Skin prints?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">A nomenclature of my own design, as is this chemical agent that makes it possible. It instantly reveals objects touched by whichever person is under investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Brilliant, Mr Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...As long as it doesn't turn everything completely odorous and black.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I assure you, my dear fellows, you will witness my forensic talents in action very soon indeed!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah yes, the crockery of the failed thespian and the mustachioed bookworm.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">His name is Mr Soseki Natsume. You really should try to remember it.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You're right. After all, I've entrapped the man twice now. Yes, the deeply malicious bookworm has a deeply malicious moustache.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear, I'm not sure about that. A deeply misfortunate moustache, perhaps...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">That too. The moustache is indeed misfortunate. But only because it is malicious!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, what wonderful reasoning, Mr Sholmes! You've won me over yet again!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I believe...you tried to eat some soap once, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">True, yes. I had a theory that it may cleanse the inside of my digestive system, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Was it particularly dirty, do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed it was. For I had mistakenly imbibed some ink at the time, assuming it to be coffee. 'I must cleanse at once,' I thought to myself. Quite logically, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Only you could have an anecdote about swallowing soap.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Mr Sholmes, about this...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Dull.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">If you will produce such dull items with such a dull countenance, you must expect a dull response. At the very least, you could do something about your face, my dear fellow. I crave visual stimulation!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...something like this?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah ha ha ha ha hah! Indeed, that is quite the stimulation I desired!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's the spirit, Runo! See you later!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, until later.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no, Mr Sholmes! We were thinking you'd come with us.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You were?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes! Of course! You said so just a moment ago! You said we'd witness your forensic talents in action.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, yes. I do recall saying something along those lines. But you go on ahead. I shall be sure to follow you later...in all likelihood. ...Probably. ...Maybe. ...Well, I might.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Your commitment astounds me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, thank you, Mr Sholmes! We'll eagerly await your arrival!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Bye-bye, Runo! Bye, Susie!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes seems to be making funny faces at something on his desk... I thought he said he was going to come with us to Mr Shamspeare's room.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No doubt he's preparing something, Mr Naruhodo. Something amazing!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Zzz...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And he's doing it whilst asleep! Is there no limit to the man's talents?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Hello again, Inspector Gregson.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">What are you doin' here?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm, well...we were hoping to have another look around, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The lawyer representing the defendant has a right to examine the scene, as I'm sure you're aware.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yeah, I know the score.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Yes, one other thing... The soap on the ledge outside the window. Did you find it? With the tea in it?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yeah, we found it alright. And there was a small amount of tea in it, as you said.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I knew it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">It's with the identification section at the Yard now. They're lookin' into it. The results should be available later today.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's wonderful news! Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">......... Pretty impressive performance in court this mornin'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Nothin'! Forget it! Just make sure you don't disturb anythin' in here!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Are you looking for new clues, Inspector?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">...On Lord van Zieks's orders, yeah. 'Don't come back till you've got somethin' for me,' he says! Tsk...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear. Poor you...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yeah, poor me! Because we've already searched every bleedin' nook and cranny in this place. I dunno what he expects, to be honest. Thank goodness for warm chips, is all I can say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Well, at least he's honest.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you ran out of change, you wouldn't even have any light, let alone heat. For the needy, London's winters can be very harsh.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's true. But if you think about it... ...even the wealthy would find themselves freezing if they ran out of small change.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">London's winters can be very harsh for the forgetful, too, then. <thought>Frankly, I'm starting to wonder if Susato-san and I are going to make it to spring...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's true. We don't even have a meter at Baker Street, let alone a gas stove...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look how dark the stain on the floor is underneath the meter there.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, from all the water dripping out after the ice coins melted, as you established in court this morning.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's a very large and obvious stain, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Shamspeare must have used an awful lot of ice coins, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...It was an ingenious idea, I'll give him that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah the ill-fated teacups from which the two men drank on the ill-fated night...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">During their heated literary debate, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Who's stronger, Romeo or Juliet? ...It sounds like it was quite a 'discussion'.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Now I think of it, I'm sure that the two lovers in the play ended their lives with poison... .........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's fiction, Miss Susato; let's hope it stays that way.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So it turns out that Mr Shamspeare wasn't eating the soap after all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right. The mystery of why he had it on a plate whilst holding a fork in his hand is solved.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes. To prise his latest ice coin out of its mould. And in the process, he accidentally broke the bar of soap in two...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It certainly was hard to imagine, let alone deduce.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The sun never shines in this room, thanks to that depressing bricked-up window.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yet, with enough determination, you can always remove the bricks to set some soap outside, can't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That sounds like a very wise life lesson, Miss Susato.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Only if you plan to follow a life of crime, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes! What are you up to over there?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What a question, indeed! Was it not your good self who asked me to attend the scene?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Oi! What are you doin' there, Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">'What are you up to over there?' 'What are you doing here?'... Dear me, once a great detective, one is always under scrutiny, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Is now the time, Mr Sholmes? Are you about to show us your forensic talents in action as you promised?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">With the greatest of pleasure, my dear madam!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...what's all this?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">'All this' is precisely what you requested, Mr Naruhodo. Herlock Sholmes's sensational Skin Print Seeker gun! Moments ago, I took a sample from the teacup that was used by the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A sample? From Mr Shamspeare's cup?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Each individual leaves microscopic secretions on everything he or she touches. A sample of those secretions is all I need to produce this... a refined indicator solution. By liberally spraying the room with this chemical... ...everything the victim touched is instantly revealed with the aid of these goggles. Here, try them out! There. Now, spray the chemical indicator about and all will be revealed?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Spray? How, how do I do that exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">A little press of [A / X / space] on the area you're interested in is all that's required. ...Like this!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Wh-What is that stuff? It's like fog!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">A suspension of the chemical indicator in a pressurised gas. It's the most efficient way to cover a large area. That was another invention I discovered incidentally whilst I was developing this idea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>As you do...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Go ahead! Try it, my dear fellow! We may learn something interesting about the victim's movements on the night in question.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well...there's nothing to lose, I suppose... Let's explore!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look! There are dozens of handprints here!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So there are. A great many indeed. So much so that it's hard to make out any one individual print, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Brrr... It sends a chill down my spine...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Perhaps...he was leaning against the wall while he admired this picture?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Unlikely, I would say. It's a rather dull scene, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And without wishing to state the obvious... ...you wouldn't generally admire a picture from such close quarters, I feel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh. Very true, Miss Susato. <thought>It's a bit of a mystery, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Look at all this here!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, yes. Interesting... A multitude of the victim's handprints.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Why are there so many of them on the floor in this one spot?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ooh! Perhaps he had a bad fall just here?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">There's nothing obvious that he would have tripped over though, is there?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm...I wonder... Personally, I often stumble when there's nothing obvious to trip over.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I think that's something only a great detective would do, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, this is quite a puzzle. Handprints all over the floor...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, there's no obvious explanation...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">We did. But there are...two places in particular that are of interest, I would say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The handprints on the floor there...and on the wall by the picture, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! And I think the floor warrants closer investigation! I won't be a moment... ......... Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What is it, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Look here, Mr Naruhodo! One of the floorboards has popped out!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">One of the...? You mean... <thought>It's a secret hiding place?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Excellent work, Miss Susato! So...what do we have in here?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Oi! What are you lot doin'?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Inspector Gregson!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Stand aside right this minute! It's my job to investigate there!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">No need, Inspector. You continue to dig in to your portion of chips, whilst we dig around under the floor here.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Your fancy talk's puttin' me off my food anyway, Sholmes! A new bit of evidence is exactly what I need.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Wow, a secret hiding place under the floor! What a find!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's not a hiding place you could make use of in Japan. I don't think I could lift a straw tatami mat...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, I know. But I never expected one of these wooden floorboards to move, either. It's got me wondering about the wall over there, too. Aren't you curious?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! I'll investigate at once! ......... There's nothing behind the picture, sadly. Only the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hmmm... How disappointing.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But then...how do you explain the handprints?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I really can't think why anyone would have been touching the wall over and over in one place like that.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">There you are. A print for you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Thank you very much! <thought>His invention can make prints, too? Now then... ...I wonder if Inspector Gregson has found anything under the floor there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm desperate to know!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So am I!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'd love to know if there's anything hidden underneath that floorboard there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Allow me to ask Gregson now. After all, we're well acquainted. Inspector Gregson! Really, it's been too long!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">...What is it, Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I thought perhaps you might show me what you've found there. Seeing as we're such good friends.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">...We're not friends.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...No, I...suppose not. A dismal failure!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...I heard. <thought>Ugh, I'd kill to know what was under that floorboard.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">......... Alright then, fair's fair.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">You did discover the hidin' place, after all. I suppose I should at least fill you in.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really, Inspector? Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Do it quickly, my dear fellow! If there's one thing I know about this man, it's that he blows with the wind! As fickle as the weather!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Oi! Stop makin' me out to be some kind of nut! There were three items under the floor there: a newspaper clippin', a photographic print and a tin box. Now...what do you want to know?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Looks like this was cut out of the paper about three months ago. It's about a convict who got sick and died while he was servin' time up in Manchester.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How terrible...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">It made the headlines down here in London as well. The bloke had been sentenced to death, you see. But nature got him first...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my goodness! He'd committed a capital offense?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Man by the name of Selden. Nasty piece of work, into burglaries and murder. They say the hoard he'd knocked off was worth about a thousand pounds.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A hoard? Of treasure, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Jewellery and the like. But he'd hidden it somewhere, and no one knows where. And now he's dead. The papers loved it, of course. 'A Thousand Pounds Lost En Route to Hell!' or some such was the headline.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Does it not strike you, though? Why such an article would be so carefully ensconced under the floor?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">......... I suppose now you mention it...it does seem a bit odd. Perhaps I'll go over the paperwork we've got on Selden back at the Yard and see if I can turn anythin' up.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Looks like this was cut out of the paper about three months ago. It's about a convict who got sick and died while he was servin' time up in Manchester.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How terrible...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">It made the headlines down here in London as well. The bloke had been sentenced to death, you see. But nature got him first...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my goodness! He'd committed a capital offense?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Man by the name of Selden. Nasty piece of work, into burglaries and murder. They say the hoard he'd knocked off was worth about a thousand pounds.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A hoard? Of treasure, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Jewellery and the like. But he'd hidden it somewhere, and no one knows where. And now he's dead. The papers loved it, of course. 'A Thousand Pounds Lost En Route to Hell!' or some such was the headline.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Does it not strike you, though? Why such an article would be so carefully ensconced under the floor?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">......... I suppose now you mention it...it does seem a bit odd. Perhaps I'll go over the paperwork we've got on Selden back at the Yard and see if I can turn anythin' up.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">So...this is the photograph I found. Looks reasonably recent to me.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes...it would appear to have been taken on the street in front of the house here.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And the gentleman on the left is Mr Garrideb, the landlord, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But who's the young man on the right? Mr Garrideb's son perhaps...?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Perhaps. You can take that print if you like.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">We can presume, therefore, that the Yard already knows. The identity of the young fellow, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! <thought>Is that true?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Hmph. Well it's too bad if we do. Unfortunately for you lot, leakin' information isn't one of my pastimes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear inspector, if I may be so bold as to point something out... Pastimes are for one's leisure. But this is for work.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">......... All the more reason I'm not tellin' you!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">A dismal failure!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...I heard.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I wonder why a photograph like this was hidden under the floor... I mean, Mr Shamspeare himself isn't in it.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Photographic prints are still rare treasures in the East End. I imagine Mr Garrideb was rather delighted to have been immortalised. He probably made a proud present of it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, thank you for this photograph, Inspector.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, taken outside this very building, it would seem.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And the young man on the right is... <thought>...who exactly?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">You're wastin' your time, sunshine. Like I said, leakin' information isn't one of my pastimes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear inspector, if I may be so bold as to point something out... Information exists for the very purpose of being leaked!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">......... Not in my book, it doesn't.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... I rather think it's not in my book either, in truth.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I don't even have a book. <thought>I suppose we'll have to try to find out for ourselves...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Now this tin box looks interestin', doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Might I suggest, Inspector...that you open it? If you were to find something inside that reveals the truth behind this case... ...I wouldn't be in the least surprised.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yeah, funnily enough I've already had a look. It's completely empty.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What?! Shamspeare! Give us a clue, man!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You didn't even have the chance to utter a word, Mr Naruhodo. But anyway, at least we've found out what's inside the box.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, thin air. It's empty, rather like how I Feel inside. <thought>Is there nothing more to this box, then? I wonder...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh look! It's that lovely little kitty cat! What was its name...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's Mr Natsume's, isn't it? I don't think we ever asked him, actually. Why don't we call it, um...Wagahai? You know, like Mr Natsume refers to himself in Japanese. <thought>I wonder how he got in here? Clever cat...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, wonderful! Well then, Wagahai...here's something delicious I bought for you from the cats' meat man!</line>
<line speaker="Wagahai">Miaow...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Hee hee...he couldn't be happier now, look.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I just hope we can bring some happiness to his owner, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wagahai">Miaow.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That was a cheeky little miaow, Wagahai.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, but he's so adorable! I could sit and watch him forever!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think...he may not appreciate that after a while. And we have an investigation to get back to.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Mr Natsume is back!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So he is. ...Mr Natsume! Hello!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I...am a cat.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I don't know who Mr Natsume is. Or Herr Lock Sholmes. I don't know about courts or trials or Old Baileys. I am a cat. That's what I am. Just a cat.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! He's trying to escape from reality!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Trying to? He already has! Completely!</thought> SO, um...what is your name, then?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... As yet I have no name.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! He hasn't fully thought out his new identity yet! Maybe it's not too late to bring him back to reality!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you think...you could open your eyes for us, Mr Natsume?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... I...am not a cat.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It worked! He's back in the real world!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Wh-What's going to b-b-become of me? ...NO! DON'T ANSWER THAT! IT'S OBVIOUS! My accursed soul is never going to escape this accursed fate!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Natsume, no! This morning's proceedings in court proved that there's hope!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Yes... Yes... Locum Student Mr Naruhodo Esquire was brilliant, but... BUT! THE REAPER IS OMNIPRESENT! IN COURT! IN MY LODGINGS! Here! There! Everywhere!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...What's he looking straight at me for?</thought> I think perhaps...there are some things we should discuss?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh! Yes... Yes, we must...</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">In my WHOLE life...have I EVER been so...so MOVED as I was today? ...NO! Of course...if I cast my mind back, there were perhaps one or two other occasions that moved me more... But if I just block those out, then today, being in that courtroom, was...was... It was the most moving experience OF MY LIFE, Locum Student Mr Naruhodo Esquiiiiiire!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You're too kind.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Scotland Yard found the remaining tea, just as we'd deduced, and are analysing it as we speak.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">There's nothing wrong with that tea! They won't find a drop of poison in it! That's a...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Tell me...did you both drink the tea at the same time that night?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh yes, most definitely. Remember...drink tea while it's hot! We both poured it down our throats like it was a hot bath for our bellies!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And at the time...you were both completely fine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As shown by the fact that he and Mr Shamspeare then engaged in the Romeo and Juliet match. <thought>I suppose the focus of tomorrow's proceedings will be how the poison was taken by the victim, then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">That rotten Shamspeare! What have I ever done to him?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You don't recall him taking issue with you over anything you've done recently?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I've been holed up in my room, immersed in books. I don't recall anything... ANYTHING AT ALL!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right...</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">But what I don't understand is why he didn't let me know sooner.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Let you know what, Mr Natsume?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">About the soap, of course! What else?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... ...are you struggling with such a meagre stipend?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Of course I am! If I had money... ...I wouldn't have chosen to live an accursed existence in such accursed lodgings!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, yes...you said it's because the place is cursed that it's so cheap, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Exactly! Especially the room that I rent. The spirit of that capital offender who lived there still haunts the place, AND IT'S TRYING TO KILL ME!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Capital offender'...?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Might I ask, Locum Student Mr Naruhodo Esquire, that the next time you visit me... ...you bring scores of super-soft soaps!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">...The truth is, I didn't know the details myself until very recently. That Selden man was arrested about a year ago now. And at the time, he was hiding out in lodgings...at Mr Garrideb's house.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? He lived...where you do now?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">That's right, yes. Exactly where I live now. In my very room.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! Your room was previously occupied by a criminal found guilty of a capital offence?!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">But before his sentence could be carried out, he died in prison. That was three months ago now. ...And that's when it started... The c-c-curse...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What really is this curse you keep mentioning, Mr Natsume?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">It's already caused one death. A few months after the criminal passed away in prison... ...a man died in the room. The man who rented it after Selden, in fact. The poor lodger... He, he was f-found dead in mysterious circumstances. The room was l-locked from the inside.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Locked from the inside? <thought>Exactly like the case we're dealing with now...!</thought> So that's the convict's curse, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Yes. Well...that was the start of it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Do you have any idea how the lodger before you passed away, Mr Natsume?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">The official cause of death was asphyxia. When they discovered the body, the room was full of gas.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gas...?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I only found that out after I'd signed the lease. When Mr Garrideb came to tell me later, I couldn't stop myself trembling. In fact, if I'd known beforehand, I'd probably have been too scared to take the room.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Lucky for Mr Garrideb, maybe. But not so lucky for poor Mr Natsume.</thought> And now you believe this curse is affecting you?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">It is, it is! At first... ...I just felt as though I was being watched. All the time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And then you talked about having nightmares, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">The, the dead are t-trying to take me with them. They c-come for me and try to s-s-suffocate me! Just when I'm s-struggling to breathe...I wake up. And the room IS AS COLD AS ICE!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But...why is your room so cold?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">London winters are too cold to bear without any heating on overnight. But for some reason...even though I light the stove before I climb into bed at night... ...the pilot light always goes out and the room fills with gas.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but that's terrible! <thought>That's exactly the same situation as what led to the previous occupant's death.</thought> And then there's what happened to Mr Shamspeare last night. When he was mysteriously poisoned... <thought>There's clearly more to THAT incident than can be explained by a curse, though...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Whatever can be the cause of all these strange happenings in Mr Garrideb's rooms?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's a newspaper cutting that we found in Mr Shamspeare's room.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... Ah, so he knew, did he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">About this man, Selden. A convicted killer, and THE EVIL SPIRIT behind the curse that afflicts my lodgings!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">He's already taken one young man's life. And now... ...he's trying to take the life of another! A miserable, moustached, much-maligned Japanese man!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Natsume, if you know something, please... You must tell us! Tell us everything you can about this 'evil spirit'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, you're here now, Mr Garrideb.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Right bally business it is for me, you know. Getting out and about.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Were you at the Old Bailey, by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Naturally. Fate of my lodgings hanging in the balance and all that. Not a trial to miss.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The fate of what's already been dubbed your 'haunted lodgings', yes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">'Course, the place has caused quite a stir around the capital on more than one occasion already. As the old 'haunted lodgings' or some such.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah... <thought>Well, at least he knows.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Makes you wonder what the blazes is going on, don't you know?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes...I'm sure it does. In fact, thinking back to Mr Natsume's other trial just two days ago... ...you were at the Old Bailey then as well, weren't you? Testifying with your wife about what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">...Stopped off at the prison on the way home, in fact. Beastly business.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">So...what brings you to my haunted abode today, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Some fishy fellow from the Far East and a failed actor chap of questionable character, eh? Yes, the house does seem to have become something of a magnet for rum fellows of late. Thanks to that bally curse...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The convict's curse, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Ah, heard the stories, have you? Rotten scoundrel was arrested here, then the next chap in the room goes and keels over. Then there was that woman who dropped dead just outside on the street, not to mention the actor yesterday. Am I next, eh? Well...can't help but get the collywobbles, can you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">When you say the woman who dropped dead outside on the street...do you mean Miss Green?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Because Miss Green, who was stabbed by the knife, and Mr Shamspeare, who was poisoned last night... ...are both very much alive still.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Yes, well... So is that blasted convict's curse, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Personally, I should be quite content with such lodgings. A bath, a toilet, a fireplace, a fascinating history... Why, it sounds like the lap of luxury!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm, I'm not so sure about that...</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Well, there's no bath or toilet included. And no fireplace, either.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...you do look out for your tenants, don't you? By watching the rise and fall of the flames in your gas lamps up here.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Yes, never hurts to keep an eye on things. In case there are any...mishaps or suchlike.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I think you've had your mishap already, sir! Ah ha ha ha ha hah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That's not helpful, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Heaven forgive me. The words just came to my lips!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Some fishy fellow from the Far East and a failed actor chap of questionable character, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's no need for that, Mr Garrideb.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's right. Mr Natsume is in no way 'fishy'!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm...he is undeniably peculiar, however.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is it right that he took the vacancy immediately after the previous tenant passed away?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Yes, that's right. I asked the estate agent to find someone and he popped up the very same day. Never come across a chap so keen for a place with...a background, as it were.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't think it was the room's background he was keen on so much as the cheap rent, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So...how long has Mr Shamspeare been lodging under your roof?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">That failed actor chap? Hm, let me see... Oh, of course! Yes, it's been three months now. Quite sure of it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Only three months... He's quite new here too, then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And to what do you owe your certainty in that regard, Mr Garrideb, if I might ask?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Well, it was that Selden scoundrel, as it happens.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Selden? The convict, you mean? <thought>Do Selden and Shamspeare have some kind of connection, then?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">That convict chap, Selden... Passed away in the clink three months ago now, you see. Some malady or other.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, we've seen the report from the newspaper at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Well, it was only three days later that the tragedian showed his face. The actor fellow.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Yes, I remember it quite distinctly.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'Tis small, this world we inhabit. Prithee landlord, hear my request... I, the humble Shamspeare, do desire to take thy room on the middle floor offer'd erewhile for rent.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Hm, terribly sorry and whatnot, but that won't be possible. Already have a lodger on the middle floor. Ground floor room's vacant, though...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'Nothing can be made out of nothing.' ...Let me repeat mine will unto thee.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Those curls must be muffling your ears! The room on the middle floor's taken. It's ground floor or nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">......... Very well, we have an accord.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Glad to hear it. Welcome to Briar Road!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Lo, a Shamspeare dance to celebrate!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">From what I heard in court today, sounds like the chap was thieving gas. And he was three months in arrears with the rent, too. Yes, the fellow was a bally player alright!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Thank you for your candour, Mr Garrideb. We are most grateful. By way of appreciation, allow me to say one or two words... 'Give me my robe, put on my crown. I have immortal longings in me.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... What's happened to you?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Shakespeare, my dear fellow! One of his most famous lines. I wished to divulge my own learning of the subject. For I...have a turn for literature too, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Perhaps you could turn your attention to more apt lines then?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Yes, Duncan Ross... Young chap was attending art school. Had to work to pay for it, mind. Moved into the middle room floor about a year ago, after that criminal, Selden, was arrested. Young students are always on the hunt for rooms with a history behind them.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A history of cheap rent, maybe, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Yes, well anyway...it was one morning about a month ago now... Hadn't quite worked out the old trick of watching the gas lamps to see what my lodgers are up to at the time. So sadly, I was rather tardy to discover what had happened. Smell of gas that alerted me, it was.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah yes... Synonymous with the smell of death...</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Called the police straight away, of course, and the officer kicked the door off its hinges. But once we got inside, we all bally collapsed!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Because of the gas?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Yes. Room was full of it. No air at all. Stove must've gone out while the poor chap was sleeping in his bed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So Mr Ross suffocated to death...</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">'Course, the police gave me a sound ticking off because the gas pipes were so old and all that. Can't tell you how much it set me back to have the lot replaced all over the house.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But even after you had all that work done, Mr Natsume says the same thing. That the stove goes out at night whilst he's asleep in bed.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Well that's the bally curse! The convict's curse! I've done my duty as a landlord now!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Someone's feeling defensive...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Garrideb, about this photographic print...</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Ah, yes, the 'scene'. I thought the bally fellow was as dead as a doornail! Jolly welcome news that he's alive. For him and for the room.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'For the room'? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Well, it matters, you know. When I come to let the room next time, people will ask. And there's a world of difference between a room where someone died, and a room where someone nearly died.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">They sound awfully similar to me...</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Ah, an Altamont gas meter, yes. Decent fireplace in here, of course, so no need for a gas stove. But there's nothing better than a gas lamp for reading in bed, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Actually, Mr Natsume mentioned that the gas supply to his room kept failing.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Ah, yes, that... I had the gas company look into it. But they couldn't find a thing wrong. The chap must've been imagining things.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I don't think he was imagining it. The poor man woke up unable to breathe.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Think it was put down to ghosts at work or some such in the end. Place must be haunted.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Garrideb, could I ask you to look at this photograph? Is that your son who's with you there?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">No no, not at all. He was a lodger here once. Duncan Ross was his name.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Duncan Ross...</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">A street photographer happened to be passing, so I asked him to take a shot. Just for kicks, really.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Was he by any chance the lodger before Mr Natsume?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">......... Yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, the young gentleman who died in the room in mysterious circumstances. Just what Mr Moustache was waiting for, one might say...</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">...Yes, young Duncan lived in the room at the top of the first flight of stairs before that Japanese chap.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Would you mind telling us a little more about him?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">About young Duncan. The night before the poor chap perished... ...he'd been writing a letter. A letter of affection to a young lady.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">A love letter, you mean?!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Yes, where did I put it now...? Ah, here it is! Left it on my desk.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">If you'll excuse me... Let me see now, what does it say...? 'To my most beautiful and charming sweetheart...'</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Um...do you think that we should be reading such a personal piece of correspondence?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear Miss Susato, that is precisely why I prefaced my reading with 'If you'll excuse me'!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I will NOT excuse you, Mr Sholmes, no!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Sadly he didn't address it, though. So I've no means of delivering the thing. Rather sad, really...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I see... <thought>That's going to play on my mind...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">But really, the identity of Mr Ross's sweetheart has no bearing on the case. I think we should leave well alone.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I suppose you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed, the intended recipient's address is missing. However... ...there is a name attributed to the man's 'most beautiful and charming sweetheart'.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes, please! I've already had to chastise you about this once.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">'...My undying love to you, my colourful darling, Olive Green.'</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">O... Olive Green?! <thought>The woman who was plunged into a coma after a knife plunged into her back outside this house five days ago! The victim of the last case Soseki-san was in court for, who regained consciousness only yesterday! Is it just chance that her name has come up now? Could it possibly be a mere coincidence?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo, whatever can this mean?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Reading personal correspondence can have its merits, you see, Miss Susato. Ah ha ha ha hah!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo, I've just finished speaking with the doctor. It seems Miss Green is well enough to be discharged at last.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is good news. But hopefully, just before she leaves-</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What is it? Miss Green! <thought>What was that?! She clearly just hid something behind her back!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Green">One, one moment! ...I'll be with you in a jiffy! Oh...hello, everyone. What are you all doing here? The doctor has said I can be discharged, so I'm just getting my things together.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Miss Green...what were you just doing?</line>
<line speaker="Green">Oh! Um...nothing...really. I was just about to take some medicine the doctor prescribed for me, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...we were hoping to have another quick chat with you if that's alright?</line>
<line speaker="Green">I...don't really have anything else to tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Alright, she's definitely behaving strangely. Let's see if we can't coax something out of her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is the card that Miss Green was looking at so intently before, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo. We shouldn't be peeking at a young woman's private effects.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Right. I should save peeking for gentlemen's effects only...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">You mustn't do that, either.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And maybe you, Miss Susato, shouldn't be peeking into a young man's mind, either, hm?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is the bottle that Miss Green was just about to drink from when we arrived.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes... She looked rather preoccupied, didn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Perhaps it's very bitter. I can't stand bitter medicine.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I suppose that could be it...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In fact, whenever a doctor prescribes me medicine for a number of days, I always take it all at once.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, if you have to take something you don't like, it's best to get it all out of the way in one go, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... And I thought it was Miss Green I should be worrying about at the moment...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's wonderful news that you're going to be discharged, Miss Green.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Oh, yes... I mean, thank you. Once people are better, the hospital staff don't want them lingering and wasting space. Not people like me, anyway. So I...I don't think I should keep anyone waiting. I probably shouldn't stand around and chat.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>She certainly doesn't seem to be in the mood to talk, that's for sure.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Green, about this soap...</line>
<line speaker="Green">...! I, I think I know what that is... It's that soap-shaped chocolate, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...no. This is just normal soap. Well, normal, poor-quality soap.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Oh... That was lucky... At least it wasn't a trick this time...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">A trick?</line>
<line speaker="Green">I fell for it only the other day. 'It's soap-shaped chocolate,' they said. Just one bite, and I was foaming at the mouth. I passed out, it tasted so awful!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What is it about people recently that makes them all eat soap...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, is there perhaps something you might be able to tell me if I show you this photograph, Miss Green?</line>
<line speaker="Green">Oh, is that...a corpse?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no! He's not dead!</line>
<line speaker="Green">Of course, the night he had that poison... ...I was still more or less dead here in my hospital bed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah... <thought>She was still in a coma then, that's true.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Green">And then just as I get on my feet again, that man keels over. There's a strange balance to life sometimes...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no no. Really, Mr Shamspeare isn't dead.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Green, about this...</line>
<line speaker="Green">Ah! Could you just hold that there for a moment? Don't move...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Green">......... No. No, the aesthetics are all wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Is, is it wrong that I feel so thoroughly rejected...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Green, we were hoping to ask you about someone. Mr Duncan Ross. You...knew him, didn't you? Oh no! I'm so sorry! <thought>The bottle of medicine fell down when she did!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Miss Green! Are you alright?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm so sorry. I didn't mean to startle you like that.</line>
<line speaker="Green">No. No, it's alright. I just wasn't expecting it. But how do you know about Duncan?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Ross had been writing a letter when he passed away. The landlord found it in his room. It...was a very personal letter...to you.</line>
<line speaker="Green">......... It was at the art school. That's where I met Duncan. A year ago now. He was working to fund his studies. He dreamt of becoming a professional artist one day.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And the two of you became romantically involved?</line>
<line speaker="Green">...Yes, that's right. We were very much in love. We were engaged to be married, actually. That's why he decided to move into a cheaper room. To save money for the wedding.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And that's what led him to Mr Garrideb's...</line>
<line speaker="Green">Yes. He told me he'd found the worst, but cheapest room in the entire East End. And then...one month ago... That's when it happened.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We're so terribly sorry, Miss Green.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Well...it's all in the past now, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Poor Miss Green... She looks desperately sad.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I was starting to think that's just her 'look'... ...but now I see that she has every reason to feel the universe is against her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Duncan Ross... Who would ever have thought he was engaged to be married to Miss Green?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">To lose one's beloved fianc must be painful enough.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But then Miss Green suffered that awful injury. And outside her fianc's former lodgings, too!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Fate can be very cruel sometimes...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The bottle fell off before, when Miss Green collapsed. <thought>That was...quite an earthquake...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Whatever was in the bottle?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Honey, maybe... Or treacle... Or syrup... Or all three mixed together, even...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo... ...you've been having a lot of very mean thoughts during this exchange. I'm disappointed in you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, I'm so sorry! We didn't mean to hold you up. Of course, we'll be on our way-</line>
<line speaker="???">Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Surely you were not about to leave? That's quite out of the question!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha... Mr Sholmes! I didn't realise you were here!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But of course I was, my dear fellow. Watching intently from the shadows as always.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...make your presence known next time!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes, what's this about?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Something which occurs to me with some regularity, Miss Susato, is this: Why do detectives insist on such an ex post facto modus operandi? Why solve a case after it's happened... ...instead of preventing a case before it happens? That is what sets a great detective apart!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">There is a case waiting to happen under our very noses, Mr Naruhodo. So let us avert disaster! Let us prevent this case from ever happening...with nothing but careful observation.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Alright.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">All the clues you need are set before you. You need only look, and you cannot fail to see!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You can do it, Mr Naruhodo! I know you can!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It definitely feels as though this card must be relevant. I mean, when we first arrived... ...Miss Green was standing with it in her hand in what can only be described as a very tense atmosphere.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes... It may very well be related to whatever incident Mr Sholmes believes was about to happen here. Perhaps we should ask Miss Green about it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That mouse seems to be dead, look. I didn't notice it there before, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think perhaps it drank the medicine that spilled out of the bottle. But that's the bottle that Miss Green was about to drink from when we arrived.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... You, you don't think...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, I see you've come to appreciate the true nature of this scene. That of a tragedy about to take place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I... I think it's falling into place. Miss Green, the contents of the bottle you had before has spilt out on the floor... ...and the poor mouse that drank it has sadly died.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think it's clear that the bottle must have contained a powerful poison.</line>
<line speaker="Green">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Don't worry. I will attend to the mouse presently.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Miss Green... ...were you intending to go the same way as that rodent? To take your own life?</line>
<line speaker="Green">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Once we'd left... ...you would have put it to your lips again, wouldn't you? And taken the poison?</line>
<line speaker="Green">I... I... NOOOOOOOOO!!!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Miss Green, please! Please talk to us!</line>
<line speaker="Green">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't believe she was going to take that poison...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes, your keen observational skills have saved Miss Green's life!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">To become a truly great detective, one must solve cases before they have occurred.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, what a delightful idea!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed! And why not, from time to time?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why not all the time? Then London would be entirely without crime!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And I would be entirely without an income. Everything in moderation, my dear fellow.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...? Did you say something, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, the truth. But when it comes to Mr Sholmes, you do tend to turn a deaf ear to it sometimes, Susato-san.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ten seconds later, and we would have arrived at a very different scene here. In all probability, we would not have enjoyed this most delightful conversation. Of course...perhaps it hasn't been quite so delightful from your perspective, Miss Green.</line>
<line speaker="Green">......... Actually, in a way... ...now that everything's out in the open, I feel like a weight has been lifted.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Tell me...how did you acquire that 'medicine'?</line>
<line speaker="Green">......... Well, with this being a hospital and all... When the doctor comes to examine me in the mornings... ...he always leaves the medicine cabinet open for a while. So I snuck this out when he wasn't looking.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It conspicuously lacks a label. I wonder what it contains.</line>
<line speaker="Green">I'm afraid I don't really know. But I thought, if I drank it, it might just...stop the pain somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh please, Miss Green. Don't talk of such things.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, it seems clear now that it contains poison.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that poor little mouse is proof of that.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Oh no... Oh, it's all my fault... What have I done...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I shall remove this to my office, Miss Green. ...I take it you have no objection?</line>
<line speaker="Green">...No. None.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Neither the sender's name or address appear to be written on the envelope or the card.</line>
<line speaker="Green">It arrived by post at my home the day before the incident that put me in hospital here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'I have information regarding the death of Duncan Ross. Come to The Slug and Salad on Briar Road at 5 p.m. on 17th. Don't tell anybody else about this letter or the meeting. It is a matter of utmost importance.'</line>
<line speaker="Green">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Wait a minute. The seventeenth? Of this month? That's the day... That's the day you were stabbed on Briar Road!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And...5 p.m...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Is precisely the time when the incident occurred!</line>
<line speaker="Green">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The Slug and Salad, yes... A pub on the northern corner of Briar Road.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Briar Road... <thought>...being the street that Mr Garrideb's house is on!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Does this mean that...?</line>
<line speaker="Green">Yes. I'm sure you've guessed. That day, when I was struck in the back by the knife... ...I was actually on my way to The Slug and Salad.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Goodness...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So that's what you were doing on Briar Road that day.</line>
<line speaker="Green">......... I'm sorry I didn't say anything before.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes, I'm very sorry to have had to drag up such painful memories for you.</line>
<line speaker="Green">No, it's fine.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Miss Green... ...please, promise us you won't try to...do anything like that again.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Yes, don't worry. Your detective friend has the bottle now anyway. And besides... ...I've been stabbed in the back and had a close shave with a bottle of poison and I'm still here. I think...I'm destined to see things through to the end. It might sound a little conceited, but, well...that's how all this has made me feel.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, it would appear we've reached the end of the investigative trail for today.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...it's late.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And, Mr Naruhodo...? ...Did you discover anything that may be of use to you in court tomorrow, do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Details about Mr Shamspeare...Mr Garrideb's lodgings... the convict, Selden... There are many facets to this case, and we're yet to see to the heart of it, if you ask me. That's my feeling, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I can't help wondering about the results of the analysis.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Into Mr Natsume's tea, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes. Will they have found strychnine in it or not?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, I fear that either way... ...it will be hard to escape the grip of our friend Mr Reaper.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, Barok van Zieks...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But I wish you every success, of course. And though I was late to rise this morning... ...tomorrow will be a new dawn! I intend to spring from my bed at a crisp hour and attend the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes! You're going to come?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed! Whatever happens, I shall be there! ...Assuming my eyelids cooperate in the morning.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...I think we've done all we can. All that's left is to remain focused and keep fighting for Mr Natsume's cause until the very end.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't find anything out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Nothing particular of note...</thought></line>
</xml>