<xml>
<title>The Story's End</title>
<line speaker="Luke">Where's Espella? Where could she be?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no sign of her at all.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This is very strange... I've a feeling we're the only ones around.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">P-Professor... Look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Look! It's a new story!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm? That means...that the parade has already taken place...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Anyway, let's read it!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Does this mean what I think it means...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no way... That can't be!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is this what that Great Witch meant?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Whatever the case, let's find Espella before panic spreads throughout the town.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We should probably split up. If only we had some leads...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The "appointed place of ending"... Perhaps this is referring to the town square, at which the parade always ends. ...While the "teller of the Story" can mean none other than Espella's father. As for being "silenced forever"... This is almost certainly an indication that he will lose his life.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In that case, Professor... the chances of Espella being at the town square are pretty high, right?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, Mr Wright. Let's head to the square and find her!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...! It looks like everyone in the town is here!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would appear that they all wish to see the "Final Story" with their own eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Professor, about this "Final Story"... Why would the Great Witch Bezella show up tonight, of all nights?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I have been wondering the same thing... She has never once shown herself before now. Perhaps the power of the Story is such that even the actions of the Great Witch are subject to its control...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And one more thing... Why in the world would the Storyteller write his own death into the Story?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed... There appear to be quite a few mysteries contained within this "Final Story". Although I suggest we don't dwell on them for the time being.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I agree. First things first, let's find Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Petal">You'd better hide now, 'cause you know you can't win!</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Can too! And I won't hide!</line>
<line speaker="Petal">You'll be crispy bacon in no time! Just accept it!</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Will not! You'll see! I WILL become a knight! And if I say I'll protect you, I'll protect you!</line>
<line speaker="Petal">C'mon, how's a little chicken like you s'posed to protect me from BEZELLA?!</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">JUUUUUST...WAAAAATCH...MEEEEE...!</line>
<line speaker="Petal">I told you, you're wasting your time... Now will you hide already?! Bezella's SO gonna burn you to a crisp!</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">I won't hide... I can do this! See? I brought a bucket of water with me! I'll throw it over her flames!</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">The parade was totally different this time! Inquisitor Darklaw was nowhere to be seen, and Inquisitor Barnham looked so agitated... And not only that, but they said this is going to be the LAST Story! What's to become of us all from here on...?</line>
<line speaker="Tuggit">Oh, what will become of us now?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, look! That's the Storyteller's carriage! So he's here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah! Look over there! It's the Storyteller!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">...And now...the time is upon us... The time of release from the curses of witchcraft and the Story. The legendary Bezella will appear before us, and the Story of the longest night will begin. Prepare yourselves for the dramatic climax!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">There is no reason for sorrow. My Stories are no more than a peek at the caprice and irony of unfolding fate. We are all being carried along on the vast and irresistible sea of chance. I am no more than one person in the sea of people who are here tonight. ...No more...and no less.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This isn't good...it's getting dark already. Remember what the Story said...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">"At the appointed place of ending, as twilight fades to darkness..."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And we still haven't found Espella yet...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? At the top of the tower...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look, Nick! Someone's definitely up there...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Look, everyone! The Great Witch Bezella has finally appeared. The time has arrived... This Story will come to an end.</line>
<line speaker="Man">That must be her... Can it really be...?</line>
<line speaker="Woman">The Great Witch Bezella!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Here and now, my life will surely come to an end. The Great Witch Bezella will be apprehended... and true peace will come to this town.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No, Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But...but...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright, there! Follow me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">So you WERE the Great Witch Bezella after all... A truly terrifying witch who would even attack her own father.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Get up! Get up and stand before us! Great Witch Bezella!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It can't be...Espella... There's no way...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Espella, are you all right? ...Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you okay, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">She seems to be wide awake... But she's not responding.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't get it... What happened here?</line>
<line speaker="Eve">...Meow...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey, it's Eve! Eve, were you with Espella the whole time? Can you tell me what happened here?</line>
<line speaker="Eve">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What did she say, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Nothing...she didn't tell me a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Will you people keep your distance! I can't have you getting close to the Great Witch Bezella! Until the commencement of the final trial, this girl is to be handed over to the Knights of the Inquisition. Take her away!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Sir!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Don't you DARE lay a finger on her!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Surely you must have seen her just now! Tell me, did she or did she not just summon a great big fire dragon?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But...you still can't say for sure that Espella is a witch!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's right! Someone might've knocked her out and brought her here against her will!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">...Hm?! That's ridiculous. We Vigilantes were the first ones at this tower. And when we arrived, this girl was the only person present! Any one of us would swear to it on their honour as a knight.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Things are not always as they might appear. You have yet to investigate the scene of the incident, have you not?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">There's no need! It's obvious beyond a shadow of a doubt what has transpired here. Oi, get a move on! Take that girl away before she regains consciousness!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">But, sir...there seems to be some kind of commotion downstairs...'</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">What?!</line>
<line speaker="???">You take your hands off that young girl! I'm family!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">H-hey, you... Cease! ...?!</line>
<line speaker="Patty">You lot just keep your grubby meathooks off my little Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! B-boss...</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Maya! Phoenix!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Who let this woman up here? Remove her immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">...Sir!</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Don't you lay a hand on me! <cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">*cough* *cough* What is that...*splutter*...white powder?!</line>
<line speaker="Patty">That's my very finest white flour! Be thankful of that, you whippersnapper.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Why you...you impudent...bread-brained baker!</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Go ahead and draw that sword at your own risk, sonny! I'll show you a thing or two. The rolling pin is mightier than the sword!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't you have anything better to do than intimidate defenceless women? You...dork in a tin can!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Wh-what is it with you people...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I understand how you two feel, but may I ask you both to calm down a little?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">P-Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We are the only ones who can discover the truth and save Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The professor's right. We have to keep our cool and carefully plan our next move.</line>
<line speaker="Patty">I know, Phoenix. And to think...the Phoenix I once knew could barely even plan his next loaf of bread.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If you'll excuse us, we must be on our way.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">...Hm?! Now why couldn't you just leave peacefully in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Espella! Espella! I still believe in you, my dear girl.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Take the girl away! ...That means now!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">I'm afraid, sir...that won't exactly...be completely possible at the present time, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">What now?!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">A moment ago, that new recruit got carried away and locked the entrance. Currently no one is able to leave the tower...sir.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Wh-what did you say?! That idiot of a new recruit did WHAT?! We've been ordered to take this girl to the interrogation room as soon as possible! The trial of the Great Witch is tonight! The appropriate arrangements are already under way in the square. We don't have time for this!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">S-sorry, sir! I'll go and hang that new recruit up by his heels!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Pssh... We're leaving now and that's that! Bring that witch here to me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Looks like they took Espella away with them...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That made my blood boil! Having to just stand here and watch her get dragged away like that...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We must bide our time, Luke. Don't worry, the time for action will come.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Although, at present...this place is still in complete turmoil.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Look, there are Vigilantes and knights running all over the place!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That oversized rust bucket said the trial will be held tonight, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, that would seem to be the case... According to the Storyteller's Story, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Honestly, though... who knows what will happen this time?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I simply...cannot comprehend it. Storyteller... Can this really be a suitable ending to the Story you have written? As a father, how can you possibly subject your own daughter to a fate such as this?!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Inquisitor Barnham! We have the Great Witch in custody!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Hmm...you took your time, did you not? How long is it now since the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Yes, sir, sorry, sir! It look longer than expected on account of those incompetent Vigilantes. They've only just handed her over to us.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Your excuses do not interest me. You do realise that according to the Story, the trial of the Great Witch must convene this evening, do you not?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Yes, sir! Arrangements for the setting up of the special outside court have commenced.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I wanted to gain as much information as possible before the proceedings begin. There is little time left, so get going!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Y-yes, sir! You heard the inquisitor, witch! Get moving!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Stop! Do not treat the accused like that.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Yes, sir! Sorry, sir! But, sir, this girl's accused of...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I know very well what she is accused of... But for the time being, that is precisely what she is: "accused". Not "guilty".</line>
<line speaker="Knight">I-Inquisitor Barnham...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">This girl is not a witch until she has been pronounced guilty. Treat her with respect... That is an order!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Y-yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Espella Cantabella... I would like to hear the truth from you.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Are you really...the Great Witch Bezella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...I...I'm...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ Go and prepare for questioning. ...I shall be along shortly!</line>
<line speaker="???">...That won't be necessary.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I-Inquisitor Darklaw! What... What did you just say?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I said, that will not be necessary. You see, this evening...you will not be the one standing in court.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wh-what is the meaning of this?! Who, then? Who will stand in court?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">For the trial of the Great Witch Bezella, surely it is only fitting that the High Inquisitor herself prosecute.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Y-you're not saying...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I'm saying that I will be filling the role of inquisitor in tonight's trial. Is that understood, Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">High Inquisitor... Just what are you planning?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...I'm not sure I quite follow. What are you implying?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I followed after you...and my pursuit led me into a mysterious forest. Upon doing so, I witnessed a most unusual scene... Several mysterious robed figures surrounding a character whom they referred to as the "Great Witch". The "Great Witch" hiding behind that masked exterior...was none other than you, High Inquisitor Darklaw!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">My, my, Inquisitor. How very...interesting. And where, may I ask, is your proof of this?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">P-proof?! Well...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Did you not even remove the mask to confirm the identity of that person?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Well...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I was unable to confirm anything. Thanks to her use of witchcraft, I was robbed of consciousness.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Is that so...? In that case, Barnham, I'm afraid... I will have to treat what you have just said as treason.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">And treason against the High Inquisitor means treason against the Storyteller. You there!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Y-yes, Milady!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Escort Zacharias Barnham to the dungeon for his crime of treason.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Yes, Mi... MILADY?!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">On second thought...he may prove a handful for the likes of you men alone. I shall come along and assist your escort. Now, ready the horses.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Yes, sir! I mean, Milady!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Wait right here, Barnham. We're taking you into immediate custody.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...! I do not believe it... I will not believe it... I cannot believe that Espella Cantabella... is the Great Witch Bezella. Blast! Of all the times...</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Inquisitor Barnham... Please know that it pains me to restrain the great defender of Labyrinthia...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...There is no need to apologise. I am aware that you are only doing your duty.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">B-but, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof, woof, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Constantine! What are you doing here, boy?</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof! Woof, ruff, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ My faithful companion, Constantine. I'm sorry to say...it appears that your master has reached the end of his career.</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof! Ruff, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">A great task has befallen me, but now I shall be unable to complete it. It's such a pity...</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof, woof! Ruff! Woof, woof!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Ugh...this is pitiful... The once-great Inquisitor Barnham... conveying words of remorse to his faithful dog...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">And what, may I ask, was this "great task" of which you spoke?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That's simple...to find the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The "truth"...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Until I met Sir Blue Knight and Sir Dark Hat, the question hadn't occurred to me. Is Espella Cantabella really the Great Witch Bezella? Why would the Storyteller write a Story in which his own daughter is executed? I, Zacharias Barnham, as a defender of this town, must know the truth behind this!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ I'll tell you one thing, Inquisitor Barnham. I'll tell you why you were unable to find the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What is the reason?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">There is one thing which, despite your great ability, you lack.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Something I lack...?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What you lack is...resolve.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">In order to find out the truth, you went to great lengths in following me to the woods. I don't reproach you for that. You felt it was your duty as a knight. But that's also the problem, Inquisitor. Why could you not go to such lengths when it came to doubting the Storyteller himself?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That...that's crazy! It's not right for a knight to question the integrity of his lord and master!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">And so you failed. Your knightly pride was your critical flaw.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Huh...? Critical flaw?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">That tower... the one in which the Storyteller lives... Perhaps the truth you were seeking could have been found in the small room at the very top of that tower.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What...what are you saying...?!</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">In any case...at this stage of the game, it's too late to do anything. So I suggest you assign your unfinished task to that faithful dog of yours...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Arrgh...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Very well then, Zacharias Barnham, it's time to go. From this evening you'll be spending your time in a damp, dark place...deep underground. It might be a good opportunity for you to cool that hot head of yours.</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">...Ruff! Ruff, ruff, woof!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Phew... We finally made it out of that tower.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I second that feeling. For a moment there, I wondered if we'd make it out safely...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's probably not much time until Espella's trial begins. I say we look around for clues, so we at least have something to go on.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, that sounds like a wise suggestion. However, if it's all right with you, I'd like you to take charge of this particular investigation, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-sure, no problem. But...what about you, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Me? Why, there is a place of particular interest that I would like to investigate.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A place you'd like to investigate? Where's that, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Ruff! Woof, woof!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah! Constantine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-whoa! Where the heck did he come from?!</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof! Ruff, ruff, woof!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Constantine looks rather worked up... Could something be the matter with him?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I don't know... I'll ask him and see.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah, good idea, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Ruff...ruff! Woof!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hmm...hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof! Woof! Ruff, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Eh?! No, surely not...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What is it, my boy? You look like you've just seen a ghost!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What did the little guy say?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">He... He said...his master... Inquisitor Barnham has been relieved of his duties!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean...Inquisitor Barnham is no longer "Inquisitor" Barnham...? But why?!</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Ruff, woof...ruff, woof, woof!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Apparently, he's been branded a traitor for treason against the Storyteller.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Barnham...a traitor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">How very peculiar... This has all happened rather too hastily for my liking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If that's true...then who's going to take his place as prosecutor in the trial this evening?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, according to Constantine... that will be High Inquisitor Darklaw herself!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">High Inquisitor Darklaw...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...It would appear this incident has taken a further turn for the dramatic. We would be wise to attend to our respective investigations without further delay.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Just a moment, Professor! It seems Constantine wants to tell us something else...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'd be very interested to hear anything you wish to add, Constantine.</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof! Woof! Ruff, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It appears he'd like to show us the way.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Show us the way? Show us the way to where?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">He, uh...wants to show us the way to... the Storyteller's Tower.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Storyteller's Tower...? Why there?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">According to Constantine... There should be a vital clue up there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A vital clue?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ho ho! This is most fortuitous.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Professor...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It just so happens that when I said there was a place I wished to investigate... that tower is precisely where I meant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! No kidding...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">For the time being, everyone's attention is focused on the town square. So perhaps it might just be possible to enter that tower while it's not being quite so heavily guarded. At least, I presume that may be the case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You may have just found a chink in their armour, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Isn't that tower where Espella used to live when she was a kid? Hmm... What kind of clue do you think could be hiding up there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe the clue lies in Espella's past...</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Ruff! Ruff! Woof, woof!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Constantine says he knows a shortcut... He can lead us straight to the Storyteller's Tower. "Follow me, Sir Top Hat"...he said!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright, I suggest we split up into two groups.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, Professor. Be careful up there!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Don't worry, I shall be sure to return... armed with that vital clue!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We'll be waiting for you! ...In the meantime, we'll make sure we're armed and ready for the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright... Within the Final Story was written the following: "The town, finally freed from the shackles of the Story and witchcraft, will bathe in the morning light of the new dawning day. The new town will be aglow with freedom from the past and fresh hope for the future." If this Story is to have the finale that has been promised... Espella, too, will bathe in the morning light of that new dawning day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm with you on that, Professor. Let's work together to make it happen!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Farewell for now, Mr Wright. Come on, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are, Professor! Come on, Constantine, show us the way!</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">...Woof, woof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. Let's start by investigating the scene of the crime. We've only got a few hours until the trial starts. That doesn't give us much time... Let's go, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure the professor will bring us back something we can work with. Let's be sure to hold up our end of the bargain.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You got it, Nick! ............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's Espella... Her eyes are all funny again, like last time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Like last time...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, like they were back in London. I mean, it's like she's completely spaced out again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Now that you mention it... <thought>...It was almost like she was being controlled by some kind of drug or magic back then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nuh-uh, no way! This is just downright DISGUSTING! We can't let them get away with this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. We're definitely on the same page there, Maya. C'mon, let's get started.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You said it! I'm as serious as a heart attack, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Figures, there's still a ton of people around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, considering what happened, I guess it's only natural. There seem to be fewer knights, though...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Look out!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Make way...make way!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh! Ouuuuuch!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">You wimp! How could you be sent flying by a little bump like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, um...excuse me... <thought>So he knocks me over and I get yelled at? Yeah, that's fair...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I've gotta say, Nick, I think you just set a new record...for the most super-dramatic fall ever!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, come on, Maya. What do you expect when someone in a METAL suit bumps into someone in a CLOTH suit?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">What are you two doing here, anyway? This area is supposed to be off limits to the likes of you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We, um... Well, y'see, we're the ones defending Espella Cantabella.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Oh ho ho! Then you must be the "Sir Blue Knight" that all the town is talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He sure is! Bluest knight in all the land!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's right. I'm the Blue Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Hmm...you look a little GREEN for a knight, if you ask me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...thanks?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Well, feel free to investigate the area. Over in the square they're setting up the special outside court to be used in the upcoming trial. We Vigilantes are spread thin guarding here, so do your best to keep out of our way!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, there he goes. Y'know, Nick...you're becoming quite the celebrity around here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure celebrity is quite the right word. ...Hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's up, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like the Vigilante that ran into me just dropped something.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What is that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like some kind of patrol record for the guards.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Patrol record?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judging by what's written here, it looks like they've been taking turns guarding this bell tower 24/7.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You mean they've been guarding it around the clock? Why would they do that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Beats me. But the important thing here... is the fact that it was under close guard at the time the incident took place.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, right... So I guess it would've been impossible to just stroll in through the front door, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. <thought>Anyway, it might be a good idea to hold on to this for now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So anyway, where were we? ...Oh, right! Off to see the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Better have a look before another "dork in a tin can" shows up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like they've left the crime scene completely untouched.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah...even that flour the boss threw at them is still all over the place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I still can't believe she took on a bunch of fully armed Vigilantes...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">With only a bag of white flour and a rolling pin, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just goes to show how much Patty cares for Espella, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Of course she does! After all, Espella's like family. That's another reason we just HAVE to rescue Espella, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then what are we waiting for? Let's bust out that magnifying glass and get this search on the road!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this...a control panel? I wonder what it's for...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... If it's a control panel, shouldn't there be a button or a lever or something? Wait a sec...what's that? There seems to be some kind of recess here. Looks like something fits inside it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey...nice catch, Maya! <thought>That recess... I've seen something shaped like that before.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What is it, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, it's nothing... Let's keep looking around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this...a control panel? I wonder what it's for...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... If it's a control panel, shouldn't there be a lever or button or something? Wait a sec...what's that? There seems to be some kind of recess here. Looks like something fits inside of it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey...nice catch, Maya! <thought>That recess... I've seen something shaped like that before.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! This shape... It's...Espella's pendant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're right...it IS Espella's pendant! <thought>I knew I'd seen that shape before!</thought> But, why? Why would her pendant fit inside this recess?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't ask me! Spirit channelling, supernatural possession... those are things I know, Nick... Well, seeing as we don't know, there's only one way to find out! Let's slot it in there and see what happens!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, calm down... <thought>I guess there's no harm in trying.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Vigilante:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-who me?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Yes, you! What exactly are you up to?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um... W-we're just...y'know, carrying out our own investigation...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">BAH! You can't fool me! That thing you just picked up... The thing that, even as we speak, you are attempting to conceal in your pocket. What is it?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh...you mean this little thing? It's, uh... Well, I guess you'd call it... a pendant.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's, um...absolutely nothing to do with that whole crazy incident just now! I swear Nick's attorney's badge on it!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">...Enough! I saw it! ALL of it! Every single move... From beginning to end...including just now! That right there is the one piece of evidence I was looking forward to coming back and picking up myself!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">I saw it too!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Me three!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Me four!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">...Now then, hand over that important piece of evidence...NOW!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Uuuuugh, shoot!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nooooo! Espella's pendant...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Snatched away from us, just like that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">I must report this to the High Inquisitor immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Me too! I'll accompany you, Chief!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Me three!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Me four!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There they go with Espella's pendant... And I was totally planning on giving it back to her the next time I saw her... But more than that... I soooo wanted to try fitting the pendant into that recess in the panel!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What now...? No way is that panel just there for decoration... I'd better add it to my items, for future reference.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The recess in this panel... it's the same shape as Espella's pendant.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah...so it is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, why? Why would her pendant fit into this recess?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't ask me! Spirit channelling, supernatural possession... those are things I know, Nick... Well, seeing as we don't know, there's only one way to find out! Let's slot it in there and see what happens!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, calm down... <thought>I guess there's no harm in trying.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Vigilante:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-who me?</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Yes, you! What exactly are you up to?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um... W-we're just...y'know, carrying out our own investigation...</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">BAH! You can't fool me! That thing you just picked up... The thing that, even as we speak, you are attempting to conceal in your pocket. What is it?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh...you mean this little thing? It's, uh... Well, I guess you'd call it... a pendant.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's, um...absolutely nothing to do with that whole crazy incident just now! I swear Nick's attorney's badge on it!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">...Enough! I saw it! ALL of it! Every single move... From beginning to end...including just now! That right there is the one piece of evidence I was looking forward to coming back and picking up myself!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">I saw it too!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Me three!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Me four!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">...Now then, hand over that important piece of evidence...NOW!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Uuuuugh, shoot!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nooooo! Espella's pendant...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Snatched away from us, just like that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">I must report this to the High Inquisitor immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Me too! I'll accompany you, Chief!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Me three!</line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">Me four!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There they go with Espella's pendant... And I was totally planning on giving it back to her the next time I saw her... But more than that... I soooo wanted to try fitting the pendant into that recess in the panel!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What now...? No way is that panel just there for decoration... I'd better add it to my items, for future reference.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder what this panel does... I bet it controls something.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I really wanna know what this recess is for!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's exactly the same shape as Espella's pendant... I bet there's a reason.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! How about we steal it back from those Vigilantes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Maya... I don't think we want to go getting into any more trouble than we are in already.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... I wonder what this is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like a robe to me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A robe...? Say, this reminds me of the robes those weirdos in the Eldwitch Woods were wearing. C'mon, Nick! Try it on, try it on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've got to be kidding! This thing's drenched from all the rain. And besides...it's covered in that flour Patty threw all over the place.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah...I guess you're right. It does look pretty beat up, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And that flour's not coming off easily... it's all stuck to the wet robe.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know...I can't put my finger on it, but there's something weird about this robe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Weird?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Remember when we first arrived here... I could swear there was nothing like this lying around, was there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm...I'm not really sure. <thought>...But I sure don't recall seeing it.</thought> This robe's pretty big. It looks like it would fit someone my size.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess that means it can't be Espella's, since she's small and aerodynamically built, like yours truly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anyway...it may provide a useful clue. Let's make a record of it for now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, get that soggy thing away from me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, boy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at this...it's a pendant. <thought>The leather strap seems to have broken.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait, I know this! This is... It's... Espella's pendant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! I knew I'd seen it somewhere before.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Anyway, we should pick it up before one of those dorks sees it! Come on, Nick...quickly! Just pop it in your pocket!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, okay... I'm on it already...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at this...it's a pendant. <thought>The leather strap seems to have broken.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait, I know this! This is... It's... Espella's pendant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! I knew I'd seen it somewhere before.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Anyway, we should pick it up before one of those dorks sees it! Come on, Nick...quickly! Just pop it in your pocket!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, okay... I'm on it already... Hey... Hold on a sec, Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? What's up, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's something about the shape of this pendant...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Something about its shape...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've seen this shape somewhere recently...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Well...if you say so, Nick! Let's shape up and take another look around. If we're lucky...there might just be some amazing clue waiting to be found!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...I guess there might! <thought>Let's take another look at that recess...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here's the bag of flour Mrs Eclaire used to hit those knights. Looks like it's still all over the place.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Boy, the boss sure is something, huh, Nick? Now THAT'S the power of love!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The bag of flour was brought here after the parade, so it won't really be of any use as evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey...this looks like a floor plan of the tower.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, you're right! But I don't remember seeing it here before...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess the Vigilantes must have been using it for their investigation and left it behind when they hurried off.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">According to this floor plan...there's a bell on the floor above this one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it is a bell tower... It'd be kind of strange if there was no bell.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, but... there's no sign of any ladder leading up to the next level.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Or even a stepladder... <thought>Does that mean the bell can't be rung?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Anyway, Nick...this floor plan could be useful. Hurry up and stash it in your pocket!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya... I hate to think what you have stashed away in that spirit medium's outfit.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's called being decisive, Nick! C'mon! We're doing this for Espella, remember?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, yeah...I hadn't exactly forgotten.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigilante">The preparations of this evening's special outside courtroom have now been completed! Summon the High Inquisitor! ...It is time we prepared for the trial! Each and every citizen shall no doubt wish to bear witness to this evening's trial. Overcrowding is to be anticipated. All officers to their stations! Let's help this final court session find a proud place within Labyrinthia's history!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like we're out of time, Maya. I guess that's the end of this investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You think we'll be all right? We didn't really have time to finish...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We did what we could in the time we had. Let's go... I have a feeling Espella's going to be moved to the defendant's waiting room soon.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............ You know, Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Hm? What?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I've been thinking... It's no accident that you and I found ourselves in Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The reason we're here...is for the trial tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ I know what you mean... I think so too. And I'm sure Professor Layton and Luke feel the same way. I just know they'll bring back a clue or two to save Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah...you're right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That means we've got to give this trial everything we've got, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, Nick! Let's do this thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You bet! We'll do what we do best. We'll fight to the very end...for Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What is it, my boy?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What do you think about what happened tonight?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... On the surface, it certainly did appear that the Storyteller's assailant... could be none other than Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But...surely not!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">However, even if it did seem that way, that does not necessarily make it the truth. And if it transpires that Espella is in fact innocent, then there must be some form of contradiction or proof to support as much.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............ Yes, you're right! I'll bet Mr Wright won't miss even the slightest shred of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright and Maya are investigating the scene of the crime as we speak... We, meanwhile, must search for something to prove Espella's innocence. In doing so, the truth should become evident as a matter of course.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I see! In the time that I've spent with Espella, I've never once doubted her character... There's just no way she could do anything as terrible as what happened in that square. I believe in her, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I know you do, Luke. We are Espella's friends...and as such, we must believe in her.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Too right!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">First, let's make our way through the gate.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Uh-oh! The door's still locked! And there are no knights here to open it.</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof! Woof! Ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What's the matter, Constantine?</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Ruff, ruff, ruff...woof!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's great, thanks! He says there's another way in, which only the knights know about!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's a relief... Could you show us the way, Constantine?</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof!</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Good evening, Mr Layton. It's been a while since we last met.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, indeed, Miss Mystere. But I must say, I'm surprised to be meeting you at a place like this.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">After seeing the Storyteller's parade earlier, I've been unable to simply sit still in the library. But at the same time, wandering around aimlessly doesn't solve anything either. Then again, meeting you like this, Professor, has given some meaning to my wandering. If you'd like to try your hand at any unsolved puzzles or puzzles that you didn't manage to encounter... I will happily show you them now. How about trying a puzzle or two? Solving puzzles can help relieve stress, especially in difficult times such as these.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">How about trying a puzzle or two? Solving puzzles can help relieve stress, especially in difficult times such as these.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's dark over there, so I can't see what's in the water.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Luke, this is not the best moment to be looking for fish in the moat. We must go.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Thankfully, the helpful dog showed us another way in.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">No one's here. Not even anyone to open the gate.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, that's our chance to sneak in! The guards seem to be gone!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Without the Storyteller to protect, they are at a loss as to what they should be doing.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Who'd have thought the Storyteller would come to such an end...? I'm still finding it hard to believe, even now. I mean, what's to become of us?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Hmph, wish I knew! I'm more worried about Inquisitor Barnham. He's being held on suspicion of treason... This whole thing is just one big headache... No matter what, the future ain't looking too bright!</line>
<line speaker="???">Enough of your pathetic whining! You call yourselves knights?!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Oh! Captain!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">The Storyteller's gone... Inquisitor Barnham's gone... And who do you think is suffering the most because of it? The townsfolk, that's who! It's now that they need us the most! We must be there for them, to offer our support!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Yes, sir! That's certainly true, but... with things the way they are, what can we possibly do...?</line>
<line speaker="Captain">...Pitiful! ...Hmm? Over there, isn't that...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would appear even the knights are unsettled, my boy.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What's going to become of Labyrinthia now?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, according to the Final Story, once all this is sorted out, there will be fresh hope for the future. So it's a little early to be losing heart just yet.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I hope you're right... Let's do our best to make it so, Professor! What's this? Someone's coming this way... Isn't that-</line>
<line speaker="Captain">And what are you two doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We're heading for the Storyteller's Tower. There may be something left to uncover, so we're going there now to find out.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Did you say...the Storyteller's Tower?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Uh-oh... I hope this doesn't mean we're about to be surrounded by knights pointing swords at us again...</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof! Woof, ruff, ruff, woof!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">...! Well, if it isn't little Constantine! Oh, I see... This must mean you're working on behalf of Inquisitor Barnham... Well, in that case, the tower is up ahead! You may proceed. In fact, I insist that you proceed. I have a feeling there's some unfinished business that only you can take care of. For all our sakes...go there and fulfil your quest. ...And in doing so, show us all that there is still hope for the future of Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Captain...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Very well. We shan't let you down. Let's go, Luke. The Storyteller's Tower stands right ahead of us.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Look! I can see the tower right over there! But how do we get to it?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I believe this may be where our little friend comes in handy... Wouldn't you say, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Right. Of course!</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof! Woof, woof, ruff! Woof! Ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hmm...I see. You're saying there's a path? He says there's a path leading from behind the Audience Room right over to the Storyteller's Tower!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">One could hardly ask for a better guide.</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof! Woof! Woof!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh, really? He just said: "You've nothing to worry about while I'm here!" And then he added: "You might want to worry about that Sir Blue Knight, though." ............ I hope Mr Wright and Maya were able to come across some clues...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I don't think we need worry too much about them. I'm sure they'll be all right. Wouldn't you agree, my boy?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Of course, Professor! While I was teaming up with Mr Wright, one thing became clear to me... He's definitely someone that will always do his best to protect his friends!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I agree, Luke. He's a fine young lawyer with a heart of gold. I'm quite confident the trial is safe in his capable hands.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Me too! And then there's Maya...always strong and courageous! Not to mention full of energy! She's a bit reckless sometimes...but always with good intent!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We're lucky to have them on our side.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...I'm really glad we met them, aren't you, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, Luke, I'd certainly agree with you there. Both Mr Wright and Miss Fey are friends that can truly be relied upon. But at the same time, High Inquisitor Darklaw will be a most formidable opponent. ...One unlikely to make any careless slips. Which is why we must all do our best and work together.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Including me, right?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Of course. I certainly couldn't do this without you, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Don't worry, Professor! I'll give it everything I've got!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's the spirit, my boy!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow! You don't realise how tall the tower is until you see it up close like this.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It certainly looks ominous in the moonlight.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There's a vital clue waiting for us here... isn't there, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's what I'm counting on, Luke. And it would seem... that Inquisitor Barnham had the same idea.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That would explain why Constantine is helping us...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">So this is the tower in which the Creator resides... The tower that none of the townsfolk, nor even the knights, dare visit.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's surrounded in secrecy, that's for sure. It's a bit like the Eldwitch Woods...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. Those woods are certainly an enigma in themselves.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Not to mention those underground ruins... talk about mysterious places! If the Storyteller really did know everything about Labyrinthia... I'd have liked to have asked him a thing or two about them!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's possible there may be clues related to those places, as well as a number of other matters, waiting for us within that tower. In which case, there could also be any manner of traps or contrivances awaiting us as well. We shall have to be doubly careful from here on in.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Got it, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof! Ruff! Woof, woof!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...You've what? You've completed your mission? He says he's worried about his master and wants to return to him now.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We couldn't have come this far without your fine guidance, Constantine. We can take it from here.</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof, ruff, woof, woof, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Constantine says we're the ones his master chose, so he knows he can leave this quest with us in good faith.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We're honoured, Constantine. Thank you for your help.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yes, thanks a lot! Take care on your way back!</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Inquisitor Barnham loves this town more than anyone and has done his utmost to protect it. Let's bear that in mind too, Luke. We have a responsibility to fight to the end. For him and for everyone else in this town.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm ready if you are, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The tower was built upon this tall cliff side. I can only assume this was the Storyteller's design.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">If that cliff collapses, the whole tower looks like it'll go along with it! ...Are we sure we want to go inside?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks like this bridge is the only way to the tower.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This is quite the long bridge, indeed. I don't see any traps or contrivances here representative of the Storyteller.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Look, Professor! You can see the ocean from up here! We must be at the coast of Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The sea is quite tranquil here. There's not a ship or light for miles.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It seems the mechanisms put in place to protect the tower are still operating.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Does that mean we can't get inside?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">No, I wouldn't say so... This particular mechanism is in the form of a puzzle. If we solve it, perhaps we can enter.</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, you did it!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Doesn't it seem peculiar to you, Luke? To get here we had to make our way beyond the guard post and through the knights' garrison. That would normally be considered sufficient defence against intruders, or so one would imagine.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yeah, I guess you're right... There were several knights around, as well.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And yet, in addition, we found that contrivance in place on the door. It would suggest to me that something of great importance must be contained within.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Let's go on in and find out, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Hm... You're still hanging about here, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes... I had a feeling there was something I'd left unfinished, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Well, if that's the case, why not take the opportunity to solve a puzzle?! We Knights of the Inquisition won't give up, even in a situation as tough as this one! As long as there's a knight standing, we'll be here protecting this town!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Captain">That was some impressive puzzle solving! Tell me, where did you acquire such skill?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Oh, it was nothing. I can solve this kind of puzzle over tea and scones... just as any gentleman can.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Hm... I'm not sure I quite follow... But now's not the time to worry about that. We're doing our best to protect this town. Make sure you do your best too!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Very well. I'll certainly do my best to live up to your expectations.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'll do my best too!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">We're doing our best to protect this town. Make sure you do your best too.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ooh, I can hear the horses in there! I'd like to chat with them.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's a big stable. It just shows how important horses are for getting around here in Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The horses are all in a good mood. They're neighing, "This hay's sooo good!"</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, there's just no one around. It's unnaturally quiet.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The fog has cleared up, so the tower's there for all to see and admire its height!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, let's see if we can reach the top of that tower, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A royal-looking crimson...purple... fuchsia carpet.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This place has not changed in the least since we last saw it.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's so empty without the Storyteller, though.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A mysterious symbol representing the sun and the moon.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The sun and the moon have something in common. They both shine in the sky.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This cannot be a mere decoration. Someone has drawn it here for a reason.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor! I can see the Storyteller's Tower from this window!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We must cross the bridge to access the Storyteller's Tower.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">No lights are on in the tower. No one's home, from the looks of it.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Are there any other puzzles you'd like to give a go?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">That was splendid!</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Any time you wish to try your hand at some puzzles, be sure to come and see me.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Even with your puzzle-solving prowess, I see you couldn't solve this one.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Fear not. I was just testing the waters. I'll be back later with my solution.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Don't give up, Professor! Even on a puzzle as tough as this one!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">We Knights of the Inquisition won't give up, even in a situation as tough as this one! As long as there's a knight standing, we'll be here protecting this town!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This puzzle is quite formidable...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Let's try again, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We'll have to crack the puzzle on the door before we can enter.</line>
</xml>