<xml>
<title>The Fire Witch</title>
<line speaker="Mugger 1">We don't want no fuss, and we don't wanna hurt you, all right?</line>
<line speaker="Mugger 2">Yeah, we just want your money, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Mugger 1">And you'll give it to us, won't you?</line>
<line speaker="Mugger 2">Without any fuss...</line>
<line speaker="???">Ignaize!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-what... What is this place? The room is lit but it's still somehow dark. And the atmosphere feels...heavy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! What are we doing in a place like this...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-how should I know?! We're just a couple of bakers...but I don't think they brought us here to make bread... <thought>Yikes... Is it me or is that guard staring daggers at us right now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...Mr Wright! Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! Espella! What exactly's going on?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm sorry... I was the one who sent for you both...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You...sent for us?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I...I'm being put on trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-wait, what?! What happened?!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I don't know! I just don't understand what's going on... I-I didn't do anything wrong! I couldn't possibly...murder anyone...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">M-murder?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I beg you, Mr Wright! Please, I need your help... Just one more time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? You need MY help? What could I possibly do?! Espella, I'm just a baker... The only thing I know about law is how not to get on the wrong side of it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............... Wait, hold on a sec! Espella... What did you just say? You said you needed Nick's help "just one more time"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"One more time"...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm not quite sure myself... But when the knights came and took me, a vision suddenly appeared in my mind. It was Mr Wright... He was fighting for me...defending me! That brave blue figure... It was clear as day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was..."fighting" for you? N-no way... That's impossible! I mean, it's like I already said... I'm just a baker! I have a hard enough time rolling dough, let alone defending someone in court!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I thought the same thing too, at first. But...I don't think that's quite true. You...and Maya... At some time, somewhere... you helped me. ...You fought for me, as a defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A "defender"...</thought> ............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's wrong, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wish I knew, Maya... But hearing Espella mention a "defender"... I can't help but feel something inside of me just burning at the mention of it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knight">Accused! Defender! It is time. Head forth, you two.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Head forth"...? Um... Where are we going exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">To the courtroom in which today's trial will be taking place...the Chamber of Fire!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ch-Chamber...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">of Fire...?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Make haste! If you are but a moment late, a guilty verdict will be delivered immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaaaaat?! N-no way...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright... I...I'm truly sorry, Mr Wright! I know this is all so sudden... It's a lost cause, isn't it...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......... Well then, let's head inside, Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This overwhelming pressure...it feels so familiar somehow. Almost like déjà vu.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">M-Mr Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's go, Maya. Maybe we'll get a better idea once the trial gets under way.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">......... Aaaaall right! Let's do it to it, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is this heat? It's like an oven in here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I will now pronounce the verdict. This court finds the accused... guilty of being a witch!</line>
<line speaker="Girl">No, I'm no... I'm not a witch! Please! Please, I beg you to reconsider! I'm not...</line>
<line speaker="Man">Witches are to be cast straight into the hellfire!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-so this is the-the Witches' Court...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So? How are you feeling, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......... I'd forgotten what this felt like up until now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The butterflies in my stomach...and tension so thick you could slice it with a knife... All of these feelings... <thought>...These are all feelings that I'm definitely familiar with!</thought> Anyway... We're here to fight for Espella...and get her out of this place!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...That's right!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court is now in session for the trial of Espella Cantabella. ...Defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honour?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yours is a face I have not seen in any past trials... But no matter... Start by stating your name, defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honour! My name is Phoenix Wright, ace baker!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A baker?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I asked him to come, Milord! I want him to represent me. This court dictates that the accused is free to assign a defender of their choosing... Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......... Hmm, very well. At any rate, the result of this trial shall not change...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That aside... I have not yet seen hide nor hair of the inquisitor assigned to this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Inquisitor"... Oh, right. I should've noticed earlier. No one's there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Should the assigned inquisitor fail to appear in court, I will have no choice but to dismiss all charges. He is an inquisitor of high calibre. But if he does not come forward soon... this trial will end, and victory will then be declared in favour of this baker!</line>
<line speaker="???">Anime cutscene</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Knights of the Court, I have but one question for you both... Are you prepared to cross swords?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I, Inquisitor Zacharias Barnham, am indeed prepared to do battle, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Something amiss, baker?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, Your Honour. I just didn't realise we could have swords here in the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It is the way of the Court Knight. A knight must always ensure that he rides with a blade at his side. Now then... State your name, Sir Blue Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh? My name is Phoenix Wright. I'm a baker. <thought>How many times will they make me say it...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">......... A baker?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, quit with the long face! You look miserable!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">No need to waste your breath. This trial will be over before you can utter a single objection.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">For the security of all of Labyrinthia... my blade shall rend your defences swiftly and without mercy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh boy... What's with all this excitement? You'd hardly think this was a courtroom... The crowd doesn't seem very interested in law, that's for sure. It's like they're all just hoping for a guilty verdict...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Inquisitor Barnham, you may begin your opening statement.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...As you wish, Milord. First, let us begin by recounting the events leading up to the murder. ...Is that acceptable, Sir Apprentice Baker?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh... "As you wish"...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The murder occurred this very evening. Yesterday, there was heavy rainfall in the area. Eventually it gave way to sunshine... which came just in time for today's parade. Although a few hours after the parade ended, the rain set in once more.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That must have been when Espella and the others were at the Great Archive...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It continued to rain until just before the incident, which took place on a small path leading to the market. The accused had been out doing some shopping at the market. She returned home on that very same path. And on that forest path, two rogues, named Robbs and Muggs, are said to have accosted the accused. One could assume the accused simply acted in "self-defence".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Robbs and Muggs...those two have appeared in court a number of times in the past.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Two rogues, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">So far, it may appear that the accused was more the "victim". However, the situation soon changed. That's right. The accused, Espella Cantabella... knowingly and mercilessly murdered her two assailants!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Y-yikes... There's that weird excitement again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe we now fully grasp what happened. It is getting late already. ...Let us begin the trial. Inquisitor Barnham, you may now begin.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">As you wish, Milord. The inquisition will now hear eyewitness testimony regarding the night of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Eyewitness testimony", huh...? Looks like this trial is finally getting under way... I can't back down now... I have to fight! But I'm just a simple bread-making baker... living a simple bread-making life... Urgh... This situation is more twisted than a pretzel...and I'm smack in the middle of it. But I have to do this to save Espella! Okay, let's see if I can untwist this testimony and put this thing to bed!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Allow me to welcome you all. Now, would each of you please state your name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">As I already explained, Sir Apprentice Baker, this is the "eyewitness testimony".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, I understand that, but... There are four witnesses!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. This many people inside the courtroom could pose a health and safety issue...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honour... That's, err...not quite what I meant! Witness testimonies are supposed to be done one-by-one... As in, one witness at a time...</line>
<line speaker="Mary">What are you talking about, child? We'd be here all night if we did that!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">That's right, young man. We have witnessed the very hand of fate reach out to us this evening!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Um... Could we hurry this along, perhaps? These flowers won't sell themselves... as much as my boss wishes they would.</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">The path to knighthood is an arduous one, but I remain steadfast in my resolve, as I travel down this long road! I shall not falter! I will be victorious!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Witnesses. Again, state your names and occupations.</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">I am known as Wordsmith. But what is a name? How doth one describe an occupation? Like the bubbling of a babbling brook... I flow gracefully around the rocks and debris that is life, nary a worry in my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right...so I guess that means he's jobless.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mary">My name is Mary. And this darling kid is Snowy.</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaa!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Snowy and I often travel to the edge of town to sell delicious fresh milk. Milk like that doesn't happen overnight! I work my hands to the bone squeezing each drop out...literally!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That sounds pretty frightening...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kira">I'm Kira... I'm a flower seller. If you would all be so kind, feel free to purchase one of my beautiful flowers at any time during the trial. There's no way I'll sell them all by morning. Oh, the life of a flower girl is so hard...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeesh, talk about a hard sell...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightle">My name is Knightle! I aim to join our town's order of knights! I study night and day, though I am still but a mere squire... Joining the Knights of the Inquisition is my life's ambition! And I, Knightle, will do whatever necessary to join!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...So he's jobless, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Honourable witnesses, I ask that you show this court your best when delivering your testimonies. Now, tell us what exactly you all saw on this ill-fated eve!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">The delicious scent of mid-evening dinner permeated the air, and a soft light shone faintly in the distance.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Muggs grabbed the girl by the arm. It looked like he almost pushed her to the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I heard a faint voice cry out. The next moment, those two villainous men burst into flames!</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">There was not a trace of fire to be seen in the area! Without a doubt, "magic" must have been used!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-magic...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Sir Apprentice Baker, you may now begin your interrogation.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I have but one piece of advice. I suggest you pay it heed. Do not waste the court's time by grilling these witnesses over irrelevant nonsense, Sir Apprentice Baker.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Are you all right, Nick? They sure love calling you an apprentice baker, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll be honest with you, Maya, I have no idea how I'm feeling right now. But... I know it's all up to me. As her "defender", Espella's fate is in my hands.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have to believe in her... And I'll need to start believing in myself. I can do this... I believe Espella is innocent... And I'll fight until the end to prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Yeah, that's the spirit! We can do this thing, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">The delicious scent of mid-evening dinner permeated the air, and a soft light shone faintly in the distance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Dinner time. When else would the scent of dinner be in the air, if not dinner time? ...Do you see?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Not so much.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The sun had already set by that time. ...That should be adequate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The sun had already set...?</thought> Um... So, you clearly witnessed what happened tonight, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">I have been dubbed a "witness", thus I must clearly have witnessed something. ...Do you see?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In that case, how much light was there in the immediate area at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Enough to see the nose on my face, but not enough to see the trees ahead. ...Do you see?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, no... That doesn't add up. If the area was completely dark, then you couldn't possibly have "witnessed" anything. ...Do YOU see?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">...! Nevertheless, something caught my eye. It was a most ominous sight. Ominous is what that sight was!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... Okay, I get it. It was "ominous"...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I hate to disappoint you, but there was, in fact, "light" in the area.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Take a look at this. This is a drawing of the crime scene, based on the witnesses' accounts, as penned by the Court Illustrator.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The..."Court Illustrator"...? <thought>I've never heard of that before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Look carefully. This shows what the scene looked like at the time of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...an illustration of the highest quality, as always.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Now then... we have established that by the time the murder occurred, the sun had already set. And so, naturally, the defendant was carrying a fire-lit lantern, as we can see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-a lantern...</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Eureka! Indeed! Yes, that is what I was saying earlier! There was a lantern! A lantern, I say!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, please...you totally forgot...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">To be honest, I did not imagine it would be necessary to present this, but... Milord, here is the lantern in question. This is what was responsible for the light illuminating the area.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. The court accepts this into evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Speaking of which, Inquisitor Barnham. In this drawing... the accused seems to be holding a milk bucket of sorts. What became of this?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That... is a strange case indeed, Milord. That bucket seemingly disappeared from the murder scene.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The milk bucket disappeared, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">There has been talk of wolves living in the nearby forest. It is thought they often make off with the items they find on the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great...wolves that steal your stuff... Remind me to never set foot in that forest.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is great, Nick! We've got new evidence now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, yeah. I guess you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y'know, Nick, you really don't look like just some normal, "run-of-the-mill baker"... I'd say you're more like a... "somewhat articulate run-of-the-mill baker"! I think you might even have a knack for being a defender!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's a clear contradiction somewhere in that testimony, and I'm going to find it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">My word! How many times must I say it? There was a lantern, was there not? 'Twas due to the lantern, I say!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I still think you totally forgot...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick, why don't you try presenting that lantern when you find a contradiction in one of their testimonies?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, that's not a bad idea.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mary">Muggs grabbed the girl by the arm. It looked like he almost pushed her to the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mary">That's right. That man...he grabbed the girl's arm and pulled out a knife. ............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Or...was it Robbs that grabbed the girl and held the knife...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Oh dear. Now, let's see...Muggs was the short one and Robbs was the...no, no! I think it was the other way around... ............ Hmph! Well, it doesn't really matter which was which now, does it?! How am I supposed to keep track of those ruffians?!</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No one was asking you to...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">For the record, Muggs was the short one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mary">That's right. That man...he grabbed the girl's arm and pulled out a knife. ............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Or...was it Robbs that grabbed the girl and had the knife...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Oh dear. Now, let's see...Muggs was the short one and Robbs was the...no, no! I think it was the other way around... ............ Hmph! Well, it doesn't really matter which was which now, does it?!</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's all well and good, but I was kind of just hoping you'd testify about the lantern...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Honourable witnesses, please continue with your testimonies.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I heard a faint voice cry out. The next moment, those two villainous men burst into flames!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Well, it was the accused. It was Espella's voice. No doubt about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, do you know Ms Cantabella?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Y-yeah, everyone knows her. Her name is pretty familiar around here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder why that is...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kira">After hearing her cry, I turned around and that's when I saw it...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The two of them being swallowed up by the flames...you mean.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I have never, ever in my life witnessed another sight so dreadful as that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Well, it was the accused. It was Espella's voice, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And did you get a good look at Ms Cantabella's face?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Yes. I mean, she was carrying that huge lantern, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You're only sure because all the other witnesses just finished saying they saw her with the lantern...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightle">There was not a trace of fire to be seen in the area! Without a doubt, "magic" must have been used!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">What an absurd statement!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Say what...?</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Think about it! The knaves were engulfed in flames, in the blink of an eye! The. Blink. Of. An. Eye! There was not a single trace of any other fire source to be found in the area! Not. A. Trace! Therefore, there is only one true explanation as to what caused that inferno!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And...what would that be? <thought>Let me guess..."magic", right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">There is no "crime" in simply not knowing, but refusing to accept the plain truth? There lies the true "crime", Sir Apprentice Baker!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is quite the "crime" indeed, defender!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...A-anyway...it doesn't matter. I just have to find a contradiction in this testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">No way! Espella can't be a witch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">What an absurd statement!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Say what...?</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Think about it! The knaves were engulfed in flames, in the blink of an eye! The. Blink. Of. An. Eye! There was not a single trace of any other fire source to be found in the area! Not. A. Trace!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>Did I hear that right? I think I just found a contradiction in this testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's do this thing, Nick! Hurry up and present something! Hit 'em with some decisive evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looks like that's it for their testimonies...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, are you feeling okay? You've never, uhh, cross-examined anyone before...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Up until now...my life has been all about baking... Kneading dough, rolling it, baking it... Day after day, the same thing... This trial isn't any different from baking... These witnesses...they're all just kind of like fresh dough!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's our job to roll out the contradictions and bake their testimony into something this court can stomach!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If Espella is innocent, then there has to be a contradiction somewhere in these testimonies. ...And when I find it, I'm really gonna crank up the heat! <thought>First things first... I've got to gather as much information as possible.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Espella was carrying a lantern at the time of the murder... That fact definitely contradicts a certain witness' [sic] testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's right! But... Even if we know what the contradiction is, where do we go from there? I mean, what CAN we do? We're just a couple of bakers, after all...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...No, Maya. I think you're wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know why, but I feel like... I know how to do this. <thought>If you're going to speak up in court, there's only one thing that people will listen to... and that's evidence. I just have to try and present evidence whenever there's a contradiction in one of their testimonies!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, Nick! Let's give their testimonies another listen!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... ...... ............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what is the matter, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Wh-wh-what's with the sudden pointing?! I-I am a soon-to-be member of the honourable Knights of the Inquisition! I accept your challenge! Have at you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You say that no fire was present at the scene of the crime, meaning the defendant must have used magic. Unfortunately for you, that is not the case.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...What do you mean, Sir Apprentice Baker?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What I mean is that the defendant was, in fact, carrying a lantern. ...A lantern containing fire! Those two "rogues" were actually burned by the flame that was inside that lantern... That is the only logical explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">My, what a startling conclusion you've come to, Sir Apprentice Baker.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">"The only logical explanation"...? Do you agree with this statement, honourable witnesses?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">It is presumptuous for a man that knows nothing to claim that he knows something about which he really knows nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">...Besides, how could one teeny-tiny flame be strong enough to set them both ablaze like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Uh.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">There were two of them. How could that flame engulf them so fast?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Furthermore! If they did burn as you claim they did, do you mean to suggest that they were soaked in oil or something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Well, Sir Blue Knight? It would seem you have bitten off more than you can chew.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaarggggh! <thought>I definitely didn't see that coming...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What say you, Milord? Do you have any thoughts on the proceedings thus far?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ Given the testimony as we have heard it... this court has come to its conclusion. 'Twas a truly gruesome and merciless act. An act for which only one thing could be held responsible... The nefarious crime of magic!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Is there something you have forgotten to mention, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not exactly, Your Honour. It's just that... I mean... You just said..."magic"... That can't be right, can it?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What are you suggesting, Sir Apprentice Baker? Witches use magic, which in turn brings about disaster. ...Such is the way of this world, is it not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-well, yeah... <thought>That may seem to be the case... but no way is that actually possible!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court finds Espella Cantabella, the accused, charged with being a witch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Espella...a witch...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">A witch's existence in this world is a crime in itself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The ability to use and control magic is a criminal offence, indeed... As such, any witch found practising magic will be sentenced to death by fire!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">N-no! You're wrong! I'm not a witch!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Sir Apprentice Baker, I do not envy your current predicament. Milord! Hand down your guilty verdict against this witch immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Put a sock in it, bread boy! We all heard her cast the spell!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">That's right! Snowy and I heard it! Isn't that right, precious? We heard that incantation quite clearly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Uh.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">That frightening voice... There's no mistaking it! It was Espella's voice!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">These ears do not lie! I clearly heard an incantation most sinister! "Ignaize", it went!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Incantation"?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ignaize...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's no good! I just can't wrap my head around this topsy-turvy, other-worldly court.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Well then, it would seem the defence has no further objections.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...It appears so. The court finds the use of magic at the time of the murder to be an undeniable fact. Furthermore, the honourable witnesses have stated that they each heard an incantation being recited. The court finds no reason to delay its verdict any longer.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! We have to do something...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I know! But... What exactly can we say? Here, in this world, our sense of logic is completely useless!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court is ready to hand down its verdict for the case of Espella Cantabella!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What-what is the meaning of this intrusion?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I have something I believe will be of use to the defence... A weapon, of sorts.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-that's...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...The Grand Grimoire. All of this world's magic is contained within its pages. Without it, this trial cannot reach a satisfactory conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Grand...Grimoire...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We meet again, Mr Wright. Well now, it seems things are already afoot here. Although the real contest begins now. ...Are you fully prepared?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So...are you here to help us?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Of course! The professor always helps people in trouble! "It is the duty of every gentleman", right, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Professor...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...There is a saying that I find quite useful in situations such as this. "There is a time for words and a time for action."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-right...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You have been working as a baker in this town up until now, have you not? I must say, I am a little mystified. I'd have expected you to be more familiar with this world and its "system" of magic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, yeah... How can I put this... I guess that's not quite the full story.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Is that so...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I kind of had an epiphany just now. I remembered all sorts of things... Like how I'm not actually a baker... And, well...how magic can't really exist!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ Then it would seem I was correct about you, Mr Wright. You are not, in fact, a citizen of this town... Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Right. At least, it seems that way.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">However, for now, we have no option but to accept this world and its rules as a reality. Without first understanding those rules, I'm afraid you will not be able to save Miss Cantabella.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-but...things like magic only exist in fairy tales and make-believe!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm afraid, Mr Wright, it would seem magic does in fact "exist" in this world. Such a truth cannot be denied.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed...that is why the Grand Grimoire is a weapon well suited for this witch trial. At the moment, you are tantamount to a knight without a sword.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I feel more like an attorney without a chance, actually...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right then, Mr Wright! I'll explain how the Grand Grimoire works! Have a look at the Touch Screen! There, you'll see the Grand Grimoire button! Touching the Grand Grimoire button will open up the Grand Grimoire!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You will be able to present spells from the Grand Grimoire in much the same way you would present evidence. This book will surely be a most important asset for us in this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh, that reminds me. I've gone ahead and bookmarked the spell Ignaize for you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ignaize... That's the magic spell all of the witnesses said they heard, right? Nick, you should take a look at that spell!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All I have to do is touch the Grand Grimoire button, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defender has been given more than enough time. It would seem this trial has reached its end.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Is that understood, Sir Apprentice Baker? This case is quite straightforward, with very little room for doubt. The witnesses' testimony, coupled with the illustration of the time of the murder, makes it quite clear what must have occurred. This murder was the result of magic... And furthermore, the caster of said magic was none other than the accused. That, Sir Apprentice Baker, is the truth! Best you go back to baking, for I believe your days in the courtroom have crumbled!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Is everything okay, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... It would seem that photographs do not exist in this world.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Photos don't...exist? <thought>I guess that makes sense... "ye olde" time period and all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">The sketch drawn by the Court Illustrator... Therein lies your final chance, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My...final chance...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I understand the witnesses have already finished their testimony... However... If you could perhaps find a clear contradiction within this illustration...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's another contradiction...? In that case, there's still hope that I can turn this around...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">M-Mr Wright! You have to hurry! Look! The judge... He looks ready to deliver his verdict any second now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is it. This is my last chance... What...should I do?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's no good! I've pretty much run out of evidence! I just can't see another contradiction anywhere...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Just a moment, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Isn't the Grand Grimoire a new piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ah! <thought>Now that you mention it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright, I explained to you how to view the Grand Grimoire, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...That's right, he did. Okay! I can't give up just yet!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One second, Your Honour. The defence requests permission to have another look at the court illustration. I think...there might be a contradiction in there!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's just one thing you've overlooked. A piece of evidence within this book...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-the Grand Grimoire...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Absurd! I overlooked something...? You are the defender here. You should have examined the tome earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're right, I should have... But unfortunately, I was nothing but a simple baker until just now.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ Interesting. You've certainly begun to show your true colours, Sir Blue Knight. Let us see what type of knight you truly are. Have at you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defender will now show us this supposed contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The court illustration...and the Grand Grimoire... Somewhere there's a contradiction between those two, and I've got to find it! This is my last chance!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender, use this magnifying glass to locate the point of relevance. Then reveal to the court the location of this "contradiction"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The hand of the accused? She appears to be holding a milk bucket...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, but...that milk bucket was said to have vanished from the crime scene! It's quite possible...that there's an important reason behind its disappearance!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Inquisitor Barnham, what are your thoughts on this?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It is quite mysterious indeed, Milord. However, the inquisition believes it bears no relation to this case. Forest wolves simply came and stole the bucket... Nothing more.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Let us not dwell on the milk bucket for the time being, Mr Wright. Rather, we should first consider any information within the Grand Grimoire that might lead us to a contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Our new piece of evidence... Maybe I should have another look at it. I just have to touch the Grand Grimoire button!</thought> My apologies, Your Honour. Please, give me one more chance.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Granted. But be warned... You're running out of chances, defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Is this correct? Inquisitor Barnham, your thoughts?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">There is nothing to say, Milord. I believe I may have greatly overestimated you, Sir Blue Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You clearly are more baker than defender. It is best you head back to the bakery!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Darn it! Looks like my train of thought was a little off...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">I would say that your train of thought was very off, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My apologies, Your Honour. Please, give me one more chance.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Granted. But be warned... You're running out of chances, defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The contradiction is...right here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The hand of the accused? She seems to be holding a lantern...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...What is your point?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to this tome, using the spell Ignaize... requires the use of the witch's sceptre, as well as an incantation...isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Correct. For witches to use magic, they must be in possession of a witch's sceptre, also known as a Talea Magica.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If that's the case, then there's one thing that doesn't add up. Take another look at Ms Cantabella's hands. Tell me, do you see the witch's sceptre in either of her hands?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There we go! Let's see you point that sword at me now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">You did it, Mr Wright! But...wasn't that contradiction just a little too obvious?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ You may be right, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would certainly appear... that the good inquisitor is taking this particular oversight rather too well.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That is correct, Sir Apprentice Baker. But you should not underestimate me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">This is perhaps your first time seeing this item, is it not? Right here is the very sceptre you mention. One of the witnesses found it tossed in the shrubbery on the side of the path.</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Aha! Yes! Indeed, that was I! I located it! My feet found themselves ensnared in the blasted thing, and it sent me flying through the air!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Somehow...I'm not surprised to hear you fell, gramps.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... This sceptre does seem to carry a most sinister air...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Indeed, Milord. However, this sceptre will only work while in the hands of a witch, with the incantation being said aloud.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww... That's too bad... I wanted to try lighting some stuff on fire.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Please don't look at ME when you say that.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You see, there are two magic gems set in this sceptre.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Magic gems... <thought>Looks like a red gem and a white gem...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">These gems each contain a particular magic spell. By simply looking at these magic gems, one can easily determine which magic spell can be used.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Quick, look at this page!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is that...the red magic gem?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Indeed. The red gem you see here is the spell Ignaize. And if you look carefully... you should notice that this sceptre also has one more spell that can be used.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One more spell... <thought>That must be the white gem!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright, I've found it! Here's the spell for the white magic gem!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Causes anything the caster touches to vanish from sight"... Urgh!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Hmph. I see you managed to work it out in that crusty head of yours.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-that's just... It can't be! The reason the witch's sceptre couldn't be seen is because the magic spell Dimere had made it disappear...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That's right. In other words... The accused conjured a cowardly spell to camouflage her own use of magic!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no... Nooooooo waaaaaaaaaaaay!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! Inquisitor Barnham, please submit the sceptre into evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is there a problem, Sir Baker?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, I understand this is a witch's sceptre. However! Whether or not the sceptre was in Ms Cantabella's possession has not yet been proven!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What are you talking about, Sir Apprentice Baker?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't it obvious? ...I'm talking about fingerprints. Supposing Ms Cantabella did in fact handle this witch's sceptre, then her fingerprints should still be on it!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-what's with this silence...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You said..."fingerprints"? Inquisitor Barnham, tell me... Just what is this baker blabbering about?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I haven't the slightest clue, Milord. It is the baker's first time in court, after all...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm afraid it's no use, Mr Wright. In this world, it would seem the concept of fingerprinting does not yet exist.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaaaaaaaaat?! <thought>I...I can't believe it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">As I have said already, best you head back to the bakery, lest you continue to serve this court more of your half-baked ideas.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>They're about as half-baked as your terrible puns, Barnham...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Forensic science does not exist here... Instead, this is a world in which "witches" and "magic" are accepted as fact. ...Truly fascinating.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What the heck?! There are just...way too many things I don't know about this world!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright. I believe you may be able to take these things you don't know and use them to your advantage.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The inquisition believes there is no room for debate on this matter. The accused clearly attempted to conceal her magic. Better luck next time, Sir Apprentice Baker. Mayhap your next loaf will not leave such a bitter taste in our mouths. Now then, Milord! I believe it is time. I ask that you render your unwavering verdict!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What's that...? Who might you be?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">My name is Hershel Layton. I am a friend of the accused. Inquisitor Barnham, please allow me to confirm what you believe happened on the night of the crime. You claim the witch's sceptre was made to disappear through the use of magic, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Indeed. Through the magic spell Dimere.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If possible, would you mind providing proof of this particular claim?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You claim the sceptre was not seen... Indeed, that is one possibility. However, a wise man must always consider every possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... What say you, Inquisitor Barnham? Can the inquisition fulfil the request presented by the gentleman with the...unusual hat?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ The inquisition cannot honour this request for proof. If you are asserting that the accused is not a witch, then the burden of proof lies at the feet of the defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>C'mon! It's the prosecu- ...err, inquisition's job to prove that a crime was committed!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">As I thought... Indeed, it would appear the accepted method of thinking in this world differs greatly from our own.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">How regrettable, Sir Apprentice Baker... and you, Sir Dark Hat.</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith/Mary/Kira/Knightle">Knightle:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Would anyone care to purchase any pre-testimony flowers? I've got a lovely array of "bewitching" lilies.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Snowy and I will not be dismissed so easily! We came here to expose the identity of this witch! Isn't that right, precious?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">A witch's sceptre, you say? Yes, yes! I know of such a sceptre! Allow me to elucidate the matter!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What do you think, Inquisitor Barnham? Your witnesses appear to have something to say on the subject.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ Very well. Most honourable witnesses, I grant your request to testify once more! Tell the court all you know regarding this Talea Magica!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ulp... Well, we've somehow managed to keep the trial going. I owe you one, "Sir Dark Hat"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Please, Mr Wright, "Mr Layton" will suffice for the time being.</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">When I saw her, the witch was carrying a large milk bucket in one hand and a lantern in the other...</line>
<line speaker="Mary">The girl had the lantern hanging from her wrist... Her hand was contorted in a strange way!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I got a good look at her hand, and it looked for certain that she was gripping something.</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">The witch was holding a sceptre in her right hand! She did not drop it once before she was apprehended!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. The accused's hand was "contorted in a strange way"... I do believe this is quite an important piece of testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I saw it! I most certainly saw it! She was holding an invisible sceptre!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">We saw it too! It was the girl up there! Without a doubt!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">I, as well. These old eyes don't see as well as they once did, but I witnessed the hazy, blurry form of the accused quite clearly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Don't tell the court you're blind!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightle">My eyesight is as sharp as the edge of my trusty blade!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm, a toy sword... How fascinating... Although I wonder if he understands the implications of that analogy on his vision...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Sir Baker, you may proceed with your interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mr Layton's given me another chance... I can't let it go to waste!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightle">When I saw her, the witch was carrying a large milk bucket in one hand and a lantern in the other...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">There is no mistaking it! That fiendishly fiendish form, with its case darker than the darkest of nights... That was the lantern!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's just a normal lantern...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... What is this? It would seem the glass is shattered. And there seems to be a sizeable amount of mud stuck to it.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">On closer inspection, it appears mud has stuck to the broken sections of glass. ...Most intriguing.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So then...when exactly did the lantern get mud all over it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By the way, witness. You also saw a milk bucket, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Indeed! I would bet my sword on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And yet that milk bucket mysteriously vanished from the scene of the crime...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">How many times must I say it, Sir Apprentice Baker? The problem is the black lantern.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">The girl had the lantern hanging from her wrist... Her hand was contorted in a strange way!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Of course we're sure! If that wasn't it, then how else would the girl manage to hold her invisible sceptre?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ma'am, please...just testify about what you actually saw.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Hmph! We just said that's what we saw! Isn't that right, Snowy?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Indeed. A handle as wide as this could be easily hung from the accused's small wrist.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Yes, that's what we were telling you! Isn't that right, Mummy's little snowball?</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's no good. They're all bent on assuming Espella was holding that sceptre...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">It seems it may be best not to pursue this particular line of questioning any further.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, that's just super...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kira">I got a good look at her hand, and it looked for certain that she was gripping something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">It was... Hm, that's right. It was something...cane-like. What was it called? A "witch's sceptre"? ...Yes, it was definitely that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Witness. This "cane-like" object... Was it, perhaps, roughly this size?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Oh! Why, yes! It was exactly that size!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's no good. They're all bent on assuming Espella was holding that sceptre...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">It seems it may be best not to pursue this particular line of questioning any further.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, that's just super...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">The witch was holding a sceptre in her right hand! She did not drop it once before she was apprehended!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Well now, that's common sense, boy! One cannot see what is not there to be seen!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In that case, there was also no way you could tell whether or not she might have dropped the sceptre!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">W-well, these old eyes of mine honed in on her hand, like a hawk, until they couldn't see straight! The young lady was most certainly holding an invisible sceptre in her right hand, while at the same time also carrying the lantern! Or do you perhaps possess some piece of evidence to suggest that she dropped the sceptre?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There hasn't been any evidence so far to suggest Espella WAS holding the sceptre...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Evidence suggesting the sceptre was dropped? Now, that is an interesting idea.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If Espella did not have the sceptre in her hand, it would have been impossible for her to have used any magic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, yeah, that's true...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm, I don't suppose... Might there be a piece of evidence that could prove this? Something to prove that Espella was not holding the sceptre at the time of the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>In other words, evidence to show that even if Espella had been holding the sceptre, she would have dropped it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Is everything all right, Mr Wright? The truth about what happened in that brief instant...will likely decide Espella's fate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to do everything I can to find a contradiction in these testimonies... Guess I should take another look at the Court Record...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is a high probability...that Ms Cantabella was not holding the sceptre. But if, for the sake of argument, she had been holding it...she would undoubtedly have dropped it at the time of the incident!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What I mean, Inquisitor Barnham, is that this lantern proves the defendant was not holding the sceptre!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The rain had ended just as the murder was taking place. That would make the path fairly muddy, don't you agree? When the thieves grabbed Ms Cantabella by the arm...the lantern must have fallen into the mud.</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">The lantern...</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Fell into the mud...</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Why, of course. That makes sense, doesn't it, my little Snowy-wowy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, what do you say, Inquisitor Barnham? If she was holding the sceptre at that time, that would mean that when she dropped the lantern, the sceptre would have fallen along with it!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Nngh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-that... Just what is this...?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Kira:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Everyone! Please, listen! Didn't we all just stand here and explain to the court what we clearly saw? It's a lantern! So what? What's so special about it?! Explain it to me so I can understand!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-so that you can...understand...? Well, I mean, it's pretty obvious just by looking at it...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Wh-what is it, Mr Layton?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There is something about this witness...</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Miss Kira, was it? Tell me, Miss Kira... How good is your eyesight, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Huh...?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">As you just heard Mr Wright explain, the answer to your query is quite obvious at a glance. Tell me, are you able to see the mud present on this lantern?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Mud...? What mud? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Your Honour, did you hear that just now?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm? Ah...yes, indeed. Wh-what does it mean...exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It means that Miss Kira's poor eyesight is the reason she cannot see the mud present on this lantern. In other words, the validity of Miss Kira's testimony is questionable, at best.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Urk... Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court! Wh-what is the meaning of this?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...What say you in your defence, witness? I highly recommend you give us nothing but the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I-I'm sorry, Inquisitor Barnham! I-it's true. I need to wear glasses...all the time, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-you need to wear glasses?!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Ah ha! Now that you mention it, I did notice something odd about you today.</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Oho! I thought you looked familiar! Gone is the mist that clouded my mind! In its place...clarity.</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Fair maiden, a pair of spectacles are as valuable as a shield to a knight. Make haste and procure another pair!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now then, Ms Kira, tell me... At the time of the incident, were you wearing your glasses?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ No. No, I was not wearing them. The truth is, I... I lost my glasses a couple of days ago...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You lost them...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So, her glasses were missing during the time of the incident...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright, might I recommend that you keep note of this fact. It could prove useful later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Am I to believe there is nothing left to prove on this matter? At the time of the murder, the accused did not have a witch's sceptre in her possession...</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Mary:</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">That's right! My trusty sword of justice shall cut through this witch's treacherous lies!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I...may have lost my glasses, but I haven't lost my will to testify!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Eureka! I remember now! Old age has a way of sneaking up on me. I'm sure you must understand!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, I understand... I understand you're all completely ridiculous!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would seem we have not yet arrived at a clear-cut verdict... ...Witnesses, you may once again begin to testify to the court. Tell us about the sceptre and how it was used in the detestable display of witchcraft that you all witnessed tonight!</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">The girl was not holding the sceptre in the same hand as the lantern... Which means, it must have been in her other hand!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">The accused is holding a milk bucket in the court illustration. Who's to say she wasn't also holding the sceptre in that hand?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">That milk bucket is lighter than it looks. Even Snowy could carry it! So she could have easily held the sceptre as well.</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">I did not see this milk bucket. Everything felt like an illusion...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The sceptre was in her other hand, you say? Indeed, such a proposal is feasible. ...Sir Baker.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes, Your Honour!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is the strangest thing... The longer this trial goes on... the more you begin to resemble a legitimate defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, no matter. Defender, you may begin your interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">The girl was not holding the sceptre in the same hand as the lantern... Which means, it must have been in her other hand!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Alas, magic's vile embrace hid the sceptre from my sight, so I did not see it per se. ...However! Through my years of knightly training, I have learned to see through such cunning trickery!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is...that so?</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">For example! This morning I found myself unable to locate the whereabouts of my trusty blade. Its location was a mystery! So I tried my hardest to think and remember where I would have kept it last... And before long... BEHOLD! It transpired I was carrying my trusty blade in its scabbard all along! Life is riddled with such trickery!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Would you say life is "riddled with trickery", Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Only if we're talking about my life, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">The accused is holding a milk bucket in the court illustration. Who's to say she wasn't also holding the sceptre in that hand?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You say "speculation"... I say it's a fact. There's just no way Espella could have been holding that thing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">As expected, this testimony is filled with nothing but assumptions and conjecture.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr Layton...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You know, Mr Wright, there does not appear to be any usable evidence present in the court illustration.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I agree. It does look that way... <thought>The milk bucket ended up disappearing from the scene... Could that actually be an important piece of evidence in itself...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Mary">That milk bucket is lighter than it looks. Even Snowy could carry it! So she could have easily held the sceptre as well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Wh-what is it now? Snowy and I don't have all night, you know! Come on then, out with it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I just have one question regarding your testimony. How exactly did you know... that the bucket Ms Cantabella was carrying was "light enough for Snowy to carry"...?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Huh?! I-I...well... You see, the girl always uses the same bucket whenever she comes to buy milk from us. Naturally, I would have seen that bucket countless times before!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You've "seen it countless times before"? That doesn't answer my question. You specifically said that bucket is "lighter than it looks"... Ms Mary, at some point tonight you must have held that bucket yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Ulp...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now then, please enlighten us as to exactly when you got your hands on the bucket!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">............ ............ ............ ...It's true. By that time, Robbs and Muggs had already been burnt to ash... And then... I noticed the milk in that bucket that the girl had been holding in her hand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The...m-milk...?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Then, when those two went up in a blaze, Snowy and I made a dash for the bucket! As the girl stood there looking confused, we took the milk from her to make sure it was okay.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">U-unbelievable... Witness, you...</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Ah! Well, it was just so wasteful! The thought of all that disgusting ash falling into such precious milk. I felt I just had to protect the milk, so I took the bucket back to the farm with me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Madam, do you mean to tell the court that you took evidence from a crime scene back home with you...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...That explains why we were unable to locate the milk bucket at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Oh, my! Y-you're scaring poor Snowy! Here! I brought the bucket with me, anyway! See? I didn't even tamper with the milk.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm sure you didn't!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court shall accept this milk bucket... as evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like that's one more piece of evidence for us...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, will the gentleman with the impressive beard proceed with his testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Why, of course. There is nothing more important to us than selling the freshest milk in town. Surely you must understand. If someone had dropped dough instead, wouldn't you want to take it back home?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-who in their right mind would be carrying pieces of raw dough with them...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Witness, I ask you don't make a habit of stealing from crime scenes... For your own safety.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">W-w-w-we apologise, sir! Please! It was all Snowy's fault!</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Talk about having a scapegoat...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">I did not see this milk bucket. Everything felt like an illusion...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Indeed. Naturally, there was no way of me noticing the witch before the crime occurred. My mind was placid as the most placid of... placid lakes... But like the early bird on its morning hunt for that elusive worm...my senses remained vigilant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You do realise the other witnesses have all testified to having seen Ms Cantabella carrying that bucket, though...?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">And...? When you have journeyed as far as I have through life, you find all is but an illusion. That is, except for Lord Storyteller, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The witnesses' testimonies are relying on pure speculation this time... That means there has to be a hole in there somewhere!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">We've got Inquisitor Barnham sweating bullets in that armour of his! I'd say he's about ready to throw it all off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not even going to begin to tell you what's wrong with that statement, Maya...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's it for the testimony... Still, something is bound to be there. I can't believe Mary took the bucket home with her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Miss Mary must be one of those thieving "forest wolves" we've been hearing about!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Let us hope she doesn't eat like a wolf as well, Luke. For her Snowy's sake.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've got this new piece of evidence... but the question is, how can I use it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Y'know, looking at this milk bucket now... It does look sort of different from the sketch, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It might be a good idea to get a nice, good look at the actual milk bucket.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All of your testimonies have come to the same conclusion. The sceptre was not in her right hand with the lantern. Therefore, it must have been in her other hand, that was holding the bucket. However, that's not it. Not by a long shot.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Contrary to what one of the witnesses stated, the milk bucket was in fact at the crime scene. And you'll also notice something about this bucket... Take another look at the court illustration. Something about the bucket seems a bit... odd, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Ngh! Th-that...cannot be!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, but it is. This particular milk bucket has two pieces of wood on either side of the handle. If you were to try and hold both the sceptre and this bucket... Well, let's just say that'd be a challenge. To put it simply... there is no way anyone could hold both the bucket and the sceptre at once!</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Wh-whaaaaaaaa?!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Th-that must mean...clearly you have the wrong bucket!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">We never lie when it comes to milk! That is the very bucket I took!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looks like the witnesses are as surprised about this as Barnham...</thought> The defendant couldn't have been able to hold the bucket and the sceptre at once. Also...we have already established that she was not holding a sceptre in her right hand. Therefore... the defendant, Ms Espella Cantabella... was not holding a witch's sceptre at any point during the incident!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! I said order! J-just what... What is the meaning of this?! In all my days as judge of this court, I have never heard such an argument! These are but a paltry set of words... And yet, they ring with such remarkable strength!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Your Honour. What you just heard...was logic.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">L-logic...you say...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...It would seem that the concept of logic does not exist in this world.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right! Then let's take this chance to knock their case down a peg or two!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm worried if we keep this up we'll all be joining Espella in a one-way trip to the flames...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Sir Blue Knight, there appears to be a hole in this..."logic" of yours.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A "hole"...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">According to the earlier testimony, it was believed the accused had the lantern hanging from her wrist by the handle. However, she supposedly dropped it, hence it being covered in mud.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">While that may be true... it does not necessarily mean the accused was therefore unable to use magic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It is merely a question of when she dropped the witch's sceptre...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what do you mean, Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It is very simple, Milord. The accused, while first holding the lantern and the witch's sceptre, cast her magic. Then, she dropped both the lantern and the sceptre.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah... The witch's sceptre was dropped after the spell was cast... O-of course...yes, that must be it!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...What say you? Sir Blue Knight? That is but a taste of the knightly knowledge of the Inquisition!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That inquisitor...isn't quite what he first appeared.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah. Sure seems that way. Just a moment ago it seemed like he'd never even heard of logical debate. Now he's suddenly USING it against us... <thought>This guy is no joke, that's for sure...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Now then, most honourable witnesses! I ask that you lend us your aid once more.</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">...!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...I request that you all testify to the court once more. Tell us which occurred first: the dropping of the lantern, or the casting of the spell...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witnesses, you may begin your testimonies! Tell this court in your own words about the sequence of events which transpired tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Of course! The lantern fell to the ground after the incantation of "Ignaize"! SPLOOSH!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">I'm as sure as Snowy is white. I made certain to keep my eyes peeled on that milk bucket, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Besides, how can you be sure the lantern fell just because it has a little mud on it?</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">These eyes do not lie! I saw the lantern in the accused's hand when the incantation was uttered!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Figures... Their testimonies are all over the place now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">These four testimonies... They are most interesting. The witnesses all saw the same thing... And yet... people's memories are evidently quite fickle. They can never be a truly reliable source.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well then, Professor! With enough poking and prodding, I bet we can really cause their testimonies to crumble!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Of course. We need to exploit their "fickle memories" to turn this thing around!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">We've got this, Nick! We'll press 'em so hard, they won't even remember what they had for breakfast!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't even remember what I had for breakfast...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ Now, Sir Baker, you may begin your interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Of course! The lantern fell to the ground after the incantation of "Ignaize"! SPLOOSH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">I say, I am positively positive that I am positive! I heard her voice and then... SPLOOSH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That "sploosh"...was that the sound of the lantern hitting the ground?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Indeed! But of course! ...Do you see?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, if you look at the lantern, you'll notice that the glass is shattered. You specifically said you heard a "sploosh". Shouldn't you have heard the sound of the glass shattering when it hit the ground?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">The sound of glass shattering...? No, I'm afraid I fail to catch your drift. I was present in an area a bit farther away from the crime scene, you see. I have no recollection of hearing such a sound!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No recollection...?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">...Precisely so. I'll have you know, I can easily hear a dog barking across town! Do not underestimate my hearing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wasn't! Relax, grandpa!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">There is nothing of interest in this testimony. ...Will the witness with the goat please proceed with her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Huh?! Ah, right...you mean us. Y-you startled us! Didn't he, Snowy?!</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">I say, I am positively positive that I am positive! I heard her voice and then... SPLOOSH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That "sploosh"...was that the sound of the lantern hitting the ground?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Indeed! But of course! ...Do you see?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, if you look at the lantern, you'll notice that the glass is shattered. You specifically said you heard a "sploosh". Shouldn't you have heard the sound of the glass shattering when it hit the ground?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">The sound of glass shattering...? No, I'm afraid I fail to catch your drift.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? But...old greybeard didn't say anything weird.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, it's not the old guy that said something weird. ...It's the person next to him.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-next to him...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah! Look there, Professor! The goat lady... she looks really deep in thought!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would seem... she has noticed something odd in this elderly gentleman's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! Th-that's right... These cross-examinations...have four witnesses. Hey, Nick, it looks like...we're not the only ones paying attention to these testimonies!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You're right. Which means...if they're all listening to each other's testimonies...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Correct, Mr Wright. Each witness is fully aware of themselves and their own actions when in the middle of their own testimonies. However... It is while listening to the testimonies of others that the witnesses may sometimes reveal the most valuable information.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I see. It's habitual. They can't tell they're doing it, but I can! And I'm going to use it to turn the tide back in our favour!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">In fact... I do believe I may have spotted our first opening in which to test this new technique. Mr Wright, could I draw your attention to the Touch Screen?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Touch Screen...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Sliding the magnifying glass during a witness' [sic] testimony will allow you to shift your focus across to another witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right. So the important thing here... isn't the witness that's in mid-testimony. It's the other three witnesses listening. It's just a matter of catching them off guard and questioning them!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you waiting for, Nick? Let's give it a shot! How about we try questioning the goat lady next to old greybeard!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Okay. All I have to do is slide the magnifying glass over to that witness!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">The sound of glass shattering...? No, I'm afraid I fail to catch your drift. I was present in an area a bit farther away from the crime scene, you see. I have no recollection of hearing such a sound!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No recollection...?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">...Precisely so. I'll have you know, I can easily hear a dog barking across town! Do not underestimate my hearing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wasn't! Relax, grandpa!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">There is nothing of interest in this testimony. ...Will the witness with the goat please proceed with her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Huh?! Ah, right...you mean us. Y-you startled us! Didn't he, Snowy?!</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">I say, I am positively positive that I am positive! I heard her voice and then... SPLOOSH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That "sploosh"...was that the sound of the lantern hitting the ground?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Indeed! But of course! ...Do you see?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, if you look at the lantern, you'll notice that the glass is shattered. You specifically said you heard a "sploosh". Shouldn't you have heard the sound of the glass shattering when it hit the ground?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">The sound of glass shattering...? No, I'm afraid I fail to catch your drift. I was present in an area a bit farther away from the crime scene, you see. I have no recollection of hearing such a sound!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No recollection...?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">...Precisely so. I'll have you know, I can easily hear a dog barking across town! Do not underestimate my hearing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wasn't! Relax, grandpa!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Did you see that...? I think the goat lady is acting kinda strange!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, there's no way I could have missed her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">There is nothing of interest in this testimony. ...Will the witness with the goat please proceed with her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">I'm as sure as Snowy is white. I made certain to keep my eyes peeled on that milk bucket, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Well, not quite. We didn't say for certain. We only believed it was on her wrist...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Believed"...?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Yes, yes, precisely! You know how you sniff milk when you're not quite sure if it's gone bad? And then your nose is assaulted by that foul odour that you weren't expecting? ...Well, it's a bit like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Ms Kira?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">H-huh? What?! Wh-wh-wh-what is it?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think of Ms Mary's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Uh...um...I just remembered something. I still have some milk sitting at home. Although it's been sitting there for two months...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I'm pretty sure it's turned into yoghurt by now...</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Ah...but wait! Maybe it turned into really stinky cheese! The stinkier the cheese, the better it tastes, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Either way, I really don't think you should eat it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa... Some people really go off the rails when you catch 'em off guard, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, "off the rails" is about right...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Please continue with your testimonies.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Heed my words, madam. Do not make a habit of stealing. For your own safety.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">W-w-w-we said we're sorry! Please! It was all Snowy's fault!</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, brother...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mary">Anyway, we can confidently say that we both saw the milk bucket, right, precious? And as for the lantern falling... We don't know much about that, do we now, shnookums?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Besides, how can you be sure the lantern fell just because it has a little mud on it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Well, maybe the mud was already on the lantern before any of this happened... Did you ever think of that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Before any of this happened...?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Like...maybe it's been there since last week. It did rain last week too, after all... And if that's the case, then there really isn't any point arguing about whether or not she dropped the lantern...right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Mr Knightle?</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">............ Huh?! Ooooooaaaaarghhhh! Wh-what the dickens?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Overreact much...?</thought> It looks like...you have something to say regarding Ms Kira's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Well, to tell you the truth... A week ago, on a cold rainy day... I slipped and fell in some mud and got it all over my armour. I left it in an unwashed heap outside of my home.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">However! I'm certain that yesterday's rain has washed that wretched mud right off!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Um...is that all?</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">That is all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, man... I was really hoping for something a little less...pointless.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well... Please continue with your testimonies.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Indeed. What say you, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I say, take a closer look at the lantern. You'll notice there's mud on the glass.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Mud on the glass...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The lantern wouldn't be very useful with all that mud blocking out the light. Ms Kira... I'd say your little theory regarding this lantern is muddy at best!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Aaaaaaaaahhhhhhhhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I could point at witnesses till the cows come home... But that wouldn't turn this testimony into anything I can use. I've got to find a lead somewhere!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightle">These eyes do not lie! I saw the lantern in the accused's hand when the incantation was uttered!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">You are but a petty baker, are you not?! It is not your place to be telling me what is important! There is but one thing of importance... Ridding this town of its witches as quickly as possible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is everything all right, Mr Wordsmith?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">............ What is it, young one?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is there something you wanted to say about this testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">There is but one important thing in this world...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"But one"...?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">The shapes of the clouds, the babbling of the brooks, petals scattering in the wind. Naps in the sun and tears in the rain. ...Do you see?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But you said only "one" thing... I just counted five...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mary">What on earth are you yapping about?! Anyone in their right mind knows the most important thing in this world is milk! Isn't that right, my little Snowy-poo?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">To me, there's nothing more important than selling these pretty flowers of mine.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Each one of us has that which is most important to them. ...Now, continue with your testimonies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Wh-what...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...We're trying to find out the truth here.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">H-how absurd! Th-that girl is a witch, I say! A witch! I would...stake my entrance into the Knights of the Inquisition on it!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Listen well, whelp.</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">...! Y-yes, Sir Barnham!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Many young men within the ranks of the knighthood share your level of passion. However... you let your ambition completely blind you. The same way that a muddy lantern leaves one blind and helpless in the dark.</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Wh-whaaaaaaaaaa?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>This guy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, indeed... I would say he is quite the tough motivator.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Their testimonies really are all over the place.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah ha! So, is this our chance?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think it might be. Although, I don't really see any contradictions. <thought>I may be able to find something in the gaps between each of their testimonies...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... I see. How will you accomplish this, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well...all we can really do right now is gather as much information as possible. <thought>I just have to find something suspicious in their testimonies...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm on the case! I'll be on the lookout for anything that doesn't add up, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah, yes. Your assistance is most welcome, my boy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...What do you think, Nick? Did you notice anything fishy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...possibly. I think...there may be something I can use.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">R-really?! Wow! I didn't hear anything special...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There was definitely something out of place about that one witness' [sic] testimony... It was something I haven't noticed from any of the other witnesses so far...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">It appears you may have found something, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A four-witness cross-examination... This is something I've never done before. But then... maybe there's another way I should be tackling this.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I believe it is worth trusting that intuition, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay...got it. <thought>All right. Let's try pressing that old man one more time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It doesn't look like I'll be able to get any more information out of these guys.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright, perhaps we'd better tackle this cross-examination in a slightly different way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess...maybe I should try questioning the other three witnesses in the middle of his testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">While you're pressing a witness, use the magnifying glass to observe the expressions of the other three witnesses!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">When you see someone acting funny, try stopping the testimony and questioning 'em! Just tell them to "Hang on!" when you do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay, that's good to know. Let's give this brand new way of questioning a shot!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me... Ms Mary.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Oh! Do you mean...us?! Um, but... Snowy and I have nothing else left to say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I knew it. I caught her completely by surprise...</thought> Mr Wordsmith just gave his testimony... He told us all about the sound he heard when the lantern fell to the ground. Mr Wordsmith didn't seem too sure... But I wonder if you might happen to have something to say about this.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Huh...?! Well... That's... ............ ...Is that all right, Sir Barnham? May we answer the question?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ ...Do what you will, madam. There is no need for formalities.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mary">Well, we'll try and explain...won't we, Snowy? The truth is, we did hear something. That is to say...we heard the sound of the lantern's glass shattering. We're sure of it! It was frighteningly loud.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">It quite startled us, didn't it, Snowy dear? I looked in the direction of the sound, but... I couldn't see anything, let alone the girl or those two thieves. It...was a tad dark, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">When the glass shattered, the flame inside must have gone out. Hence she could not see them. ...That seems to be the gist of it.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Th-then, as I peered into the darkness, I...h-heard it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You "heard it"...? What did you hear, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">You know...THAT! I heard... the incantation for the spell Ignaize.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ What...did you just say...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">N-now... Now hold it right there, witness!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Y-yes, Milord!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The glass shattered when the lantern fell. Then, after that, you heard the incantation for the spell Ignaize. Do you swear to this court that this is, without a doubt, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">U-uh...yes. M-Maybe... I think.</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">H-how about my testimony?! Wh-what of my oratorical observation? That blasted spell, Ignaize, occurred first. Then the lantern plummeted to the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I-I...heard no such thing! There was no sound of shattering glass!</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">...Absurd! Simply absurd! So the lantern fell and the glass shattered... That does not change the very fact that this girl is a witch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what is the meaning of this?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Let's go over what we know so far. In order for a witch to use any magic, they must be holding a witch's sceptre. And yet, none of the four witnesses saw the defendant holding a "sceptre" of any kind.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's because the sceptre was made to disappear with the spell Dimere, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At the time of the crime, the two victims grabbed Ms Cantabella's arm, causing her to drop the lantern on to the ground. If, at the time, she was in fact holding an "invisible sceptre"... then the sceptre must have fallen when she dropped the lantern. Now, let's say, hypothetically...that Ms Cantabella really is a witch... In order to use any magic, she would have had to recite the spell before dropping the sceptre. However! As our witness, Ms Mary, has just stated in her testimony... She heard the incantation for Ignaize after hearing the lantern's glass shatter.</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Wha...?!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Ooooh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You do all understand what that means, don't you...? It means that Ms Cantabella, the supposed "witch" you've locked up... could not possibly have cast any magic. ...Therefore! The defendant, Espella Cantabella, is clearly in no way, shape or form a witch!</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Waaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Oooooargh!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Baaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Ohoooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Hmph! Such nonsense! Did any of you even listen to my testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">We did, but you're wrong! There was no "glass shattering"!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Are you calling me a liar, missy? You couldn't even see the mud on the lantern, when it was plain as day!</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">...What ridiculous claims, all of you!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Oh, hush! Take your little toy sword and go back to playing pretend, "Sir Knight"!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">...!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...!</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Witnesses. This is a court of law... not a playground. Must I remind you of the importance of these proceedings? Witches and their magic threaten our fair town of Labyrinthia. Your words here today...could decide the fate of every single citizen within our walls. Do you understand? As such, I expect each of you to take your role seriously and testify honestly about what you saw!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">............</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">............</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-in all my days as judge of this court, I have never seen such behaviour... Behaviour that leaves a cloud of doubt over the credibility of each of your testimonies!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Indeed, Milord... Quite a miserable set of witnesses, this lot.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Hmm, I see. It would appear...this trial has come to a sudden halt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? So...that must mean!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Quite right. It means you have won this trial, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We've..."won"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I can hardly believe the situation we have found ourselves in... I did not anticipate this trial ending...with such a strange turn of events. But due to these witnesses' dubious credibility, I can see no reason to continue. ...What say you, Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ As you wish, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="???">Some Guy:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Who is this...this buffoon...?!</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">...Behold! Who am I, you ask? Who AM I? Why... I'm the man that's gonna single-handedly save this trial! I'm the fifth witness! Har har!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Say whaaaaaaat...?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even Barnham didn't see this one coming!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">...Just as I thought! This trial was goin' down the drain before I got here! Okay, you lot! Assemble! We need a strategy meeting, ASAP!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">I say...who are you?!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Thank goodness you showed up!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">We can't give up now, everyone!</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">It has come down to this. To arms, everyone! We shall do battle against that baker and that hat seller!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I-I can't believe this... What the heck is going on?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Hmm. Truly fascinating. It seems a new witness has taken the stand. What's more, he...appears to be quite the formidable witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I guess... This trial...is still far from over!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, then... We will now continue with the trial of Espella Cantabella.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh boy... A group of witnesses huddling up before a joint testimony in a witch trial... You can't make this stuff up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Inquisitor Barnham. If I may ask you a question.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Yes...Milord?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We now have five witnesses on the stand... So, I must ask... Why was this obnoxious-looking man left out of your initial group of witnesses?</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Baldy's right, Barnham! That's just cold-blooded!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">There is but one reason, Milord. I did not know this "witness" even existed.</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You, sir, failed to come forward... When we were asking for witnesses for this very trial, you were nowhere to be seen!</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">That's 'cos I didn't hear a peep about it! I ain't usually around at night, except for maybe at Rouge's tavern!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So...you're basically telling us that you were up all night drinking...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Hmph, anyway. It's all water under the bridge now, s'far as I'm concerned! Just leave the rest to yours truly! Har har har har har har har har haaaaaaar!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">During the last interrogation, the defender brought forth some surprising proof. Namely that there was little possibility the accused could have used magic... I have never heard such a claim. It must be the doing of this..."logic".</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">What rubbish! "Lodge...ick", y'say? I ain't got a clue what that is! But I do know that 'dis bread bakin'... BAKER oughta head back to the bakery!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Eloquently said...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Oi! Gramps! Give me and my partners over here a chance to speak! You wanna know how this witch managed to be holdin' that sceptre, don't cha?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ Oh! When you say "gramps"... you wouldn't mean me, would you?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">I fail to see anyone else meeting such a description!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">We'll... We'll show you she's a witch!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">I'll bet Snowy's beautiful white coat on it!</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">...En garde!</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">All right, team! Let's do this! Witnesses...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ Ahem, yes, well... Let us proceed with the testimonies!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Why do I feel like I've totally lost control of this situation?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kira">It's clear as day...Espella is a witch! We are NOT backing down on this!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">When she dropped the lantern, the sceptre was not yet in her hands.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">The sceptre must have been hidden by magic and carried on her back.</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">The rogues grabbed her by the hand that held the lantern, so she must have had another way of holding that sceptre.</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">That's easy! The girl just put the bucket down on the ground and picked up the witch's scep...scept...magic stick!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...So, she had the witch's sceptre behind her back. She then dropped the lantern and reached for the sceptre after it fell. If that is the case...then it must have been possible for the accused to have used magic!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is bad... Thanks to this guy, now all the witnesses seem extra determined to pin this thing on Espella...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">They each harbour a shared anger towards witches and magic... Such is the cause of their strong desire to see a guilty verdict passed as quickly as possible. However, such confidence... is undoubtedly bound to cloud their better judgement and thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, I think you're right. <thought>I don't think these guys mean any real harm, but... they're all riled up, they don't even realise how distorted their idea of what happened tonight has become. At least, that's how it seems.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Th-this isn't good, Professor! The witnesses aren't thinking straight! They're completely blind to the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ Sir Baker. Erm...rather, Sir Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You do not appear to be a mere simple baker...that much is clear. On the other hand... you are no ordinary defender either.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ Never before... has a defender managed to clash and do battle with me here, on this battlefield, as an equal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Sir Blue Knight. ...This trial has not yet been decided. If there is any doubt in your interrogation... I will not hesitate to strike your case down where it stands!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender, please begin your interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">It's clear as day...Espella is a witch! We are NOT backing down on this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Uh-huh, that's right! Espella is a witch... That's our story and we're sticking to it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is a courtroom, Ms Kira! We're not interested in your "story"! We're interested in the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ You know what I think? I think "stories" have the power to touch our lives in really meaningful ways.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Last year, I read a book about a flower girl, who brought peace to the world with all the pretty flowers she sold. Because of that story, now I tell myself, "Kira, one day you'll fill the world with beautiful flowers of your own!" That story inspires me to sell more flowers. ...It's pretty much the same as this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What a...very touching story.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Indeed. I have heard nary a truer tale. Wouldn't you agree, Sir Blue Knight?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Maybe it's just me, but I'd have preferred something a little more relevant.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm afraid our logic may do us no good here. Let's move on to the next witness, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">When she dropped the lantern, the sceptre was not yet in her hands.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">............ I ask you, youngling... Were you paying attention to this trial?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Well, then! Magic made the sceptre invisible, did it not?! Thus, my old age clouding up my vision has nothing to do with anything! The sceptre actually vanished!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no. What I'm saying is...if it really was invisible, you wouldn't be able to actually prove it.</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Not so, young one! We can prove it! The girl is a witch! There is your proof! So, my old age clouding up my memories has nothing to do with anything! The sceptre magically vanished, you see!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Okay, okay. We get it.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">When the lantern fell, you claim the sceptre was still not in her hand yet. So, that means...?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">The sceptre must have been hidden by magic and carried on her back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Well...it's like my little snowflake here. Whenever my darling gets too heavy, I hoist him up and carry him on my back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean your baby goat...right?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Yes, yes. There isn't a cuter little goat in this entire courtroom! Right, precious?</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know it's been asked already...but you didn't see the witch's sceptre, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">W-well, no, but... It must have been made invisible by magic and then put on her back! You know, Snowy is still such a tiny little thing...if I put him on my back, you can hardly see him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I hardly see the point of that comment.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So the accused grabbed the witch's sceptre after the lantern fell...?</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">The rogues grabbed her by the hand that held the lantern, so she must have had another way of holding that sceptre.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">What?! Why?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why? Well, for one thing, you're hiding behind what I assume is a shield...</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Heh heh heh heh heh heh heh... Well played, Blue Knight! You managed to see through my steel guard technique.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your steel WHAT technique...?</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">You tried to penetrate the depths of my mind and deceive me once with your witchcraft of words... But! You will find your words are futile against the strength of my shield, crafted from wood harder than steel! Now then, have at you! ...Attack me if you dare!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, no! Just... Just listen a second!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm... Looking at this sketch, it's quite clear the accused could not have held the sceptre in the same hand carrying the lantern... Witness, explain to the court just how the accused held the sceptre.</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">That's easy! The girl just put the bucket down on the ground and picked up the witch's scep...scept...magic stick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Tha's right! Reckon if she did that, she'd have no problem holdin' that thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Ah, but! No one said a thing 'bout NOT seein' her put the bucket down either, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Mr Wordsmith?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">...What is it, oh boisterous blue one?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me, what do you make of this witness' [sic] testimony just now? He has stated that the defendant: "put the bucket on the ground". The other witnesses never mentioned that.</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">............ Let me tell you something, young man. Long have I lived and prospered... In that time, I have forgotten much... Dreams, aspirations...even love. I simply forgot about that milk bucket. Like one would forget about a single drop of water within the bucket that is life...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Ummm... Thank you for that, Mr Wordsmith. No...further questions.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I still don't understand a single word that comes out of his mouth, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sheesh... I guess it's back to the drawing board.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Ms Mary.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Huh?! You mean...Snowy and me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me, what do you think of the witness' [sic] testimony just now? The accused placed the bucket on the ground... No one has said anything about this until now.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Ah, th-that... That must be how it happened. The girl probably placed the milk bucket on the ground, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mary">...Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ergo, you should be able to confirm to the court whether or not the bucket really was placed on the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Mary">...Y-yes. Yes, that's right! Isn't it, my little cuddle pumpkin?</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I knew it... There's something fishy about her testimony. But...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, it would seem we require a decisive piece of evidence... if we are to expose the contradictions in these witnesses' testimonies!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I just have to think of what that could be.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Ms Kira?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Huh? Ah...yes? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me, what do you think of this witness' [sic] testimony just now? The accused placed the bucket on the ground... No one has said anything about this until now.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ Why, you're right. How odd. Everyone must have simply forgotten. ...Myself included.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">But, yeah... Espella definitely did put that milk bucket down. That way she was able to easily grab her sceptre and use magic... Easy peasy, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Th-th nerve, Nick! It looks like she's trying to peg Espella as a witch every chance she gets...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Really... I don't know how much more of this testimony I can stand...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Mr Knightle.</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me, what do you think about this witness' [sic] testimony just now? He claims the accused placed the bucket on the ground... No one has said anything about this until now.</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">...I am reminded of but one thing, sir. A battle tactic important to any knight. Imagine...in one hand you hold your sword and in the other your shield... When suddenly, from the shadows...an itch of epic proportions takes to your back! ...What doth one do? Indeed, what CAN one do? Well, let me tell you... One must...drop one's sword and fell that unholy itch with a well-timed scratch to one's back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Right.</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">A crafty witch would surely use the same tactic, would she not? I call it my signature "Back Scratch Attack of Great Justice"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Right.</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">By the way... Be wary when using that tactic in battle. I find my opponents rarely give me ample time to remove my armour and scratch...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Ummm... Thank you for that, Mr Knightle. No...further questions.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mr Knightle sure takes the whole knight thing super seriously, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sheesh... I guess it's back to the drawing board.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-well, yeah, but...</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">There ye' go! These lot probably just didn't see it happen, is all. "Never question a witness!" ...That's what me pappy always said! Ain't a doubt in me mind! That witch put the bucket down before usin' the sceptre!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">If that is indeed accurate, then it would seem we may have found our truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Wh-what...? Whatcha talkin' about?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It had only just stopped raining moments before the crime took place. As a result...the ground was very muddy. If Ms Cantabella really placed this bucket on the ground, like you claimed she did... then it should be caked with mud, just like the lantern was after it fell!</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Har har haaaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well...? I'd say that clears up your muddy testimony, wouldn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Ah... Uh... Well... Hey! Barnham!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">You just gonna sit there lookin' pretty? C'mon, gimme a hand here!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Flattery will get you nowhere, witness... other than perhaps to the dungeon. ...At any rate, there is but one question we ought to ask: why is there no mud on that bucket?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">To the witness with the goat... May I ask you a question?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Huh?! A-are you talking to us?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Indeed. You admitted to the court that you returned home with the milk bucket. Illegally, I must add.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">My...oh, my... Such harsh words, Inquisitor...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">When you took the bucket home... you must have simply wiped the mud from the bucket, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">........... ............ ............ You know... Now that you mention it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>N-no way... Don't tell me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mary">That milk bucket... Ah! That's right! I remember now! I don't know if what was on the bucket was MUD, exactly...but it certainly was dirty! Before taking it inside with me, I remember wiping it clean with an old rag.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-are... Are you kidding meeeeeee?!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">...Exceptional work, Inquisitor Barnham!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Right, right! It all makes perfect sense. See? We were right all along! Weren't we, Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">I knew that sword weren't just fer show, Barnham! You sliced his argument in two!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mary">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're absolutely sure there was mud stuck to this milk bucket?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Oh, my... Well, truth be told, I don't remember whether it was mud, exactly. But I do remember cleaning the bucket off when I got home.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would seem... the defence has failed to disprove the witnesses' claims. Of that, we can be quite certain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Har har! That'll teach yer, Bluey! You got that right! Do me a favour, will ya, gramps? I wanna change me testimony just a tiny bit!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ I will allow it, only if the witness refrains from name-calling in the future.</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Yer got it, gra...er, Milord! Well, all this court mumbo jumbo has left me thirstier than a dog in a desert! *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">That witch there was holdin' the stick. I even heard her say the incantation-thingy. ...That's right, I witnessed it all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Because there's no mud on it...is that what you're saying?</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Hey, we went over this already! We know the goat lady wiped off all the mud!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Mmm...we really don't remember. But, maybe...? I guess maybe there was mud on it? ...I mean, she couldn't hold the sceptre without putting the bucket on the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Ms Mary, please give a definitive answer!</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">You all done, Bluey? Talk aaaaall you want, 'cos it ain't gonna help! Ya see... the five of us, we saw what that witch went and did! We saw it clear as day! Get it? If five heads are better than one, then ten eyeballs are better than two! And these ten eyes don't lie! That girl is a witch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... A most peculiar way of phrasing it, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Okay, we done here?! We're burning moonlight here, people! Morning's a-comin'! There ain't a magic spell strong enough that could change what the five of us saw tonight!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>These testimonies... Something's definitely not right here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-what do you think, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no way this "disappearing sceptre" explains what actually happened. I mean, no one saw anything! How can anyone prove it was there?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Th-this is starting to get really annoying...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>They can talk all they want about an invisible sceptre, but...no way is anything slipping under my radar!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">I do believe that is correct, Mr Wright. Somehow, we must find a clue that can lead us to another opening.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, you're right... And I think "Mr Personality" over there may be the key to doing just that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>They may all have their own reasons for accusing Espella, but there's also one thing they all have in common... They genuinely believe Espella is a witch!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Were we to disprove that belief...there would be no way for them to regroup. The witnesses would have to acknowledge the truth of what happened tonight. They are, after all, witnesses. They must be fully aware of what actually transpired!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That means I've got to pay extra attention to their reactions and testimonies!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">I think you'd better observe the witnesses, Mr Wright. You can do it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've got to try and get the truth out of these witnesses somehow!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, uh...mister?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">U-um...earth to gramps?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender, when you say "gramps"... might you, by any chance, be referring to me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no! Of course not, Your Honour! Mr Wordsmith, are you listening?!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">............ I heard you quite clearly the first time, young man. These ears hear all... The crackling of the fire...the whispering of the crowd...and now, your voice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If that's the case, then allow me to ask you a question. You were clearly deep in thought just now... Do you have something to say about this man's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">............ Indeed so. I felt something was amiss. However...what that means, I cannot say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Amiss...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Witness, could you tell us... what precisely was amiss with this third-rate testimony from this third-rate witness?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What a burn, Barnham...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Five heads are better than one... Ten eyeballs are better than two... ...As I listened to this man's testimony, I could not help but become aware of something most odd. Tonight, when the crime occurred...we all made haste to that terrible scene. The delicious scent of mid-evening dinner permeated through the air, the shadows of those present cast through the dim light... And yet, there were but four figures standing in that vicinity, myself included.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Four...? H-hold on one second! You're saying that there were only... four witnesses at the crime scene tonight?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">............ These eyes may be old, but they know what they saw!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Is something the matter, Ms Mary?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">No...it's just that...Snowy and I are trying to remember what happened at the time. I remember the flames erupting into the air. That's when Snowy and I made our mad dash to save the precious milk... And when those two ruffians were set ablaze, the flame filled the area with light. In that sudden flash of light, we could see that there were other people around, besides ourselves. And that's when I saw them... The other people that scrambled to the scene along with us. I'm quite sure of it. There were only four of us there at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="???">Don't be stupiiiiiiiiid!</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Oi! You lot better stop speakin' outta turn! "All for one and one for all", remember? We all promised to take this witch down together, didn't we?!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">It's not quite that simple! We saw what we saw!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Well, I say it's all about the numbers! And I counted! I counted, I say! I'll have you know my counting is flawless! On nights when sleep eludes me, I can count sheep from moonrise to sunrise!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Four witnesses, five witnesses... What difference does it make?! Things all started getting muddled when YOU showed up!</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Wh-what the...?! You sayin' it's MY fault?! I was there, you fool! Didn't I just finish sayin' that?!</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">My testimony is strong as steel! ...Even if it's not completely stainless!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! I said order! Wh-what... What is going on here? You claim the number of witnesses does not add up?! I have never paid witness to such an outrageous conflict!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There is but one answer to this puzzle. A single possibility...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Without a doubt, "magic" must have been used at the scene of the crime. Furthermore, it would indeed appear that there were only four witnesses present at the scene... And yet, currently, we are faced with five witnesses testifying to the court. That certainly is quite a fatal contradiction... with only one possible answer. Would you not agree, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>The answer...it can't be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Well, out with this supposed "answer", Sir Blue Knight! What is your explanation for the current number of witnesses?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's possible...that the witnesses were mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">I say! Are you insinuating that my senses are those of one past his prime, young man?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">I'll have you know, part of my job is to count the number of goats on my farm. I think I can accurately count four people! Perhaps you should go back to counting loaves of bread!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yup. They're mad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright, even if they are mistaken, I'm afraid that would not change anything. So...let us endeavour to seek out a more pertinent possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even Layton sounds annoyed...in a gentlemanly sort of way...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It would seem Sir Apprentice Baker and Sir Top Hat are in disagreement.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I suppose I owe you for that most unflattering moniker.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The defence should think twice before recklessly casting such accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, maybe the witch put a spell on them. You know, to affect their testimony. Like... "Alla-ka-WRONG!" ...or some weird spell like that.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright! There's no record of "Alla-ka-wrong" in the Grand Grimoire!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The witch's sceptre has two magic gems. "Ignaize" and "Dimere", Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What... What a ridiculous spell!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uuuuuh... You think? It's not any more ridiculous than those other spell names...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That was simply dreadful!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The next time you spout such drivel, you shall tell it to the flames. Is that clear?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">C-crystal clear... <thought>Uh...can I get a do-over...?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">While it might seem far-fetched, the reality is actually rather simple. The real witch...and the real murderer in this case... is actually one of these five witnesses!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wha...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whaaaaaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You're telling us that the witch is amongst this group of witnesses?! What utter rubbish! ...There is no possible way that such a claim could be true!</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Th-tha's right! You've got a lotta nerve accusin' one of us of bein' a witch!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">We have told you nothing but the truth... yet you still have the gall to bat around such an outrageous accusation?!</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Behold! Behold, as my trusty shield deflects your petty words like...the petty words that they are!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ Inquisitor Barnham...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Yes, Milord?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I would like to see a sketch of the crime scene at the time of the incident. Do you have one in your possession?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Yes... Certainly, Milord. I have one here. I requested it from the Court Illustrator, just in case...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Witnesses! I would like each of you to mark your location at the time of the murder... here on this crime scene sketch! ...Quickly, now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The number of witnesses doesn't add up... It looks like we're getting somewhere now. But we haven't even scratched the surface of this case yet! And it's all thanks to this top-hat-wearing gentleman...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...The court accepts this crime scene sketch into evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If one of the witnesses is the witch... That could only mean one thing. Somebody here isn't telling the truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">That would indeed appear to be the case, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Listen well, Sir Blue Knight. The path you tread now is a dangerous one. Claiming that a witch is among these most honourable witnesses... is a serious accusation. Should it prove to be a false one... you will find yourself at the other end of my sword. Do I make myself clear?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? But, that...that wasn't so much my suggestion... I mean, the gentleman here with the lovely top hat was the one who urged me to say it.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It is the same thing, Sir Blue Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. It is the same thing, Sir Baker.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is the same thing, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh boy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Now! Ready your sword!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-ready...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Were you listening? You claim the witch is not the accused and that someone else at the crime scene was the true culprit. If what you say is true, then surely you can tell the court exactly where this person was at the time of the crime...can you not? Come now, Sir Blue Knight. Only you can enlighten us as to who this "real witch" actually is!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Sir Doughy Defender. Show us where the witch was at the exact moment the murder took place!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">"Probably"...?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">"This person"...?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">"I think"....?</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaa!</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">...You're so bad at this "defender" stuff, it makes me wanna drink! *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...If I may, Mr Wright. Remember that if one of these witnesses is indeed the witch... then there is a high possibility that particular witness is not telling the truth. Do bear that in mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So the "witch" must be lying, huh... If that's the case... That must mean a certain person wasn't where they claim they were...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's when the witch must have cast Ignaize, right? Take a look in the Grand Grimoire. We're bound to find something in there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even if the witness is lying up a storm... whatever is inside this Grand Grimoire has to be the truth, right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Sir Doughy Defender, do not waste the court's time with any more such ridiculous answers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uuuuugh... Darn it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Somewhere around there...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It looks like it is your head that is currently "somewhere" else, Sir Blue Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I believe he is trying to convey...that your answer was incorrect.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Well he didn't need to be so harsh about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">...If I may, Mr Wright. Keep in mind that the real "witch" is among the witnesses, so we cannot be completely certain that their testimonies are all true.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-of course. That's true... <thought>Well, looks like relying on the witness testimonies is out the window...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright! The witch used the spell Ignaize, right? Take a look in the Grand Grimoire. We're bound to find something in there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even if the witness is lying up a storm... whatever is inside this Grand Grimoire has to be the truth, right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Sir Doughy Defender...do not waste the court's time with any more such ridiculous answers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uuuuugh... Darn it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witch must have been standing...here!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The Grand Grimoire...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to this tome, Ignaize summons a circle of flame...within a one metre radius of the caster. In other words, the witch had to have been within one metre of the flame when casting the spell!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Most intriguing... Since you seem to love showing evidence... prove it! How was the witch able to hide in plain sight?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't have a clue how this is relevant. What do you think, Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I think this mysterious "real witch" of yours... is not the only thing hiding from you, Sir Blue Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Perhaps you should focus your efforts on finding some actual evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Gaaaah! <thought>Hmm... A way to stay hidden from sight, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">I believe the correct word you're looking for may be "vanished", rather than "hidden".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Vanished"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Remember, you have more than just the Court Record to hand, Mr Wright! Be sure to also check the Grand Grimoire!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Hmph... That look in your eyes. You just won't give up, will you? ...Very well. I will grant you one more chance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...This Talea Magica contains two magic gems. Ignaize and one other spell... That's right. The spell Dimere.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Dimere... Ah! I-it cannot be!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's right. There was most certainly a witch present at the crime scene. Only...they were completely invisible... All thanks to the magic spell Dimere!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wh-what FOOLISHNESS is this?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court! D-defender, what are you getting at...? I thought the witch used Dimere... to make the Talea Magica disappear!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">A-are you... Are you implying that is the reason for the conflicting number of witnesses?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, it is! Which means, witnesses... someone amongst you is not disclosing the entire truth, and that person is the witch we seek. I believe this is the most probable scenario.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Honourable witnesses... You will testify to the court one final time. Tell us exactly what you saw and what you did not see at the scene of the crime...</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">H-how absurdly absurd! The purpose of this trial is to convict THAT girl of the crime, is it not?!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">That's right! W-we...are NOT witches!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Witnesses, I ask that you listen.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There is a witch mingling among you. ...That's right. I'm afraid you are all no longer "brothers in arms". The true opponent here...is within your own group.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The real "witch" is one of these five witnesses, huh? Fine by me... Time to put an end to this trial!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightle">You wish to know where we were all standing tonight? It matters not! Would the flames not burn just the same?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">That flame... I never saw anything like it! It quite literally left me speechless... I couldn't even so much as scream.</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">I heard the tiniest cry, and then when I turned around, the blighters were roastin'... So I rushed right over!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">I heard the incantation, then the flames suddenly erupted... I'm certain of it. I only saw three people there with us!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">As I said, there were only three others present. Like that man there, who was stumbling around like a newborn calf.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm... A most heinous act, indeed. No small wonder these witnesses are so confused...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">A witch amongst the witnesses...what an utterly baseless claim!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think so, Barnham... The only baseless claim in this case is of Espella being a witch. It's more than a little likely one of these witnesses is the culprit! These testimonies are bound to tell me who the real witch is!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightle">You wish to know where we were all standing tonight? It matters not! Would the flames not burn just the same?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Defender! I fought with burning vigour this night! Do not belittle my efforts!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R...right...</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">A knight does not just run away at the mere sight of fire! Ha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No one even said anything about running away...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightle">If I may be perfectly straight with you. The pillar of fire illuminated the area as it rose high into the air... There, by the fire, was the witch! And excluding the two unfortunate knaves, I counted three others at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Ms Kira?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Eeeeek! Wh-wh-wh-what do you want?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You looked like you had something to say... about the testimony just now.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Well, it was about the number of people at the crime scene. Have you ever played the daisy petal game?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-daisy petal...game?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">One witness... Two witnesses... Three witnesses... Four witnesses... Five witnesses... Six witnesses...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm... What an adorable game. It seems like something out of a fairy tale.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Seriously, Your Honour...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Anyway. You may continue your testimony, Witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly! That means there were only four witnesses at the scene of the crime...</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">Hold on, sir! You cannot say that for certain! Perhaps I missed the other witness... Maybe they were obscured by this shield! See? That is another possibility!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Anyway. How about we NOT talk about your shield any more.</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">...Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">That flame... I never saw anything like it! It quite literally left me speechless... I couldn't even so much as scream.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Yes... It's the kind of thing you only read about in books. The moment that pillar of fire erupted... I could feel my throat tightening up... It was so difficult to breathe, I couldn't even manage so much as a scream.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Quite... After all, the flames engulfed the scene in the blink of an eye.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Yes... I'm sorry... That's why I can't really remember...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So you can't remember the number of people at the crime scene? Naturally, that is understandable, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">That's also why...I was a little late getting to the scene compared to the others.</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">I heard the tiniest cry, and then when I turned around, the blighters were roastin'... So I rushed right over!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">It might've been someone sayin' the incantation for that spell. Me memory's kinda hazy on that one... Scared me good though! Never jumped up to me feet so fast in all me life! Nearly had a heart attack, I tell ya...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">"Jumped up"...?</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">'Sright! It was still rainin' cats and dogs, so bein' the resourceful chap that I am, I decided to doze under a tree fer a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is everything all right, Mr Wordsmith?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">............ What is it that you want this time, young one?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I just wanted to know if you had any thoughts on the testimony just now...</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Ah, yes. ...Thoughts about slumbering under trees, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Slumbering...?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">I often find myself weaving the most intricate of dreams under that very tree. Of course, I could not nap tonight. Not with that...uncouth man usurping my special dreaming spot, could I?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Are you using this cross-examination to argue over a napping spot...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Let us hope such arguments do not lead to any criminal acts in the future.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Witness, please continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So you slept under a tree in the rain... Why am I not surprised...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Anyway, I tried to put out the fire by chuckin' some of me drink at it. Amazingly, didn't do much good though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right...</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">But they ended up roasted, huh? Turns out magic won that fight, awright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This guy...is unbelievable...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Emeer">I hurried to the scene! But then I ended up tripping when I heard someone call me name from behind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Mary">I heard the incantation, then the flames suddenly erupted... I'm certain of it. I only saw three people there with us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Well...I believe so. But then, when you think about it... Can anyone really be "absolutely certain" of anything?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It...worries me that you're saying that in the middle of a cross-examination...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I believe the witness means that there is no way she can be certain whether there were four witnesses or five at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Anyhow, there was a matter of great importance that Snowy and I had to tend to.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... You must mean...</line>
<line speaker="Mary">That's right! The milk! If any soot had got into that milk...it would be the tragedy to end all tragedies!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could I stop you there, mister?</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">MISTER!</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaargh! Whoa! Tone down the volume, Bluey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's my line!</thought> Does anything come to mind...regarding Ms Mary's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Nope. Not really. ...Nothin' important, anyways. Just that I think this old lady is full of it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">I'm talkin' about the milk, man! The milk! You'll know the second you try the stuff. It ain't nothin' to write home about, let me tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">What are you saying, you dolt?! Who on earth would let YOU drink anything as delicious as the milk from my farm?! A ruffian like you is better served by whatever unthinkable liquid is in that never-ending mug of yours!</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Are you guys using this cross-examination to argue over milk...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Let us hope such arguments do not lead to any criminal acts in the future.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Witness, please continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... <thought>No use crying over spoiled milk, I say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mary">Ahem. As I was saying... I ran as fast as I could to get the girl away from the flames. Then, I took the milk bucket from her and wrapped it up in my scarf.</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It doesn't look like there's anything out of place in her testimony...except for maybe her priorities.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">As I said, there were only three others present. Like that man there, who was stumbling around like a newborn calf.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Hmmmmmmmmmm. That is how it has come to pass.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By the way...what do you mean by "stumbling around like a newborn calf"?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Ah, yes. That was a man as inebriated as he was loud. Quite the humorous sight it was, I dare say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He must mean the witness permanently glued to his cup of...whatever it is he's drinking.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">When I saw the flames rise up into the sky, I wondered to myself: "My word, whatever could that be?" However, I could not simply walk over to check... My knees were a bit weak from shock, you see. That's when the wobbly-legged gentleman came running over. The next thing I knew, he tripped over with all the grace of a grizzly bear on stilts. A responsible adult should know better than to go stumbling around in the dead of night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is something the matter, mister?</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">MISTER!</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaargh! Whoa! Tone down the volume, Bluey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's my line!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Sir Blue Knight... Next time please THINK before trying to press this witness!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like this guy even managed to scare Barnham half to death...</thought> Now then...sir. About Mr Wordsmith's testimony just now... He claimed you were "stumbling around". What does he mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">I'm gonna set the record straight right now: in no way was I "stumbling around" anywhere! I'd like to think of it more like... "staggering with style".</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">A responsible adult should know better than to go stumbling around in the dead of night!</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">Hey, look, I don't just go "stumbling" around, like some clumsy idiot. I've got more sense than that! But anyway... I kinda tripped over a large stone... I mean, you don't exactly see what's on the ground in front of you when you're running at full pelt, right? So...you could say I put me life out on the line provin' that you really need to watch where you're going when you run!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How courageous of you... Someone give this guy a medal...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Milord, this testimony is a meaningless waste of everyone's time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Well, defender? Is there a point to this particular line of questioning?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is there anything worth pursuing here? What should I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness stated earlier that he tripped over a "large stone". Mister, I have one question for you: why weren't you watching what was in front of you?</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">W-well...to be honest with yer, it ain't much of a real reason but... Somethin' suddenly caught me attention. ...Outta nowhere, I sorta heard someone call out me name.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You heard...your name?</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">'Course I turned around when I heard it. Who wouldn't? When a woman calls your name, you pay attention, amiright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So...you heard someone call out "Hey, you!" from behind, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">What?! I said they called out me NAME! How many guys do you know called "Hey You"?! Me name is Emeer! And don't you forget it, Bluey! Y'hear me?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hm...I must say, this gentleman really does not strike me as an "Emeer".</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You know, Professor... it's not a very memorable name, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...That's harsh.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Honourable witnesses, is there anyone among you who was aware of this man's name prior to now?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Not at all. He's always just been "mister" to me.</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">A knight's name is only as good as the name of the sword he carries!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">It is the first I have heard of this... I dare say, I did not expect his name to be one such as "Emeer".</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I'm sorry, but I didn't know his name either. I only remember the names of my most loyal customers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ooookay. It looks like absolutely no one knew this witness' [sic] name...</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Y'know, it ain't really much of a surprise to me either. Har har har har har har har har haaaaaar! But seriously... I definitely heard someone call me name. When you get to be me age, you really start to wonder when you'll find that true love, y'know? I thought that pretty voice tonight might've been me sweetie...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Your Honour. I don't believe we should be so quick to label Mr Emeer's testimony meaningless, would you not agree? ...I request that the witness add this amusing anecdote to his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Understood. Witness, amend your testimony. But please, reflect only the important points of your story!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">I'm tellin' ya! I heard someone call me name, and I was lookin' around tryin' to find them!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... There's no point in wasting time with meaningless questioning...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Is that so...? I must say I am a little disappointed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I just...thought I noticed something. ...Perhaps it was just me.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">If you do notice something in a person's testimony, Mr Wright, all you have to do is question them again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's right. I should take the time to question them as much as possible...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Let us return to the interrogation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, that certainly doesn't surprise me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Fascinating... I wonder just why he "stumbled"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is that it for the testimony...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Is something the matter, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I hate to say it, but...it looked like there weren't any contradictions.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Is that right...? Hmm, just as I thought. I suppose the only option at present is to try and coax some more information from the witnesses.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean...catching them off guard, right?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Precisely.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, it's worth a shot. <thought>Let's see how they respond to a little hard questioning!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is that it for the testimony...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Is something the matter, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, well... It looks like our favourite witness made a few changes to his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">His wording might have changed, but he's still saying the same thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, it doesn't really affect anything. Still... <thought>There's something about this guy's testimony that stinks more than he does...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ Are you referring to that gentleman there? I agree. That is, I also noticed something peculiar in his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Which one of these witnesses is the real witch? There has to be something that I'm still not seeing in these testimonies!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, excuse me, mist- ...I mean, Emeer!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Ah, don't sweat it, Bluey. "Mister", "Hey You"... it's all the same to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You stated that you heard your name being called from behind... Are you absolutely sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Ah...well, right or wrong, it sure sounded like me name. I mean, what else could it have been? I wouldn't have remembered it happenin' if I hadn't heard somethin', right? Still... Maybe there's a chance I just imagined it, huh? But anyway, I remember it came from somewhere behind me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>From somewhere behind you...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Is something the matter, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr...err, Emeer's memory isn't the most accurate, but if what he says is true... then there's definitely something there.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">"Something", you say...? Might you mean... A contradiction?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I think so. Although... I don't know. There's just...something strange about his testimony... <thought>I don't see any decisive evidence in the Court Record that can help...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Do you mean to say you've found a contradiction that cannot be supported by the evidence...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Defender, I must warn you. From here on... any unnecessary questioning will be dealt with accordingly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>If I don't answer correctly here... it's curtains for the trial and for Espella!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you are intent on finding a fault in this witness' [sic] testimony... you will need to present decisive evidence to back up your claims!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's not one single piece of decisive evidence in the Court Record... ...What do I do now?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mr Layton!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I have an idea. I believe...there is a weapon, of sorts, with which you may be able to expose this contradiction without the need of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>A "weapon"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Now, defender. Give us your answer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes, Your Honour. The defence finds that the witness' [sic] testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I hate to say it, but... I can't bet Espella's life on this one!</thought> The defence has no further questions, Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Well now, it would seem you do have some amount of common sense.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I am disappointed, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Th-that voice...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright! Please! You can't give up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">My fate...is in your hands. I'm counting on you...and Professor Layton! That's why...I need you to go on! Please, don't give up on me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>Of course...I can't give up on Espella! I have to keep going!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honour! The defence... believes there is a huge contradiction in the witness' [sic] testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Whatever do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You have my utmost thanks for placing your trust in me, Mr Wright. Let us discuss the one remaining weapon in this cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...The "remaining weapon"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">This trial has taught us a valuable new technique to be used in the courtroom, has it not?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You mean...questioning... Right, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed it is, Luke. Each of the witnesses in this trial has given their own account of what occurred. Therefore...whenever one witness has testified, the other remaining witnesses have listened. ...That gives me an idea. In addition to catching a witness off guard and questioning them about another's testimony, there is...one more thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's something else we can get from a five-person cross-examination...?</thought> ...! Th-that's right, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, Mr Wright...contradictions. Should one witness' [sic] testimony differ from another's testimony, then... I suppose that in itself can also be considered a contradiction, can it not...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Testimony contradicting testimony... I never would've thought of that until now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Enough. Sir Blue Knight, are you prepared to present to the court... evidence proving the contradiction within this witness' [sic] testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness' [sic] testimony...does not contradict any evidence. It contradicts a testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wh-what are you talking about...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is time, Mr Wright! Have a look at the Touch Screen. There, you will see the testimony of the witness in question, as well as those of other witnesses. Keep your eyes peeled and identify the contradicting testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All right! Let's give this another shot, Nick! And make sure you don't forget to take a look at the Court Record, too!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">I hurried to the scene! But then I ended up tripping when I heard someone call me name from behind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix/Layton">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix/Layton">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Layton">P-please, just a moment, Mr Wright! Perhaps it would be wise not to leave this quite so...up to chance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-but! I've got nothing but the witnesses' testimonies to work from!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's not just the testimonies, Mr Wright. I recommend you have another look at the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Court Record...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This man testified that he heard a voice call his name "from behind". The important thing here is the position of all parties at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The connection between the witnesses' positions and their testimonies... Okay, time to rethink this one!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...How sad. It would seem the only contradiction to this witness' [sic] testimony...is you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-my mistake! Just give me one more chance! One of these witnesses definitely contradicts this man's testimony. And that person is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The person contradicting this man's testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">is none other than...you! Miss Kira!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">A-are you both pointing at me...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At the time of the incident, that man heard someone's voice call his name.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That voice...belonged to you, Miss Kira. It could not have been anyone else.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And yet, in your testimony, you stated that you were in such shock during tonight's events that you couldn't even speak.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This is...a clear contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Layton">He heard a woman's voice calling his name. ...A very concrete reason, and reason enough to believe his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Th-that's right! Why me? People barely hear me when I'm out selling my flowers...that's how soft my voice is! And besides, there WAS another woman at the scene, wasn't there?</line>
<line speaker="Mary">M-me?! What are you getting at, young lady?! Do you honestly think a woman my age would be out late at night in the forest, flirting with questionable men? Besides, I didn't even know this pathetic man's name! How could I have called out to him?!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Neither did I! And even if I DID know his name, do you really think he's the kind of guy any self-respecting girl would want?!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">C'mon, ladies... I...I'm standin' right here, y'know...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Um, as I was saying! The only person that guy could've heard from "behind" him was you, Ms Kira!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The defence wishes to present evidence to prove this claim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">To accuse a witness like this young lady here... Why, this is simply unheard of! I must warn you, defender, if you cannot prove your accusation to this court, you will see the underside of my gavel! Show us the evidence proving this young lady was the one who called out to this man at the time of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Layton">My apologies, but... I believe that may not be the correct piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yikes...that was fast.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Please, Mr Wright. Having come this far, do not falter here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright! Please stop kidding around... Listen to the professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Think about it, Mr Wright. We'd both been following the same train of thought until just now...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm sorry! <thought>I have to hurry up and think of something!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...You can think all you want, Sir Baker, but not before taking a penalty. Now then, I will grant you another chance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a look at this and you'll have your answer.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is...the crime scene sketch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can see the position of each witness during the crime. The only person that he could possibly have heard from behind him...was none other than Ms Kira!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">...*sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Did you, in fact, see this flower girl's face?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Y-y'know, now that you mention it... Seein' as I'd fallen down an' all... I don't think I saw her face...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay...but you heard her voice, right?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Hmm...lemme think... The voice came outta nowhere... It was kinda high-pitched... An' I guess it kinda sounded like her... But I can't say whether or not it was this girl's voice...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">And there you have it, Sir Blue Knight. ...Such a pity.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Milord! It is clear that the defence's claim is nothing but a pointless waste of the court's time. ...I recommend you deliver unto them a penalty befitting such behaviour.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm... Indeed, Inquisitor. Ready yourself, defender!</line>
<line speaker="???">............ ...Heh heh heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what is that laughter?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Pardon me, Milord...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">It looks like...you've finally arrived at a decision. That means this has nothing to do with me. Isn't that right, Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...What are you saying?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I'm saying...that it's time for me to stop peddling testimony and get back to peddling flowers. I mean, look at all of these flowers left over. It's going to take until sunrise to sell them all if I stay here any longer. Or maybe, Milord... You and the rest of the court would be interested in buying my entire stock of flowers to help a girl out...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Ah, no, I don't think... I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Then it's settled. Now, if you'll excuse me. My apologies for the interruption.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">U-understood. The court will dismiss the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well...Miss Kira. It would seem you are beginning to show the court your true colours.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Oh? Whatever do you mean? Okay then, everyone. It looks like that's that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Now, that's funny. You say it isn't over, and yet the rest of the court seems to think otherwise. Isn't that right, Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ ...The inquisition maintains that the real witch is the accused, Espella Cantabella. This girl...is nothing more than a witness. As such, the court cannot force her to stay against her will.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Th-this is bad! If they let her walk out now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! Do...you think she could be...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The real witch...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kira">You really like throwing around accusations, don't you, Sir Defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Let me spell it out for you one last time, so even you can understand. I didn't know this man's name at all before today. I still don't remember it. So how could I have called out to him? ...Do you get it now? Now then, until we meet again. Don't forget to buy some flowers on your way home, everyone.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Is there something else you wanted?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You don't seem to realise... what you just let slip.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...! What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This man testified that he heard his name called at the crime scene. However... you had no knowledge of his name at the time...is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">That's right! This weirdo is just imagining things! Like I said, I've already forgotten his name, even though he told it to us earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There is just one problem, Miss Kira. Namely, what the voice he heard tonight was actually saying.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean? That's obvious. It was a name, wasn't it? Now, uhh...what was that name again?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">...Milord, I'm still here, y'know...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Y-you're saying that what this man heard tonight... wasn't a name, but rather...something else entirely?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed I am, Inquisitor Barnham.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Something else"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's only one other thing it could be. It's a stretch, but the possibility is there!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's right, Mr Wright. That single possibility...is the key to solving this mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Is the defence ready to present its evidence to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Ngh... This is ridiculous! I demand you let me go, this instant!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Witness, what you are being accused of is not to be taken lightly. You will not leave this courtroom so long as any reasonable doubt remains.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender, you may present your evidence. Show the court what the voice this man heard tonight was really saying!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaargh! <thought>I guess that wasn't right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Regrettably, it is your fault that the inquisitor continues to call me by that unflattering nickname, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's right! It's all your fault, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Milord, I request a penalty be delivered to the defence, for wasting the court's time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Granted. You only have yourself to blame, Sir Baker.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uuuuurgh... <thought>Someone hand me that Talea Magica... so I can make myself disappear.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">That reminds me, don't forget to check out the Grand Grimoire, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, mister... Um... I'm sorry, what's your name again? You've, uh...got a name...that no one seems to be able to remember for some reason.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Hey! It's Emeer! Me name's Emeer, darn it! How many times have I gotta say it?!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">No matter the number of times you say it, you do not look like an "Emeer".</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Again, I only remember my most loyal customers' names, and he doesn't look like he could afford even a single daisy.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">C'mon guys... Stop kickin' a guy when he's down!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Mr Emeer. What you heard tonight at the crime scene was not your name. Your name just so happens to sound exactly like a certain other name.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Another...name...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The answer is right here in this tome. I'm talking about Amere...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-A...mere?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What he actually heard at the time wasn't his own name... It was the name of a magical incantation!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wh-what the...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Kira! Have you forgotten what you said just a few minutes ago? You quite clearly stated that you didn't know this man's name!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...The defence proposes the following: the true criminal, this supposed "witch", is not the defendant, Ms Espella Cantabella... but instead, the witness who was heard uttering the magic incantation...Ms Kira! She's our witch! You used magic to vanish from the scene and tried to frame Ms Cantabella instead!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">... ...... ............ Noooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I am referring to a contradiction, naturally.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>Hey, that's my line!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Milord, the inquisition would like to set the record straight regarding what transpired this evening.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Inquisitor Barnham.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Sir Blue Knight, you claim the following: at the time of the crime, the accused, Espella Cantabella, was surrounded by the two rogues. Then, in order to frame the accused as a witch... Ms Kira cast the spell Dimere and made herself vanish. She then moved in closer to the victims... at which point she cast Ignaize. Thus causing the incident seen by our witnesses tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed...that does seem to be the claim.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The problem...is what happened next. There is a contradiction in the defence's account of Ms Kira's movements.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A contradiction...in her movements...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Allow me to continue. The witnesses have stated that they each ventured out towards the crime scene. Which is when Ms Kira, the "witch", made her way to this point, while still invisible. When she arrived at said spot, she then cast Amere and reappeared to join the other witnesses. ...And there you have it. That is accurate, isn't it, Sir Blue Knight?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's correct. Then, Mr Emeer heard her call his "name".</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Well then, I have but one question that I would like you to answer: why would a witch need to do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Supposing Ms Kira were a witch, surely she would not have made the conscious decision to reappear when she did. One would imagine she would remain hidden ...and [sic] flee the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Qu-quite right! That's what I'd do if I was a witch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Given that point, there would be no viable reason for her to recite the incantation. In other words... it is inconceivable that this flower seller, Ms Kira, could be a witch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">......Nghh......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...That's right. You all heard it. It's just as Inquisitor Barnham said. Me? A witch...? The idea is laughable!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>N-not good! She's completely bounced back on to her feet!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oooooh... We were so close, too!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I...I can't believe Inquisitor Barnham! Can't he see it...? You just have to take one good look at her! It's obvious she's the real witch here!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Remember, Mr Wright: at times like this, a cool head will prevail.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mr Layton!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm sure you have had to fight your way out of circumstances such as these many times before. This situation is no different. As a defence attorney, what would you usually do at such a time...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What...would I usually do...? Of course... There's only one thing that can get me out of a situation like this... I've got to flip this case on its head and think outside the box!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...It would seem the defence has nothing further to add.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Why, of course. That's because everyone knows the truth. ...They know that girl right there is the real witch! That settles it, then! Go ahead and deliver your verdict, Milord!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Regardless, the defence still maintains that Ms Kira did utter that incantation and make herself reappear... Now, the question is: for what reason? <thought>If she really didn't have to use that spell, then why use it in the first place? If I can find the answer to that question... then this entire case will start to unravel!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Most fascinating. Very well. Allow us to hear this theory of yours. Tell the court why it was necessary for the witch to appear at the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, we're still in the game. Once you eliminate the impossible... whatever remains must be the truth!</thought> The reason Ms Kira reappeared at the scene of the crime was...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The answer is obvious. She must have wanted to become a witness herself!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Have a look at the number of witnesses. We already have four other willing witnesses. Becoming a witness on purpose would accomplish nothing. She may as well have sat in the stands and watched the trial!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-well...you... You don't know that for sure! <thought>Nope... He's absolutely right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender, something tells me you must be thinking something along the lines of: "he is absolutely right".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uuuuuuugh... <thought>Please quit reading my mind, Your Honour!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suggest you think before opening your mouth...Sir Doughy Defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Shoot! Looks like I'll have to think of something else...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You have one more chance. Please, tell the court... Why would it have been necessary for the witch to reappear at the crime scene...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The answer is obvious. She was trying to give herself an alibi!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Oh, is that right...? Tell me, what would that alibi have been?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-well, just give me a minute... I'm getting to that part!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That will not be necessary, Sir Blue Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Think about it. Why would she have needed an alibi... if no one could have seen her to begin with?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-well...you... You don't know that for sure! <thought>Nope... He's absolutely right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender, something tells me you must be thinking something along the lines of: "he is absolutely right".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uuuuuuugh... <thought>Please quit reading my mind, Your Honour!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suggest you think before you open your mouth...Sir Doughy Defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Shoot! Looks like I'll have to think of something else...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You have one more chance. Please, tell the court... Why would it have been necessary for the witch to reappear at the crime scene...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't think of any other possibility... This has to be the answer.</thought> Isn't it obvious? She was trying to cover up her own crime.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Oh, is that right...? Tell me, why would she do that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-well, just give me a minute... I'm getting to that part!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That will not be necessary, Sir Blue Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Think about it. What would she have to hide... if no one could have seen her to begin with?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Heh...heh heh heh... You heard the good inquisitor! No matter how you look at it, there'd be no reason for me to reappear. ...Assuming I was the criminal, that is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Urgh! <thought>I can't argue with her there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mr Layton!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Explain yourself, Sir Top Hat.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You have stated that Miss Kira had no reason to reappear. However...the situation changed and it became necessary for her to show herself. Isn't that right, Miss Kira?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Huh...?! Wh-wh-wh-wh-what're you talking about?! I-I-I-I have no idea what you mean!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would seem...the defence must clarify their argument with evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Mr Wright. I believe that Miss Kira did not intend to reveal herself at the crime scene. Rather, that something occurred which forced this young lady to make herself reappear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What was so important that she had to reappear and risk being spotted...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Defender. Tell the court why it would have been necessary for the witch to appear at the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Tell me, Sir Baker, what relevance does this have to the trial?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have no idea, Your Honour! Maybe there's...ah...magic at work here!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">H-hold on one moment, Mr Wright! Perhaps you are letting our sudden rise in momentum cloud your better judgement.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, boy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Defender. I see your argument has vanished... as has your credibility!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, Nick! We're so close! We've got this witch on the ropes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe...Ms Kira left behind some really decisive evidence at the crime scene... Something must have happened... Something that meant she had to reappear in order to cover her tracks. <thought>There has to be some piece of evidence that she left at the crime scene...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Kira, you usually wear glasses, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Huh...?! I-it's like I already told you. I lost my glasses a few days ago...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you absolutely sure about that? Or did you not, in fact, lose them tonight? ...During the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...! O-of...course not!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps you accidentally dropped them while you were committing the crime... Then, as you were attempting to make your escape, you noticed they were gone. Therefore, you made yourself reappear... in order to search for your missing glasses!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Noooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Let us assume, hypothetically, that the witch did in fact drop this "evidence". That does not explain what purpose it would serve for her to make herself reappear! It would still make more sense for her to escape under cover of darkness!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wh-what...?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright, do you understand what I'm suggesting?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes! <thought>He means the reason Ms Kira made herself reappear at the crime scene... Okay, this is it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender! Enlighten us... Why did the witness feel the need to make herself reappear?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The answer is simple, Your Honour... Someone must have found her glasses!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">I say! I am not some "heartless" cretin!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Snowy and I were only interested in the milk, not some useless pair of glasses!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Look here, Bluey! Do I look like the kinda guy who would take someone else's stuff like that?!</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">...Absurd!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That was quite the all-out attack...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess that means...I was wrong, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">We can end this in one fell swoop. Now then, Mr Wright! Let's give this a bit more thought, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The answer is clear, Your Honour... The lenses on her glasses must've broken!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">"Clear"...you say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Clear as day! How else do you explain the fact she's not wearing them right this minute?!</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">............</line>
<line speaker="Mary">............</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">............</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps your point is not as clear as you thought it was.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh...I think the only thing broken here is my confidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">We can end this in one fell swoop. Now then, Mr Wright! Let's give this a bit more thought, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The answer is simple, Your Honour... she couldn't find her glasses!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">She...could not find them...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you've noticed, she's still not wearing her glasses right now.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Nghh!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Th-that's right! It doesn't change a single thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tonight, the two victims were engulfed by flames, courtesy of a magic spell. That very instant, four witnesses saw the flames erupt at the scene. It was at that point... That something you didn't expect occurred: you suddenly lost your glasses.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. You were scared that if your glasses were discovered at the scene of the crime... you would be suspected of being a witch!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wh-what did you say...?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If you recall, it had been raining quite heavily at the crime scene beforehand. Had she stated that she dropped her glasses before the crime, then naturally... one would expect the glasses to be soaked in water and covered in mud. However, the rain had already stopped at the time the crime itself was committed. In other words... One look at the clean, dry glasses would reveal she had dropped them later... Thus implicating her as the witch!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Nooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">I should have known... I was perfecting my "Rainfall Rending" technique in the forest... and not once during the rainfall did I see that flower maiden travelling along the nearby path!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's not all! In order to frame Ms Cantabella as the witch... you needed to leave this witch's sceptre behind at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I see! That would be the most definitive evidence that she is the witch...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The objective here...was to have somebody else discover the staff at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">Alas, that person was I!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">However... No doubt you came to realise that one can deduce which spells were used simply by examining the magic gems on the sceptre. In this case, one can see that the "witch" must have used Dimere to vanish from sight and make her escape.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's why, Ms Kira... you were left with no option but to reappear at the crime scene. That was the only way for you to avoid suspicion if someone were to discover your glasses at the crime scene! By reappearing, you'd be able to explain that you simply dropped your glasses when you rushed to see what had happened!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...... ...... You know... I've let you both ramble on and onnn... But...playtime is over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">So? So that's...it, then? I'm a witch because I dropped my glasses? I must have said it...how many times now? I lost my glasses days ago... Were you even listening? I'll say it again. Over a MILLION times! "I lost my glasses! I lost my glasses!" Do you LIKE evidence, Sir Defender? Do you LOVE proof, Sir Top Hat?! Then, PROVE I dropped my glasses at the crime scene! Ha! You CAN'T prove it! In. Other. Words. You lose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-that is correct... Proving such a thing...would indeed be impossible. To prove that the witness...dropped her glasses at the crime scene... ...What say you, Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ 'Tis indeed a question of proof, Milord. These glasses have been missing from the very beginning. The Knights of the Inquisition...found no trace of these glasses anywhere near the crime scene. Therefore... this witness cannot, in any way, be accused of being a witch!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">You heard the man.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-but! We were so close!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That girl is a witch! Can't anyone else see that?! What should we do, Professor?! ...Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Well, it would seem the young lady has finished what she had to say, wouldn't you agree, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes. It certainly looks that way, Mr Layton.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">What the...? What's with that face? D-do you find something funny here?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...It is as you said, Inquisitor Barnham.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">E-explain...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The defence raises just one further question. Why were you unable to find those glasses?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I... What do you mean...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You must have searched the area quite thoroughly looking for them. And yet, even now the knights have been unable to locate those glasses. Did you ever wonder why?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, that has become quite the mystery! Surely they must be around somewhere...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The glasses were lost to the wolves. That is the only explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...There is still one remaining place that you have not searched tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Huh...? Wh-what did you say...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The glasses were supposedly not found at the crime scene... Leaving only one other possible place!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wh-what is this...? You two... Have at you, Sir Blue Knight! Draw your blade, and reveal to the court where the glasses are supposedly hiding!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looks like I've somehow managed to make it through my first witch trial... It all comes down to this... The final piece of evidence... Time to clear up this case once and for all!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">I leave the rest in your capable hands, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The piece of evidence pointing to the one place not searched tonight is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The evidence you're looking for...is this right here!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...I now realise where our efforts should have been focused during our investigation. We should have searched the bakery where you work!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what do you mean?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I'd have apprehended you and thrown you in the pillories myself, for impersonating a defender... You have proven yourself but a stale imitation of a true Court Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I believe he is referring to you, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, I gathered as much... <thought>Looks like that wasn't right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Such reckless claims are completely unacceptable at any point in a trial, let alone at such a pivotal stage. I cannot allow this to go unpunished, defender!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't give up now! Try again! We're still in the home stretch here, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is it. This last piece of evidence... I have to get this right, for Espella!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tonight... there was one thing that was carried away from the crime scene right under everyone's noses.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">C-carried away...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I am speaking, of course, about this.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That's...the milk bucket that disappeared from the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Thus far, the defence's claim that the glasses were dropped at the crime scene has been regarded as mere speculation. ...However. If, Miss Kira, we find your glasses within the contents of this milk bucket... then our "mere speculation" will suddenly become fact!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wh-what manner of witchery...?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...What are you TALKING about?! Y-you're crazy! Just...crazy! N-no way could my glasses be inside that stupid bucket! That's just impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How about we quit with the speculation and actually find out...? What do you say, Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Th-that'll just waste the court's time! D-don't listen to them! Don't...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ 'Tis mandated...that the Knights of the Inquisition investigate any and all possibilities during the course of a trial.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Milord! The inquisition requests that this milk bucket be searched immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...V-very well! ...... ......... ............ Oh! Wh-what... WHAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ms Kira. As you can see, your glasses have been found inside the milk bucket. The truth is out. Nothing you say can change that now.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Which leads us to the next question... Specifically, a question of when. When did you drop your glasses into the milk bucket...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...! Wh-what...?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Wh-why is this happening?! This whole thing is ridiculous! Th-the answer is obvious, isn't it?! I dropped them afterwards! After I ran over to see the fire... I took a tiny peek inside that milk bucket! That's when they fell in...</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Mary:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Ngh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Each of these four witnesses has stated they heard the spell Ignaize being cast at the time of the incident. According to the Grand Grimoire... Ignaize "summons a circle of flame within a 1 metre radius of the caster". In other words... the real witch must have been at Ms Cantabella's side at the time of the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Indeed. That is when the glasses fell into the milk bucket. Therefore, there is only one logical conclusion. Only one person who could be the true witch.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...Ngh... Nghhh...Nghhh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What a very strange trial this has been... From the very beginning, we have all paid witness to an unusual set of circumstances. A baker turned defender, a surprise extra witness...and now, a "not guilty" verdict for the accused... Never have I seen such a spectacle!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ms Kira.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell us WHY... Why were you trying to frame Ms Cantabella?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You could easily have escaped the crime scene without a trace. There was no reason to frame anyone... This crime was a result of nothing but your overwhelming ill intent.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">To frame a person as a witch... is to condemn that person to death by fire. Surely you must know this... so why Espella Cantabella?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">............ Do you have any idea what it feels like to be a witch?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>What it..."feels like"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kira">...I didn't ask for this. I didn't ask for these powers, but I have them. And now, here I am... Begging for my life... I was living such a peaceful life until now. Selling flowers, getting scolded by my boss for not selling enough of them... That's why I was trying to put an end to these trials once and for all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Put an end to the trials?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">You all know what I mean! The one condition written in the Story that will end these witch trials!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">When the Great Witch Bezella has been put to the flames and vanquished from this world, these trials will come to an end...</line>
<line speaker="Kira">This was my chance to finally end all this. ...At least, that's what I thought. The sun had begun to set on that lonely forest path, and there wasn't a soul in sight. I always carried my hidden Talea Magica with me in case of a moment like this... I used my magic to expose that girl for what she really is! If I had been successful... then all these trials would finally end and I could go on living my peaceful life...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...What-what-what are you saying...?! A-am I hearing this correctly...? Are you actually accusing Espella Cantabella...?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Why do you think no one has ever seen the legendary Great Witch? It's because she's been hidden in our midst the entire time! She's protected! She's hidden from us! It's all part of the Story!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">P-part of the Story...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Kira">No! Please! I know you've all noticed it too! You could end this! All of this! That girl... It's all because of that girl... I beg you, please! She's... Please release me! Knights of the Court, isn't it your duty to protect the people of this town?! Give me another chance!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...That is where you're wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">'Tis indeed a knight's duty to protect... We are impelled to protect the citizens of Labyrinthia...against you and your ilk! The reason you were offered my protection until now was because your guilt was uncertain. There was the possibility that you were not a witch... The circumstances were such that it seemed another was guilty. That possibility has since disappeared and your innocence along with it. You now find yourself at the other end of my sword.</line>
<line speaker="Kira">N-no...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Vile witch, enemy of Labyrinthia! May the fires purge you from this land!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Espella:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">If...if it means putting an end to these horrible trials... Let me take her place! Let me be Bezella! Send me to the flames! P-please... If it would save her lif-</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This trial has proven beyond a shadow of a doubt that this flower seller, Kira, is a witch. And according to the law, all those found to be witches will be executed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-did he say "executed"? He can't mean...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This is most unsettling!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Bailiff! Ready the fire!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Nooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">No!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No! Don't do this!</line>
<line speaker="Kira">Listen to me! Don't let her fool you! Espella is the Great Witch! Hear me! There's no time to waste! She's Bezella! Take her... and then these witch trials... will be no more! The witch trials will end-</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So far we've always managed to pull off a win and get a "not guilty" verdict, but... winning has never felt this depressing...</thought> ...Oh, Espella! Are you all right?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes. I just... I just want to thank all of you. You all came to my rescue yet again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well, yeah. Of course we did.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-hold on a sec', Espella! What...did you say just now? "You all came to my rescue yet again"... You don't mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes. I...remember everything. I remember the last trial... I suppose that makes this the second time we've met...and the second time all of you have helped me.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...! Mr Wright, am I to infer that you and Espella have met before?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... Yeah, it seems that way. You too, Mr Layton?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Hmm. Perhaps it would be best if we briefed each other on what has transpired.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay, what should we discuss...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Espella paid us a visit in London. She had in her possession a letter from an old acquaintance of mine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that right...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Accidenti helped drive Espella straight out of Labyrinthia!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...You both kept me safe from the witches that were chasing me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait, did you say "witches"...? So they appeared in London too?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Regrettably, I am unable to say that our protection was absolute. When we saw you last, it seemed you'd managed to escape, courtesy of that passing freighter.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">O-oh yeah! That's right! What happened to you after that, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I rode the ship along the river for a while... before arriving at a nearby port. And then... that's when I met Mr Wright and Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I didn't know where the ship would end up... I...I felt very lonely out there...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Please accept my sincerest apologies. I'm afraid there was nothing else I could do to prevent it.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">No, no! Please don't blame yourself, Mr Layton! I...just didn't know what to do. So I tried to look for something...anything on the ship that might help me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Boy, you sure found something, all right! Or rather, someone... You ran into a master thief working as part of the ship's crew!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">D-did you say..."master thief"? C-crikey! That's amazing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wouldn't exactly say it was "amazing".</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">After that, I was taken to court...and that's when Mr Wright helped me.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...I see. Then, perhaps... somewhere deep within your mind must have existed a memory of that previous trial... and of Mr Wright. Hence why you thought to seek out his help when you found yourself in such an unfortunate situation this evening.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That makes sense! After all, Nick did make legal history that day in jolly old England!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">D-did you say he made "history"...? W-wow! That's incredible, right, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wouldn't exactly say I made "history"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">But then...after that, I was never able to find my way back to the professor. Even after I went through the pains of finding that clue, it ended up being taken away from me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A clue, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes. The tag that was hanging around the neck of that sweet little stuffed toy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That tag...was a clue? A clue for what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">I had a lot of time to think while I was on that ship. I thought about a lot of things... Like how to try and find a way back once the ship arrived at its destination. Things like that...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Find a way back"...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">A way back to Mr Layton and Luke... They were the only ones I knew I could depend on to help me.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...The pleasure was ours, Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">But...no matter how hard I tried, I couldn't remember the name of the town where they lived.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh?! You mean London, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh! That's it! "London"! That's what was written in Carmine's letter to Mr Layton. ...The blue teddy bear I found in that room was wearing a tag around its neck.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sorry, Espella...but PC Badger looks nothing like a teddy bear.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">On the tag, in very small letters, was written "London"! I recognised the name of the town... I thought it might be an address.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's because that stuffed toy was used in a special promotion, run by the London Metropolitan Police.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, that's right! Espella, you must have known that address was super important, so that's why you kept the tag, right? That way you could meet up with Mr Layton and Luke again.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I just...felt so lonely and helpless...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder, though... Who do you think really did it? Hit Olivia over the head with a pipe, I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, yeah...I guess we never did find out who the real culprit was...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ I do believe that may have some connection to the group of witches.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">What?! You mean, the witches that were chasing us through London?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. It could be that they noticed your escape on to that ship and managed to infiltrate their own way aboard.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">C-could it be...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Soooo...you're saying there was some big, scary witch lurking around the inside of that cargo hold?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...I'm afraid there is a rather high possibility that was the case. Those witches were intent on seeing you brought back to Labyrinthia, no matter what. However, in order to do so, they had to make certain you did not become entangled in any situation that may stall your capture.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... In other words, the situation with Ms Aldente, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Precisely. They must have knocked that crew member unconscious and attempted to recapture Espella before the police could arrive. However, their plan was clearly foiled, given that you ended up in court regardless. ............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And that's when she became my client...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">I...I just can't clearly remember anything that happened back then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you think there's a possibility that someone was pulling Espella's strings through the entire trial?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, maybe you're right... There was something a little strange about Espella at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright. Espella was introduced to you at the time as a schoolgirl, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">She would have had no knowledge of the world outside of Labyrinthia. That being the case, having her stand in an English courtroom as she was would pose a serious problem... Meaning that someone must have been attempting to cover up Espella's identity.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What?! But, Professor...could someone really do that?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That they could indeed, Luke. And if it is as I suspect... I believe our adversaries may be far more powerful than we originally thought.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just exactly who, or what, are we dealing with here...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, guys! Let's head back to the bakery for now! I bet the boss is waiting for us with one heck of a pastry feast!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh... Actually, I... I can't go home just yet.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh?! You can't? Aww...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Well, there are still a couple of legal procedures to be taken care of before I can go home. Please, you all go on ahead without me.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Is that so? Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I really must thank you all. Thank you so much for everything.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All righty then, Espella! We'll catch you later!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes. Farewell for now.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright, please allow me the pleasure of a proper introduction. My name is Hershel Layton. I am a professor of archaeology in London.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A...a professor...? Huh... Well, my name is Phoenix Wright. I'm an attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">As I suspected, you were no ordinary baker after all, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...I thought it was pretty weird myself, to be honest. I mean, I really did believe I'd been a baker all my life... But the more everyone kept saying it, the less sure I was that it was actually true. <thought>Just where did that memory come from, anyway...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey, Professor... If Mr Wright is an attorney, that must mean he's as smart as you, right?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ha ha. I'm afraid I can't really say, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm...buuuuuut... Behind every ace attorney there's an even smarter - not to mention beautiful, witty and utterly amazing - ace assistant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I think you also forgot humble.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">My name's Luke Triton. I'm the professor's apprentice!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm Maya Fey. And Nick here is my apprentice! Isn't that right, Nicky-boy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Nicky-boy"...? Hey, wait! Why am I YOUR apprentice?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Anyway, we should all head back to the bakery. Let's get a move on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure Espella will be back before we know it!</line>
<line speaker="???">...I would not get your hopes up about that, Sir Blue Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-Inquisitor Barnham!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Most impressive work tonight... 'Tis a shame you have kept such ability hidden until now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Trust me, Nick's lawyer abilities beat the pants off his baking abilities any day of the week.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, moving on! What do you mean by that, Inquisitor? Why can't Espella go home?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">New charges have been brought against Ms Espella Cantabella.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What?! N-no way... That can't be right!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You have realised it, haven't you? She is being charged under suspicion of being the Great Witch Bezella...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sh-she what...?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">How can that be? Am I to assume that charge is based purely on Miss Kira's accusation?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ It was not I who made the decision...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Regardless... the girl will return to court at the appointed time for further trial. Until then, I am to seek out any and all evidence pertaining to the Great Witch.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Pardon me, Inquisitor. When exactly is this appointed time?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...The investigation into this allegation will conclude on the day of the Storyteller's next parade. That would be...two weeks from today. Following our investigations into the matter, the trial of the Great Witch shall proceed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-what the...?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It would appear the girl has been withholding a dark secret from you all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Espella...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Espella Cantabella's questioning is set to begin shortly. That means visiting hours are over... I recommend you leave immediately.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Espella? The legendary Great Witch Bezella...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">The Story that dictates the fate of an entire town...and now a so-called "Great Witch" named Bezella... Most intriguing. It would seem to be up to us to uncover the answers to these mysteries.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But how are we supposed to manage it all in two weeks? Where are we going to find any evidence?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hm... Y'know, I was thinking... How do you address a Great Witch...? "Hail to thee, oh magnificent magical one!" Or maybe just: "Wassup, witchy baby?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What difference would it make? She's called a "great witch"! That's not someone I'd ever wanna meet!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ I believe I've thought of a solution to our problem. It's actually rather simple.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Professor Layton?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Allow me to explain, Mr Wright. The only way we may be able to solve the mysteries of this town and its residents is if we join forces.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>...He's right. We've come this far... There's no way we're just going to give up on Espella!</thought> Okay, I'm on board. I look forward to teaming up with you, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Me too, Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um...m-me too, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Now then, shall we press on? This marks the beginning of our own story... one dictated by ourselves and written by our own hands.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It does? I don't see anything out of the ordinary.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Is that so?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Let that be a lesson, defender. I recommend the defender take more care in raising his objections...or else.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have a feeling the judge's gavel has something to do with that "or else"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm...? I don't see anything odd...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's an...um...contradiction... somewhere in there...I think...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">From the look on your face, I can see that you are not convinced. I'm afraid I must hand down a penalty, defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...And I'm convinced from the look on your face you really loved handing down that penalty, Your Honour...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Are you saying that piece of evidence is somehow relevant to this statement?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It isn't, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is not. But this penalty is certainly relevant to your performance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I really think...the judge enjoys handing down these penalties.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Does it? I don't see how it does.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Penalty?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...If only there was a magic spell for objections...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">That'd be a REALLY lame spell, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Unfortunately, I do not see anything out of the ordinary here, defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaarrrgh! <thought>Shoot. I was way too hasty in presenting that evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y'know what they say, Nick: "Haste makes waste."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Unfortunately, our idea of what constitutes "decisive" evidence differs greatly. Defender, please refrain from hurling such ridiculous evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm sorry, Your Honour...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Or next time it shall be you that is "hurled" from this courtroom, Sir Blue Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Yikes. No need to get physical...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Mr Wordsmith?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">............ What is it, young one?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you have something to say about the testimony just now?</line>
<line speaker="Wordsmith">............ My mind is like the mid-afternoon sun... serene and hazy, mellow and yellow... As the day rolls on and the sun sets... My forgotten thoughts are my only regret...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It looks like he has a lot to say... none of it about the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Either that or he just isn't even listening.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Witnesses, continue with your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Ms Mary?</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you have something to say about the testimony just now?</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hello? Ms Mary...!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Baaa!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Doesn't look like she has anything to say. The goat sure does, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh...this witness is starting to get my goat.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Witnesses, continue with your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Ms Kira?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">...! Wh-what do you want?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you have something to say about the testimony just now?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">I've got far more important things on my mind right now. Like, will my boss fire me if I don't sell any flowers tonight?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Kira">He fires me. He fires me not. He fires me. He fires me not. He fires me. He fires me not...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nope. She's got nothing, Nick. ...Except maybe the sack.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I honestly didn't think being a flower seller could be so...stressful.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Witnesses, continue with your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Mr Knightle.</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">...What is it that you want to ask, baker turned defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you have something to say about the testimony just now?</line>
<line speaker="Knightle">"Something to say"? Hm...I have but one thing. The path to knighthood is an arduous one, but I remain steadfast in my resolve, as I travel down this long road!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Thank you for...that, Mr Knightle. Whatever that was.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Witness, please continue with your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, uh...mister?</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">*gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* Hey, gimme a sec while I polish off this drinky-poo here. All right, Bluey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-okay.</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">*gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Are you almost done?</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">*gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... How much more do you have left?</line>
<line speaker="Some Guy">*gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...never mind. Let's just move on.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Witness, please continue with your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, uh...mister?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">*gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* Hey, gimme a sec while I polish off this drinky-poo here. All right, Bluey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-okay?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">*gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Are you almost done?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">*gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... How much more do you have left?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">*gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... I don't think he's ever going to finish.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Witness, please continue with your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court sees no reason to further continue this trial. The real identity of the accused has been thoroughly proven. As such, the court finds the accused, Miss Espella Cantabella...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Your kind is a pox upon our land, and for that you must be sent to the fire. Detestable creature of magic! May the flames purge you from this earth!</line>
</xml>