
<xml>
<title>The Rite of Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Maya">.........</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya looks exhausted, but I can't blame her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, I was thinking about it all day yesterday... I never properly asked you to defend me, did I?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It doesn't matter. I'm on this case till the bitter end.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I know. That's why... I wanted to officially ask you for your help.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You got it, Maya! Let's do this. We gotta wrap this up and get back home so you can make your dream show come true. "The Steel Samurai vs. The Plumed Punisher," right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You bet!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You look as if you did not sleep last night, Barbed Head. It is written all over your face. How can you expect to put up a respectable defense like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm all fired up, and raring to go! <thought>I guess Maya's not the only one looking exhausted.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...........................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hm? Rayfa doesn't seem in the best spirits herself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. Go ahead, feign confidence now while you are still able. For I will see to it that your last rites are read to you this day!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Heh, guess it was just my imagination...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ready, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, Maya, let's head on in!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, if everyone is ready...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is ready, Your Magistry.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The prosecution is ready. Let us begin without further delay.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, no prayers this time, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I already offered my prayers for the latest victim during my visit to the crime scene. Being that the accused has already been found guilty of the first murder... ...let us hasten this trial, so we may put this dead lawyer walking out of his misery.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I could not agree more. In yesterday's trial, the accused was already found guilty of murdering the high priest. And today she will be tried for the murder of his disciple, Puhray Zeh'lot. Now then, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi, your opening statement, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Certainly. The accused has now slain two of the most devout clergymen in Khura'inism. Even the lowest level of Hell -- the Hell of Tickling -- would not be punishment enough.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*gulp* Th-Then... what t-terrible fate awaits her?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Bahlgilpo'kon Hell -- a realm of eternal agony. There she will suffer the endless punishment of ja'gar by the galuun of Puhlmo'ten. Furthermore, Guhljaama--</line>
<line speaker="Judge">E-Enough, enough! My blood runs cold at the mere thought that such a terrible place exists.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I was going to ask for a translation, but on second thought, ignorance is bliss.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">N-Now then, please continue, minus the part about the terrible hell awaiting the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">As you wish... The victim of this heinous crime was the high priest's disciple, Puhray Zeh'lot. He had been training under the high priest while living at the priest's home.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I had met him a number of times, and he seemed like an earnest young man. How tragic that he met such a terrible end.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The murder occurred at the Plaza of Devotion, during the Purification Rite. It was a bold crime carried out while the plaza was full of the faithful deep in prayer. The Warbaa'd Dagger was found impaled in the victim's upper back. The stabbing caused a spinal cord injury that killed him instantly.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, the Warbaa'd Dagger. Lady Kee'ra's weapon of choice.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">We have already established that the accused's prints were on the weapon. Incredibly damning evidence in itself.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-No... I didn't do it!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Would the defense care to respond?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The accused is innocent, and nothing can convince me otherwise! After all, the crime scene was packed with worshippers. How could my client possibly have committed this murder without a single witness?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The accused's fingerprints on the murder weapon alone is enough to render a verdict. As such, I see no need to debate this any further.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, once Her Benevolence conducts her Séance, it will be clear for all to see.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............... Your Magistry, might I have a word?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm? Is something the matter, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It is about the Divination Séance...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That's enough!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Your Benevolence!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Stop right there, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...As you wish. Forgive me for overstepping my bounds.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What was that all about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head, have you made peace with your fate? For this time, the Divination Séance will bring you to your knees!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm ready. And I accept your challenge. <thought>The only problem is, I have no weapons at my disposal. Our only hope now is what we can glean from the Séance vision and Rayfa's Insights.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The Divination Séance if you please, Your Benevolence.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, let us begin. ...Nayna! O Holy Mother! We hold this Divination Séance in your name! Let the eyes of everyone here be clear, and our ears be unstopped! O Dance of Devotion! Guide the victim's soul to me! So that we may receive their final memories in the Pool of Souls!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Your Benevolence! What in the world...?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Urgh... I was unable to evoke any sort of response. I called out the spirit's name many times... but to no avail!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Just as I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait, what does he know that we don't?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I had sought to confirm the contents of today's Divination Séance. After all, it is customary for the prosecutor to verify it beforehand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come to think of it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I must go perform a Divination Séance for Puhray Zeh'lot. It is our custom for the prosecution to review its contents before a trial begins.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And that is why I sought to stop Her Benevolence from performing it here. However, she insisted that it be done. She wished to try one more time here in the Hall of Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would appear Her Benevolence is tired from her manifold duties.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I am not anything of the sort! The victim's spirit will not answer my call, but I know not why! It is my sacred duty to convey the truth through the Divination Séance!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Rayfa...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What are we to do without a Divination Séance?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I suppose I shall have to deliver the last rites without them. The prosecution has already taken that into account when preparing for today. I am fully capable of proving the accused's guilt, with or without a Divination Séance.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ha ha ha ha ha! You never fail to impress, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is bad... The Divination Séance was my one and only hope.</thought> Your Magistry, Her Benevolence said she isn't tired! So, shouldn't we try to find out why the Divination Séance failed?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How curious, Mr. Wright. Why have you suddenly taken such a keen interest in the Divination Séance?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, explain yourself! The Divination Séance is for shedding light on an accused's crimes! It is the Holy Mother's hammer of wrath, that is ever poised to pound you into your grave! You should fear it, not plead for it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I believe in my client. Plus, yesterday, somebody told me something that changed my mind: The Divination Séance was once thought of as just another piece of evidence. If we were to correctly interpret the visions through careful analysis... ...then they would lead us to the truth behind what really happened. And the truth will show that my client, Maya Fey, is innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The truth is, you don't have anything else to fall back on, huh, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Maya, please, you're not helping.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">How dare you?! The voice of a mitamah is to be feared, not utilized by vile lawyers such as you!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Séances exact a heavy toll upon the royal priestess. It would be best not to burden her any further. Or does the defense feel that it can pose no counterarguments without the Séance?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, of course not! <thought>He saw right through me! I'll have to find a way to make the Divination Séance happen, or we're toast.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, since the Divination Séance is not possible at this time, I see no other choice. Let us proceed with the trial without the Séance, as Prosecutor Sahdmadhi suggested.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Thank you, Your Magistry.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Why you...! I will not forget this, Barbed Head! This will NOT be the last you see of me!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Now then, I will now proceed by providing an outline of the case at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. If the lead detective would please come to the stand, we may begin.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">........................ ...Sorry, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Detective Skye... I understand how you would wish to save the accused and the defense. They are your friends, after all. But you must let them go... and move on.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">B-But...!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">There is only one way to save them now: By giving their souls the chance to burn away the taint of their sins in the infernal flames.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ooh... I... I... I can't do this!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah! No eating in the sacred Hall of Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ms. Skye!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Y-Yes?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't worry about me and Nick. You just do your job. I'm sure Nick will figure something out... eventually!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">............... Right. Thanks, Ms. Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">How very brave for a criminal with a tainted soul. Very well, Detective Skye. Please proceed.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Okay, I can do this... Let me start with an overview of this case.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The latest victim was Puhray Zeh'lot.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... Well, that certainly makes sense. Would the defense care to respond?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I didn't spot any inconsistencies in her testimony so far. And I don't have any evidence in my arsenal. What am I going to do now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I was just wondering about how much the police actually looked into Acolyte Zeh'lot. Because it just might prove to be the key as to why the Divination Séance failed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you getting at?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm, well... It's just a hunch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait a second. During my investigation... ...Rayfa told me about how the Divination Séance works. If I could figure out why it failed... ...maybe she could try it again. Okay! Time to press for some more information!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">The latest victim was Puhray Zeh'lot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">According to the neighbors and others who knew him... ...he was a deeply devout youth.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I, too, have heard his name mentioned as one who was a fervent practitioner. I suppose you might say he was the high priest's star disciple.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Furthermore...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He had been training under the high priest, and living at his house for the past two years.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">We took statements from his neighbors and his fellow monks. They all corroborate our initial findings.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about you, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Well, when I first came here... ...I saw Zeh'lot praying under the high priest's instruction.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... So the results of the police investigation seem to check out...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The high priest's widow Beh'leeb Inmee has identified the victim's body.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh? ...Well, no! We also checked the ID card he carried and the data in his family registry. But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But what?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">His personal information didn't match any of the public records we cross-referenced.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe that's why the Divination Séance failed.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I-I'm not sure what you mean, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here's what I'm thinking...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim's address was wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um... Mr. Wright? Even if it was wrong, how would that affect the Divination Séance?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, uhh... You're right. It wouldn't. <thought>What was it that a Divination Séance required, again? Oh, right! Then there is only one possible answer!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">It looks like the fact that his personal info wasn't in the public records isn't important.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Ema, it is important.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim decided to hide his identity for some reason... In other words, he was using a fake name! The royal priestess uses a deceased's face and true name to summon their spirit.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Why, yes, that is indeed true.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">If he was using a forged ID and there is no mention of him in our public records... ...then he was likely an illegal immigrant. They are not uncommon here in Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An illegal immigrant? <thought>Come to think of it, Rayfa mentioned something about immigrants yesterday.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">But if that's the case, we have no way of knowing who he really is. We'll have to proceed without holding a Divination Séance this time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I had always thought that Acolyte Zeh'lot was Khura'inese. Oh, how the high priest must be lamenting his disciple's deception in the Twilight Realm. Well, Mr. Wright? What do you think? Should we add this to the testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is an important fact. Please add it to the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It would seem to be a fact most inconvenient for the defense. But, if you insist. Detective Skye, please add what you just said to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes, Your Magistry.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"He was an illegal immigrant, so we don't know his real name."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Your Magistry. There's no need to add it to her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, then. Please continue if you would, Detective Skye.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes, Your Magistry. We still don't know the victim's true identity, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Y-Yes, that's very likely the case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that I have an opening, what next? It's still not going to help me learn Zeh'lot's true identity. Was he really an illegal alien?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">He was an illegal immigrant, so we don't know his real name.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No, not if he was an illegal immigrant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you actually confirmed that he was in Khura'in illegally?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, we don't have any conclusive evidence. But there's also no evidence of him being a citizen of Khura'in, either.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hoh boy... Now what do we do...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What if there was a clue in the evidence you gathered?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's probably our only hope at this point. <thought>If he really was an illegal immigrant, our proverbial goose is probably cooked.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He may have been mistaken for a rebel and killed due to his connection to the high priest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm sorry, Mr. Wright, but... </line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But...!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">No "ifs," "ands," and most of all, no "buts." The accused was posing as Lady Kee'ra. And she killed Acolyte Zeh'lot because she mistakenly believed him to be a rebel.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Th-That's not true!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm sorry... The verdict has already been read in that case. I have to assume that it's fact now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arngh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, you mentioned that Ema's testimony might hold a clue as to why the Séance failed.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I did, but it's really just a hunch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That might mean there was a mistake made during the investigation. It would have to be information that would impact the Séance. Hmm, what could it be...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now I know why the Divination Séance failed, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm, nothing's really changed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, which means we're in big trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If he really was an illegal immigrant, it's going to be real hard to find out his real name...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess our only choice is to give up on the whole Divination Séance thing. If only there was some way to find out the victim's real name...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, Detective Skye... But the police missed something important in their investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh?! Wh-What are you talking about?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim was undeniably a Khura'inese native! And this crime scene photo proves it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-It does?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a little hard to see, but look closely. You'll see clear proof that the victim was Khura'inese.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wh-Where? I don't see anything that would prove that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This proves the victim was Khura'inese!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, don't worry, Your Magistry. I don't understand it, either!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your ineptitude is equally unfathomable, defense!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh... I better take a good look at that photo again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your claim that the victim was Khura'inese... Is it not but another one of your lawyerly untruths?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No. If you look here in this photo, you'll see that he's definitely Khura'inese!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at this tattoo right here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why that's... a tattoo of a peach?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I would like you all to think about the meaning of this tattoo.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, umm... The victim really liked peaches?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, peaches are a favored delicacy here in Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">They happen to be a personal favorite of mine. The sweetness of their abundant nectars and the softness of their perfectly ripe flesh... They are a blessing from the Holy Mother herself.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, I've suddenly got a craving for peaches!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...After the trial, Maya. Right now we have bigger fish to fry. Unfortunately, that is NOT a tattoo of a peach.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...It is not a peach, you say? Then what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a closer look. Haven't you seen something like that before? Namely, the tattoo on the high priest's brow.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This mark is only borne by members of the Khura'inist clergy!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, they're shaped differently, but there's a reason for that. The victim had the peach-shaped tattoo inked over an existing tattoo for some reason. However, the dark red portion is exactly the same as the mark all Khura'inist clergy bear.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, you're right!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Until about twenty-some-odd years ago, everyone did get one, didn't they? I myself bear one on my right buttoc--</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">That is entirely too much information, Your Magistry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Information on everyone who enters the clergy is maintained at the temple! All we have to do is look up a monk with a mark in the same spot!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm on it! I'll let you know if I get any hits!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">That will not be necessary. If you seek information on the clergy... ...I have it all right here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! You never cease to amaze! ...So, tell us, is there anyone who fits the bill?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.............................. ...There is just one, and his name is Rheel Neh'mu. He became a monk twenty years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then that must be the victim's real name.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But why would he have tried to cover up his tattoo with another one?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah... There must've been some reason...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! That's not important right now. The important thing is we know his real name.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're right! Your Magistry! Now that we know the victim's real name... ...the Divination Séance might finally work!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... A lawyer who willingly seeks a Séance... This is entirely unprecedented.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Heh. You are but digging your own grave, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We won't know that until we try. <thought>Sure, it's risky, but it's our only hope!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Let the Divination Séance be held once more! </line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">.............................. Why would a lawyer work so hard to see the Divination Séance be held once more? You are a fool, Barbed Head. And your foolishness shall yield no gratitude from me. For with the truth revealed by my Insights, I shall gladly seek your demise!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Bring it on, Princess. Because I will correctly interpret each and every one of your Insights.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph! You will regret ever thinking you could use my sacred Insights as evidence. O Holy Mother! We hold this Divination Séance in your name! Let the eyes of everyone here be clear, and our ears be unstopped! O Dance of Devotion! Guide the victim's soul to me! So that we may receive their final memories in the Pool of Souls!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Oh, my! It is just as Mr. Wright surmised. Puhray Zeh'lot wasn't the victim's true name! And now at last, we have seen the victim's final moments!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But... All we could see was the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You seem terribly disappointed. I take it you did not find any fodder for one of your infamous turnabouts?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ngrk!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I, on the other hand, have discovered something: Conclusive evidence that establishes the accused's guilt!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You did?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ha ha ha ha ha! A most surprising surprise attack! ...So, tell us, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi, what is this conclusive evidence you have found?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...The Plumed Punisher theme song that the deceased heard. Please consider this item here. It was confiscated from the accused during her interrogation.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, that's my Plumed Punisher strap!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">When you press the magatama on the Plumed Punisher's belt...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It seems the accused inadvertently pressed the button in the midst of her crime. This strap is an extremely rare item, is it not, Ms. Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You'd better not break it! There's only one of those in the whole wide world!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maya, noooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Heh heh heh heh! It is just as I said. Your flights of fancy... have come crashing down on you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She sure seems to be enjoying this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I've never seen her look so thrilled before either.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It is time to accept the fact that the Divination Séance is far more than mere evidence! It is the very truth that brings the hammer of justice down upon the accused!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is as conclusive as evidence can get. Now then, if there are no further objections...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this? Do you take issue with the Divination Séance?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, I have issues with it. I just don't know what they are yet. But that's never stopped me before!</thought> The Divination Séance is not the absolute truth! It only becomes the truth after it's been interpreted correctly.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Grr! You do not know when you are beaten, do you, you foolish lawyer. I am the only one who speaks for the mitamah of the deceased! If you believe there to be errors in my Insights, then let us see you prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The victim was offering up his prayers...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That is everything the deceased experienced in his final moments.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Her Benevolence's Insights have painted a detailed picture, both vivid and true.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I didn't notice any holes there. As they stand now, those Insights are really stacked against us. I'll just have to go over each and every one of the deceased's sensations very carefully.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The victim was offering up his prayers...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was it really the night of the rite...?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What do you mean? It could not be otherwise! The accused slew Acolyte Zeh'lot after killing the high priest during the Purification Rite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The only problem is, the deceased's spirit does not corroborate that.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What's this?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a good look at what the victim smelled. Do you see how it says "gingihl"? Acolyte Zeh'lot shouldn't have smelled any gingihl on the night of the rite!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let me back up my statement with some evidence for you. This should explain how the victim couldn't have smelled gingihl on the night of the rite!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">			</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............... To be frank, your assertion stinks, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Does it smell that bad?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. I nearly passed out from the stench.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I didn't know my bluffs had such a pungent aroma...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would seem that the smell of gingihl is unrelated to the case at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, the fact that the victim smelled gingihl is extremely important. It's important because the smell shouldn't have been present on the night of the rite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The high priest's wife, Beh'leeb Inmee, told me about the Feast of Blessings. The feast includes a number of gingihl-based dishes. And they're only supposed to be served at a certain time the day before the rite!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, I believe you're right! I had completely forgotten about that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">During the feast, the unique smell of gingihl pervades the entire kingdom. The fact that the victim smelled it means... ...he was murdered between noon and 3 PM the day before the Purification Rite!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That's enough!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. I am not so easily fooled! Did that autopsy report not make it clear? The estimated time of death was during the rite!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, right. I taught her about that yesterday.</thought> Forgive me, Your Benevolence... ...but the estimated time of death is just that -- an estimate. Depending on the circumstances, it's possible for it to change.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Wh-What's this?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Like, if a body was kept cold, the slowed rate of decay makes the death seem more recent.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, I believe I have heard something of the sort before. Hmm... If it is as Mr. Wright claims... ...the estimated time of death in the autopsy report will have to be revised.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Nnnggrrrrrrrrrrr! Barbed Head! You... You blinded me with science!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry... <thought>Wait, what am I apologizing for?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. ...No matter. The murder may have occurred in the afternoon hours the day before the rite. Nevertheless... The murder weapon with the accused's prints on it is incontrovertible evidence. I will now amend my Insight to account for this new truth.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The time of death has been corrected, leaving my Insight infallible.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! A change in the time of death is bound to cause some sort of an inconsistency!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I had something that showed what it was like on that day, it could really help.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The victim was offering up his prayers...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The change in the date and time of the crime... ...has caused a new inconsistency to surface.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What's this?! Augh! You are making that irritating face again! Cease that at once!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but this is the face I was born with. Now, let's focus on what is important -- what the victim saw in his final moments.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Do you have bats in the belfry, Barbed Head? There is nothing to see. The ground at the plaza was all that entered the victim's eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Impossible, you say?! ...Do explain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This piece of evidence shows why the plaza's ground was not visible that day!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">			</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.............................. Are you sure that shows why the ground was not visible?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm positive!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I know not what the defense thinks he sees... ...but I see a lawyer spouting nonsense.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps this will open his eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay, I guess that wasn't it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, I will ask you once more. What piece of evidence shows that the plaza ground was not visible that day?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This newspaper has an article that is tiny in size, but huge in importance. It says that the ground was covered with "thick, white ice" the day before the rite.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What?! B-But...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The victim did not see so much as an ice cube on the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. And so we must ask: What WAS the victim looking at in his final moments?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">If you have something to say, then say it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The last thing the victim saw was not the ground at the Plaza of Devotion. This can only mean that he was killed elsewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Wha--!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Wha--!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wha... WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?! Then where do you propose the victim was actually killed?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, tell us where! Otherwise, your argument is worthless!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, about that... <thought>Argh, I hadn't gotten to that part yet!</thought> Any ideas, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... Let me think... Well... it's somewhere green and shaggy, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right, but where could that be?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What is it, Barbed Head? Giving up already?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-Not at all! <thought>Now, where have I seen something green and shaggy...?</thought> This shows where the victim was killed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">	</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">	</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That shows where the victim was killed?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll leave it up to your imagination.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I was imagining giving you a penalty, but now I don't have to just imagine it anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Imagine that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I knew it. The victim could not have been killed anywhere but the plaza.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, he was killed elsewhere! <thought>It was somewhere green and shaggy. I know I've seen someplace like that, but where?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The secret hideout the rebels were using!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The rebel hideout? There was no such place anywhere on the floor of that chamber!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're absolutely right. <thought>There's no place... on the floor, anyway.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then what did the victim see in his final moments if not the floor of the rebel hideout?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is what the victim saw in his final moments!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Hm? It looks like some of the moss about halfway up has been disturbed. ...I wonder why that is?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If the reason why the moss had been disturbed is what I think it is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright? You've suddenly grown quite silent.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, sorry. I was thinking about my answer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... how could he have been killed in such a place?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good question... What are your thoughts, Your Magistry?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Didn't your mother tell you not to answer a question with a question?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mamma mia... <thought>The same pattern as the one at the plaza... Let's take a good look around.</thought> Your Magistry! Please give me another chance!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, then. But there is a limit to my patience. Now, show me where you believe the victim was killed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The shaggy green surface the victim saw was one of the moss-covered stone slabs! As you can see, there are two distinct hand-shaped impressions in the moss here. I believe the victim was killed while he stood there with his hands pressed against the slab!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I concur. There is no proof that a murder occurred in the rebel hideout.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Indeed! What evidence do you have of this?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've already shown you the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please take a look at this second version of the photo I just showed you. You can see the results of the luminol test I performed in the rebel hideout. This is proof positive that someone had been bleeding in front of that stone slab.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is this true?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This information has already been provided to the police.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Detective Skye, to whom does this blood belong?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">W-We thought it was the high priest's blood that flowed in from outside... ...so we haven't tested it yet.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then you must do so at once!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Y-Yes, Your Magistry!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It appears the police have finished testing the blood. Detective Skye, your report, please.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The blood found in the rebel hideout... ...belongs to Puhray Zeh'lot, just like the defense claims!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Detective Skye, do you realize what your blunder has done to me? When this trial concludes, I want to see you in my prayer chamber. There, I will deliver a joyous sermon onto you for eight hours straight.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I-I'm really sorry, but... Please, anything but that!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Nick, maybe, just maybe... ...this is the chance we've been waiting for!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yep, it would seem so. <thought>I hate to do this to Ema, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Go for it! It's full speed ahead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim was killed in the rebel hideout the day before the Purification Rite. Then, his body was moved to the Plaza of Devotion by someone we've yet to identify! So, when we thought we saw Acolyte Zeh'lot praying during the rite, he was already dead!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Aaaaaaugh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's not all. If he was killed at the Inner Sanctum, that would explain one more thing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And that would be...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How the time of death was made to look later than it actually was. The proof of which, was left behind at the sanctum. This points to how the time of death was made to appear later than it actually was!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-And why not?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Then let us test this idea on YOUR body.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Errr... Pass?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright's body may still be alive, but he appears very much brain-dead.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Urgh... I blew that one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So no one attempted to cover up the true time of death.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I believe someone did!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, these are... photos of the Inner Sanctum?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd like you to focus on this one. The proof is right here in this photo. This is how the time of death was made to appear later than it really was. Do you see how the snow has been removed from this one spot only? That's because it was used to keep the victim's body cold. And that's why the time of death wasn't what it seemed!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That's enough!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The time was mistaken? And the place, too? And just what do you believe that proves?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That my client is innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What of her fingerprints on the dagger, and the Plumed Punisher theme the victim heard? You have failed to address these two key pieces of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk! I-I see your point.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wasn't this your big chance, Nick?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ahh... I'm really hoping that the difference in location can invalidate... ...either the weapon or the theme song from being used as evidence against you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Actually, that might be possible. At least, for one of them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really?!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What's this? You say you can contradict our argument for a key piece of evidence?! Very well, let us see you try!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, take a good look at the rebel hideout photo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Uhh... ...Oh! The defense can invalidate this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The dagger with my client's prints on it. It's inconsistent with the facts that have come to light!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I fail to see how you can contradict the fact that her fingerprints were on the weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We do not take kindly to such stalling tactics here in the Hall of Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh, sorry... <thought>I guess there's nothing wrong with the murder weapon. Then that leaves...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You have not found any contradictions with the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the fact that the murder didn't occur at the plaza DOES affect the evidence! It results in a contradiction with the Plumed Punisher theme song the victim heard!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The Plumed Punisher theme? And how do you intend to support such a claim?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Since the murder happened in the rebel hideout... ...there's something there that played the theme song, other than my client's strap!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It wasn't the strap?! Is this true?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The item that played The Plumed Punisher theme song was this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a brand-new Plumed Punisher collectable!  It was just released the other day!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Nonsense! I have never seen such an item before!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Nor have I.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why is everyone around here a Plumed Punisher expert?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems there was nothing there that could have played the Plumed Punisher theme.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Your Magistry! Something in the hideout played it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is a Plumed Punisher alarm clock. I believe the victim heard its alarm go off!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That's enough!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What proof do you have that the alarm went off?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What proof do YOU have that it was my client's strap that played the theme song?!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Auuugh! Do not twist the facts with your lawyerly wiles! Either way, the accused would still be guilty based off of her prints on the murder weapon. And here is what really happened!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Though there have been some twists and turns, that is the truth of what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arngh! <thought>I won't get anywhere until I can eliminate the dagger.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Most impressive, Your Benevolence. I see no inconsistencies anywhere in the prosecution's case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, there is one!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this?! You still claim there to be an inconsistency?!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. Try as you might, the outcome will always be the same.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The victim stood with his hands on the stone slab in the hideout.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim was originally thought to have been stabbed while bent over in prayer. But he was actually standing with his hands against the stone slab. So the question is, where did the sensation of something heavy come from?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Yes, I see your point.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Since the victim was standing, he couldn't have been held down.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Eeeep!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then tell us, Mr. Wright, what was that heavy sensation felt by the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... What caused the heavy sensation Zeh'lot felt? Any thoughts, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhh... I agree, that sense of heaviness seems important, but... There's also the matter of Zeh'lot's hands on the stone slab. Why were they even there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could it be related to the cause of the heavy sensation?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright? Do you have an answer for us?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Of course! <thought>If I just envision the state Zeh'lot was in when he was killed...</thought> The cause of the heaviness the victim felt was...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The killer jumped on him from behind!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmm... Why do you suppose the killer would do that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe they craved human contact!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">People who crave human contact do not kill those they seek contact with. But it's clear you've lost contact... with reality!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Talk about a reality check...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wasn't there something really heavy in the rebel hideout?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course! That's it! The cause of the heavy sensation...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The only conceivable cause is... ...the stone slab falling over, trapping the victim underneath!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...! The stone slab came falling down on him, crushing him underneath.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. That was the cause of the heavy sensation the victim felt.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Or do you claim that the dagger was plunged in after the slab had fallen on him? Plus, had the killer been behind the victim, they would have both been crushed together.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well? Would you care to explain?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sure, I'd love to. That doesn't mean I can! Hmm... How could the dagger have been plunged in after the slab fell on the victim?</thought> The killer couldn't have plunged the dagger into the victim after the slab fell on him. But, what if the murder weapon wasn't what we thought it was?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Well, there WERE other weapons in the rebel hideout. But the entrance to the hideout is right by the stone slab. There isn't enough space between the two to use any of the weapons found within.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... There's not much space by the entrance, is there... <thought>So, what was the real murder weapon, then? I better think of something!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">If the murder weapon wasn't the dagger... ...then the dagger must've been plunged into the victim after he was already dead. That means he was stabbed at least twice, but the autopsy doesn't mention that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then he must've been stabbed in the same spot with something shaped like the dagger.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Would the defense care to offer an explanation sometime this century?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait, wasn't there something dagger-like near the scene of the crime? ...Something that had a shape similar to the Warbaa'd Dagger?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Present your evidence at this time, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This shows what really killed the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I do not see any similarities with the evidence presented.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack... Now that you mention it...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your ignorance shall cut you like a knife, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Something shaped like a dagger...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I better compare the shape of the dagger with the rest of the evidence again.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, I would have the defense cut the nonsense and offer a proper answer this time. What really killed the victim, if it wasn't the dagger?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is this not the photo from the scene of the high priest's murder? Are you suggesting the murder weapon is hidden herein?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is what really took Puhray Zeh'lot's life!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops, I think I flubbed that one!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Your barbed head would have made a far more effective weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ha ha ha ha! Indeed! Perhaps the real murder weapon was the defense's own cranium!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You won't be laughing after I show you what really killed the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, you will not be laughing after this penalty, either!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yowch! <thought>Let's try that again... It's right here in the photo... The sharp object that took Zeh'lot's life!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But that is the...!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The warbaa'd statue?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly! The warbaa'd statue has dagger-like feathers protruding from it. That is what really took the victim's life!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Haven't you heard? The warbaa'd statue also functions as the hideout's door.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The statue can pull a complete switcheroo!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">A switch... eroo...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To put it simply... it's a revolving door!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A revolving door?! Why, that makes perfect sense!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Therefore, I believe the truth behind the Divination Séance to be this! As the victim entered the secret hideout, the stone sculpture came toppling toward him. He threw up his hands to stop it, but its weight forced him backwards. Unfortunately, the warbaa'd statue was right behind him.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Th-This... This cannot be...!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That's enough!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">B-But the accused's fingerprints were found on the dagger!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She had held it while rehearsing for the rite. Which is when her prints got on it!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Gah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is a shocking turn of events, but... ...there is a great deal of circumstantial evidence in the defense's favor. I believe we must accept that the warbaa'd statue was what killed the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now that we know how Acolyte Zeh'lot really met his demise... ...there's no basis for claiming my client committed this crime!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nice work, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...How can this be happening yet again? The Divination Séance...  is the only truth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Your Benevolence. It's not the truth itself, but it IS a means for shedding light on the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Nnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you understand now? Your kingdom needs lawyers so that they can interpret your Insights.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">B-But... That means I... ...I have been misinterpreting the voices of the spirits all this time?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Your Benevolence! Are you unwell? All the color has drained from your face.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">........................ I will be fine. Continue your proceedings without me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...As you wish.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I feel kind of bad for her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, I would have the defense continue. Please explain what you have learned now that we know how the victim actually died.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Acolyte Zeh'lot was killed in the hideout before the high priest's murder. That means the body found at the Plaza of Devotion was moved there by the real killer... ...but only after the Warbaa'd Dagger was thrust into him... ...to make it look like the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That does seem to agree with what we now know. But why would the real killer go to such lengths?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe stabbing Acolyte Zeh'lot's body with the dagger and moving it to the plaza was...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was a warning from the Twilight Realm. You know, something like... "Thou shalt not leave bodies lying around the Inner Sanctum."</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You putrid-headed lawyer. Have you already forgotten? The high priest's body WAS left lying in the Inner Sanctum.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">If the killer did not wish for bodies to be left at the Inner Sanctum... ...they would have moved the high priest's corpse, as well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>W-Well, he's not wrong...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">How is this for a warning, Mr. Wright? Thou shalt not offer half-baked answers!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Next time, I better look before I leap.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. It seems the reason why the body was moved will remain a mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Your Magistry. I believe I can explain why!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe this was a crime committed for fun. The killer is someone who loves watching people react to murder scenes. That explains why they placed the body where so many people would see it!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">But then why would the killer bother meddling with the estimated time of death?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, umm... That's a good point.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Sitting through your silly answers is no fun, but I do enjoy levying penalties afterwards.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh... Well, I don't.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. It seems the reason why the body was moved will remain a mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Your Magistry. I believe I can explain why!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was an attempt to make my client look like a serial killer. That's right! The real killer planned all of this. This forged serial murder case!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">They did?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's it, Nick! Keep hammering away!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Like those putrid, hole-riddled clumps of curds that only a rat like you could love... ...your reasoning, much like your putrid, hole-riddled brain, has putrefied.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's his deal with things going putrid...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You have yet to overturn my argument that the accused is the killer. A careful analysis of the chain of events up to the killing exposes the truth as follows: Disguised as Lady Kee'ra, the accused found the rebel hideout the day before the rite. But Acolyte Zeh'lot had followed her there after noticing her suspicious behavior. Caught by surprise, she pushed the stone slab toward him... and we know the rest.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-I've never been to the rebel hideout in my life!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">When the high priest arrived at the sanctum the next day, he realized what she had done. That is when the accused murdered him in order to silence him.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I believe Prosecutor Sahdmadhi has posed a compelling scenario. The defense, on the other hand, has yet to disprove the accused's guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The dagger in his corpse was likely a warning to the rebels. Something along the lines of "Lady Kee'ra will slay the Defiant Dragons."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So that is why she moved the body to the plaza for all to see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now he has the judge convinced, too?! I thought I'd finally made some headway!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright? About time for one of your groans of distress, is it not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">("G-Groan of distress"...? It kills me to admit this, but I've got nothing to counter his argument with. And I still haven't disproven the allegations </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is it not time to end your futile struggle? You were already judged guilty yesterday. That makes you a dead lawyer walking. Accept the death that now awaits you, and in doing so, finally know peace.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">A dead lawyer walking, indeed... Then again, are not all lawyers who practice in Khura'in? But I must admit, I misspoke earlier. Allow me to amend my statement. I had said the defense's reasoning had a putrid, cheese-like smell... ...but I now realize the stench was from his own putrid body, on the verge of death.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now I'm a rotting zombie... Think... Who could've killed Zeh'lot the day before the rite? Who knew about the rebel hideout, and could gain access to the Inner Sanctum?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Only those involved with the rite can enter the sanctum, so... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Wait a second! <thought>Only a rebel would've known about the secret hideout. And the only person who was involved with the rite, had access to the sanctum... ...and was suspected of being a rebel is...</thought> Ahhhhhhhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Did somebody come to mind?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes... Except there's one huge problem.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A huge problem?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">What are you two going on about? Plotting your escape from this sacred hall? I would not put it past you, considering you have no means to raise further objection.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I don't do something, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi will have this one in the bag. I'll just have to bluff my way out of this, regardless of that huge problem.</thought> Your Magistry, I believe there is another suspect in Puhray Zeh'lot's murder!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, there is one person who knew everything!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">D-Does such a figure truly exist?! Tell us, who might that be?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe the prime suspect in Acolyte Zeh'lot's murder is...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh... Whaaaaaaaat?! Wh-Why would you say such a thing, Nick?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry, Maya. I had to say something, and I guess I just panicked.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I pity the accused or being saddled with such a rash lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Jeez! This is all your fault, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Don't worry, Maya! I'll get it right this time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you fail to give a serious answer this time, I will personally put a muzzle on you. Now, who is this new suspect you believe to have killed the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. I, too, find it hard to believe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ulp... I guess that makes three.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Three strikes and you're out, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh,  I'd better rethink my strategy... <thought>I'm looking for someone who was allowed to enter the sanctum and knew of the hideout. Such a person could very well have killed Zeh'lot!</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you fail to give a serious answer this time, I will personally put a muzzle on you. Now, who is this new suspect you believe to have killed the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It had to be someone allowed to enter the sanctum, and who knew of the hideout. And that would be... the high priest. He could've committed the crime if it occurred the day before the rite!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You would pin a crime upon the dead, knowing very well they tell no tales? Have you no shame!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Dead men tell no tales... That is definitely a problem. If only the high priest could tell his side of the story.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Umm. Hmm... ...Wh-What? Do I have something on my face?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Wait a second! <thought>Could this actually work?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, no! Don't tell me I have some of my breakfast caught between my teeth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No, if there's even the slightest possibility, I'll have to go with it!</thought> Your Magistry! Dead men DO tell tales! Therefore, I would like to request the high priest's testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">His... testimony?! And just how do you propose we get the deceased to testify?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a way for the dead to testify!  It's known as...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All we have to do is have another Divination Séance with the high priest's spirit!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">We already conducted a Séance with his spirit during the previous trial.What do you possibly hope to gain from another one?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Speak of that sacred ritual needlessly, defense, and reap the consequences.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How could we get a dead man to tell his tale? Ah!  I wonder if Maya could...!</thought> Your Magistry! There IS a way for the high priest to testify.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Summon him here by means of spirit channeling!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What did you just say?!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Spirit channeling? Has this lawyer finally gone insane?!This is sacrilege! May the Holy Mother strike him down!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Peace! I am frankly astonished you even know of such a thing. But spirit channeling is a secret art that only Her Eminence Queen Ga'ran can perform. And Her Eminence is far too busy with other duties to perform it at our pleasure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I suspected as much. That means our only hope is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">..................... ...It's okay, Nick. You can tell them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, Maya...! I thought you wanted to keep it a secret here in Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't worry. It's not like it's against the law or violates some religious precepts, so... ...I don't think we'll be punished. At least, I hope not.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But this is a crucial period for you. It'll decide whether you become master of Kurain.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We don't have any other choice, now do we? If I'm found guilty, it'll be a lot worse than not becoming master of Kurain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...All right. Thanks, Maya. Actually, there is someone here who is capable of channeling spirits.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">But even Her Benevolence Princess Rayfa finds the Divination Séance to be a challenge. Who could possibly have greater spiritual power than she, aside from the queen?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Th-That... That would be... me.</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Is this some sort of a joke? A foreigner could not possibly have such power!Even the royal priestess is incapable of such a feat!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Peace! Peace, I say! ...Is this true? Is the accused capable of performing the secret art of spirit channeling?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm...  well...  yes. Yes, I can.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, Your Magistry, we'd like your permission to begin!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That's enough!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Your Benevolence!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">This is an outrage! An outrage, I say! First, you make a mockery of the Divination Séance, and now, spirit channeling?!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Her Benevolence speaks the truth! Spirit channeling is a sacred rite!Foreign devils! I say they should be put to death immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Still your voices! Barbed Head, spirit channeling is a most sacred and secret of arts. Are you prepared to face the consequences of what you propose?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, I am.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Your Benevolence, are you saying you approve of their use of spirit channeling?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I will judge whether their claim is true. If this is but another of their lies, they shall be executed on the spot!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, then! Umm... Your Benevolence? What if the accused accidentally calls forth an evil spirit?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Do you truly believe this foreigner is capable of channeling spirits?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, umm...  no, but I wanted to be sure, as I am responsible for the safety of all present.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Well, an inexperienced practitioner could inadvertently call forth a dangerous spirit. But do not fear, for I have a Magatama of Parting. With it, I can send spirits back to the Twilight Realm by halting the flow of spiritual power.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Th-That is a relief, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">These foreigners have thrown down the gauntlet. Let us not shirk from their challenge! We must prove them guilty and deliver their last rites! Do I make myself clear, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Perfectly, Your Benevolence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, the accused may channel the high priest's spirit. But first, we must take a short recess to prepare. We will resume as soon as the preparations are complete. Until then, this court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, Maya, but this was the only way. You sure you're up for this?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Thanks for believing in me, Nick. Even though I don't know if my channeling ability is on point yet...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, right... Before she started training here, her success rate was only about thirty percent.</thought> I know you can do it, Maya. <thought>At least, I hope she can!</thought> So you sure you're ready?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, at least I think so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't sound so confident. What about all your training?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Training's one thing. Actually doing it is another!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I see... (Uh, oh... If she fails to channel the high priest, we're </line>
<line speaker="Maya">Relax, Nick! You can count on me! I'll show you what my training's done for me! This will be a moment you never forget!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Okay... <thought>I just hope it's unforgettable in a good way.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Once we hear Abbot Inmee's story, I'm sure the truth will come to light!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I hope so, but he was hiding the fact that he was a rebel, so... ...I doubt it'll be as cut-and-dried as all that.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">They are ready for you. Please return to the Hall of Justice at once.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, Maya, 'm counting on you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You got it! Here we go!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We have received official approval for the accused to channel a spirit here today. Now, if you will, Ms. Fey, please proceed.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Yes, Your Magistry.</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">I can't believe this! Only the queen should channel spirits!Execute them! Put them to death right now! Death! Death! Death! Death! Death! Death! Death! Death!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>C'mon, Maya! I'm counting on you!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">........................ I have been studying here in Khura'in for two years now... ...so that one day, I will be the master of Kurain, a village of spirit mediums back home. But first, I shall show you all the fruits of my training in your kingdom.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow,  she seems really confident.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. A neophyte practitioner such as you could not possibly channel a spirit.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, Your Benevolence, how about this? If I succeed, will you stop calling me a neophyte?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Very well. ...IF you succeed.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I will. Just you watch! O spirit of Tahrust Inmee, slumbering in the Twilight Realm... Return now... to the world of the living!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Hrrm? What is this place?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">N-No...! Th-This cannot be!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">P-Pohlkunkaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">...I-It's the high priest! The accused really can channel spirits!I don't believe it... The accused's spiritual power is the real deal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Go, Maya!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I do not understand... This cannot be... This simply cannot be...! ...I-I--! I must step out now before I forget myself!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Abbot Inmee!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">...Would this be the Twilight Realm? And what of this luxurious mane of hair...? Is it perhaps a gift from the Holy Mother, for decades of faithful service?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A... Abbot Inmee?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">My! But if it isn't His Magistry. Have you, too, shuffled off that mortal coil?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please, do not count me among the dead. It is only you who has passed on. But the spirit medium, Maya Fey, has brought you back among us today!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Wh-Why... Acolyte Fey has mastered the secret art of spirit channeling?! I suppose that explains these gorgeous locks.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">When I pass from this world, I, too, hope to be channeled with a full head of hair!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Though it be for the briefest of moments, I give thanks for this splendid coiffure. ...Praise be to the Holy Mother! However, this kimono is a bit too snug for my tastes. ...If you would excuse me! There, that is better.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Could we get to his testimony now? <thought>And I wish he'd kept his top on!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Hrrm? Why, you are that foreign lawyer the people speak of as of late. And is this not the Hall of Justice? Why have I been summoned here?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Forgive us for calling you back from your eternal rest... ...but you have been accused of murder. Might we ask you to testify on your own behalf?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">...I have been accused of murder? That is troubling, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AAAAAH! Wh-What's with that crazy pose?!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Is this really cause for such astonishment? Even the lowliest of monks can achieve such body control with the proper training.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh...  I wonder if Ahlbi will be able to do that someday.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Will the defense please explain the situation to the high priest?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd be happy to. Your disciple, Puhray Zeh'lot, has been murdered. It happened on the day before the Purification Rite. And the crime occurred in the rebel hideout hidden within the Inner Sanctum.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">A-Acolyte Zeh'lot? He has been killed? ...Who would do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Someone who knew of the hideout, and had access to the Inner Sanctum... In other words, YOU, Abbot Inmee. After all, weren't you secretly a rebel?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">..................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh dear... That's still Maya's body...I hope he doesn't break anything.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Hrrrmph. .....................</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Wow! The high priest is amazing!To think he had mastered such an advanced prayer pose!He's still worthy of our veneration, even if he IS a rebel!Praise be to the Holy Mother! Praise be to the Holy Mother!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Oh, my. Have my rebel allegiances been exposed? Not even my wife knew of that. It seems to rest in peace is not my fate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did you, a devout priest of Khura'inism, join the rebellion?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Oh, right!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Abbot Inmee, the prosecution believes the one who slew both you and Acolyte Zeh'lot... ...to be Maya Fey, who had been playing the role of Lady Kee'ra in the rite.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Hrrm. Being that I was dead until just a moment ago... ...my memory is a bit hazy.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Could you please do your best to remember?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">...HRRMMMMMM! It is all coming back to me. It is as Prosecutor Sahdmadhi concluded. I was slain by none other than Maya Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The high priest's statement has proven my assertions with regards to his murder correct.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">NOOOOOOOOO! B-But what about Acolyte Zeh'lot?! You were the one who killed him, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Hrrmm...? I know naught about my disciple's murder. Furthermore, I have an alibi of my own.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An alibi?! Seriously?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ha ha ha ha! It seems the testimony the defense had been hoping for is working against him. Now Abbot Inmee, your testimony, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Yes, yes of course.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">I have an ironclad alibi for the time during which the murder took place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You had guests? <thought>Just past noon... That's right about the time Zeh'lot was murdered!</thought> Are you sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Absolutely.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come to think of it, Rayfa told me about a spirit's memory...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">A spirit's memory is cut off at the moment of death.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So even a spirit that is brought back after centuries doesn't sense any gap in time... ...between the moment of its death, and the moment it is channeled?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, and yet, it clearly recalls all of the memories it had in life.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The high priest seems to know exactly what he's talking about. So, the question is, what would be the best angle of attack?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">I have an ironclad alibi for the time during which the murder took place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Hrrrmmm... Are you, perhaps, mocking me? Or is it, perhaps, the Kingdom of Khura'in itself you wish to ridicule?</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">C'mon! Everyone and their grandma knows what alibi means!We're not a bunch of country bumpkins here! We have plenty of courtroom dramas on TV!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Peace, peace! Peace, I say! Mr. Wright, would you care to clarify your last statement?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Please! Don't take it the wrong way! It's just, alibi is a rather technical term for a priest to use so naturally.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">I assure you, I know how to use the term. In fact, I had even hoped for a chance to do so one day. I suppose that even I, a high priest, am not immune to such trivial worldly attachments.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh, I see... <thought>Still, he seems unusually calm and composed. It's almost as if he had prepped himself for something like this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Just past noon on the day before the rite, I was entertaining guests at my home. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">That I was. We gathered around the table for a most enjoyable conversation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He said his guests could corroborate his alibi. That can't be good for our case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure that was the same day as the murder? Maybe you've misremembered.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">KAAAAAAAH! Do not doubt my mnemonic faculties! I may have died, but my memories up to that point are crystal clear!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry...  <thought>...He's pretty thin-skinned for a priest. Though, I guess I should've known better than to doubt his memory...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">A spirit's memory is cut off at the moment of death.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So even a spirit that is brought back after centuries doesn't sense any gap in time... ...between the moment of its death, and the moment it is channeled?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, and yet, it clearly recalls all of the memories it had in life.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Ahh... There's nothing better than enjoying gingihl cuisine with dear friends. That way, everyone's breath becomes equally malodorous!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right...</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">And I believe my guests can corroborate this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">It was none other than His Magistry, along with his family. He couldn't attend the rite due to work, so he stopped by ahead of time. My my, how his daughter has grown.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Wait a second.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let me set the record straight right now. I am NOT a rebel. Thank you for that wonderful meal, Abbot Inmee. Lady Inmee's cooking simply cannot be beat!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">...So there you have it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When exactly was His Magistry at your home?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">He was there from 2 PM to 3 PM. Indeed, precisely the time period within which Acolyte Zeh'lot was slain.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, and we had a rousing chat concerning the game of Kachu'demahl.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'll just have that added to the testimony. After all, it was I who visited the high priest's home.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"My guests that day were His Magistry and his family. They visited from 2 PM to 3 PM."</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">My guests that day were His Magistry and his family. They visited from 2 PM to 3 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As sure as sure can be! Oh, how wonderful it is to finally have my actions be admissible as evidence in court!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">His Magistry was at my home during the exact time period of the murder. Come, let us put this behind us. I could not have possibly committed this crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How can you be so sure? What if the clock or watch you were using was off, or you misread the time?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There was a clock right near the table, and it had the exact same time as my watch.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Now do you understand, lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How am I going to attack his alibi? Maya, what do you... Oh, right... She's kind of busy right now.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">What? Is there something on my face? Hrrrmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, not at all! <thought>I'll just have to start chipping away at that statement about his alibi.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh...! <thought>His Magistry's a witness?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Are you satisfied now? There is not a single discrepancy in Abbot Inmee's alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I-If I give up now, it's all over!</thought> N-Now hold on a second! <thought>Is there something, ANYTHING wrong with the high priest's testimony?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait... Never mind.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I thought as much. After all, there can be no killer other than the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. And therefore, I see no need to continue these proceedings.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Do I really want to give up now? If I do, Maya will be found guilty. Was there really not a single thing wrong with the high priest's testimony?</thought> Please, Your Magistry, wait.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There IS a discrepancy in the high priest's testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There is? Well then, perhaps you could explain what it might be.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is what was wrong with his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The meal was too short to be a Feast of Blessings celebration.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The length of the feast is of no consequence. Besides, Lady Inmee's testimony regarding the feast was the same as her husband's. Or would you suggest Abbot Inmee and his wife are lying?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. I see no problem as you allege.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oops... I guess I'm wrong then.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems there is nothing wrong with Abbot Inmee's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I beg to differ. There IS a problem! A big one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's way too friendly with you, Your Magistry. Are you two perhaps, more than just friends?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-M-Mr. Wright! What on earth are you suggesting?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You seem awfully flustered, Your Magistry.  That seems kind of suspicious.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">You are free to think anything you like about our relationship. But it has nothing to do with the case at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I concur! Now, I believe you know what comes next.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Guess I got a little carried away there...)</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems there is nothing wrong with Abbot Inmee's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I beg to differ. There IS a problem! A big one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">After Abbot Inmee was channeled... ...no one ever stated what time Acolyte Zeh'lot was murdered!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">N-Now that you mention it...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Despite that, you claim to have an alibi from 2 PM to 3 PM. That means you knew that Acolyte Zeh'lot was dead... ...when you were still alive!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Haaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait... I think I saw something just now... No, I must be imagining things.</thought> So, tell me, how did you know what time the crime had been committed?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Ummm... About that... Hrrrmmmmmm... HRRRRNH! ...Open your heart! Let the Holy Mother in!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Why! We've been blessed with the high priest's sacred words of prayer!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">All who serve Her Holiness must strive to banish worldly desires from their soul! Open your heart! Let the Holy Mother in! Purge your mind of greed and bias!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I feel as if my very soul has been cleansed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can't fool me! Prayer may banish worldly desires, but it can't make a contradiction disappear!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">How can you be so sure?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's that supposed to mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">This lawyer seems to think little of the power of Khura'inist prayer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">..................  Y-You never cease to amaze, Prosecutor. As he has surmised, there was a listening device installed at the hideout. It enabled me to instantly learn of anything unusual, even when I was not there.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Remember, the rebels had been using this as a top-secret hideout. It would be perfectly natural for them to install such an apparatus.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait, come to think of it, when I was searching the rebel hideout...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm? <thought>There's something under the banner. A microphone? What's this doing here? Was someone trying to record something with it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That was a listening device...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">It starts recording whenever it detects movement. And I heard just such a recording after His Magistry and his family left. If you look in the desk in my study, you will find the tape in question.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right, then... Bailiff!</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Yes, Your Magistry!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Go retrieve the tape in question from the high priest's home.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">At once, Your Magistry!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The power of Khura'inist prayer... Even a putrid brain such as yours should understand it now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's like the contradiction really did vanish.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">We shall ascertain the content of the recording once we have the tape. In the meantime, I would ask Abbot Inmee to continue with his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">I was entertaining His Magistry and his family when the crime occurred.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to find some way to attack his alibi. If only Maya were here... She has a way of putting me at ease. But seeing her like this is only creeping me out!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Though the high priest was a rebel, he was still a Khura'inist holy man. Therefore, take care in your questioning, lest you invoke the ire of our people.</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">How dare he suspect the high priest! May the Holy Mother strike him blind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>As if this wasn't hard enough already...</thought> Nice try, but I'll stop at nothing to find the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">I was entertaining His Magistry and his family when the crime occurred.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Indeed. My wife Beh'leeb was treating them to her wonderful home cooking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your wife was there that day?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Why yes. She was in the kitchen cooking up a storm the entire time.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">She takes her culinary duties most seriously, you see. That is why she was in the kitchen cooking without pause the entire day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So, the judge never saw Mrs. Inmee? Should I have Abbot Inmee add that statement to his testimony?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please add that statement to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">As you wish!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I doubt Mrs. Inmee has anything to do with this case.</thought> Please continue with your testimony, Abbot Inmee.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">After His Magistry left, I listened to the tape recorded via the listening device.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">My wife Beh'leeb was in the kitchen cooking the entire time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">The menu that day featured "hahtin'supaise" and "mehl'tenmoht". They are both traditional Khura'inese dishes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't even begin to imagine what those are...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Thank you! It brings me great joy to know you enjoyed your meal. Now, once His Magistry and his family had left...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Mr. Wright. Do you still feel the need to question the high priest? His alibi is as tight as tight can be.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This isn't going so well. I'd better ask him about something else.</thought> ...I'm curious, Abbot Inmee. Did you stop by the rebel hideout after His Magistry left?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">...Yes. I thought it would be wise to assess the situation. But as I said before, there was nothing to see. The hideout appeared as it always had.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the victim's body...?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">It was nowhere to be found. Acolyte Fey must have already disposed of it, and anything else incriminating.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So,  when you saw the rebel hideout... ...it looked like it does in this photo?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Hrrm... Yes, I would say that is how it appeared that day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So the stone slab had been put back in place...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Is it not time to concede defeat?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, wait! I need just a little more time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. If you insist...</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">When I listened to the tape later, I heard a man and a woman quarreling.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Indeed! Each night, I would secretly check what the listening device had recorded. I would've been in serious trouble with my lovely wife had she discovered my secret.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you really tell what happened by the audio alone?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Long years of ascetic training have sharpened my hearing. It is but a simple matter for me to ascertain a situation by the sounds I hear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Practicing Khura'inism improves your hearing?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Hearing is but one of the senses it can improve. If one can focus and attain inner peace, all five senses can be sharpened. ...Why, the warbaa'd over in the bazaar just cried. Did you not hear it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gimme a break...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Mr. Wright. Do you still feel the need to question the high priest? His alibi is as tight as tight can be.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This isn't going so well. I'd better ask him about something else.</thought> ...I'm curious, Abbot Inmee. Did you stop by the rebel hideout after His Magistry left?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">...Yes. I thought it would be wise to assess the situation. But as I said before, there was nothing to see. The hideout appeared as it always had.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the victim's body...?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">It was nowhere to be found. Acolyte Fey must have already disposed of it, and anything else incriminating.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So,  when you saw the rebel hideout... ...it looked like it does in this photo?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Hrrm... Yes, I would say that is how it appeared that day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So the stone slab had been put back in place...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Is it not time to concede defeat?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, wait! I need just a little more time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. If you insist...</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">It sounded like an altercation between Acolyte Zeh'lot and Acolyte Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">I'd say that was the most reasonable conclusion under the circumstances. Or perhaps Acolyte Fey has an alibi that you can prove?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... I-I'm afraid not.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Then I suggest you make like a mollusk, and clam up! Now, I will continue my testimony if I may.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Mr. Wright. Do you still feel the need to question the high priest? His alibi is as tight as tight can be.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This isn't going so well. I'd better ask him about something else.</thought> ...I'm curious, Abbot Inmee. Did you stop by the rebel hideout after His Magistry left?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">...Yes. I thought it would be wise to assess the situation. But as I said before, there was nothing to see. The hideout appeared as it always had.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the victim's body...?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">It was nowhere to be found. Acolyte Fey must have already disposed of it, and anything else incriminating.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So,  when you saw the rebel hideout... ...it looked like it does in this photo?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Hrrm... Yes, I would say that is how it appeared that day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So the stone slab had been put back in place...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Is it not time to concede defeat?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, wait! I need just a little more time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. If you insist...</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">After that, there was a loud noise, followed by haunting silence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">It was a terrible crashing sound. Poor Acolyte Zeh'lot...  It must have felt so heavy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It must've been the sound of that stone slab falling over.</thought> <thought>Should I have him add that statement to his testimony?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please add that statement to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">As you wish.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's probably not that important.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">I would describe the noise as a terrible crash. Poor Zeh'lot... It must have felt so heavy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Yes, the sound, no doubt, was poor Zeh'lot's death knell. Such a tragedy, for he was a fine disciple. I would ask all here today to give a prayer for his departed soul. Zuh'shiray matahmee yomah!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Zuh'shiray matahmee yomah! Zuh'shiray matahmee yomah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I feel like such a jerk for just trying to do my job right now...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Mr. Wright. Do you still feel the need to question the high priest? His alibi is as tight as tight can be.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This isn't going so well. I'd better ask him about something else.</thought> ...I'm curious, Abbot Inmee. Did you stop by the rebel hideout after His Magistry left?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">...Yes. I thought it would be wise to assess the situation. But as I said before, there was nothing to see. The hideout appeared as it always had.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the victim's body...?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">It was nowhere to be found. Acolyte Fey must have already disposed of it, and anything else incriminating.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So,  when you saw the rebel hideout... ...it looked like it does in this photo?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Hrrm... Yes, I would say that is how it appeared that day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So the stone slab had been put back in place...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Is it not time to concede defeat?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, wait! I need just a little more time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. If you insist...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So, all he knows about the crime is what he heard on the tape? And he was with His Magistry and his family at the time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Now that I have proven the soundness of my alibi... ...I believe it is about time for me to return to the Twilight Realm.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What's the rush? Why not enjoy some more time among the living?! <thought>I better find a way to attack his alibi soon. I'll just have to press harder and hope something useful comes out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I doubt there's much more testimony I could wring out of him by pressing. And I can tell the judge is growing impatient. There have been some changes in both the testimony and the evidence. That means there could very well be an inconsistency somewhere. I've got to find it -- before he returns to the Twilight Realm!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Abbot Inmee, you said, and I quote: "Poor Zeh'lot... It must have felt so heavy."</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">..................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why do you think he felt something heavy? You said the hideout looked like it did in this photo. If so, there's nothing that would lead you to believe he had experienced a heavy feeling.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">..................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The fact is, of course, a stone slab did fall over onto Acolyte Zeh'lot... ...impaling him on the warbaa'd statue behind him. But that was only revealed through Her Benevolence's Divination Séance earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Would the defense please get to the point?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My point is, simply hearing a crashing sound... ...shouldn't have automatically led him to conclude the victim was crushed to death.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I still don't see your point.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm saying that the high priest knew. He knew how the victim was really killed!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that is information only the real killer could've known!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I-I definitely saw it that time! I've got the high priest's spirit shaking in his boots -- or should I say, sandals!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's true. So he can't be the killer. However, he knew how Zeh'lot was killed -- something only the killer could know. Can this discrepancy be resolved somehow?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright?! We're waiting for an explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I was just getting to that. <thought>Time to think of something quick!</thought> The high priest knew something only the killer could've known because...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He heard it during this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How could that be? The true cause of death came to light before Abbot Inmee came back to this world.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... Umm, well then maybe...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let me stop you right there before you waste any more time with your inane excuses.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess I couldn't have wiggle my way out of that one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you're going to make such a bold claim, I insist you back it up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry, I'm going to do just that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe he figured it out later. After all, we figured it out. He could have, too!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">W-Why, yes, it is as the lawyer says.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. You are stating the obvious... and negating your own point, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, umm... Oops? L-Let's pretend that never happened!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then you shouldn't have brought it up in the first place!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Urk! Now I'm really on His Magistry's bad side.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you're going to make such a bold claim, I insist you back it up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry, I'm going to do just that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He must've heard how the victim died from... umm... ...from the real killer!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Hrrrrrrrrmm? The real killer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Of course! That makes perfect sense. I don't want to believe it, but this is the only possible explanation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, tell us! Who is this real killer?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's gotta be someone close to the high priest... Someone without an alibi... The person most likely to be Zeh'lot's killer is...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.....................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...On second thought, I changed my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You are free to change your mind, but that won't change your punishment!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That was pretty sloppy. The high priest has an ironclad alibi. But was there someone who didn't?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I expect a serious answer this time, defense. Who do you believe is the real killer?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Magistry, while you were visiting the high priest's home... ...you didn't see Mrs. Inmee at all, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No,  I never saw her, but... Wh-What does that have to do with anything?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did the high priest ever leave your sight?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, we were talking the entire time. And the food was brought right to the room's entryway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, the high priest has an ironclad alibi. But his wife does not!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">What the devil are you insinuating?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm insinuating that Mrs. Inmee might have killed Acolyte Zeh'lot!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No... We can't entirely discount the idea. Especially if you consider that... ...Mrs. Inmee could've been the one posing as Lady Kee'ra.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-Are you suggesting that Mrs. Inmee killed her husband, as well?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As sad as it is to think she'd kill her own husband to rid the kingdom of rebels... ...I don't think we can rule it out.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Tahrust:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yikes!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">You claim my wife is that rebel-hunting Lady Kee'ra? And that she slew both Zeh'lot and myself? My lovely wife?! That is utterly impossible! KAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yikes! I have never seen the high priest so angry!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It is as Abbot Inmee stated. And the accused has already been found guilty of his murder. It is far too late to overturn it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That's right, Mr. Wright! N-Now apologize to the good priest before he gets angry again! Quickly now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I'm not going to apologize! The true identity of Lady Kee'ra is a major piece to this trial's puzzle! Admit it, Abbot Inmee -- your wife, Lady Inmee, killed you. Yet even now, you continue to lie in an effort to protect her.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Tahrust:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ack, I completely forgot about that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">That abominable Lady Kee'ra figure who slew me and Acolyte Zeh'lot was the accused!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is bad, but I can't give up now!</thought> D-Don't forget! My client doesn't have the strength to fight rebels, either!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">..................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How could a weak young woman like her possibly...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Surely, the accused possesses the strength -- or should I say, the power. ...The power to battle those black-hearted rebels.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">...My good prosecutor, I see you have come to the same conclusion as I. Such keen insight!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Then you have figured it out as well, Abbot Inmee? May I ask you to explain it to this putrid-brained lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Certainly. For I cannot allow him to frame my lovely wife for murder! Foreign devil! Your Magistry, allow me to testify as to how Maya Fey is that murderous Lady Kee'ra!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Well, if it would assuage your anger... ...then by all means, please testify!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Acolyte Fey channeled Lady Kee'ra's spirit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Do you understand now? Murder by spirit channeling explains everything. This is the only way the accused could have defeated one rebel after another!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Indeed, I am a living... or shall I say "dead" proof of her terrible power.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaaaagh! <thought>Maya's ability to channel spirits... It's come back to haunt her!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Now, is it not time to let it go, and move on, defense?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, never! I'll never give up! <thought>Now what? Think, think...! How can I prove that Maya couldn't have channeled Lady Kee'ra?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Acolyte Fey channeled Lady Kee'ra's spirit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Far-fetched, you say? Why, the very fact that I am here proves she has the power to channel spirits.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh... B-But you've no proof she actually channeled Lady Kee'ra.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Oh, but I do.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">She is a spirit medium who knows Lady Kee'ra's true name, so she could have done it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">We are talking about the infamous "rebel hunter" here. That modern-day Lady Kee'ra has captured many a rebel all by herself. And among them have been more than a few great warriors.  Who but the real Lady Kee'ra could have accomplished such a feat?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Hmm, it would be difficult for a mere mortal. That leaves the real Lady Kee'ra of legend as the only likely answer.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Indeed! Is this not proof enough that the real Lady Kee'ra of legend had been channeled?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The real Lady Kee'ra of legend. That's an oxymoron if I ever heard one. Then again, the people of Khura'in believe legends to be true.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">So, it was the real Lady Kee'ra who returned to root out the rebels among us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">There is no way to prove that. But to doubt the existence of Lady Kee'ra is to doubt Khura'inism itself. It is not for us to question. We must simply believe.</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Yeah! How dare you doubt our legends?!You'll regret saying that, you pohlkunan! Lady Kee'ra's gonna strike you down!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ulp! <thought>I won't get anywhere until I can refute their claims with some evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">She attacked and killed me with a strength far beyond any mortal woman.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">You need but look at the wound she inflicted upon my body. ...Though I had hoped to never have to think about that again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your wound...? <thought>It was pretty deep, and there was a tremendous amount of blood.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">And while Acolyte Zeh'lot was rather small in stature, he was strong. Nevertheless, he was no match for the sheer strength of Lady Kee'ra.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya's spirit channeling is proof that she's Lady Kee'ra? This is not good! I'll have to prove she didn't channel the original Lady Kee'ra!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Tome of Secrets is only given to the priestess who performs the Purification Rite. Is this your proof that my client could have channeled Lady Kee'ra?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Yes, indeed! For it contains the true name of Lady Kee'ra, a secret only revealed within!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Abbot Inmee... I'm afraid you're mistaken. This couldn't have been used to channel Lady Kee'ra.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">What nonsense?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Wright, would you care to explain?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is why my client couldn't have channeled Lady Kee'ra!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, umm... nothing, as far as I can tell.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, as far as I can tell, this has everything to do with a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I know the answer's here somewhere. I just need to remember the requirements for spirit channeling.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems there can be no doubt that the accused channeled Lady Kee'ra.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, she couldn't have!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lady Kee'ra's face is hidden behind a mask in the Tome of Secrets! You need both a name and a face to channel a spirit!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">...It can't be!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Without a face... ...it would've been impossible for my client to channel Lady Kee'ra!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Therefore, the claim that she became Lady Kee'ra by means of spirit channeling... ...is patently false!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Gah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And with Lady Kee'ra out of the equation, my client had no motive to commit murder!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But then... ...who is the rebel-hunting Lady Kee'ra we've been reading about in the paper?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Yes, who is this other suspect, if indeed there is one at all? Let us hear the defense's brilliant deduction!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Think, THINK! The true identity of Lady Kee'ra is the key to solving both murders! I thought Mrs. Inmee was suspicious, but her pregnancy takes her out of the running. And Mr. Are'bal is a rebel, so that doesn't make sense. That leaves us with... Hmm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, you have that look again. The one where you know you have to say something, but you can't figure out what it is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is my chance to really turn up the heat. I'll just have to stir the pot till something floats to the top!</thought> Your Magistry, I know who's been posing as the rebel-hunting Lady Kee'ra!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes! Completely!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I sense that I may regret this, but please go on and explain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Your Magistry. <thought>This is who's been posing as the rebel-hunting Lady Kee'ra!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">But has that not been my assertion from the very start?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would appear the accused is guilty after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Err... Umm... I made a mistake! Your Magistry, I'd like to strike my previous statement from the record!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. But there will be no striking this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! I'm sorry, Your Magistry...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph, I will not tolerate silly answers like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know. I've got a serious answer lined up this time, I swear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! These may be tears of laughter, but rest assured there is no mirth here for you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is no laughing matter! Let's think about that again. Who could be posing as Lady Kee'ra? If I cross off all the unlikely suspects, there's only one name left on the list!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Khura'inism teaches us to be merciful, so in that spirit I am giving you another chance. Who do you believe is posing as Lady Kee'ra?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The true identity of the rebel-hunting Lady Kee'ra we seek is... ...Puhray Zeh'lot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Magistry. I whittled down the list of suspects until there was only one left.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, of course! <thought>I will have some in a moment, that is. At least, I hope so... Maya wasn't Lady Kee'ra, and neither was Mrs. Inmee or any of the other possibilities. That leaves Zeh'lot, and I have the evidence to prove it!</thought> The evidence that proves Acolyte Zeh'lot was posing as Lady Kee'ra is this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I fail to see your point.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course, you don't! I just wanted to throw that out there and see what happened!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, here's your answer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... curiosity's killing my case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, I will ask the defense once more. What proof do you have that the victim himself was Lady Kee'ra?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is what proves that Acolyte Zeh'lot was Lady Kee'ra: Lady Kee'ra's warning letter!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">How absurd! What could that possibly prove?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Prosecutor Sahdmadhi. You stated that this warning letter proved that my client was Lady Kee'ra. And the reason you gave was that the high priest's house was locked tight. But there was another member of the family who lived there.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Therefore, Acolyte Zeh'lot could have delivered the warning anytime he wanted!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">...What is he talking about? That's just not possible!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">...............</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Are you saying Lady Kee'ra was not the culprit, but rather the victim?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's exactly what I'm saying.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But...! That would... That would overturn the entire premise of this case! This trial has proceeded on the assumption Lady Kee'ra was behind the serial killings. But if Lady Kee'ra is one of the victims... ...who was the killer, and what was their motive?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The only suspect left is Mrs. Inmee. And there's only one possible motive!</thought> What if Mrs. Inmee is a rebel?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Fiend! You're still bent on casting suspicion upon my lovely wife?! Blasphemer! You have no evidence of this! Repent for the mistrust in your soul! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Hrrrrrngh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Was Lady Inmee a rebel, and did she pose as Lady Kee'ra to kill Acolyte Zeh'lot? Or was Acolyte Zeh'lot a rebel, and was the accused the Lady Kee'ra who killed him? I would say either scenario is just as likely. ...What are we to do now?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Tahrust:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, but what of it?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Heh heh heh heh heh. So that's it... Heh heh... Heh heh heh heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's gotten into him?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Ho ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! HA HA HA HA HA!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-Abbot Inmee! Just what is so comical?!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Forgive my outburst... That has simply tickled my funny bone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What did?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">The theme song came from the Plumed Punisher clock, you say? ...Hmph! That alarm could not possibly have gone off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What makes you say that? The clock was working just fine the last time I checked!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Try using your head for a change. Would not the existence of a secret hideout be given away if an alarm kept going off?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, you don't mean...</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Indeed! We leave the alarm switched off at all times!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-Nooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-In that case...</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">I am sad to say that the defense's claim does not hold water!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Would you care to respond, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, umm... <thought>This can't be happening. Not now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">This should put an end to the lawyer's futile struggles. The theme song the victim heard was from the accused's strap, just as we suspected. Therefore, the accused is the rebel-hunting Lady Kee'ra, and the victim's killer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I need an opening. Something I can raise an objection to.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">That Plumed Punisher theme song Acolyte Zeh'lot heard in his final moments... I, too, heard it by way of the listening device.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But did you really? If you had heard it, why didn't you testify to the fact before?!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Is it not obvious?! I did not know such a tune could become a key matter of dispute. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, the matter of the theme song came up before Abbot Inmee was channeled.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right. Well then, umm... What if he's lying about the clock's alarm being switched off?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Miserable wretch! That would be a pointless lie -- one easily disproven!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">If you check the clock, you will see that the alarm is, in fact, switched off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh... Come to think of it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmm... What a fine item. And this switch...If I'm right... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We set the switch back into the off position before we left.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">I remember hearing it clearly. Those distinctive taiko drums in the intro are etched in my mind. They went... Daka don-don-don, don-don-don-don!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Distinctive taiko drums in the intro?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...This trial has gone on far too long. Shall we move ahead to the verdict phase now?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">By all means. And let us also return Abbot Inmee's spirit to the Twilight Realm.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Before I go, let me say a word to my darling wife... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The high priest's statement is inconsistent with a certain piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is?!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Still you writhe in defiance of your fate? The very sight reminds me of a tortured soul,  writhing in flames! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You won't be saying that once I show you the evidence. <thought>Now, all I have to do is pick the right one! This piece of evidence is inconsistent with that statement about the taiko drum intro!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">..................  Alas, I am afraid your "drift" is lost on me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is it, now? <thought>Did I get it wrong?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense is up to his usual tricks again.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Then let us whip him into shape!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ha ha ha ha! By all means, Abbot Inmee! Please do the honors!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Open your heart!  Let the Holy Mother in! KAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What if I refuse...? Now, what was the high priest's exact statement again?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">I remember hearing it clearly. Those distinctive taiko drums in the intro are etched in my mind. They went... Daka don-don-don, don-don-don-don!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please! Let me try that again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is what's inconsistent with his statement. ...My client's Plumed Punisher strap.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">What does that have to do with anything?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It plays the Plumed Punisher theme song. And here it is! The theme to "The Plumed Punisher: Warrior of Neo Twilight Realm"! Do you see what I mean? The music the victim heard in his final moments... ...might not have been the Plumed Punisher theme song!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm? I'm afraid I am not following you. What was it if not the Plumed Punisher theme?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In his final moments, Acolyte Zeh'lot heard...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">People praying!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Are you suggesting they were praying to the beat of the Plumed Punisher theme?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">No one would do such a thing in the holiest of holy Inner Sanctum.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I have never heard of anything so absurd.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, me neither... <thought>The high priest heard a distinctive taiko drum intro. But the Plumed Punisher theme doesn't feature taiko drums.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's clear now. The victim did indeed hear the Plumed Punisher theme in his final moments.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Your Magistry. That's not what he heard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was the music from the Dance of Devotion coming from the temple!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">I distinctly heard the Plumed Punisher theme. Or are you suggesting the music for the Dance of Devotion... ...has been changed to the Plumed Punisher theme?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do not make light of our religious traditions, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack... I didn't mean any harm, honest. <thought>The high priest heard a distinctive taiko drum intro. But the Plumed Punisher theme doesn't feature taiko drums.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's clear now. The victim did indeed hear the Plumed Punisher theme in his final moments.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Your Magistry. That's not what he heard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are no taiko drums in the intro of the Plumed Punisher theme! So what Acolyte Zeh'lot actually heard in his final moments was...  ...the theme of "The Steel Samurai: Warrior of Neo Olde Tokyo"!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Peace, peace! Peace, I say! ...Mr. Wright. What is this Steel Samurai of which you speak?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Steel Samurai: Warrior of Neo Olde Tokyo is an action-hero show from America! The Plumed Punisher theme is a total rip-- Err... I mean,  is very similar to it. If you didn't know about The Steel Samurai, you could easily mistake the two.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">But the fact that Acolyte Zeh'lot heard music from an American action-hero show... ...is irrefutable evidence that the accused was in the secret hideout!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, no. You have it backwards.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">B-Backwards...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. Ms. Fey met an avid Plumed Punisher fan here in Khura'in. And as a token of their friendship... ...she traded a certain Steel Samurai item she had for the Plumed Punisher strap.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Hrrrmmmm?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And this avid Plumed Punisher fan... ...was the one who killed Acolyte Zeh'lot?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. And that avid fan is none other than the high priest's wife, Beh'leeb Inmee!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I'm prepared. ...To turn this entire case upside-down, that is! <thought>This is my last chance! I better take a deep breath and review the evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, then. Please present your evidence, if you would, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The evidence that proves Mrs. Inmee was the one who killed Acolyte Zeh'lot is this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">We are neither Steel Samurai fans, nor fanatics. You would not be using this nonsense as a means to befuddle us, would you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Saw right through that, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright... I have warned you before. Keep this up, and I really WILL have your tongue plucked out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's right here in this family photo! Proof that Mrs. Inmee and Ms. Fey traded items featuring their favorite characters!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The proof that they exchanged items featuring their favorite characters is right here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So, THAT is the Steel Samurai you've been going on about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, that's definitely it!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">That is the Steel Samurai? But there is nothing even remotely samurai-like about it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Did you think to fool us because we lack knowledge of that show?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should've known better than to try and fool Prosecutor Sahdmadhi. Okay. Something bearing the Steel Samurai's likeness should be in that family photo. And that will prove that Mrs. Inmee and Maya made a trade!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at Mrs. Inmee's left wrist. You can see The Steel Samurai's trademark topknot right there!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">...............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which clearly makes this a Steel Samurai watch!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Hargh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, I never knew your wife had such hobbies, Abbot Inmee!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This family photo was taken right before Acolyte Zeh'lot was murdered. By that point, my client had the Punisher strap, and Mrs. Inmee had the Samurai watch. So, what the victim heard in his final moments... ...was none other than the sound of the watch Mrs. Inmee was wearing!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Tahrust:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now what?! He's been pretty quiet up to this point. What does he have up his sleeve?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">There is a big, gaping hole in his flimsy claim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A big, gaping hole? I don't think so!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Oh, no, I'm afraid it is there, all right. ...Just like the big, gaping holes in your putrid brain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My brain is neither putrid nor full of holes. I'm not a zombie, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Heh, says the dead lawyer walking... He who is narrow of vision focuses on what is before him, never seeing the big picture. Or as they say in your country, you cannot see the forest for the trees! For if it is as you said... ...and Lady Inmee, the rebel, slew Acolyte Zeh'lot, the rebel-hunting Lady Kee'ra... ...then the rebel hunter would have been dead before the high priest was slain.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That means...! The high priest could not have been slain by the rebel-hunting Lady Kee'ra!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ack! How could I have missed that?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Who are you going to say killed the high priest now?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Do you finally understand? The sheer size of the holes that riddle your putrid brain?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! <thought>I'm in hot water now. I don't have any other suspects in the high priest's murder!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You mindless zombie. You should have begun your journey into the Twilight Realm long ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No. I will never give up! I just need to think things through and figure out... ...who really killed the high priest!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If Acolyte Zeh'lot had been Lady Kee'ra, he couldn't have killed the high priest! So, the question is, who did? Maybe I can get to the bottom of this by reviewing the events of this case in order! What evidence could tell me something about the crime scene before the murder? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Warbaa'd Dagger! ...No, that was found later, impaled in Zeh'lot's body. It doesn't tell me anything about the crime scene before the murder. I better think of something else.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right... Maya said that the spring had been stained red before the rite even began. The spring was already red before the high priest's murder because of...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The high priest's blood? ...No, that doesn't make any sense. The high priest's murder happened during the rite, not before. So, that means... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right... Zeh'lot had been killed in the rebel hideout the day before the rite. ...And his blood had flowed into the spring. Wait a second. The high priest knew that Zeh'lot had been killed in the hideout. So why didn't he report it to the authorities? If Maya had been the killer, he could have easily had her arrested on the spot. Why didn't the high priest inform the authorities right then?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He wanted to threaten Maya. ...Wait, why would he do that? I better think of another reason why he didn't inform the authorities.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If he reported Zeh'lot's murder...  ...the authorities would find out about the hideout. That's what he was worried about! But by going through with the rite... ...the high priest risked having Maya see the spring running red with blood. Why did he have to go through with the rite? Did he want to...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did he want to kill Maya? But he had any number of other chances to do that. The fact that she's still alive must mean he wasn't out to kill her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He wanted to set up the crime scene to conceal the hideout! But how was he planning on concealing the source of the blood in the spring?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe he tried to empty the spring. Wait a second. It was still full of bloody water. Which means it hadn't been emptied. There must've been some other way he tried to conceal the source of the blood.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe he tried covering it up with Maya's blood. No, that can't be right. Maya didn't have a scratch on her. Time for another idea...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He concealed the source of the blood with his own. That was how he kept the rebel hideout a secret! ...It's all starting to fall into place. I know who killed the high priest! It was...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya! ...Wait a second, that can't be right. She had no reason to conceal the source of the blood in the spring. The answer lies in who DID want to hide it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was there a third party at the scene of the crime? Hmm, I don't know why anyone else would want to conceal the blood's source, though. I better think of something else. The answer lies in who wanted to conceal the source of the blood in the spring!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't believe it! The high priest took his own life to keep the rebel hideout a secret!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The high priest wasn't murdered by anyone. He took his own life to keep the rebel hideout a secret!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">WH--!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">WHA--?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WH-WHAT'S THIIIIIIIIIIIIS?!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">...........................</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Th-The high priest... committed suicide? I have never heard anything more absurd!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What hole?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You still fail to understand. You truly cannot see the forest for the trees! You claim the high priest took his own life. But have you considered who brought the dagger to the Plaza of Devotion?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">After the high priest was killed, the dagger was thrust into Acolyte Zeh'lot's dead body. Only the accused, Maya Fey, could have done that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is as Prosecutor Sahdmadhi says. Your claim is rather porous in its logic. And your evidence is too weak. You cannot prove that the high priest took his own life to conceal the rebel hideout.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk! <thought>They're right -- the dagger was impaled in Zeh'lot's body... ...but his body had been placed at the plaza the previous day.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright? Would you care to respond?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Zeh'lot's body was already in the plaza the day before the rite. But what if the dagger was also already in him at that time?</thought> The dagger was never at the Inner Sanctum.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course! That's it! </line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">What is "it"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was no need to move the dagger. It had already been stabbed into Acolyte Zeh'lot's body the day before the rite.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?! So that means... What does that mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It means the dagger wasn't the weapon that took the high priest's life!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-The real weapon?! <thought>I've got nothing, but I know there had to have been a weapon there! Maybe if I think back on the trial thus far, I'll spot the clue I need.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well? Would the defense care to tell us what the real murder weapon is?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is what really killed the high priest!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right! I was just testing you to make sure you were listening!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yet again, all you have tested is my patience, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why did I even do that? We thought the high priest had been killed by the Warbaa'd Dagger, but... ...if it was something else that had killed him... ...it would have to be dagger-like in shape.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you prepared to show us what you believe really took his life?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">.........I do not recall ever seeing that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You just heard it from the horse's mouth. And now, you'll hear this from mine: penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to present some conclusive evidence, or it's all over! We thought the high priest had been killed by the Warbaa'd Dagger, but... ...if it was something else that had killed him... ...it would have to be dagger-like in shape.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you prepared to show us what you believe really took his life?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What really killed him has been at the Inner Sanctum all this time. And its lethality has already been demonstrated by the late Acolyte Zeh'lot. That's right! It was the warbaa'd statue!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Poh-Poh-Poh-Poh-Poh... POHLKUNKAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...You believe that that statue claimed both victims' lives?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you care to chime in, Abbot Inmee?!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Hrrm! Ngah-ah-ah... No...! He lies! Pay him no heed!</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Lady Inmee!</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">...Darling, don't you think this has gone on long enough?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Tahrust:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Please, Abbot Inmee, let your wife speak.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Hrrrm... Hrrrrrrrngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, Lady Inmee, please continue if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">..................... It's that time again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what time would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Two thirty in the afternoon... The time my husband conducts his daily prayers. And... the time Puhray was slain.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That sound! It's...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Steel Samurai alarm!</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">.........I, too, like to pray at the same time as my dear husband. So, I set an alarm to remind me each day. But I had no idea it would come to this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">........................</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">No, stop! She knows not what she speaks!</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Your Magistry... I am the one who slew Acolyte Zeh'lot.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">HRAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-Abbot Inmee! Bailiff, summon a physician at once!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The physician is now attending the high priest, so there is no need to fear. Now, let us continue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Um... And what about the half of him called "Maya" that's still among the living?</thought> Mrs. Inmee, will you tell us everything you know?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">The truth is... I am a rebel, just like my husband. This tragedy unfolded before the rite, during the Feast of Blessings. I had gone to the rebel hideout to prepare it for Datz's escape.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's when Acolyte Zeh'lot suddenly appeared?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">...Yes. Puhray was shocked when he saw me there.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Acolyte Zeh'lot did not know you were a rebel?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">...I do not believe he did. I believe he was there simply to investigate the hideout.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And then he suddenly came face-to-face with Mrs. Inmee...</thought> So, the true identity of the rebel-hunting Lady Kee'ra was Puhray Zeh'lot?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Yes... He was a member of the secret police, serving directly under the minister of justice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The secret police?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">And this is what he said to me... "I can kill rebels with impunity. The justice minister has my back!" He was using his position within the secret police to deal us rebels a heavy blow. But murder sanctioned by the crown is still murder.</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Heh, even without the DC Act, Dhurke and his insurgent scum buddies' days are numbered.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What's that supposed to mean?!</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Let's just say... I got a little trick up my sleeve. So I'd watch it if I were you. 'Cause you got a defiant attitude -- like one o' them dragon dupes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The trick up Minister Inga's sleeve was Lady Kee'ra...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">N-No... This can't be! My father would never...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This must be a bolt out of the blue for Rayfa.</thought> This explains why Acolyte Zeh'lot abandoned his real name.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Yes... He even went as far as covering up the tattoo that all Khura'inist clergy members receive.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Lady Kee'ra was a member of the secret police? That explains why no order was given to investigate her attacks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I'm not alone in hearing this for the first time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">But... But... This cannot be...</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">...Is this true? The justice minister is sanctioning state-sponsored murder?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Peace! ...Now, Lady Inmee, please continue.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Puhray suddenly lunged at me. That's when I pushed the stone slab toward him with all my might. But I never meant for what happened next to occur...</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Tahrust:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Abbot Inmee! Are you sure you're all right now?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">I am sorry you had to see that. But you need not worry about me. I am already dead.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Please. We need to know what was so important that you would take your own life.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">After I learned that my wife had accidentally slain Zeh'lot... ...I chilled his body with snow to make it seem as if he died more recently than he did. Then, I later moved it to the Plaza of Devotion and inserted the dagger into his wound. The plaza was empty at that time, for it was before prayer time had started. Finally, I placed his body in the prayer pose... ...knowing that no one would notice anything was wrong until the rite had concluded.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It is perfectly plausible that no one would disturb him if he seemed to be praying. We do treasure our prayer time, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you admit you tried to pin this crime on Maya Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">...Yes, this was all my doing. I never told my wife of my plan. For surely she would have tried to stop me.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">.................................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How did you get Ms. Fey's fingerprints on the dagger?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">I had her hold it while we were rehearsing the rite the day before. And right before the rite, I drugged her with a sleeping agent. Then, I put Lady Kee'ra's robes over the warbaa'd statue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That means... ...Maya was probably already groggy by the time the rite started.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Finally, I ended my own life... ...to ensure that the crime would appear to have been by Acolyte Fey's own hand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... But when your body was discovered... ...Lady Kee'ra's robes were on the ground. How did they end up there if they were on the statue?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">After I impaled myself on one of the statue's dagger-like feathers... ...I used the last ounce of my strength to hurl my body backwards. As I did, I grabbed onto the robes, taking them with me, as I fell back onto the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How terrible! What possessed you to do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You needn't have committed suicide simply to frame the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Prosecutor Sahdmadhi... As one well-versed in our kingdom's legal system... ...I would expect you of all people to understand.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Understand what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This kingdom's legal system... Mrs. Inmee's crime... Your suicide... It can't be... That would be sadder than sad.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, I believe the defense knows of what the high priest speaks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, I finally understand. This explains why the high priest took his own life!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't you see? The reason is right here!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">There is nothing to see, for that bears no relation to the question at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, umm... Did I get it wrong? <thought>Why would the high priest commit suicide? If it was for his wife's sake... then maybe...!</thought> Now I finally understand why the high priest took his own life!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...The Defense Culpability Act. Circumstantial evidence supports Mrs. Inmee's killing of Acolyte Zeh'lot in self-defense. However, it would be next to impossible to prove it without a lawyer. That's why the high priest wanted to pin the crime on Maya Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...I fail to see what that has to do with his suicide.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In Khura'in, the Divination Séance is the most important piece of trial evidence. The high priest wanted to frame Ms. Fey as a serial killer. It was a clever plan in which he made sure he'd see Lady Kee'ra in his final moments.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">...The lawyer speaks true. That is why I placed Lady Kee'ra's robes upon the warbaa'd statue. I made it seem that Acolyte Fey was the rebel-hunting Lady Kee'ra.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Rayfa:</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Forgive me, Your Benevolence. ...But it was the only way to help my lovely wife.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you had approached me first, I could have proved that the murder was in self-defense.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Perhaps... But I had little faith in lawyers, despite being a rebel.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">How utterly foolish to cast away one's life for such a reason! There must have been other ways to cover up the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Yet, had I done so, my wife would rush to my defense. And when the case went to trial... ...she would suffer the same fate as I under the Defense Culpability Act. I could not have lived with myself had she been convicted because of that fiendish man!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Th-This... This cannot be... All I have done under the laws of our kingdom... It has all been...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Rayfa... She's really taking this hard. But I can't say I'm surprised.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Mr. Phoenix Wright. It is time to show the might of your legal prowess! You mustn't allow another innocent soul to be charged under that despicable law.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Of course. I'll do whatever I can.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">What I have done to you and Acolyte Fey is unforgivable. I can only offer my most humble of apologies. Your Magistry...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">I ask that you please look after my wife.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You have my word.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Your Benevolence, it is time that I return to the Twilight Realm. The Magatama of Parting, if you please...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...............Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Beh'leeb:</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Y-Yes, it would be more fitting for you to send him on his way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mrs. Inmee...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Darling... I'm so glad I was able to see you one last time. Thank you... for everything.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">I'm sorry to leave you like this, my love...</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">But now you can watch over me from the world beyond.</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Yes, always and forever...</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">And with every breath I take, my darling, I'll be thinking of you.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Farewell, my darling Tahrust.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...The high priest has returned to the Twilight Realm.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I feel great! I guess that means he didn't leave any regrets behind. Oh...! But what about the trial, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It's over. It was a sad reality born of love, and a great tragedy born of the Defense Culpability Act.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I see no need to continue this trial. Does the prosecution have anything to say?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Mr. Phoenix Wright... I owe a debt to you -- one that I will pay back in court someday.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, to deliver today's verdict, and overturn that of yesterday's trial. With respect to all current and previous charges against them... ..I hereby declare the accused, Maya Fey, and her defense, Phoenix Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, I was thinking, Nick... The legal system here is really stacked against the defense. It's totally unfair!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, it even forced the high priest to make the ultimate sacrifice just to protect his wife.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's just so sad...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Protect the status quo, or join the revolution... If the real Lady Kee'ra were here, I wonder which side she would take.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">........................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Benevolence...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Huh?! What?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was, uhh... just wondering. Are you all right?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Quiet, you! How could I possibly be all right?! ........................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, she's not doing well at all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">......Who do you think you are -- suddenly appearing before me... ...trampling my Insights underfoot, and plunging the Hall of Justice into utter chaos! You even desecrated my mother and father's teachings, you... soulless infidel!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oof, that was a bit more extreme than usual.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">........................... What am I to do...? I had always believed that communing with a victim's mitamah... ...would lead me to the absolute truth. But each time you overturned my Insights... ...it was revealed that they served to support false charges, rather than the truth. I am left now with that heavy truth in my heart.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm sorry, Rayfa...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Perhaps I am not worthy of hearing the voices of the mitamah.</line>
<line speaker="???">That's where you're wrong, Your Benevolence.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">How dare you--?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Your role is to bring forth the voices of the mitamah into our world. If you don't do it, who will?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You know nothing, Maya Fey! It was spirit channeling, not a Divination Séance that brought the truth to light. How... How DARE an outsider like you employ the queen's secret art! But what can I do?! My spiritual power does not even approach yours! Ha ha ha ha! Is it not a cruel joke?! The royal priestess, bested by a lowly outsider?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't be so hard on yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Why not?! It is worth at least a laugh or two!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...You shouldn't talk like that!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Listen, Your Benevolence... You were just fulfilling your duty, weren't you? And you're the only one capable of performing the Divination Séance, right? The station of royal priestess is not something to abandon lightly!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...The station of royal priestess?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The people of your kingdom believe in you. But if you really mean all that you just said... ...then what are they supposed to believe in?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">! Y-You know naught of what you speak!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Actually, I kinda do. After all, I'm only here training so I can become the master of my village back home.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">A village master, you say? ...I did not know. It seems I owe you an apology. For even today, I called you a neophyte practitioner.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's all right, Your Benevolence. Thank you for finally acknowledging me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A future queen and a future village master? I guess it shouldn't be a surprise... ...considering they may have had a common ancestor.</thought> Maya's right, Your Benevolence.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">B-Barbed Head?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Insights were a crucial piece of evidence in this last trial. It doesn't matter if they weren't always one hundred percent accurate. You should be proud of what you did. You've played an important role in assuring that justice was served.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">..................... Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And besides, your Insights aren't the problem here. It's your kingdom's legal system. Without lawyers, your Insights have come to be accepted as the sole truth. And the Defense Culpability Act, which gave rise to that, is the root of it all.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">B-But that is the dangerous thinking of a rebel!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Your Benevolence. As crown princess, you are destined to rule this kingdom one day. That means there will be many things that you alone must determine. Things like how to keep your people happy, and what is true and what is false... And most importantly, what role you must play therein.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">.................. I wonder if I am even up to the task.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Knowing you, Your Benevolence, you're more than capable.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I've never heard Maya talk like this before. She's really come a long way.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What was that?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">It came from the hallway! Smoke! We'd better go check it out! Hurry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mrs. Inmee!</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Mr. Wright, Acolyte Fey... I'm so sorry for what transpired. You were almost sentenced to death because of me. I will make amends by picking up where my husband left off. I will see the revolution through, so nothing like this can ever happen again! For that is the depth of my love for my dearly departed husband!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Lady Inmee, we gotta hurry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That voice... Is that Mr. Are'bal?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">I must tell the people! They must learn that the peace we enjoy is a false one! One built on the backs of innocents charged with false crimes under that odious DC Act! We have it in our power to forge a society in which the law judges all of us fairly!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Hey there, PW! I wish we had more time to talk, but...! Dhurke! Everything's ready! It's go time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Dhurke?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">.....................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, was that the rebel leader Dhurke?!</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">After 'em! Don't let them get away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The power to forge a society in which the law judges all of us fairly... It's the start of a legal revolution...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">..................... Hey, Nick! Hate to bother you while you're lost in thought... ...but I just got this great idea!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"The Steel Samurai vs. The Rebel Dhurke"! I bet it'd make for another awesome TV show! And if we threw the Plumed Punisher in there...! Everyone would go nuts over it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>............I'll never get what she sees in those shows. But it's good to know that no matter what happens, Maya will always be Maya.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Let it go, and move on. Abandon this folly. You know very well your evidence proves nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nice try, but you can't make me give up. I'm going to prove I'm right!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You can point your finger as much as you want, but you're simply wasting your time. It is a pitiful sight to see a lawyer who doesn't know when he is beat.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm? Did the defense have something he would like to say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That fell on deaf ears.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry. That scream just sort of slipped out.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't know about trials in your country, but we refrain from such rash outbursts here. Perhaps this will deter any future urges you might have.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not helping my case in the judge's eyes, both literally and figuratively.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Inconsistent...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly! That's where the inconsistency lies!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, I believe it is in the defense's thought process that the inconsistency lies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh. Guess there wasn't an inconsistency there after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Looks like you can't count on your bluffing skills to save your butt this time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... This is a tough one.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, to me, there's something about this one statement that seems off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, it does sound a little strange, doesn't it? Thanks, Maya. I'll take another look at the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You can always count on me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're looking a little pale there, Nick. Are you all right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This trial is really putting me through the wringer.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe it's just a matter of getting the information you need.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right... Thanks, Maya. <thought>Guess I'd better keep pressing, then!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Once you get more info, you can use it to make one of your famous bluffs!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She makes it sound like bluffing is my default move.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It sure looks like you could use my help, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, please...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, you know how the victim smelled gingihl? That sensation just seemed out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The smell of gingihl, huh? Thanks, Maya! <thought>Okay, time to check the Séance vision again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, have you found any inconsistencies yet?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... I've been trying my best, but...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I didn't notice any problems with the sensations that appeared.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then I guess we better focus on what the victim saw in his final moments.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Another look at the updated Insights might help, too. A change in the day and time of the murder could result in an inconsistency.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. Let's review the Séance vision while comparing it to the Insights.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't find any inconsistencies, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't give up yet, Nick. I mean, what about that Insight? You know, the one that said: "The victim stood with his hands on the stone slab in the hideout." Something about that doesn't seem to match up with the deceased's sensations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see what you mean... Let's compare the victim's sensations to that particular Insight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh, I can't find any inconsistencies in there. Maybe I overlooked something important. That one statement doesn't seem right, but I can't put my finger on it. I'd better look at the evidence again, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh, I can't find any inconsistencies in there. Maybe I just don't have enough information yet. I should try pressing the witness some more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This trial need not be drawn out any longer. The defense has failed to counter the charge filed by the prosecution. In accordance with the law, I invoke the Defense Culpability Act against the defense. Now, then. This court finds the accused, Maya Fey... ...and the defense, Phoenix Wright... </line>
</xml>