<xml>
<title>The Golden Court</title>
<line speaker="Maya">It doesn't make sense...*sob* How has it come to this...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The darned witch! Why did it have to happen to the professor, of all people?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You've got to believe me, Nick! I may be a spirit medium, but I'm no witch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry, I know it wasn't you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Hmm? Say, have you seen Luke today?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I haven't seen him since last night. He was crying all night... I didn't know what to say to him...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No kidding... He's the one suffering the most from all this... Poor kid...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He probably needs some time alone with his grief. We should leave him be.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah... He shouldn't have to see this trial. It'd be too hard for him.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, it's Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you doing here, Espella? Have you been cleared of the accusations?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">No...not yet. If only it was that easy... It's just that... I'm not technically under arrest, so I got special permission to come here. I'm free to go wherever I like...within this building.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Uhm... I... I heard about Mr Layton. It's awful... He was such a good man!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ I'm sorry, Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Huh? What are you apologising for?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We were supposed to find clues connected to Bezella... but we couldn't find anything. And now the professor's been...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">No, don't say that! It's not your fault! And I don't believe a word of what they say about Maya! She isn't a witch!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Thank you, Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Uhm...Mr Wright... Do you mind if I assist you in court today?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I...I know I may not be of much use... but I'll do what I can! I want to help you and Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella...</line>
<line speaker="???">...Excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-you're...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Greyerl, butler of the late Master Belduke. I have come to enquire after Miss Maya. It is most regrettable what happened yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, thank you for coming all the way here! ...Hmm? You look really pale, Jean. Are you all right?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Oh, please don't worry about me. It's merely that, since the incident, sleep has eluded me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I spent the night searching through Master's notes on alchemy. I hoped there may be some mention... of a method by which something turned to gold may be reverted back to its original form.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were looking for a way to... rescue the professor?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Human fate is often cruel. But that's also why we must never lose hope.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Jean...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, we're coming!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Cheer up, Maya! I'm not just going to let them sentence you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I just wish all this would stop already. Whether someone's a "witch" or not... no one deserves to be burned!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know. I can't stand for it either.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ If you'll kindly excuse me now, I must return to my duties.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, no problem. We, uhm, appreciate you coming to see us. <thought>Something's bothering me... Jean seems somewhat odd today.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Let's go, Mr Wright! The trial is about to begin!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem... The trial of Maya Fey shall now begin, as scheduled. Knights of the Court, are you ready to cross your swords of justice?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Inquisitor Zacharias Barnham always has his sword ready for the work of justice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh...defence ready, Your Honour. At this stage, I've just gotta give it all I've got!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ It would appear the defender has thrown down the gauntlet, Sir Barnham. Now, before we begin...may I have a word with you, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honour!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Last time me met, you stood in this court as an apprentice baker. In all honesty, when I saw you for the first time, I thought to myself: "A baker should stick to bread baking."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Is that so? <thought>What a fine first impression I made...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">However, today you are not merely some befuddled maker of sweet buns. I am obliged to fully recognise you... as a knight of law and justice on par with Inquisitor Zacharias Barnham.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, may your duel begin! Fight bravely and expose the truth behind this heinous crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>They treat him like some sort of celebrity...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">He may be adored by the crowds, but when he pointed his sword my way, you managed to shield me from his accusations! Maya clearly isn't a witch! So surely your victory is certain!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you for believing in me, Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Espella Cantabella...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">......!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I have given you leave to come to this trial today. However, that does not mean... that the charges against you have been dropped. Rather than worry about others, you should consider your own situation!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ Thank you for granting me your permission, Inquisitor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Inquisitor Barnham, you may begin your opening statement.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">As you wish, Milord. As usual, let us commence this trial by first recounting the events. If it pleases you, Sir Blue Knight...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As, uhm, you wish...Inquisitor. <thought>I still can't get used to this terminology...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">This heinous crime occurred in the residence of the late Newton Belduke, the alchemist. Here is the sketched plan of his residence. This room, of a somewhat questionable nature, is the alchemist's study, in which the incident took place. The only ones present at the moment of the crime were the accused and the victim. No one else. The witnesses, who arrived at the scene seconds later, have indicated where they found the accused and the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The sketch is accepted as evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The accused took Sir Layton's life with the most cruel of magic. A living man one second, a golden statue the next! Such wickedness!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Magic that turns things into gold? ...Sure, why not?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Several townspeople rushed to the room and paid witness to the horror of this magic. The accused has been captured and charged.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Goodness, that is terrifying! Rumours have reached me that the victim was a most scintillating man. I'm not quite certain whether it was prior to or after... But incidentally...was this Sir Layton not the same hat maker who attended our previous trial?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, he wasn't a hat ma-</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Bizarre as it is... Sir Layton's profession and origin remain unknown. He was a stranger in this city... that is all we know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">And you, sir, his acquaintance... You are an unusual presence in our city yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Today's case certainly is peculiar.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">And that is not the last of the peculiarities, Milord. The alchemist's study has been the scene of another strange incident in the past...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah yes, I remember it as if it were yesterday. The mysterious death of Newton Belduke himself.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Indeed, Milord. Regrettably, the only case of witchcraft still to remain unsolved in our fair city. The witch may have escaped her punishment back then... but perhaps today is the day on which both these mysterious crimes shall be solved.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? Wh-what are you implying?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Patience! You will know soon enough, Sir Suddenly-Pale Blue Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How interesting. It seems that the inquisition have something up their sleeve. Now, Inquisitor Barnham, you may begin.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Thank you, Milord. The inquisition summons the witnesses to this malicious crime of witchcraft!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If only... If only I'd made it to the room sooner... Maybe I could've prevented all this from happening... I won't let Maya take the rap for this! I'll find every single crack in their testimony and prove it wasn't her!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Welcome to the Witches' Court, honourable witnesses. Now, let us hear your names and occupations.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">I am known far and wide as Emeer Punchenbaug I, soon to be the new head of Punchenbaug's Retail Organisation, "PRO".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-wait a minute, witness!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">What's that, blue squire?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're...that guy from the previous trial! Just...what the heck's happened to you? You look like you've been on one of those "ultimate makeover" shows...</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">............ Whatever do you mean? Me name is Emeer Punchenbaug I, soon to be the head of Punchenbaug's Retail Organisation, "PRO".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what is the meaning of this, Inquisitor?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I do not care to delve into this witness' [sic] personal affairs.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like he remembers him all too well...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witnesses, pray continue.</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Oh dearie, dearie me. It is I who usually asks the questions... I am, you see, but a humble teacher. Call me Ms Primstone. The children of Labyrinthia Primary School have the privilege of learning the truths about this world from me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>An elementary school teacher, huh... Good to know at least one witness seems sensible.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪The winds carry my song, it's Birdly Stringing along! Parrot and bard, ensemble avant-garde!♪</line>
<line speaker="Cracker">Oh dearie, dearie me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>At least it's not another goat...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">What a smart bird! He just imitated that teacher perfectly!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm Luke Triton. My occupation is... the professor's apprentice!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you doing there?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...I made up my mind. I'm doing this for the professor! A gentleman has to pursue the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But...Luke. That's where the inquisition's witnesses stand!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I...I'll never... I'll never forgive that witch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A gentleman shouldn't glare at people as if he wants to hit them in the face...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">L-Luke...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">"Your friend today can be your enemy tomorrow." Such is the hard reality of the battlefield.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witnesses, we will now hear your testimonies. Tell us all of this wicked incident, which you have been unfortunate enough to witness.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">I heard a scream and an incantation, and then when I entered the room, the victim was already all shiny!</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Mayhap something caused discord between erstwhile friends? Mr Silk Hat had a knife at the ready, in his hand!</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Victim of magic, sparkly and done for, I heard the staff fall on the floor♪</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The professor must have seen through Miss Maya's deception and confronted her right there, face-to-face!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... Thank you all... However, one part of the testimony was somewhat confusing... You there...the singer...</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">Singer? Could you possibly mean me, Birdly the bard, Your Excellence?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, that would be you, singer. This "staff" that you said...sung about...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It is as you suspect, Milord. This very witch's sceptre.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">There are two different magic gems attached, meaning the perpetrator could have used two types of magic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...it would seem so.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">This gem here enables the use of a gold transmutation spell, "Goldor".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Goldor"... Just the word alone makes the tiny hairs on the back of my neck stand up.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Har har har, that's the one, all right! That's the dreadful incantation that I, Emeer Punchenbaug I, also heard!</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Oh dearie, dearie me! I have seen that sceptre, so I have!</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Clank! Tips over the golden man! The sceptre falls. Not the witch's plan!♪</line>
<line speaker="Cracker">Oh dearie, dearie me!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">How dare she do that to the professor!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">By the way, this witch's sceptre was found on the floor, near the victim. If you'll turn your attention to the sketched plans, it was located right here. A sceptre dropped by the accused would naturally tumble to exactly that spot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You are on edge today, Sir Blue Knight. Is it because your friend is on trial? Perhaps you had better cool yourself down.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Well, anyway. The court accepts the sceptre as evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Thank you, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Inquisitor Barnham, may I ask you something?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What is it now, Sir Blue Knight?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We know that one of the gems is for the spell Goldor, but what about the other one?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">A naive question...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Naivety may be no hindrance to a baker, who spends most of his time amidst bread. But it can be your undoing here in court. Would a knight put a weapon in his enemy's hand?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's telling me to do my homework, huh.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright! I'll look for information about that magic gem in the Grand Grimoire!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Espella. That would be great.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Just leave it to me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She seems very happy to help.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defender may interrogate the witnesses.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">I heard a scream and an incantation, and then when I entered the room, the victim was already all shiny!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Whaddya mean, blue squire?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your gaudy...uhm...colourful outfit! I mean, your attire was different last time. A little more...modest.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">The Emeer you knew back then is no more! I am a new man now, reborn into the higher echelons of society. *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's he drinking? There's a skull and crossbones mark on that bottle...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Enough idle chatter. The witness heard a scream and an incantation, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">That's right! It's just like what you said earlier, Inquisitor Barnham! It was the spell "Goldor". And it was, without doubt, the voice of the accused that said it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, however...it's rather peculiar. When I saw the accused and the victim together last time... they seemed to be on friendly terms.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The next witness will dispel your doubts, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Mayhap something caused discord between erstwhile friends? Mr Silk Hat had a knife at the ready, in his hand!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">The other day I saw you all together in this very court, and you were evidently friends.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, yeah...that's true, but what's that got to do wi-</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Now, everyone! Listen carefully! No chatting in the back row! What I say now will be in the next exam! Ms Primstone's lesson number five! "Friendship leads to nothing but trouble." People would not break up and part their ways in anger if they did not become friends in the first place!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The kids in her class must grow up to be "model citizens"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Oh dearie, dearie me! What I saw in that room curdled the blood in my veins! Mr Silk Hat was pointing that glittering knife ever so threateningly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is everything okay, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">No, of course it's not okay! The professor was a true gentleman... And no gentleman would go around threatening people with knives!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I couldn't agree more...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Silly boy! I saw your professor pointing a knife. Are you insinuating that I am a liar, you cheeky little whippersnapper?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The professor would never do that! You don't know him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>At least Luke's found someone else to antagonise...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Uhm, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I think there was some important information in Ms Primstone's testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, I'm sorry! It's not my place to say things like that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, I didn't notice anything. What could that be? What was Espella about to say?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella, why don't you tell us all what you've noticed?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, is that okay? It's just something I'd like to ask Ms Primstone about...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, just go ahead and ask her.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Uhm, excuse me, Ms Primstone? Do you mind if I ask you a question?</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Oh! It's you! Miss...Espella Cantabella!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Ms Primstone, did you actually see the knife that Mr Layton was holding?</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">I...I did, as a matter of fact, yes! I remember that glinting blade very well. A most frightening sight it was, too...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">And you saw that from the door, didn't you? Now if we look at the sketch... When the incident took place, Mr Layton must have been facing this way, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That must have been the case. Otherwise the witness would not have been able to see it.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Uhm, well, that's all I wanted to ask. The more information we have the better, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The direction the professor was facing... That could be important.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This information shall be added to the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm sorry I jumped in like that, but I really wanted to help...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not at all, Espella! We were able to get some more info, which may just come in handy.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">You...think so?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, the next witness shall continue with the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It won't do any good to make Espella the centre of attention now.</thought> Sorry, Espella. Can I get back to you about this a bit later?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, of course! No need to apologise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She looks a bit disappointed. I'll have to remember to get back to that later...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, the next witness shall continue with the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The professor threatened Maya with a knife? <thought>That sounds hard to believe!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Perhaps he discovered that she was a witch, or she tried to attack him first. Ms Primstone's lesson number seven! "Secrets lead to nothing but trouble." From the smallest of secrets can sprout the largest of arguments! This one is going to be in the exam!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Everything's the beginning of trouble to her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Uhm, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I think there was some important information in Ms Primstone's testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, I'm sorry! It's not my place to say things like that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, I didn't notice anything. What could that be? What was Espella about to say?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella, why don't you tell us all what you've noticed?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, is that okay? It's just something I'd like to ask Ms Primstone about...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, just go ahead and ask her.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Uhm, excuse me, Ms Primstone? Do you mind if I ask you a question?</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Oh! It's you! Miss...Espella Cantabella!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Ms Primstone, did you actually see the knife that Mr Layton was holding?</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">I...I did, as a matter of fact, yes! I remember that glinting blade very well. A most frightening sight it was, too...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">And you saw that from the door, didn't you? Now if we look at the sketch... When the incident took place, Mr Layton must have been facing this way, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That must have been the case. Otherwise the witness would not have been able to see it.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Uhm, well, that's all I wanted to ask. The more information we have the better, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The direction the professor was facing... That could be important.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This information shall be added to the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm sorry I jumped in like that, but I really wanted to help...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not at all, Espella! We were able to get some more info, which may just come in handy.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">You...think so?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, the next witness shall continue with the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It won't do any good to make Espella the centre of attention now.</thought> Sorry, Espella. Can I get back to you about this a bit later?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, of course! No need to apologise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She looks a bit disappointed. I'll have to remember to get back to that later...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, the next witness shall continue with the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">The other day I saw you all together in this very court, and you were evidently friends.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, yeah...that's true, but what's that got to do wi-</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Now, everyone! Listen carefully! No chatting in the back row! What I say now will be in the next exam! Ms Primstone's lesson number five! "Friendship leads to nothing but trouble." People would not break up and part their ways in anger if they did not become friends in the first place!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The kids in her class must grow up to be "model citizens"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Oh dearie, dearie me! What I saw in that room curdled the blood in my veins! Mr Silk Hat was pointing that glittering knife ever so threateningly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is everything okay, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">No, of course it's not okay! The professor was a true gentleman... And no gentleman would go around threatening people with knives!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I couldn't agree more...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Silly boy! I saw your professor pointing a knife. Are you insinuating that I am a liar, you cheeky little whippersnapper?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>At least Luke's found someone else to antagonise...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The professor threatened Maya with a knife? <thought>That sounds hard to believe!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Perhaps he discovered that she was a witch, or she tried to attack him first. Ms Primstone's lesson number seven! "Secrets lead to nothing but trouble." From the smallest of secrets can sprout the largest of arguments! This one is going to be in the exam!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Everything's the beginning of trouble to her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">May the next witness speak of what they saw!</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Victim of magic, sparkly and done for, I heard the staff fall on the floor♪</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">...As you wish, my musically impaired friend. Simply put, when I entered the room, the victim was worth his weight in gold... for obvious reasons. He tipped over and fell heavily on to the floor. The room became drearily silent. And then, I heard that sceptre tumbling across the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">May I ask you something, Ms Primstone?</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Dearie, dearie me! Oh dearie, dearie me! My dear, do not frighten me so! I feel like a schoolgirl caught napping during class...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Primstone, did you see the witch's sceptre at the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Well, about that... I must confess, I do not clearly recall.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't remember...?</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">When I went into the room, the golden man fell down and made quite the ruckus. That is why I did not notice a sceptre being dropped.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you didn't see it, after all...</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">But I am certain that witch girl had it. She must have been hiding it behind her back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Now, we would like to hear the next witness' [sic] testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This next witness is a bit problematic...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Couldn't he have just said it like that the first time around?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Clearly the witch must have dropped the sceptre, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">............ I must confess, my eyes were rather more drawn towards the brilliantly glistening golden statue. I did not witness the witch dropping the sceptre, no. But I did hear it...and my sense of hearing is peerless!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Now, we would like to hear the next witness' [sic] testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This next witness is a bit problematic...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">The professor must have seen through Miss Maya's deception and confronted her right there, face-to-face!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............ Ever since we came to this town...lots of unbelievable things have happened. And that's why... from now on, I'll only believe what I see with my own eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Luke...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">When I went into that room, the only people I saw were the professor and Maya. The professor had been turned to gold... and Maya dropped that sceptre!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's not true!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I didn't have any "sceptre"! And we weren't the only ones in tha-</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Silence! The accused has no right to speak! Be silent or you will face punishment! We can end this trial immediately, should you decide you feel talkative again.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...! I...I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Luke? Is that really the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? Uhm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you really see the sceptre?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............ ............ I...I don't know. When the professor turned to gold and collapsed right in front of me, everything seemed to fade to black... And then...I could've sworn I at least heard Maya drop the sceptre.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The sceptre was found at the scene of the crime. That is the unavoidable truth. Only the accused could have dropped it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Mhm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This isn't looking good...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">I feel so sorry for Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's so full of anger and despair that he can't think clearly.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ He said he can't forgive the "witch". I understand how he feels...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Anyway... I need to find a way to calm Luke down first of all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Luke, you said that you will only believe what you see with your own eyes. But what you think you saw may not be the whole truth.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a close look at the sketch of the crime scene... At the time of the incident, Professor Layton and Maya were standing here. Now, we have learned from Ms Primstone's testimony which way the professor was facing. He was facing this way.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You have testified that the professor confronted Maya face-to-face. But looking at the sketch of where they were standing, one thing is clear... There is a contradiction in your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Uwaah?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However, you can see in the sketch that he wasn't threatening Maya. So then, who was he pointing the knife at?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The professor would never point a knife at anyone! I was the one who opened the door to that room, so I was the first witness...and I saw no knife! Miss Primstone's testimony is not reliable!</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Oh, dearie me! Will you look at this child, sputtering nonsense and talking badly of his elders!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Yes, Milord?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It should pose no difficulty to verify whether or not the victim had a knife. After all, that...sparkling golden body of his has been found at the scene of the crime, has it not?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ Indeed it has, Milord. Court attendants! You heard the judge! Bring the victim into the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Seems like they're going to bring the golden statue...*gulp*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">P-Professor...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Look at that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh, did it get damaged in transit?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor... PROFESSOR!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So this is the power of the gold transmutation spell. Most spectacular... It looks like the work of the finest artisans!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I assure you it is the work of no artisans, Milord. By the way, the missing arm has not yet been found.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I...I can't believe this! Professor...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suppose we should add the victim to the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The poor professor who, while searching for evidence, became evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is unfortunate... I thought the evidence would be as good as gold... but although it technically is, we are still no closer to discerning whether or not the victim was holding a knife.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maya:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The professor didn't have a knife! And also... There was another person in that room! The real witch was there too! Please believe me!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Accused, do I really need to warn you again? Inside the cage, you are to behave like a bird that has forgotten its song. Speak again and you shall be punished. Or are you in a particular hurry to taste the flames of justice, little bird?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">*sob*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Sir Blue Knight, your ignorance is no longer even a surprise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You do not know what transpired at the crime scene. You think this man was pointing at another person, you say? Let me tell you this. Nearly everyone in this court other than you knows what Sir Hat was pointing at.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wh-what?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Well, honourable witnesses? Is that not so?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">I, Emeer Punchenbaug I, love me some gossip and stories of the occult!</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Elusive like mist, the magical beast! Its chilling breath brings about death♪</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Oh dearie, dearie me! You could use some education, Blue Knight. I can offer you private tuition, but it will not come cheap!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">If the professor wasn't confronting Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witnesses, you will now testify. Tell us all about this other presence at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">We all know what happened to that alchemist, so this case's no mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Same place, same magic trick. This time, her luck ran out and she dropped that magic sceptre.</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪The truth obscured by a twisted ruse, The witch couldn't vanish but did confuse♪</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It happened because the professor unravelled the mystery behind all these witches...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The "same magic trick" was used?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">They are referring to an incident from three months ago. Much like this incident, a man lost his life to witchcraft in that very room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It was the master of that residence, Sir Newton Belduke, the alchemist.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">He suffered death by strangulation... Finger marks were left on his neck. He had locked himself in his study, and the key was still in his pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In other words, no one could have entered that room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The perpetrator disappeared from a locked room...just like in this case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">A large amount of powdered medicine was spilt all over the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Powdered medicine?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Sir Belduke was an alchemist. He possessed various medicinal concoctions.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Due to the presence of that powder, had anyone entered that room, clear footprints would have remained. Yet there were none.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's the kind of mystery that the professor would have loved to solve...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thus there were two unnatural circumstances to Sir Belduke's death. The culprit's disappearance from a locked room... and the fact that they appeared not to have walked on the floor. It's almost as if they flew away.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">In other words, it couldn't have been the "Dimere" magic that was used in my case the other day...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Seems like the killer levitated above the floor, strangled Belduke and vanished into thin air...</thought> But what does that have to do with this trial?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It has been three months since that murder. Despite that, we still haven't been able to find the witch responsible. But now, having eluded us for so long... that witch has finally been brought before this court! We will have justice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-whaaat?! <thought>No way... Now he thinks Maya killed the alchemist, too. We weren't even here back then... But it's not like I can explain that to him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Well then, why don't you interrogate the witnesses? ...Now that you are aware of the connection between the two murders.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender, you may interrogate the witnesses. May their testimonies lead us to the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">We all know what happened to that alchemist, so this case's no mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Yeah. A real shocker, all right. Everyone was talkin' about it. People don't say this out loud, but y'know, eh? You're thinking it too, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't have the faintest idea what you're talking about...</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Ain't it clear as day?! He was an alchemist. An alchemist! Alchemy's just like magic, ain't it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Sir Belduke was a man. Only a woman can be a witch... What's more, witchcraft has nothing to do with alchemy. They're...different. Somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Alchemy is the mysterious art of manipulating the forces of nature. ...Or so it is said.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Well that sounds a lot like magic to me! Alchemy's incomp...incomprehensi...sible to regular people! S'all magic really! And y'know, a coupl'a days before the witch got 'im, there was that lightnin' that struck...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Lightning?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Glad yer askin', because I like tellin' that one! All of a sudden, like a bolt from the blue sky, there was this bolt from the sky...only it wasn't blue! The sky lit up an' turned blood red. And then, out of nowhere, an old-lookin' bell tower appeared in a burst of flames! Makes ya realise Mother Nature's pretty powerful stuff, eh? *gulp* *gulp* *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You have strayed off the topic at hand, witness. This is a courthouse, not an inn. Save your...thrilling stories for later.</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Same place, same magic trick. This time, her luck ran out and she dropped that magic sceptre.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">You could say I am a scholar, and my knowledge is vast and diverse. I know a thing or two about witchcraft. Therefore, I have a very good idea of the type of magic that must have been used this time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The magic behind this mysterious figure that appeared out of nowhere, glided through the air and vanished after making the kill?</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Indeed, yes. And the witch's sceptre confirms my theory.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">A brilliant deduction. I am honoured to have studied under an excellent teacher such as yourself, Ms Primstone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She was his teacher? Actually, I guess that kind of explains a lot...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Our Occult Crime Analysts have arrived at the same conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright! I found it! The page about the purple magic gem! The spell's called Famalia.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Famalia"? What does it do?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The spell Famalia, bound within this purple gem, is used to summon a familiar.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Familiars appear out of nowhere, glide through the air and vanish when their task is accomplished... They are evil, bloodthirsty spirits used by witches to perform outrageous crimes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Evil spirits? Are you saying that the witch used a familiar to...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It was a familiar that took Sir Belduke's life. And now it has appeared again. Sir Silk Hat was probably trying to ward off the evil spirit with his knife. But what good is a knife against an occult creature? It completed the task given to it by the witch and promptly vanished. Thus bringing us to the conclusion that... Sir Belduke and Sir Silk Hat were both killed by the same witch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaa-whaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What an...unexpected turn of events. The two incidents have been shown to be connected... due to the same witch's sceptre having been used in both cases!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, this is terrible! Now Maya is accused of two murders...</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Oh dearie, dearie me! I was right, as always. This gruesome murder will be in the next exam. Make sure to take notes! Now, I shall divulge what really happened.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">We are all ears, Ms Primstone.</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">That hat maker was pointing the knife at the witch's familiar.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Oh dearie, dearie me! No, I did not. When that boy opened the door... the familiar had just disappeared. Had the boy opened the door sooner, no doubt we all would have seen it. If he were my student, I would have made sure to teach him not to dilly-dally!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is everything all right, Luke? You seem to be in deep thought about something.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">No, it's not right at all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is there something in Ms Primstone's testimony that you'd like to comment on?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's what I keep telling you! The professor wouldn't point a knife at anyone!</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Dearie, dearie me. What an impertinent child! I'm telling you, I saw a knife. I distinctly saw the glint of a sharp blade!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Luke">"A mere detail"?! "Matters not"?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my... Anyhow, I wonder... where could that missing arm be?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Y-yeah! That ought to be looked into!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, that's right. The arm... Wasn't it found at the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I swear, I never saw it there!</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Oh golden arm, where can you be? Reveal yourself, listen to my plea!♪</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Oh dearie, dearie me! I'm afraid even I did not notice it!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It is indeed astonishing that the arm could have disappeared from the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The professor will need his arm when he returns to normal! It's an all-out robbery! Go and investigate it!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The boy's request is not unreasonable. I will order our Occult Crime Analysts to search for it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How could the arm just up and vanish from the crime scene? That just might be the clue I need to give me the upper hand over Barnham...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court considers the whereabouts of the arm irrelevant to this trial. Mr Wright, make sure that you limit your interrogation to relevant matters.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, continue with the interrogation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's talking about Luke, huh...</thought> And when you entered the room, you saw the victim pointing at something?</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Pointing a knife, no less. A knife! As I told you before, it was a sharp, glittering knife. The poor man thought a knife would work on a familiar! Had he attended my classes, he would have known better.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In any case, there's no proof that the victim actually had a knife. <thought>It's certain now that the professor and Maya weren't facing each other.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Next witness, you may...um, sing us your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪The truth obscured by a twisted ruse, The witch couldn't vanish but did confuse♪</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">As you wish, Sir Musically Impaired Defender. A certain man was killed some three months ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean Sir Newton Belduke, the alchemist, right?</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">It was a "locked room murder", accomplished through the use of a certain mysterious spell.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that same magic has been used in this case too.</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">The witch that committed the crime disappeared without a trace.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She hasn't been found to this day, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">............ That's pretty much what I expressed in my song.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I knew all that already.</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">Even a peerless bard such as myself may not always be completely up to date with all the latest information. Isn't that so, Cracker? You understand, don't you, my peerless feathery partner?</line>
<line speaker="Cracker">...<cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> <cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> ...<cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> <cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Espella">What an adorable bird! He's imitating you this time, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm being parroted by a parrot...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">We capture all witches. Without exception. This one may have been at large longer than others...but she will not escape us.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Next witness, continue testifying.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It happened because the professor unravelled the mystery behind all these witches...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The witch's identity, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Can't believe I'm getting stared down by a little kid...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">............ Don't get me wrong. I want to believe you and Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But...I saw the witch's sceptre on the floor! No one else could've dropped it. When I saw the professor, everything went black in front of my eyes...but I did hear the sceptre fall to the floor. There was a witch in that room...and it had to be Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Luke...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">If only the professor were here to tell me what to believe in...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">What do you think, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We need to dig down to the truth as soon as possible. For Maya...and for Luke, too.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I hope we can do it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It'd be easier if there were some clear contradictions in their testimonies, but I haven't noticed anything...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Perhaps this time... we should take a step back and observe each witness while they're not the one speaking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The four of them are listening to each other's testimonies... That may give me an opportunity to question them on one another's testimonies and find gaps in their story.</thought> You're full of good ideas, Espella. How about we give that a shot?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Sure!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mister, do you have something you'd like to share with us?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr Emeer!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">It's Mr Emeer Punchenbaug I to you, Bluey! The likes of you oughta show some respect for a future man of wealth such as me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You seem to be looking ahead to a future full of newly gained riches...</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">I can look wherever I bleedin' please! A-anyway, why yer lookin' at me like that? I dunno 'bout that golden bloke's right arm!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Excuse me, Mr Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm? What is it, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I may be wrong, but... there's something about that man. Wouldn't you say he looks, uhm... suspicious?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not just you. Everything about him is so shady it makes me want to double-check my pockets... Mr Emeer, stop pretending you don't know anything about the victim's missing arm!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">P-p-pretendin'? I told ya, I know nothin'! Nada! Zero! Nil! I ain't seen it. Or heard about it. Or put it in me pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Put it in your pocket...?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">It wasn't me, honest! Seriously, I've got nothin' to do with it!</line>
<line speaker="???">???:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-order! Order! Who is that person?</line>
<line speaker="Price">You want to know who I am? I'm Price the pawnbroker! And this man is a shameless, cheating bum! He had the nerve to lie to me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What did he lie to you about?</line>
<line speaker="Price">I'll tell you! On the day of the crime, Emeer came to my shop... He waltzed up to me saying he'd got his hands on a superb work of art, rare as gold dust!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think I know where this is going...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That "work of art"...could it be...?</line>
<line speaker="Price">I've got it right here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just like I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh my...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor... It's the professor's arm!</line>
<line speaker="Price">It's pure gold, exquisitely crafted. It was entitled...hmm..."Towards Tomorrow", or something like that. I'd never seen a piece of gold so fine before... And so, suspecting nothing, I paid that rascal a rather handsome sum.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who would have thought...</line>
<line speaker="Price">And what am I hearing now?! That it was a human arm, no less! You, sir, are a monster! You're as bad as a witch's familiar yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">I didn't know it was his arm, I swear! When I saw it, it was already like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">I was last to the scene, and it caught me eye right away!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And then it found its way into your pocket and you pawned it?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You mounted it on a crude stand, gave it a tawdry title and passed it off as some kind of a sculpture...</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't try and look away from the truth now!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Darn it! I can look wherever I darn please! I'll look away from the facts and forward to the future! Always look on the bright side!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Where were we now...ah, yes. The victim's arm has now been successfully reattached by one of our masterful craftsmen. Knights of the Court! You may resume the inquisition.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At least one thing's clear now... As everyone can see, the victim definitely wasn't holding a knife!</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Oh dearie, dearie me! It seems I may have been mistaken after all. When you think about it, the victim had already been turned to gold when we entered the room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to the witnesses' testimonies, that was the case, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Well then, I'm sure you'll concede that it was easy to mistake that glittering pointing finger for a knife.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Indeed, the victim's finger has a glint to it resembling that of a sword's edge.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Such a sense of power and intensity... It's enough to send a shiver down the spine of anyone being pointed at.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">No puzzle is a match for the power of the professor's pointing finger!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess no one remembers I'm known for pointing like that too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">I think your pointing finger makes quite an impression too, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's just taking pity on me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Is that all you had to say, Sir Blue Knight?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">As I said before, whether the victim had a knife or not... is completely irrelevant.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Y-yeah, what he said! You'd better apologise to me now! Badgerin' me for no reason like that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is that all there is to it? Or could that arm hold some other clues...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">We've come this far... Maybe there's something else you could ask about.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's right. I need to ask some more questions.</thought> Well then, Mr Emeer. Perhaps you could tell me one more thing about that arm.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you tell me when you found the arm?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">I told ya before, it was when I entered that room. It really kinda stood right out, y'see! Glitterin' on the floor like that...ya couldn't miss it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And yet, no one else noticed it. How do you explain that?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">I guess they must've been lookin' at the golden hat guy when he fell down. I was the last to enter the room, so I noticed the arm before the, uhm...rest.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">And as soon as you noticed it, you slipped it into your pocket like a common thief?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Eh heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is no laughing matter, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Well, Mr Wright? Maybe he knows something else we could use!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, I suppose I'd better ask him about something else.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why don't you tell me how much you got for that arm?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All that glitter you're wearing... The money for that must have come from somewhere. And if you managed to buy all that for the price of one arm... It must've been worth a small fortune. It is gold, after all...</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">A-are you... thinking of selling it? The whole body?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You have lost my respect, Blue Knight... Apparently you are no more than a greedy knight blinded by the glitter of gold.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">How could you, Nick?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh...I shouldn't have asked. They all took it the wrong way...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">I won't judge you, Mr Wright... But for now, let's ask him something else. Maybe he knows something we could use!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, guess I'd better ask him about something else.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You found the arm on the floor, pointing upwards, you said?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Yeah, I did! Finders keepers, I say! It was pointing straight up at the ceiling.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The arm somehow happened to fall down in such a way that it landed upright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What are the odds of that? Actually, that reminds me of a puzzle...</thought> Now, if you could just show us on this floor plan here... I'd like to know the exact spot where you found the victim's arm.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Sure, I remember that well. It was...right there.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph, yes. That's where you would expect it to have fallen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>Now, if that's where it was... then something's definitely not right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">If you keep looking at that sketch so intensely, you shall burn a hole in it. Or perhaps... you're going to claim there's a contradiction in it somewhere?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This arm is the final clue left by the professor... Even after turning to gold, he was pointing out something important... Namely, the key to solving this case!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, defender? Do you see any problems in the locations as marked on the sketch?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's no use. There's nothing odd in the sketch.</thought> ...No, it's all good.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Inquisitor Barnham, you may proceed.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It took us longer than expected, but we have finally managed to ascertain some facts. The defendant attacked the victim using two magic spells enabled by the witch's sceptre found at the crime scene. The witnesses each saw the very moment at which the victim turned to gold and collapsed. And then the witch dropped the witch's sceptre.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is bad...there's nothing here I can object to!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>That voice!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I didn't have a sceptre! Look at the sketch again, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maya! <thought>The sketch? But I DID look at it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright! I've been thinking about it... and I'm sure Mr Layton must have left us a hint somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's gotta be something in the crime scene sketch! Maybe it'll jump out at me as soon as I raise an objection...</thought> Your Honour! The defence would like to withdraw its previous statement!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What did you say...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please, if you'll all take a look at this floor plan... you'll notice that there's a contradiction in the location of the arm!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">To claim this at such an advanced stage of the trial... I trust you understand that you will be held accountable, should this prove to be a waste of our time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah...I get the picture! But there's no time to worry about that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course there is a problem.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Pshh! And where would that be, precisely?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The professor's arm has armed me with some vital evidence. Its location leads to a huge contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In that case, why don't you enlighten us and show us this so-called contradiction? What contradiction does the victim's arm create?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And this is...the victim's arm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah! Would a broken arm fall on its end and stand up neatly like that? It's even less likely than a coin landing on its edge!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender... This is not so much a contradiction as merely an oddity.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">An oddity reminiscent of yourself, foolish Blue Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm sure if you knocked Mr Layton's statue down a hundred times, his arm would end up like that at least once!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Knowing the professor...I bet it would happen!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay, okay, I get it. My mistake.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You appear to be looking away from the facts, rather like a certain witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I won't look away from my mistakes... but I will keep looking on the bright side! <thought>...And on the bright side, that's one possibility eliminated. All the more chance of getting it right next time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph... What say you, Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I believe that was a definitive proof... that there is a contradiction here. Not in the sketch, but rather in this court. That contradiction is you, Sir Blue Knight. Perhaps you had better go back to your bakery.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I think...what Inquisitor Barnham means to say is that your objection was a little off the mark. I could be wrong, of course...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh. Yeah, I got that, Espella. I'm not that clueless... <thought>I've got to get it right next time! I don't want to make a fool of myself again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You appear to be looking away from the facts, rather like a certain witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I won't look away from my mistakes... but I will keep looking on the bright side! <thought>...And on the bright side, that's one possibility eliminated. All the more chance of getting it right next time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The contradiction is right here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And this is...the witch's sceptre...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's go over the order of events, as per the witnesses' testimonies. First, the witch cast a spell on the professor, turning him to gold. When all of you rushed to the crime scene, that golden statue fell down, making a loud noise. Next, the witch dropped the sceptre.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What are you getting at, Sir Blue Knight? All witnesses agree with this order of events.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. They all agree that's how it happened... But then there's the arm.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Well, what about it? Spit it out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's assume that Maya was the witch... Now, look at the sketch again. The witch dropped the sceptre after having turned the professor into gold. The sceptre tumbled along the floor... and was found here, as asserted by the prosecution. However, that would be impossible. There's no way it could have been there!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh... I see it now!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Ngh... The...arm...it was...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm glad you seem to have noticed. The victim's arm was on the floor right here, standing on its end. Therefore, the sceptre couldn't possibly have fallen that way. Ergo, it couldn't have been the defendant who dropped the sceptre! In other words, Maya is not a witch!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Nghhhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Orderrr! How can this be...? The inquisition's reasoning has been proven invalid through just one single piece of unusual evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Call it Layton's magical touch! The professor sacrificed his arm to leave us just the evidence needed to turn this thing around!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">That was amazing, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Even if"...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">in [sic] the many trials I have attended, I have become well-versed in certain aspects of magic. I am all too aware of its potential to confuse people, befuddle their minds and make their memories hazy... No one can resist such a maddening influence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you trying to say, Inquisitor?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The sceptre could not have tumbled across the floor if the arm were in its way. ...However! Can we be sure that is where the arm was? Are all of the witnesses able to confirm its location at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">...!</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I was about to get ready to leave...but it seems there is need for further questioning. Testify once more, witnesses! Tell us of the golden statue and the Talea Magica!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I was only focusing on the professor, so I don't remember much else.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">I dunno...I got there last. 'Sides, that thing was glintin' and glitterin' away, so I couldn't see much else.</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Bewitched by love, or beloved by a witch, The poor cove knows not which is which♪</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Dearie me, I remember! How obvious it seems now. The staff was dropped before the statue fell over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa, wait a minute! What you all said just now... is totally different from your previous testimonies!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Sir Blue Knight. You are starting to notice it now, aren't you? That is the way of magic. Such is the effect this black art tends to have upon those who witness it. The witnesses are not lying, but simply having trouble remembering the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What a convenient excuse... Confronted with magic, their brains turn to mush, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ever since our ancestors drank from the fountains of wisdom and obtained the capacity for reason... witchcraft has been the one thing to remain incomprehensible, even to the most intelligent of us.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Nevertheless, the onus is on us to stand up against magic and pass judgement on these witches! And so, here we are, doing battle with the weapons of the wise: words. With words, we shall pass judgement upon this supposed witch.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender, you may begin your interrogation and help us arrive at the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I was only focusing on the professor, so I don't remember much else.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............ I thought so... I mean, I thought so before, but now... The more I think about it, the less certain I am that I actually heard it! How could I have been paying attention to anything else when the professor was... When he was... *sob* My memories of everything else are too fuzzy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess Luke was too shocked to take in his surroundings and notice anything else... I doubt I'll get any more information out of him for now.</thought> I'm sorry, Luke. I understand how hard this is for you.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Let's move on to the next witness.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">I dunno...I got there last. 'Sides, that thing was glintin' and glitterin' away, so I couldn't see much else.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">The arm of that shiny gent next to you, Bluey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh... <thought>Poor Professor Layton...more valued now than ever before...</thought> And you didn't notice the sceptre on the floor?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Y'know, I wasn't even looking at the floor. Me eyes were kinda glued to me new source of income! If anythin', I may've looked up at the ceiling, since that's where it was pointin'. Finders keepers, eh? Into me pocket it went! *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Someone arrest this guy, please...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Bewitched by love, or beloved by a witch, The poor cove knows not which is which♪</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">I shall simplify it once more just for you, esteemed Knight of the Court. First of all, let's talk about love. It's a pretty neat slant rhyme for "cove". A "cove" is slang for a "chap", you see. Then we have the word witch and its homophone which.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr Emeer, you seem to be pondering something very deeply.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Bwah! Ya caught me unawares there, Bluey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did something in Mr Birdly's statement catch your attention just now?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Nah. Nothin' in particular. I was just thinkin'... That bard's song really got to me... I really kinda feel it in me heart.</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">I appreciate your appreciation of my art.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Y'know, I meant to ask you somethin'... Why don't you become me private bard? You could sing all about the heroic life of Emeer Punchenbaug I!</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">I could gladly sing of your adventures if it pleases you, kind sir.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Yeah, that's exactly what I want! Show me what ya've got!</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">Very well. As per your request...</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Har har, yeah! Very poetic! *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Your drinking manner is quite inspiring,  But whatever is that skull bottle hiding?♪</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>So, we've learned...nothing useful at all. Just that Emeer has questionable taste in music...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Sometimes it is best not to probe too deeply, Sir Blue Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, then... Let us just pretend we heard none of that and proceed with the interrogation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh... Right...</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">Next, we have the delightful consonance of beloved and bewitched. It is, ultimately, a song about confusion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm confused...</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">............ To be honest, there's nothing more to it. It is merely an artistic expression of my feelings.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So...it's got nothing to do with this case, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">I am a well of melodious words and poetic music. That is my only claim.</line>
<line speaker="Cracker">Aaaaaah! Oh dearie, dearie me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">Oh, what could my peerless partner Cracker be thinking about now, I wonder. Perhaps I should sing a song about it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, please...that's fine.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't believe another song will be necessary. Let us move on.</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Dearie me, I remember! How obvious it seems now. The staff was dropped before the statue fell over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Well, that couldn't have been helped.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How so?</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Now, now, everyone, listen well! Pencils in hand, be sure to take notes. Ms Primstone's lesson number four! "Memories are not always pretty". Some things are better forgotten. Trying to remember them only leads to trouble! This will be in the exam!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You are saying that the victim fell over and his arm broke off after the sceptre was dropped, are you not?</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Correct! Well done. And so, the contradiction is no more.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's no use... These guys aren't making any sense.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">What Inquisitor Barnham said must be true... They've been confused by magic!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">We always try to make sense of what we see. So when what we see makes no sense, we lose track of what's real.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess that makes cross-examination a little pointless... At least, when everyone here believes it's so easy to get confused by magic.</thought> Well, we need to do something, or else Maya will be done for... I'll listen to the witnesses again and try to find something we can use...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Good luck!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Luke, would you like to say something?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............ Oh...sorry. Guess I spaced out a bit. What is it, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You seemed to be thinking pretty hard about something during Mr Birdly's song...err, testimony just now. Is there something you would like to share with us?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............ Well... I've been thinking about what Mr Barnham said a while ago...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was that, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That humans who witness magic become confused and lose sight of what's real... and they end up not knowing what actually happened... Well, I was thinking Mr Barnham might be right. And then...it occurred to me that there might be a way... I mean, we do have with us...</line>
<line speaker="Cracker">Aaaaaah! Oh dearie, dearie me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This situation seems oddly familiar...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I asked him earlier if he remembers the events clearly or not. He said he has a memory better than an elephant and remembers everything perfectly well!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ah, that's right! I almost forgot...Luke can talk to animals!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright, I know it sounds crazy... but please let me try! Let me ask Cracker to testify!</line>
<line speaker="Cracker">Aaaaaah! Oh dearie, dearie me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Should I...? I'm stuck now anyway, and the witnesses' testimonies are all over the place... A new testimony would be a wild card, but it might be just the thing to turn this trial on its head! But it's a crazy idea, all right... If I make a mistake now, it'll put me in a tight spot!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender, are you still with us? This is not the time nor place for daydreaming. What do you intend to do?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Heh...it looks as though you've exhausted all means for a counter-attack, Sir Knight in Blue. Is it not time you drop your sword?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you have no further questions for the witnesses, defender, I will consider your interrogation finished. What will it be then? Are we finished here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've got zero time to think it over... Better make a choice now! Should I summon the parrot as a witness?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's totally nuts! I can't let a parrot testify... No one would take it seriously!</thought> Your Honour, the defence has no more que-</line>
<line speaker="???">Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>Oh, that voice...</thought> Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, Luke's given you a chance! Don't waste it! Aren't you used to grasping every chance there is, no matter how crazy it seems?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright, I don't know much, but... ...Luke's eyes look so serious. Why not accept his proposal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>Okay...I'll give it a go!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honour, the defence would like to summon a new witness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A...a new...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">witness...you say? [sic]</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who do you have in mind?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's...a witness you all know... by the name of...Mr Cracker.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mister...Cracker?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I know of no man by that name!</line>
<line speaker="Cracker">Mister! Cracker!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defence summons its new witness, Mr Cracker the Parrot!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A... A parrot as a witness?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="???">By the way, kind sirs...</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">I suppose you should know that my dear companion never forgets a sound he hears.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He remembers everything he hears, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's definitely worth asking Cracker to testify!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court sees the situation as follows... The witnesses' testimonies do not hold together. In fact, they are as erratic as that bard's songs. I cannot see this trial getting any more confusing. Very well...the defence may summon this avian witness!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>By hook or by crook, I'll do whatever I can to save Maya! Be it summoning a parrot or a familiar... whatever it takes. Within the boundaries of the law, of course.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm, all right. Witness, state your name and profe-</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah, that'd be me, wouldn't it? Don't mind me... Just think of me as a perch for Cracker, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">And just what is the purpose of questioning a bird?! A parrot may be able to repeat what others say, but it cannot talk on its own!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Luke:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Cracker remembers every sound he hears, even just the once, with absolute perfection. So let's have him testify exactly what he heard!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And if Cracker can repeat every sound... I'd say this should be a valuable testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I cannot believe this is happening...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A witness that cannot talk will not lie, either. This idea is much to my liking. Well then. May our new witness, Cracker, testify to the court! We wish to know exactly what you heard from the beginning of the incident!</line>
<line speaker="Cracker">...Aaaaah!...Slam!...Dearie, dearie me!...Clang!...Godoor!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Why, those are the sounds of the incident... exactly as Cracker heard them!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Ludicrous! Evidently, this is nothing but a farce after all!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean, Inquisitor Barnham? I must admit I found the parrot's testimony quite impressive.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Even if that bird can accurately recall the sounds... it is clearly useless when it comes to... the order of events!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You mean there's a problem with the order?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">First, the witch used magic to turn the victim into gold. Then, the witnesses arrived. It is reasonable to assume they cried out in terror when they did so. And yet, this testimony does not accurately convey such an order of events!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph... Indeed, it is as you say, Inquisitor Barnham.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The parrot's capacity for imitation is excellent. I will concede that its testimony does have some entertainment value. However! This animal's testimony cannot be allowed to stand as proof in this honourable court of law!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Don't write Cracker off just like that!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Do you now see how foolish you were to summon this parrot as a witness?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ughhh...not good, Phoenix. Not good at all... Should I really go through with this cross-examination when it feels like everyone in this court is against me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I thought it would be possible to glean the truth from Cracker's testimony... But it's easier said than done... Guess I shouldn't have got my hopes up! I know it's no use, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Don't look at me like that... Man, talk about pressure...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defence wishes to cross-examine the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What? Are you serious?! Did you not hear what I said? Are you choosing to ignore MY words?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A witness that cannot talk cannot lie, either. This parrot's testimony is the naked truth. He's simply repeating the sounds as he heard them.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's humans who make assumptions about the meaning of those sounds and arbitrarily decide whether the testimony's good or not. But, as Knights of the Court, shouldn't we be striving to uncover the truth to which this parrot holds the key?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ The truth, you say...? Very well! Show us the "truth" that this bird purportedly knows! Interrogate that parrot! Meanwhile, I shall enjoy the show.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Will you? Will you do it, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh, do you think it's hopeless?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Uhm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender, you may interrogate the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Cracker">...Aaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, yeah... I may have let out a teeny scream... I was so horrified when the professor suddenly turned into gold like that, right before my eyes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that's when...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhh... I-I'm really sorry! I won't talk again, I promise!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Unfortunately for you, Sir Blue Knight... there is no way you can prove that it was the voice of the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Analyse what? A "voiceprint"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's nothing... Just forget what I said. <thought>Oh, boy... This world is driving me crazy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, then. You may carry on with the interrogation.</line>
<line speaker="Cracker">...Slam!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Cracker">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Mr Birdly?</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">How may I help you, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd been meaning to ask this before, but... why are you still on the witness stand?</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">Are you suggesting I should leave my dear partner alone with strangers who cannot even sing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">The very sight of Cracker causes the finest of songs to effortlessly form in my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Right...anyway... Would you mind remaining quiet for the rest of Cracker's cross-examination?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suddenly got the munchies... Ahem, continue the interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hmm, he seems to be saying: "Don't ask me, mate!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender, this is getting us nowhere.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh, it would seem so, Your Honour... <thought>Yeah...I can see that myself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">By the way, I was the one who opened the door. I was worried about the professor, so I barged right into the room.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Poor Luke...</line>
<line speaker="Cracker">...Dearie, dearie me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Luke">When we entered the room, we all kind of reacted in surprise. But I guess the teacher's voice stifled all the rest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Mr Birdly?</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">How may I help you, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd been meaning to ask this before, but... why are you still on the witness stand?</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">Are you suggesting I should leave my dear partner alone with strangers who cannot even sing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">The very sight of Cracker causes the finest of songs to effortlessly form in my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Right...anyway... Would you mind remaining quiet for the rest of Cracker's cross-examination?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suddenly got the munchies... Ahem, continue the interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Ms Primstone is known for her stentorian voice of authority, allowing her to easily rise above the chatter of unruly children. Her voice would still be ringing in the pupils' ears long after a class had finished. Ah, that takes me back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If only Maya's scream was as easily recognisable.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right, let's move on to the next sound!</line>
<line speaker="Cracker">...Clang!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Mr Birdly?</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">How may I help you, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd been meaning to ask this before, but... why are you still on the witness stand?</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">Are you suggesting I should leave my dear partner alone with strangers who cannot even sing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">The very sight of Cracker causes the finest of songs to effortlessly form in my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Right...anyway... Would you mind remaining quiet for the rest of Cracker's cross-examination?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suddenly got the munchies... Ahem, continue the interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I'd better not pursue this one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Luke...you poor thing.</line>
<line speaker="Cracker">...Godoor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder...</thought> Luke, what about you? Did you hear the incantation too?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............ I'm sorry... I can't seem to remember. After I saw the professor in that...in that state...my memory of what happened next just isn't clear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Mr Birdly?</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">How may I help you, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd been meaning to ask this before, but... why are you still on the witness stand?</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">Are you suggesting I should leave my dear partner alone with strangers who cannot even sing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">The very sight of Cracker causes the finest of songs to effortlessly form in my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Right...anyway... Would you mind remaining quiet for the rest of Cracker's cross-examination?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suddenly got the munchies... Ahem, continue the interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, Luke. I know this is very painful for you. <thought>Anyhow, the important thing is that incantation. Somehow...I get the feeling there's something odd about it. It just doesn't seem quite right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Do you think there's anything important in Mr Cracker's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm. There does seem to be a fundamental problem with what he repeated... <thought>Why would the incantation come after the professor was turned to gold?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">But Mr Cracker can't tell lies, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... He can only repeat the sounds he's heard. <thought>Maybe we're just misinterpreting Cracker's testimony...</thought> For the time being, let's have another look at the Court Record and the Grand Grimoire.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is a critical contradiction in this testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">We are all aware of that, Sir Blue Knight. This contradiction is between your so-called desire to find the truth and the fact that you are interrogating a parrot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's not what I'm talking about, Inquisitor. There is a contradiction here that makes one thing particularly clear... the fact that we have clearly all made a wrong assumption!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...How so?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Luke, can you ask Cracker to repeat the incantation once more?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">R-right you are!</line>
<line speaker="Cracker">............ ...Godoor! ...Godoor!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">G... "Godoor"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to the Grand Grimoire, the name of the gold transmutation spell is "Goldor"... Now, Inquisitor, it would seem to me that the spell we've just heard is in fact a different one entirely!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well I never... Unbelievable! "Goldor" and "Godoor"...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Nnngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-another spell...that we haven't yet considered?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, the next question that needs to be asked is: just what is this Godoor spell?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh! Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I've found it. The page about the spell... Godoor. It's listed in the Grand Grimoire...right here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">exists? [sic]</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wha-whaaaaaaat? Order! Order! I demand order!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just like I thought. Cracker remembered it exactly.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">But then...what kind of magic is this "Godoor"?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Well, Milord...the Grand Grimoire describes it in the following way... Godoor: "Creates a portal on two sides of green-coloured walls. The portal will disappear after five minutes".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Creates a portal?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">On green-coloured walls?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A portal spell...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Aren't you a lucky man... It appears even the Grand Grimoire is on your side. However, there is a fatal flaw in your explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What...what flaw is that, Inquisitor?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It is really quite simple. Think back to how the alchemist's study looked at the time of the incident. Do you remember any green walls? Because I do not. There were none. All the walls were coated with white plaster. In other words... It was impossible to use Godoor in that room!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph... I, too, have visited that alchemist's study since the incident. I remember very well that all the walls in that room were a dull shade of white!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Your little theory was interesting, Sir Knight in Blue. But it has proven to be nothing more than that - a mere wild guess. As long as you cannot prove that this Godoor spell was used, your little theory shall be considered no further.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In all honesty, I was very surprised to learn of such a spell's existence. However... as long as it was impossible to have used this spell at the crime scene, your deduction leads us nowhere. So let me ask you now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, Your Honour?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you, perchance, have any proof that you could show us? Can you prove that it was feasible for the witch to have used Godoor in that room?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is no coincidence! That spell must have been used at the crime scene! But do I have the proof that it was even possible to use Godoor...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's been on my mind for a while... That inexplicable mark. It has to be the evidence that ties up all the loose ends!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I hate to say it, but I don't have any proof, Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Heh. The spell has been broken for you at last.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright! Are you going to just let it go like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, Espella, the walls in Belduke's study were white.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That may be so. But would you have a look at this? The spell Godoor creates a portal on green walls, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Green...hmm...</thought> Ah! <thought>Wait... I think I might just have something!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defence wishes to present evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Im...impossible...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The determination in your eyes made me think you would. Now then, we shall allow the defence to present its evidence to the court! Present the proof that the spell Godoor was used at the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ What do you think, Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Sir Blue Knight... I have a question for you. Godoor is a spell used to make portals appear in solid walls, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm, yeah, that sounds about right...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Well, fortunately we have several doors here already, so there is no need to resort to magic portals. Now, choose any door you like and leave the court!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arghhh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is to say, presenting that piece of evidence was a mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Dang! Why did I show them that? I've gotta have something better...right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The walls in the study are coated with white plaster... Not all of them, though. There is just one spot which is green.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh? There is?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I noticed it when investigating the crime scene. You may recall that there was a small painting behind the desk. And for some reason, the wall behind it was painted green.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It...it was what?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I recall seeing that painting myself, too. If we look at this floor plan... I'd say it was around here.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright, I'll mark it on the floor plan!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's been bothering me since I saw it. But now it's clear what it was. At the time of the incident, a portal opened up behind that painting! In other words, that was the wall utilised for the spell Godoor!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The wall behind the painting was green, and that's a fact!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Incidentally, I remember that painting well. It was a small landscape piece. About the size of, say, an open Grand Grimoire.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, it was about that size, indeed. A small, adorable picture.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Even if a portal had opened in that small patch of green... no person would be able to pass through it. In fact, they'd just about be able to put their arm through, at the most. So will you please explain how a witch could possibly have escaped through a portal this small?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">He's right, Mr Wright! No one could've got through a portal that small!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Have you anything to say? Or are you so crushed by the realisation of your mistake that words fail you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ The portal was too small for a person... It doesn't require much thinking to figure that out.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that aside, a very obvious question remains. If it wasn't a human, then what could've passed through that portal?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You have put an interesting spin on things. Why don't you answer your own question? You talk as if you know everything, so please, enlighten us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A small portal was opened in the wall at the crime scene... And I have all the clues as to what that could mean!</thought> What went through the portal was...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm thinking it might have been... the witch, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...You don't sound very sure about that. Let me ask you this: how did the witch get through that tiny portal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, since it was a witch...she probably used magic.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There are only two magic gems in this Talea Magica.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What's certain is this: the portal opened in that wall would have been about the size of this book. If there were a portal like that in this courtroom, I'd gladly squeeze you through it to get you out of my sight!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uwaaaahhh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem, yes, well. Enough of this small talk. The defence's answer clearly made no sense.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright, don't let them make you feel small. Let's think about this one more time, and we'll surely find the right answer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A human wouldn't be able to squeeze through that portal... which leaves us with just one other possibility. It was...a small animal! Like a ferret, or a cat, or maybe even a...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright, I'd appreciate if you stopped stealing glances at Cracker.</line>
<line speaker="Cracker">Hang on! Hang on! Squawk! Hang on! Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">Are you suggesting that my peerless musical companion was somehow involved in this crime?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What's certain is this: the portal opened in that wall would have been about the size of this book. It would be too small for a person. As for your suggestion regarding small animals... Let me suggest that you leave this court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uwaaaahhh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem, yes, well. Enough of this small talk. The defence's answer clearly made no sense.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright, don't let them make you feel small. Let's think about this one more time, and we'll surely find the right answer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No human could have passed through a portal that small. Even a witch couldn't have pulled that off.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Heh, so are you finally forsaking your mistaken assumptions?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I haven't finished, Inquisitor. The fact remains that something else could have passed through that portal.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Oh? And just what would that be, Sir Blue Knight?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The portal was created after the professor had been turned into gold... The witch had a good reason behind that. She must have had to move something through that portal.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You have captured my curiosity. I'd like to know what passed through the portal! Tell us, what did the witch use that magic portal for?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">If only you would leave through a portal and never show up in front of me again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ughhhhhhhhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And remember this ancient wisdom: those who point fingers at others will have fingers pointed at them!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like my reasoning was a bit off the mark...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Let's think about it again and give it another try, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What could have passed through that small portal? Did something leave the room through it? Or...could something have entered the room through it? The witch created the portal for a reason... The answer has to be in the Court Record.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Considering the state of the crime scene... there is just one possible answer. And that is...the Talea Magica!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wrong assumption?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witch wasn't trying to remove evidence from the crime scene... She wanted to plant it. She threw the witch's sceptre into the room through that portal!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. She did it to deceive us. Her goal was to make us draw the wrong conclusions. When the incident took place, the witch herself wasn't in the room. She cast the spell from outside!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Whaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order, I say!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's not all. There's even more proof that the staff was thrown into the room from the outside.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wha...what proof?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That proof is none other than...Professor Layton's previously severed right arm!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The victim's arm? How does that prove anything?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">None of the witnesses have testified they saw the witch's sceptre. However... a few of them claim to have heard it rattling across the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please take a look at this floor plan... Since the arm was standing upright here, we know the defendant couldn't have been the one to have dropped the sceptre. Now, think about it...where would you need to drop the sceptre from in order for it to end up here?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh...oh!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Ngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right... The sceptre could only have come from the small portal created by the spell Godoor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is most unexpected. The witch wasn't in the room when the crime occurred... Or, at least, that's the defence's claim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the only thing that explains all the contradictions we've run into.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Another "contradiction"? Whatever are you referring to, Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">This is the Talea Magica that was used in this incident. As we have established, there are two magic gems in it. One for the gold transmutation spell, Goldor, and one for the shadow familiar spell, Famalia. A witch in possession of this staff would not have been able to cast Godoor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Yes...you're absolutely right. But you can't write off all the evidence supporting my theory as mere coincidence.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Why must your agreement always be followed by a "but"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What I'm getting at is... this Talea Magica...is not genuine!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not genuine...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. And naturally, the one responsible for this deception is the real culprit of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Enough of the suspense! It's too much for a man of my age... The defence shall reveal what is meant by this so-called deception!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What? The Goldor magic gem is fake?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Think about it...magic that turns stuff into gold? I mean, that sort of thing only happens in fairy tales!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is this an attempt to make us believe the crime in question never actually occurred?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Behold your glittering friend beside you! Are you honestly trying to claim that gold transmutation magic does not exist?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh, I shouldn't have said that... Can't believe I made that mistake. The Goldor gem isn't a fake. But in that case, something else must be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright, please try again! Quickly think of something a little more probable!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's easy to say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm not sure I understand. Are you saying this whole sceptre is a fabrication?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No...er, yes, actually! Who's to say this whole Talea Magica isn't a fake?! The real sceptre may still be out there, somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ You know what's a fake? You are. You are a sham, Sir Blue Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The real defender may still be out there, somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm...suddenly a little ashamed to be standing here, at your side...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh...that was a shot in the dark...and the only thing I hit was myself. The sceptre itself isn't a fake. I guess just a part of it isn't what it seems...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright, please try again! Quickly think of something a little more probable!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come on Espella, cut me some slack...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">First, I want to clarify one thing. Can we be certain that the Talea Magica in question is authentic?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Without doubt. The metal rod in its centre is called the Spina Magica. The Witch's Mark on its tip is clearly visible and highly detailed. It is impossible to forge, even by the finest craftsmen in all Labyrinthia. I can guarantee you its authenticity.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That leaves us with only one possibility. The forgery in question is... the Famalia magic gem!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wh-what?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A...forged magic gem?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But what about Famalia? Did anyone actually see a familiar at the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...! Tha...that's...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Three months ago, when an investigation was carried out into Sir Belduke's death... the results yielded the following conclusion: the spell Famalia had been used to summon a familiar, which in turn carried out the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...And the witch used exactly that to her advantage. Another similar incident at the same crime scene...don't you think that would be the perfect opportunity... for the witch to frame the defendant for her crimes? The defendant would be blamed for both the professor and Sir Belduke's deaths... and she'd be taken for the real witch.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was the real culprit's objective!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...There is a chapter in the Magic Archive, an old collection of tales of the occult... about the way to test whether or not a magic gem is genuine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">How can we test it, Milord?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is very simple. A genuine magic gem is composed of a mineral with a density lower than that of pure water. All you need to do is see if the magic gem floats on water.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That is simple indeed...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All non-magical minerals in our world, with the exception of sepiolite and a few other special kinds, sink in water. These eerily sparkling magic gems, however, will never sink when put into water. Bailiff! Remove this magic gem for immediate examination!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender... If your theory is correct, this could be the biggest occult crime in history. But another important question remains. I wonder if you can answer it... Who is this supposed real witch that threw the Talea Magica through the portal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>The real witch... There's only one person that comes to mind. Frankly, I still find it hard to believe...but it's the only possibility... Once I indict her, there'll be no turning back... Knowing the consequences, should I... should I give them her name?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">In Labyrinthia, witches are punished by fire. I know you think that's going too far... But even in a world that seems so insane to you... those who take the lives of others must be punished. That's a universal law...isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The witch turned the professor into a golden statue. And that's not all... She took the life of the alchemist too. And now she's trying to pin the whole thing on Maya... I...I can't just let her get away with that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, then... Defence, let us hear your theory. Who is this witch responsible for using Godoor and then throwing the sceptre through the resulting portal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ Are you aware of what decides a knight's true worth? It is their readiness to deal the final blow. The courage to raise their sword... Your sword hand is weak and shaky. It is not befitting a Knight of the Court!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gwahhh...!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright, are you feeling all right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witch's power is not limited to magic spells. They have a much more fearsome ability... the ability to exploit our blind spots, to hide in the shadows and manipulate us. <thought>Someone that malevolent deserves to be called a "witch". I've got to think about this again. I've got to focus on facts, not assumptions!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>When you've eliminated the impossible, whatever remains, however improbable, must be true. There's only one logical possibility. It has to be that person!</thought> The real witch is...Jean Greyerl!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm? Greyerl? I've heard that name somewhere... Wait, isn't that the butler who served Sir Belduke?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's correct.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Inquisitor Barnham, tell me one thing... Is it only females who can be witches?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Are you daft?! Of course it's only females!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Never in the history of this court, has there ever been a male witch.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You're so utterly ignorant! You should be ashamed of yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...All right, well. I'd like to ask another question. Is Jean Greyerl...really a male?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What... What a ludicrous question...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defence is certain... that Jean Greyerl is the witch responsible for using magic on Professor Layton!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At the time of the crime, Jean Greyerl was in the room next to the alchemist's study. And one of the walls in that very room... was painted green!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It...it was?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's more, that green wall... was the one adjacent to Sir Belduke's study!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What...?! This is madness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Inquisitor Barnham! Quickly, have the butler summoned to the court! Have Jean Greyerl brought here immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Certainly, Milord. It shall be done.</line>
<line speaker="???">There is no need for that.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I am here. I shall come down right away.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, it's you!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Well then, Mr Wright. Shall we begin?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Jean Greyerl.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would seem this trial has turned in a new direction. I think we all need a bit of time to take it in. We shall take a brief intermission. Inquisition, defence...sharpen your swords and wits to prepare yourselves for the next stage of this battle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honour!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It shall be done, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">By the time we resume, the examination into the magic gem should have ended as well. Now, the court is adjourned for a brief intermission!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So...it's got to be that, uhm...young butler?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know what you're thinking. I couldn't quite believe it at first, either. But... The evidence and circumstances all point to the butler. He...or she, has to be the witch. At least... it'll be certain if the magic gem turns out to be a fake.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............ But if that's the case...then Belduke's murderer was also...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. It would be Greyerl.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">No, it can't be true! He wouldn't have done that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I know Jean. He held Sir Belduke in the greatest of respect. Jean didn't kill him! I'm sure of it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Jean Greyerl...are you really what people think you are? There are still so many unknown factors in this trial...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I... ............ I'm sorry, Maya! What I did is unforgivable!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............ What are you saying, Luke? All you did was testify about what you saw.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But...but...I...should've trusted you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, you trust us now, right?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Anyway, Luke, it was thanks to you that we discovered new information.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Thanks to me?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sure! You got Cracker to testify. That was a great idea! I wish I could talk to animals! Don't you too, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, yes. I'd love to have a chat with Eve!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, Luke...will you teach us how to do it? Pretty please!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Uhm, yeah, of course! I can try.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yay! That's a promise, right?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...... Uhm, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm? What is it, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Do you mind if I join you from now on?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not at all, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I realised during the trial... that in this strange town, even what you see with your own eyes may not be real. That's why...I'm not giving up yet! Professor...I know he'll return! We can't give up hope!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, that's what I've been thinking too.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I have a feeling he'll reappear again when we get into trouble and help us out. Because, I mean...it's the professor we're talking about here!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And remember what he always says: Look forward to the future! Always look on the bright side!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Err...I don't think it was the professor who said that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's go. It's time to bring this trial to a close.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh... I have something for you, Mr Wright! Here, please take it. Maybe it'll come in handy in the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A letter, huh? Let's see who it's from... Wait... "Newton Belduke"? <thought>There are several sheets of parchment inside, but they're all blank...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">The professor and I got this when we went to see the Storyteller!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Luke! The more info we have the better.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You're welcome!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've got no proof that it was Jean Greyerl who turned the professor into gold... Even if the magic gem is a fake, it's still not decisive evidence. I don't know what will happen next... But I do know this battle's far from over.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">We will now resume the trial of Maya Fey. First things first, the Occult Crime Analysts have finished examining the evidence... They have tested the two magic gems from the witch's sceptre.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Goldor floated on the surface of the water, whereas Famalia sank."</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It was said that genuine magic gems float in pure water, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thus, it has been established... that the Famalia magic gem is a fake! Order! Order! Order in court! This does not prove that Godoor was used, of course. Nonetheless... The defence's theory does now seem more plausible. The court considers it worth looking into. ...You have no objection to that, do you, Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ No, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, bring in the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Witness, state your name and profession.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">My name is Jean Greyerl. I served the late Master Belduke... Since his death, I have been tending to his dwelling and putting his research materials in order.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...? <thought>Hmm, I don't know what it is, but... I feel like there's something a bit different about Greyerl today.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness... There is something we need to clarify first of all. As you are no doubt aware, you have been accused of being a witch...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Therefore, it is vital that you tell us... Are you a boy or a girl?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Please hold on.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why...what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Excuse my rudeness, Milord, but at this time... I do not intend to answer that question.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Why do you refuse to answer, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I had been following this trial from the gallery and so am fully aware of the utterly absurd accusations made against me. Alchemy, the art pursued by Master Belduke, is concerned with the rules and logic that govern nature. As someone who had been helping Master Belduke for quite some time, I dare say your theory is both illogical and impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I believe anyone is free to paint their walls in whichever colour they please. Besides... your theory relies on one magic gem being a fake. While that may have been proven true, another question has arisen... where could the genuine magic gem be?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! It...it must have been swapped with the fake one and discarded somewhere...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I'm afraid that's impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">If we assume, as you have claimed, that the witch used the spell Godoor... that would mean the magic gem must have been swapped after creating the portal. So tell me, when and where would the witch have disposed of the magic gem?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I see your point. Several people paid witness to the incident, and the Knights of the Inquisition arrived at the scene immediately after. During that time, no one left the building and the whole place was meticulously searched.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Naturally, my room was searched as well. Although there was not much to see, as I have few personal belongings.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Despite our inspection, nothing resembling a magic gem was found. I assure you, we have not overlooked anything. I would swear to it on my honour as a knight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">So, Mr Wright. If you wish to accuse me of being a witch... should you not first prove that there is a connection between me and this missing magic gem? Furthermore, I would appreciate it if you could please approach the matter in a rational way, like an alchemist.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The house was searched very soon after the crime... If the gem wasn't found, then it means Greyerl hid it somewhere. Somewhere the Knights of the Inquisition would not have looked. Where could it be?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness has made a valid argument. How will the defence respond?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ The knights who searched Sir Belduke's premises weren't looking for a magic gem. That's why...there is a certain place they didn't consider searching.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Interesting. You really don't give up easily, do you? In that case, perhaps you could tell us all where the magic gem is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's...in Sir Belduke's study!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The study? You mean to suggest it's at the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defence, show us the location of the magic gem. Where is the magic gem hidden?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ark! <thought>Okay, it's not Johnny Smiles we're talking about here. They actually did a good job...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Sir Barnham does look rather confident.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">He seems pretty certain that the search was done thoroughly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, you're right... <thought>And yet the witch managed to hide the gem where she knew the knights wouldn't look. I think...I might just have an idea as to where that might be.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Sir Blue Knight, I see there's still a faint glimmer of hope in your eyes. Perhaps you can come up with a better answer next time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's...in Greyerl's room!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...Did Inquisitor Barnham not say that my room was thoroughly searched?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, defence... Perhaps you would like to show us the location of the magic gem. Do you have a suggestion as to where it is hidden?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ark! <thought>Okay, it's not Johnny Smiles we're talking about here. They actually did a good job...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Sir Barnham does look rather confident.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">He seems pretty certain that the search was done thoroughly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, you're right... <thought>And yet the witch managed to hide the gem where she knew the knights wouldn't look. I think...I might just have an idea as to where that might be.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Sir Blue Knight, I see there's still a faint glimmer of hope in your eyes. Perhaps you can come up with a better answer next time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sir Belduke's premises were thoroughly searched... I don't think anything would have been missed there. You anticipated that...and that's why you hid it in a blind spot that you knew wouldn't occur to the knights!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">A blind spot, you say...? Well, where is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's...somewhere on Jean Greyerl's person!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what?! It's on the witness?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Don't tell me...the witness has it in their pocket. You're just guessing, aren't you? You think you can just say anything you like...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">By the way, I'm afraid there are no pockets in my clothing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is the second time I've seen Greyerl today... and both times, I've had a feeling that something wasn't quite right. Maybe it's just me...but it could be related to the whereabouts of the magic gem...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defence, show us the location of the magic gem. Where do you think this witness hid the magic gem on the day of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I would just like to remind you... that there are no pockets on my attire.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ughhhh! <thought>I was wrong...dang it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">But...Mr Wright... Even if it's hidden somewhere on Greyerl's person... I think it'd be a bit difficult to pinpoint that location now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, it would. In normal circumstances, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But it's not like we don't have anything to go on this time. <thought>Greyerl's outfit has subtly changed since last time... It may be to do with the gem. That change...that must be the answer I'm looking for!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Witness... We met for the first time at Sir Belduke's premises. At that time, you had an amethyst attached to your collar.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, that's right. Mr Greyerl always wears that gemstone.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Alchemists believe that amethysts emit positive energy.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Amethysts...are purple...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But when I saw you in the waiting room this morning... The gemstone you were wearing was green, not purple.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So my question now is...where has it gone? Where is that amethyst... that you supposedly "always" wear?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is something amiss, Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ When we arrived at the crime scene, the witness came out to meet us... I recall the witness wearing a gemstone... but that gemstone was green.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Green? Amethysts aren't green. Although amateurs sometimes mistake prasiolite for amethyst. But that's irrelevant now...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Witness. You've been trying to pin the blame on the defendant. In order to do that, you replaced the Godoor magic gem with a regular gemstone.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We thought the witch who killed Sir Belduke had used the spell Famalia. You knew that if a witch's sceptre with the Famalia and Goldor magic gems attached was discovered at the crime scene... the suspect would be accused of committing both crimes. And that's precisely what happened. The girl captured at the crime scene was accused of slaying both Sir Belduke and Sir Layton.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was your plan. You removed the Godoor magic stone from the sceptre and inserted your amethyst in its place. And then...you attached the Godoor gem to your collar!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That's why, when we saw you shortly after the incident, you were wearing a green gemstone. To think...that was in fact a magic gem!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! ...Witness, is that true?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ This amounts to nothing more than conjecture. I do not believe you have any solid proof. However... I have to concede that you have surmised a logical connection between me and the missing magic gem. Consequently...I am prepared to answer your questions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Good. I will repeat what I asked you previously. Witness. State your name, profession and finally, your gender.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...My name is Jean Greyerl. I have been serving the late Master Belduke. As you can see, I wear a butler's outfit... but the truth is as the defence claims. I am...a girl.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">A girl... Unbelievable...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?! The butler is a girl?! O-order! Order! Order in the court! Jean Greyerl... Are you declaring to this court that you are, in fact, female?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-but...everyone in town was under the impression that you are a boy...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...Just listen to them. Listen to the wild gossip and accusations. Alchemists pursue knowledge of the rules that govern nature. But to the townspeople...alchemy is no different to magic. Had they known I was a girl, they would have taken me for a witch. That's what Master Belduke was worried about. He told me it would be safer to pretend to be a boy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In other words... you disclose that you're a female, but deny that you're a witch?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ I would have thought that was obvious.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She knew that once her gender came into question, she wouldn't have been able to conceal it. That's why she made this public now. It was the most rational choice for her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Inquisitor Barnham, may I ask you one question? Has all the evidence in this "Golden Gentleman" case already been presented?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Why do you ask?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">As it stands, you do not have a single piece of evidence proving that I am a witch. Given the lack of pertinent evidence against me, I would like to be permitted to return to my duties.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph... What say you, Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ It has been proven that the two gems were swapped. However, it may also have been possible for the accused to have done so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">This is a place of judgement. There is no need for us to understand the reasons behind a criminal's actions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">After all, those whom we judge are other-worldly creatures...they are witches. It is impossible for a human being to understand the reasoning of a witch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Is there nothing we can do? At this rate, Maya will be...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Barnham still thinks Maya is a witch! We've made it this far...and yet, it feels like we're back at stage one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">It seems there are no more rational arguments against me. Now, if you will kindly excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't have much on Greyerl when it comes to the professor's case... But should I just let her go?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's so cool-headed and prepared for every question I ask. If I'm too persistent, it may only end up getting worse... I'd better wait a bit and see what happens.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">B-but, Mr Wright! We won't have another chance! We need to act now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ You're right! But I wish you'd tell me these things sooner.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">And I wish you'd realise them sooner...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't afford to back away now!</thought> Ms Greyerl! Hold on just a moment!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Oh, is there something else you need to ask me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't leave yet, Ms Greyerl!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Is there something else you wish to ask me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who cast the spell Goldor? We still haven't found the answer yet!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I'm afraid I'm not the one to answer that. With all due respect, that's your job.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">We have heard all we can from the witnesses. In the current circumstances, you cannot insist that this witness is a witch!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is the opinion of the court, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no way!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............ Mr Wright. I think...if the professor were with us now, he'd tell us... to view the problem from a different angle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">From a different angle? Could you be a bit more...specific?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............ I think the professor would say... "The one who knows the answer to that question better than anyone else...is you."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's nothing else I can follow up on regarding the professor's case... What else can I do, though?</thought> Well, Luke, thank you for sharing your mentor's words of wisdom with us. I'll figure something out... ...Ms Greyerl.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's nothing else I can follow up on regarding the professor's case... So what can I do? There's only one other option...</thought> Ms Greyerl! I have to ask you to remain at the witness stand.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Is there something else you wish to ask me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your testimony is not over yet. There's still something you need to tell us about.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...Mr Wright. I'm afraid I cannot help you. I have told you all I could about this incident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And I'm afraid you've got the wrong idea, Ms Greyerl.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honour. What this witness needs to testify about is not the professor's unfortunate incident... but rather, the incident from three months ago. Namely, Sir Belduke's death. As she was present in the building at the time, working as a live-in butler, she needs to testify about the events of that day!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">About Sir Belduke's death?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The fact that one of the magic gems was swapped leads me to a single conclusion. Both crimes, the murder of Sir Belduke and the transmutation of the professor, were the work of the same witch. The truth behind the alchemist's death may also hold the answer to this case!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph... What is your opinion on this, Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ I'll allow you to have your way this time, Sir Blue Knight. The inquisition has no objections.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Inquisitor Zacharias Barnham... It seems you have lost that unyielding attitude so admired by the townspeople. Here you are now, letting a novice defender lead you by the nose... It is hard to believe you have been known as the "Unwavering Sword of Justice", for your usually cool-headed judgement...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You know little about me, witness. Do you think I care about defending my name? It is this town that I wish to defend.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Sir Belduke's murder is the only case to have remained unsolved for so long. Jean Greyerl, you shall now testify about it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As demanded by both the defence and inquisition... the witness will testify about Sir Belduke's death. Any questions?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">No, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I must, however, mention one more thing before we begin. If it cannot be proven that Jean Greyerl is a witch, as claimed by the defence... the court will irrevocably consider Maya Fey to be the witch responsible for both crimes. Is that understood?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You have no choice, Sir Blue Knight. If you don't want the trial to end right now, ready your sword and face the challenge that awaits.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But...the opponent is a real witch! It's a gamble that puts Maya's life at stake!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Nick... ...Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>M-Maya!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">No witch is gonna outwit you in court. You're an ace attorney, after all! So...let's do it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ The defence accepts the conditions. Let's proceed with the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Hmph...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Inquisitor Barnham, you may begin.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">We shall start with a brief summary of the incident. About three months ago, in the dead of night, Sir Belduke, the alchemist, was murdered. The crime took place in his study, just as with this incident. The room had been locked from the inside. The victim was found still seated in the chair at his desk, so we can assume he was attacked while working. There were very clear strangulation marks visible on his neck.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh... There's something trickling down from his mouth. Is that blood?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Yes, most likely. The victim probably bit his tongue as he was struggling with his assailant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And you said earlier that some white powder was spilled all over the floor, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Yes. Hence, we expected to find the killer's footprints. However, there were none. The killer must have somehow approached the victim without stepping on the floor. After murdering Sir Belduke, the killer left the room without opening the door.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Undoubtedly, the crime must have been committed with the use of witchcraft.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The body was discovered the following morning by the butler...Ms Greyerl.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The body was found by Greyerl, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, Inquisitor Barnham. The Court Illustrator's sketches will be added to the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, witness. Begin your testimony. Tell us about the events spanning the night of the crime, from the evening beforehand until you discovered the body.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">At around 1 o'clock at night, I excused myself and left Master Belduke in his study.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Potions and concoctions" were confiscated?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The victim was an alchemist, after all. We were hoping the items confiscated from his study could provide some clues. Besides, such things must not fall into the wrong hands. It may not be standard practice, but it was deemed necessary. The confiscated goods are stored in our secret vault. The only person with access to them is the High Inquisitor, Lady Darklaw.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">It has caused me great difficulty, as I have not been able to put Master's research materials in order as a result.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The confiscated items shall be returned as soon as Sir Belduke's murder is resolved.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ I shall be looking forward to that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defence, you may begin the interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">At around 1 o'clock at night, I excused myself and left Master Belduke in his study.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...Yes. Master had a habit of conducting his experiments at night, so it was the usual time for me to finish my work.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Weren't you helping him with those experiments?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">He would sometimes have some errands for me, but alchemists generally keep their experiments a secret. That's why I would always excuse myself at that time, unless Master had some other tasks for me.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">And that night there was no more work for you?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...That's correct. I wished Master a good night as I shut the door behind me and then heard him lock the key. There was nothing unusual about him. At least, nothing I noticed.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">When I called him for breakfast in the morning, he did not respond. The door to his study was locked.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Master would always take his breakfast at 9am, so it was around that time.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">So you didn't have the key to Sir Belduke's study...is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes. There is only one key to that room and Master always kept it with him. Master's research was a...very delicate matter, you see. We had to take strict measures to prevent outsiders from entering that room. Occasionally, delinquents would try to make off with one or other of Master's medicaments.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Thieves stealing from an alchemist? I can't tell if that's incredibly brave or incredibly stupid... Probably the latter.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That's why the door to that room is made from thick oak wood. I wouldn't have been able to force the door open on my own.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She couldn't have entered the room before that, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">A neighbour had come for a visit just then, so we forced the door open together.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The only key to that room was in Sir Belduke's pocket. The only way to enter the study was to break the door open.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And you managed that with the help of a neighbour who came to visit?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes. It wasn't a social visit, mind. He came as a patient.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A patient? Can you tell me more about him?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh, I think you're pushing it this time... A witness is hardly irrelevant!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Grrrr...ngh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's got him so shaken? He looks as if he just had a rush of blood to the head.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Master Belduke had been making very potent medicines, among other things. We would get people coming from the town at all hours of the day or night asking for them. And yet, in return for all the help Master offered, people would gossip about him dabbling in witchcraft...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Err... So you broke the door together with a neighbour?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes. When I explained the situation to him, he brought over an axe. Then he proceeded to attack the door with great force, smashing it into splinters.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I see. By the way, about that neighbour... Who was th-</line>
<line speaker="???">???:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Could it be that it was you who...</line>
<line speaker="???">Where're you lookin', old man? I'm right here! And as for who I am... I'm the alchemist's neighbour... and a witness in that case, too!</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Passion for justice seething within, Emeer is always at the crime scene!♪</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Yep, that's me! Emeer's the name! How've ya been, Bluey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you really the alchemist's neighbour? ...Seriously?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">I know, right?! Freaky coincidence, eh? But yeah, his house's next to mine. *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Ridiculed earlier, Emeer returns! Drinking like a king, he never, ever learns!♪</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...That's why I tried to stop you from asking about the neighbour!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Huh?! Why so cold, Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Unable to hold his steady, cold gaze, Emeer drinks fast, as if in a daze♪</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And...the musician standing next to you...</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Ah, yeah. Tha's me private BARD, Birdly. A right music'l GENIUS.</line>
<line speaker="Cracker">Hold on! Hold on! Oh dearie, dearie me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh dearie ME...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, no use shutting the stable door after the horse has bolted. Let us move on. Witness, since you're already here, you may as well add your testimony. Testify about what you witnessed on the morning after the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">You can count on me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Well, yes, he does. Once every two days, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? Mr Emeer...do you suffer from a serious illness?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Uhh, yeah, kinda. In a manner of speaking... I can't believe I'm still alive, to be honest with ya. I'm always drowsy, always hungry. An' to top it off, nasty murders keep on occurrin' wherever I go...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I'm sick and tired of listening to your babbling, so cut it right there.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">If I may express my personal opinion... I believe Mr Emeer has a truly remarkable ability to come up with different illnesses every day.</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Emeer comes often for his medication. Be it inflammation, irritation or radiation, It is certainly not a fabrication♪</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Tha' day I thought I could use some delicious POTION, so I went t'see th' alchemist!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Delicious potion? Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">An' when I got there, I saw th' butler was 'n a bit of a pickle. Th' study was locked, y'see.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Then you went to get an axe and broke the door?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">That's right! Always wanted t'SMASH somethin' with-'n-axe! I get them kinda urges to destroy stuff, y'see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now that sounds like something you should get treatment for...</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">It dawned on me then! The witch cast Famalia, just like in this case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Sure thing! When the inquisitors came round, I went to have a little peek at the crime scene. That's when I heard 'em talkin' about it. I was surprised, 'cause they must've come to the same conclusion as me. Crikey, they can do their job, them inquisitors, I thought. It had to be Famalia!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So he was eavesdropping...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Emeer">If I 'appen to see that Famalia user, I'll arrest 'em meself! *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Witness! You are testifying in court! Can you not restrain yourself a bit?!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Whazzat?! Don'cha see I gotta have this t'keep me spirits UP? It's th' most POTENT med'cine! *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪'Tis a drink Emeer lives to savour, With an intoxicating scent and flavour♪</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Anyway... This is a waste of time... I should be looking for decisive contradictions.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witnesses, continue your testimonies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">All the potions and other concoctions from the study have been confiscated. I wonder if they're being properly stored...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">No. Not a single thing. Even though many of those were personal items with no relevance to the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that I think about it, that room did look pretty empty.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">As I said... the victim was an alchemist and among his possessions were some very dangerous concoctions. But he did produce medicines to aid sick townspeople as well, to give him his due.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Indeed. Alchemy is highly beneficial to the townspeople, even if they fail to notice it.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It may be beneficial, but it also inspires fear. People fear what they do not understand. At any rate, I cannot return the items to you until Sir Belduke's case is solved. That is what High Inquisitor Darklaw has decided.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the confiscated goods are being kept in a secret vault by the Knights of the Inquisition?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Even the inquisitors cannot freely enter that vault. It is strictly supervised.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That was a pretty short testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">What do you make of it, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, we're talking about an incident that happened three months ago. We've got to get a bit more information first.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Miss Greyerl had plenty of respect for Sir Belduke, you know... I can't believe she would have killed him. I'm sure you'll find the truth... It's what you always do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's all they have to say, huh. I really didn't expect him to appear...but maybe I should be used to it by now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Excuse me, Mr Wright... Sorry to interrupt your train of thought...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm? Oh, that's okay. What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm wondering if it's just me...but...I've been thinking about Mr Emeer's testimony... I think what he said... is a little strange, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, yeah. How can I put it...? It's pretty obviously contradictory.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">He was so keen to testify, maybe we should give him some attention and point those contradictions out!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">What a good idea, Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's something you don't seem to understand here, Mr Emeer. The Famalia gem in this witch's sceptre is a fake. The gem is useless.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Just like this buffoon's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Therefore, your testimony doesn't hold water.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Just like anything else he says. Pssh.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Wha... What?!</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Ignored and scorned, without credibility, Will majestic Emeer now show humility?♪</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">............ Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat?! A faaaaaaaaaake?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You should have listened to the trial more carefully!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now that has been dealt with... Inquisitor Barnham. This witch's sceptre was not discovered at the crime scene when Sir Belduke was murdered, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Indeed. We deduced that Famalia must have been used, however.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph... To be honest, I've started wondering. Were Sir Layton's and Sir Belduke's murders... actually committed by the same witch?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's right, though... It's got to be the same culprit in both cases!</thought> And...at the very least... it's possible that the witch used the spell Godoor to commit Sir Belduke's murder.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wh-what!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In that case, I will ask the defence to show us proof. Do you have proof that the witch could have used Godoor to kill Sir Belduke?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Just like yer very existence, ya could say!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You're all talk. Your assertion is worthless.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Just like me very existence...ya could say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what?</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪"Here's proof", said Sir Knight in Blue, But his argument's been proven untrue!♪</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Bein' publicly ridiculed an' treated like dirt... Now you know how it feels too, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arghhh! <thought>The culprit conjured up a small magic portal in that room... and made use of it to carry out the crime. I'm sure it was possible...and there's evidence that makes it blatantly obvious!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright, let's think again about the circumstances at the crime scene and then give it another go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd like you to take a look at these.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aren't those... the Court Illustrator's sketches?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As you can see from this sketch, the victim was seated at his desk when he was murdered. And what can you see right behind the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...A small landscape painting...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Inquisitor. But there's one more point of note... Look closely at the painting. Do you notice...anything behind it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh...oh! I see it! The wall behind it had already been painted green! Which means the witch could have used the portal spell there three months ago!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witch did not have to enter the room at all! All she had to do was reach through with her arms in order to strangle Sir Belduke, who was sitting right under the painting!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Inquisitor Barnham, what say you to that?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">A fascinating theory, Sir Blue Knight. But there is a notable contradiction within it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Where would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Tell me, why do you think we concluded that Famalia had to have been used? We had a certain reason for it, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And...what was that reason, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The crime scene had been tampered with.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How so?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Imagine the circumstances of Sir Belduke's death, and it should become obvious, even to you. The victim was choked to death. And yet there were no signs of a struggle. Highly improbable, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you getting at?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Think about it. Can you imagine anyone just sitting back and letting themselves be strangled? Clearly there should be evidence of a struggle! And since we haven't found any, that must mean the killer erased all traces of a fight from the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-indeed! That would be the logical conclusion!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Now, surely it would be impossible to do any such thing, had the witch only reached inside through a portal. In order to cover up the evidence she left behind, the witch had to have used a familiar. Without doing so, there would have been no point in her using the spell Godoor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The morning of the crime... from the time Ms Greyerl and that guy entered the study... until the arrival of the Knights of the Inquisition... There was a window of time in which she had the opportunity to do so. We need to look into what happened in that window!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems we may be in need of another testimony. Witnesses, testify about what happened in the time between the body being found and the Knights of the Inquisition arriving.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Sure thing! Ask me aaanything! I'll tell ya all ya need to know!</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Oh, glorious Emeer! Tell us more! Maybe you won't be laughed at as before!♪</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Only two people accessed the crime scene in that time. Greyerl and Emeer. Believe it or not, Emeer is the key witness in this case!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Emeer">I broke down th' door an' saw th' alchemist slumped in 'is chair. Gave me a JOLT!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, what? Mr Emeer... You said the butler didn't enter the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Yup. He never set foot in there! The moment he saw Belduke, he told me to stand guard till the Knights of the Inquisition arrived. And then, off he went... "What a resourceful apprentice that alchemist has," I thought to meself.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I almost feel sorry for you, Sir Blue Knight. After all, your suspect couldn't have tampered with the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>That...can't be true!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defence, please proceed with the interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes, Your Honour!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">I broke down th' door an' saw th' alchemist slumped in 'is chair. Gave me a JOLT!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">'Course I did! We tried to get it open without resorting to brute force, but it wouldn't budge. So I went to fetch me lovely li'l axe.</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪His wooden enemy stood tall and still, Yet Emeer sprang forth - it was overkill!♪</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Heh... Did you think I lied about the door being locked?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, of course not. <thought>Boy, she's so sharp she might cut herself. Or me...most likely me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Emeer">So then I went inside. The alchemist was slumped in his chair.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">While we're at it, allow me to confirm something. When you entered the room... did the victim look the way he does in this sketch?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Yep, that's it! Spot on! Nicely drawn, too! Y'know, at first I didn't know if he was really dead. He looked like he just passed out or somethin', tired from his research. That apprentice of his is real good. To be able to tell at a single glance that the alchemist was done for!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Greyerl... May I ask you something?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think about Mr Emeer's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">There's nothing amiss. However, Mr Wright... I can tell what you are thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You...can? Well, let's see if you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">When he entered the room, Mr Emeer didn't notice that Master Belduke was dead. On the other hand, I ran straight away to call the Knights of the Inquisition. And so... you suspect that I knew beforehand that Master was dead. That's what you're thinking. Your face is like an open book.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ But, isn't that what actually happened?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">No. I knew something was wrong because Master had very fine manners and would never sleep in his chair. When I saw him like that, I was struck with a very bad realisation. I felt certain that something terrible had happened.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. I have heard about you... The word is that you're very collected and perceptive. It would seem to be the case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It would be more appropriate to call her calculating.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Somehow I feel like you're not payin' me enough attention here.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That matters not, witness. Let us proceed with the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Matters not, eh? No need to be so rude about it...</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Th' butler hurried t'call th' Knights of th' Inquisition... He never entered th' study.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Yeah! Like I said, he didn't set foot in that room. I went in and sorta didn't know what to do, but the butler sussed out the situation in the blink of an eye. He told me to stand guard...an' then he ran out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She went to call the Knights of the Inquisition, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That's correct. I went to the nearby garrison.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">We have the records of when the crime was reported. They match the witness' [sic] testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I returned to Master Belduke's house with two knights. They began an investigation immediately, taking away Master's research materials and concoctions... In the end, I wasn't able to enter that room that day.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">There can be no doubt about it. As he...she is the alchemist's apprentice, she was under close observation following the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I wasn't aware of that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So, in the end... she didn't have access to the crime scene at all on that day, huh.</thought> By the way, what were you doing at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Huh? Wha? Me?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Whaddid I do then... Ah, yeah! I was asked t'keep an EYE on things, so I wen' in t'have a bit of a look at everythin'...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Ah, well, I was asked to take care of the crime scene, wasn't I? So I had to, like, make sure everythin' was in order. I mean, y'know... It's not like I went wild with excitement after bein' left in a real alchemist's room, full of mysterious stuff!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm sure you didn't, Mr Sticky Fingers...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Uhm, an' besides...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Besides...?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">She asked me to look for somethin', so I was doin' that too. Can't refuse a request from a lady, amiright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Greyerl... You look lost in thought.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ Oh...were you talking to me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even she can be caught off guard...if I choose the right moment.</thought> You have been listening to Mr Emeer's testimony, haven't you?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes. I have.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He was asked to look for something. It was you who asked him, I assume. What did you tell him to look for?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ I think you're mistaken. I don't remember making any request of that sort.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Oi, Bluey! Were you even listening to what I said? It was a lady that asked me. The butler is a guy, you numbskull! Hey...what's up? Why's everyone lookin' at me like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Quite a while ago, we learned... that the butler, Jean Greyerl, is actually female.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Wha...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's why, when you said a lady asked you to search for something, we assumed it was Ms Greyerl.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Wha... Wha...</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Daydreaming, listening, but not hearing. That look of shock is almost endearing♪</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Whaaaaaaaaaaaaat the?! Why didn't anyone tell me before! [sic]</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Do you require a personal notification? You should have been listening to the trial!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Knights of the Court, squabbling with a witness is most unseemly. What I would like to know now is this: who was the lady that made the request of Emeer?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Uhm... Oh, yeah. That was, actually, Miss...</line>
<line speaker="???">Siiiiiiiirrr!</line>
<line speaker="???">I think, uhm...he's absolutely certainly talking about me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh...and you are...?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Oh, I'm Lettie. Hang on a minute, I'll get down there post-haste!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But...Miss Lettie, who are you, precisely?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Me? Who am I? I'm Lettie Mailer. I'm the courier.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The courier?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">A courier is a person who collects and delivers letters. Or packages.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know... Thanks anyway, Espella. <thought>I wish she'd stop misreading my mind...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Hold on, Ms Mailer. Do you mean it was you who irresponsibly made such a request to that troublemaker?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Me? Maybe. Yes. I guess so. I asked him to help me find something.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Outrageous! Why was I not informed of this?!</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Hmm. I guess no one told you...maybe because you didn't ask?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Grrrrrrr... Nghhhh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems we will need to ask you to testify, Miss Mailer. Explain to us how you were involved in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Frankly, I wouldn't say I was "involved" in anything. Hmm...now I'm in a tight spot. I bet it's because that guy said something weird about me.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Har har har har har! Ease up on me, lady. Like the saying goes... "If I'm goin' down, I'm takin' you with me". Beats bein' in a pickle all on yer own, eh? *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Miss Lettie Mailer... Testify about that day.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Siiiiiiiirrr!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>That voice could make windows shatter.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Emeer's lesser-known gentlemanly side Had me surprised, if I may so confide!♪</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Greyerl asked him to look for something?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What's that? This is news to me. What were you asked to look for? Enlighten us, witness!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">What was it, now... Hmm... Y'know, I can't remember.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, maybe if you didn't drink so much...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Does it matter? In the end, whatever it was, I never found it. I remember that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Yep! Who else? I never had the faintest idea that butler was a girl, y'see.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I apologise for having kept it secret until now.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Oh, no, no! Don't you worry about it, sweetheart. I'm very, uhm, understandin'. But, how to put it... Now that I know... It changes everythin', eh? It's a tad embarrasin' to think I treated ya like a chap. From now on...I'll show ya me gentler side!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Oh, I assure you, there's no need to treat me any differently now. I'm still the same person, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Oh Emeer, you think the girl's sweet, But I fear this candy will rot your teeth♪</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh brother...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Well, anyway... If you wanna know what I was lookin' for, ya'd better ask the courier herself! At any rate, I didn't find it in the end... whatever it was.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">All that made me pretty drowsy, so I wen' an' took-a-little NAP on th' couch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Why so surprised, Bluey? It was 9am... I'm usually still half asleep at that hour. I s'pose maybe all the merrymaking the night before added to that as well...</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪An infamous celebrity known to all inns, Emeer makes merry like a young prince♪</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">So yeah, I was kinda overcome with drowsiness. There was nothing else I could do but go to sleep, right?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">When the butler returned, accompanied by the two knights... he was supposedly sleeping noisily on the victim's couch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean, he was snoring?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Apparently, he was grinding his teeth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Urgh... I shouldn't have asked...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">But then, anyone could've tampered with the crime scene when Mr Emeer was asleep, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! Good catch, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Anyway, I'd barely caught a wink of sleep when those knights arrived... And me teeth-grindin' has sort of a paralysin' effect on people, so I've been told. So even if someone had come in, I don't think they'd've been able to do much.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Right.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Sir Belduke said he'd have a letter to send. So I came by to pick it up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Yes! I was told. By Sir Belduke. That it'd be ready in the morning. What's more, he said it was extremely important. I felt a sense of duty surging within me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Greyerl, I have a question.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did anything catch your attention during Ms Mailer's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Nothing in particular. And at any rate, to begin with...I was not aware of the fact that the courier visited us that day.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Ah! That's right. You weren't there when I arrived. And once I found the letter, I left immediately.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Did you know about this letter, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ I would never pry into Master's personal matters, such as his correspondence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Well, that should conclude the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">And so, you visited Sir Belduke's dwelling... the morning after he was murdered.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">I got a start when I arrived! The door was smashed in, and that man was walking around with an axe, rummaging about. As for Sir Belduke, he was slumped in his chair, and the butler was nowhere to be found. "That brute's gone too far," I thought to myself! You can see why, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Naturally.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In your place, I'd have thought so myself!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">That's mean...</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Anyway, I spoke with him and he told me what happened. So that's when I asked him to help me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You asked him to look for something?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Yes! The letter. I asked him to search for the letter. But in the end, the guy passed out on the couch. I found the letter myself. Then I delivered it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You actually delivered the letter? <thought>That's commitment, all right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">About that letter... Who, in the name of the Noble Author, was it addressed to?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Siiiiiiiirrr! I can't tell you that. Sorry. Couriers can't disclose that sort of info.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Couriers have a confidentiality obligation. No one wants to have the addressees of their letters made public, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I have personally never sent a letter that I would need to keep secret from the public.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ D-don't look at me like that! I was talking about public opinion on the matter, not my own!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Belduke was about to send an important letter when he was killed... That letter... Hmm... It kind of rings a bell.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>Nah, I'm reading too much into it. If I show them a random piece of evidence, they're likely to slice me and dice me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Is something wrong? You've been strangely quiet, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">If there's something you want to say, I think you ought to just say it. If a trial is anything like a puzzle, sometimes the best thing is to give it a go first and see what happens!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now a kid's lecturing me on how to be a good attorney. Ugh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Well, that should conclude the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's just a hunch...and it might not have anything to do with this case, but I need to make sure... I need to know more about Belduke's letter.</thought> Witness...</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Huh? Me? What's up?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The letter Sir Belduke asked you to deliver on that day... Was it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Huh? But. Just now. You sounded quite determined for a second there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just...forget about it, please.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ughh...I felt a cold chill run down my spine just now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Well, that should conclude the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Greyerl didn't set foot in the study...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">But then, that would mean... it wasn't feasible for her to have tampered with the evidence at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">If that's the case, I guess we'd better look at other possibilities...right, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... Unfortunately it all hinges on Emeer's testimony... <thought>But who knows what that guy might say next? I'd better treat him with extra care... Cross-examining him is like walking through a field of landmines... He just might be more dangerous than Barnham!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Let's gently press him into giving us some more information!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll be as gentle as a lamb to make sure I don't get his goat.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So now we know there was a third witness.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">But Miss Mailer only came to pick up a letter. Hmm. That doesn't help us much, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well...perhaps there's more to it than meets the eye.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A letter, huh? <thought>Belduke was about to send a letter to someone before he was killed... It may not be relevant to this case, but something about that is bothering me. Maybe it's worth asking Lettie about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The letter you found that morning... Was it, by any chance, this one here?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Ah! Yes! That's the one! But wait! How did you get it? You're a piece of work all right!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It just sort of...fell into my lap, so to speak. <thought>It was the professor who found it, but he doesn't need to know that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender! Just what in the world...are the contents of that letter?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... The letter's blank.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">All this fuss over a blank letter?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As you can see, there are some sheets of parchment inside the envelope.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed...and there's not a trace of ink on them! What is the meaning of this?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Don't forget that Sir Belduke was an alchemist. He may have used some kind of invisible ink to write that letter.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph... Indeed. That would make sense.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Siiiiiiiirrr! About that. It doesn't make sense to me.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wh-what...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Mailer?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">The thing is... when I saw that letter, all the pages were full of writing. So, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Uhm, I didn't read it. It's just that, you see...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, this is an important matter. You will need to testify about it. Tell us what you know about this letter!</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">That night... Probably about 1am. I made a delivery to Sir Belduke.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph... I see, I see. So you witnessed the victim write the letter?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Uhm... I wouldn't say "witnessed". That sounds so legal. The sheets of parchment were on his desk, though. I saw that. And they were covered in writing, margin to margin.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">But...you don't know what the letter was about?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Siiiiiiiirrr! Telling you would be a breach of our privacy policy! I can't reveal its contents. Or who it was addressed to!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, of course. I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Frankly, I didn't get close enough. To Sir Belduke's desk, I mean. So I couldn't make out what he was writing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In any case, where did you find the letter the morning after the victim was found dead?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Uhm... On a shelf. Next to his desk. In a small letterbox. Ah, yes! Right there. Next to his head. I was a teeny little bit scared, though. Coming so close to a dead man.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's where she took the letter from... It was right next to the corpse, huh.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now that the circumstances are clear, we shall proceed to the cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">That night... Probably about 1am. I made a delivery to Sir Belduke.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Look, he's an alchemist. He gets loads of strange packages. That's why. He'd often order various implements from the glass craftsman. Or have someone gather wild herbs for him. He usually carried out his experiments at night. So, yeah. He often needed items delivered in the middle of the night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did Sir Belduke seem at all different than normal when you saw him that night?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Different? Let me think. Actually, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">I think...it was about three days before. Before Sir Belduke's death, I mean. That lightning strike...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Ms Greyerl.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Oh... What... What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did anything in Ms Mailer's statement catch your attention?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ Well...just the lightning strike. Master Belduke did certainly change following that event. I wonder why it affected him so much...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>An alchemist and the sudden appearance of an old bell tower... Could there be some sort of a connection between them?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Anyway, it looks like Greyerl is as much in the dark about this as I am.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">By the way... that strange lightning strike was not the result of witchcraft.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. I see. Well then, let us carry on.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Lightning strike? Ah, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, yes. That certainly was an unusual event.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>They all seem so calm about it. A tower suddenly materialising in the town is more than just an "unusual event", right...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mailer">I had a delivery for Sir Belduke that evening, too. He looked terrified that night. As if he was scared of something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What could he have been afraid of? <thought>Was it because of the lightning strike?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mailer">I was wondering about it too... But, well. Then that incident happened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess he died before she could find out any more...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I suggest we get back to discussing the night of the crime. Witness, you arrived at Sir Belduke's residence. What happened then?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">He was writing a letter at the time. "It'll be ready soon, so come pick it up tomorrow morning." That's what he said.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Uhm. I told you before. There were sheets of parchment with writing on them on his desk. I had a very quick look. There were so many sheets. The letter must've been very long.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Then how can you explain the letter being blank now?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Siiiiiiiirrr! That's just it. That's what I'd like to know as well!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wish I had some ear plugs...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Sir Belduke... He was holding a pen when I arrived with the delivery. Se he was in the middle of writing. And also...he told me to pick up the letter next morning.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">And then you left his study.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">I left his study and wished the butler a good night. Then I went home.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Mr...um, Miss Greyerl, of course. She was in the corridor, carrying a tray. You know... Actually, I quite liked the butler. Is it really true she's a girl? It's a bit...disappointing. To me, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Greyerl... I'd like to ask you something.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Oh... Certainly. What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You stated previously... that you excused yourself and left Sir Belduke's study shortly after 1am.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes, that is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However, according to Ms Mailer's testimony... the two of you came across each other while you were waiting outside that room.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why didn't you mention that until now?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That... That's because... ............ I apologise. I'm afraid I completely forgot to mention it.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You forgot?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Miss Mailer very often comes with deliveries during the night. I did see her that night as well. But I didn't think much of it, as it's nothing unusual. I had no reason to hide that from you. Please forgive me for the confusion.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Well, that kind of thing can happen. Human memory is in no way perfect. I don't imagine there's a problem here, is there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...On the contrary, Your Honour. There's one more thing Ms Greyerl forgot to mention.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd like you to recall what Ms Mailer said about having met Ms Greyerl that night.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Mr...um, Miss Greyerl, of course. She was in the corridor, carrying a tray.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Ms Greyerl. Apparently you were carrying a tray at the time... What do you have to say about that?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Jean Greyerl, I believe you should add that to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...As you wish, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's unlikely she really forgot about it... The fact she tried to hide it must mean something!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Oh, I... I'm sorry I was unable to meet your expectations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not sure I want to know about her "expectations".</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">In any case, Miss Mailer did visit us that night. She came to deliver a package to Master Belduke. She delivered it to Master personally. There were always many things to which I was not privy.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Right. And I saw you that night. When I was leaving. I almost walked into you.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes, it's just as you say. I was about to wish Master Belduke a good night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Greyerl looks a lot more confident now... But she seemed so shaken for a moment earlier. I wonder what that was about... Maybe I missed the right moment.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Witnesses, continue with your testimonies.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Miss Mailer left just as I was bringing Master his usual drink.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">When Master's experiments continued into late hours, he would always have some juice to ward off sleepiness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What kind of juice?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Tomato juice. He'd have one bottle every night. It was my daily routine to bring it to him before withdrawing to my room for the night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me...mister.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mister!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Bwahhhhh! I...I know nothin' about it! Nothin'! Nothin' at all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Witness... What have you done this time?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Don't... Don't give me that scary look! Inquisitor Barnham! I... I... It was only...just a little bit! Seriously. Hardly anythin' at all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhm... What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Huh? Wh-whaddya think I'm talkin' about? The j-juice. The tomato juice, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The...tomato juice...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Oh, you didn't... Surely even you wouldn't!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Well, like I told ya before... I think I sorta overdid it a bit the previous night... When I woke up, me head was poundin'. That's why I went to see the alchemist. But you know what happened. And when I was left alone in the alchemist's study... it kinda caught me eye. The bottle, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The tomato juice...</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">I thought it might make the headache go away, y'know...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So you...you drank it? The juice found at the crime scene?!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Well, why shouldn't I? It's a drink, ain't it? What else do you do with a drink? You drink it, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And can you tell us where that bottle is now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come to think of it...I don't remember seeing it at the crime scene.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">It has been confiscated.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Confiscated?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">As I mentioned previously... The Occult Crime Analysts confiscated all of Master's personal belongings from the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is that so? Well, I believe we should take note of that bottle and add it to the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Yeah, so, there I was, havin' a bit of juice, when that girl came round.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Siiiiiiiirrr!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">To tell ya the truth... I don't quite remember what happened after that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's when he passed out, huh.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, you brought him tomato juice that night too?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes. I did. Master Belduke thanked me, as always, and then I left him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ Please accept my sincere apologies. It was such an obvious part of my daily routine that it didn't even occur to me to mention it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You want us to believe that you simply forgot to tell us?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That would match the evidence found at the crime scene. I do remember seeing an uncorked bottle of tomato juice there.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright! Please take a look at this! It's here in the Court Illustrator's sketch too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So it is. That Court Illustrator certainly does pay attention to the details...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Then, that would mean... the red liquid trickling down from the victim's mouth is not, in fact, blood. It is tomato juice. I think we can safely make that assumption.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Poor Master...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">When Master's experiments continued into late hours, he would always have some juice to ward off sleepiness.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You mean this tomato juice, do you not?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That is correct. I would go to the market every morning to pick up some freshly squeezed juice. He'd have one bottle every night. It was my daily routine to bring it to him before withdrawing to my room for the night.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That would be the same juice you drank at the crime scene, stealing from a dead man, would it not?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Aww, come on! I just took a sip. Well, maybe a bit more than a sip...but I didn't drink it all! I thought you guys might get thirsty durin' the investigation. See, I'm a pretty nice guy sometimes, y'know.</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪How delightful! Leftover, warm juice! Kind Emeer, you deserve no abuse♪</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">No one except you would drink that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Greyerl didn't want us to know about that juice... But why would she choose to hide it? There's got to be a reason...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witnesses, continue your testimonies.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Siiiiiiiirrr!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">I went there again the next morning, as promised. Sir Belduke was... Well anyway, I looked for the letter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Uhm, that's right. I took it. From the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Siiiiiiiirrr! Uhm. Well, it might be a crime, sure... But just look at the witch's defender. He's got to defend a witch...using any dirty tricks at his disposal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Dirty tricks? Wh-what dirty tricks...?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">It's the same for me, you know? I'm a courier. So come rain or shine, I've got to deliver. Where there's mail, there's Mailer!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">I was so inspired by the young lady's spirit that I kinda just had to help.</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Although inspired by her dedication, He betrayed a lack of concentration♪</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">It is entirely my fault that it came to that. Had I only been at the residence then...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Ughhh... Blarg.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm. Greyerl was out notifying the knights at the time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Then that guy went out like a light on the couch. I got a little scared. So I left as soon as I found the letter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">He was helping me look for the letter. And then it happened. Out of the blue. He just passed out. The rascal. He collapsed. And his eyes rolled back. He wouldn't move.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It almost sounds like he died...</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Uhm. No such luck, unfortunately. That horrible sound... He was grating his teeth. I thought my ears would explode!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Hm... Yep, not sure what came over me! Never happened to me before, sleepin' like that. Y'know, I didn't just fall asleep. More like I sorta blacked out, I guess. No idea why... Oi, you guys, whaddya think? Any ideas?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I think it bears no relevance. And there you have my honest answer.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">And I think it's good that I wasn't there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But the question is: why did he black out like that...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's really odd, even for that guy, to just suddenly fall unconscious. But... I don't think I have any evidence to show what might have caused it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright! Maybe we could use some more information.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I think Luke may be right. And I think that's what the professor is trying to tell us, too.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>To me, it looks like he's demanding I find the answer right this second... For now it's probably best to gather some more info, like Luke said.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honour, I might have a clue as to why this witness suddenly lost consciousness.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You do?!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Really? D'ya work it out, Bluey?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that's the case, may the defence present some evidence! Which piece of evidence shows why this man fell unconscious?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">*gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* Bluey! Wanna sip of this? It'll wake ya up!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I might like some as well. I'm suddenly overcome with sleepiness, due to boredom.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's getting quite late, and I must admit your tiresome mistakes are not helping me stay awake, either!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like that wasn't the right evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright! As I thought, we'd better gather some more information before venturing a guess.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I agree. And I think that's what the professor is trying to tell us, too.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>To me, it looks like he's demanding I find the answer right this second... I'll get more info and take another shot at it. Gotta think hard about this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That courier sure is committed to her work...or maybe just plain crazy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright, this testimony raises more questions than it answers, doesn't it? Sir Belduke wrote that letter the night before his death, and yet now it's blank.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a mystery, all right. But there's something else unusual in what she said.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There is?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The part about that guy going out like a light seemed strange to me as well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">That witness said he felt a surge of drowsiness at the time, but still...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something about that seems kind of odd, even for a guy like him...</thought> I have a feeling there's much more to Ms Mailer's testimony than meets the eye. I'll get to the bottom of this, don't worry.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Good luck!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That courier sure is committed to her work...or maybe just plain crazy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright, this testimony raises more questions than it answers, doesn't it? Sir Belduke wrote that letter the night before his death, and yet now it's blank.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a mystery, all right. But there's something else unusual in what she said.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">When she said "that guy" fell unconscious at the crime scene, she meant Mr Emeer, right? He said himself that he felt a surge of drowsiness at the time, but still...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe it's worth looking into the reason behind that drowsiness. What could have made him suddenly pass out and sleep like a log in a dead man's room?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh! I think I know what it might have been!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right, Luke. There's a certain piece of evidence that might be related here. <thought>I suppose I should present that evidence and test out my little theory.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Let's try it, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mister, I believe the reason you might have lost consciousness at the crime scene... is tied to a certain piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">But wasn't it just because, y'know, I had a bit too much fun the night before?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No. It was because of...this!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The tomato juice?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You passed out right after drinking this juice. Therefore, it's not unreasonable to assume that there's a direct connection between the two.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Tomato juice does not make people fall unconscious, Sir Blue Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. That's why something must have been added to the contents of that bottle! Something like...a soporific!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Y-you mean, sleep medicine?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And if a soporific was mixed in with the tomato juice... that means Sir Belduke would have been unconscious at the time he was assailed!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! Oooooooh! Th-this sketch! Have another look. The red liquid trickling down from the victim's mouth... is proof that Sir Belduke must have drank the tomato juice!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I...I had failed to consider this...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Inquisitor Barnham, I bet you remember saying this to the court: "Can you imagine anyone just sitting back and letting themselves be strangled? Clearly there should be evidence of a struggle! And since we haven't found any, that must mean the killer erased all traces of a fight from the crime scene." However! If the victim was unconscious when his assailant was strangling him... then the killer could have committed the crime through a small portal, big enough to put their arms through, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was very simple. And I think you've realised why.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">From the alchemist...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. An alchemist would no doubt have a wide array of various medicaments in their possession. And an apprentice would have little trouble stealing some of them from their study. Isn't that right...Ms Greyerl?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ How should I respond to that... "I'm sorry to disappoint you" may perhaps be the best way to put it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Even though that juice bottle has been safely stored for the past three months... I'm positive it would be impossible to find any traces of that soporific now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...You... You wicked...</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Siiiiiiiirrr!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Hold on, everyone! The butler couldn't have done that to Sir Belduke! He...she would never, ever do it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Please! Let us testify just one more time! Miss Greyerl, let's tell them! Let's prove they're wrong! They have no idea how much you've done for Sir Belduke!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Miss Mailer...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. I shall grant your request. Testify about the relationship between Miss Greyerl and Sir Belduke.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Master took me in, a complete stranger. I will forever be indebted to him.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Sir Belduke was a wonderful man! He's the one who recommended this line of work to me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's true that Sir Belduke evoked fear due to his being an alchemist... However, he was also a man of admirable character, who supported the townsfolk through his research. Why would anyone want to kill such a man? This question keeps haunting me...however much I think about it.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Witches need no reason behind their evil. That is what makes them witches.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, the defence may begin its interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Master took me in, a complete stranger. I will forever be indebted to him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I suppose it would be five years now. Before that, I'd lost everything. I had nothing and nobody left in this world.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You lost everything?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That's when Master Belduke helped me. He kindly took me in and gave me work.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What did she go through before she started working for Belduke?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Later, when I was helping Master with his research, he even taught me how to read and write. I was able to live comfortably for so long, all because of Master.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't know much about Greyerl... but she doesn't seem the type to kill someone she owes so much to.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Everyone in this town knows how you served Sir Belduke. Now, you may continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That's why I could never make an attempt on his life, through magic or otherwise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes. You can ask whomever you wish, and I'm sure they will say the same.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That is so. It is widely known that Jean Greyerl was devoted to serving Sir Belduke. It's difficult to imagine that she could brutally murder her respected master.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed, I am of the same opinion. I have visited Sir Belduke on several occasions, to enquire about this piece of evidence or that... and I must say I felt there was a strong bond of trust between him and Miss Greyerl.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Do you still think you can come up with a motive?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A motive...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Jean Greyerl's motive for murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Greyerl risked a lot to conjure up a small portal in the wall. And then she killed Belduke. But what motive did she have?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I understand. The defence will present evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Evidence to indicate Jean Greyerl's motive for murder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Precisely.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence shall now present evidence! What was Jean Greyerl's motive for murder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Can you repeat that last bit? I'm afraid I misheard.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Even I have never used a catchpenny line like that.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, I trembled a little! All those chilling stares are giving me the shivers.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright, no matter how cold everyone else might be towards you, I'll always stay on your side.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Presenting that evidence was a big mistake. Trying to show off was an even bigger one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The one who ought to tremble is you, Sir Blue Knight!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arghhhhhhhh! <thought>Well, guess I'd better revise my theory.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright, I just thought of something... We might be basing our theory on a wrong assumption.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wrong assumption?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I understand. The defence will present evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Evidence to indicate Jean Greyerl's motive for murder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...No.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wait...what?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What's this about, Sir Blue Knight?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sir Belduke's life was taken that day. That's a fact. However... was this actually the culprit's true objective?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm fairly positive this piece of evidence will lead us to the culprit's real motive!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Defence, present evidence... to indicate Jean Greyerl's motive for committing the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However, there was another incident that night, which is related to this case... And I have an idea what it was.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">"Another incident"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm referring to this letter. Sir Belduke wrote a letter shortly before his death, yet all we have here are some blank sheets of parchment.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Fascinating. Are you saying maybe a witch used some kind of ink-removing magic on that letter, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No. The spell used by the witch was, of course, Godoor.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's go over the state of the crime scene one more time. As we know from Ms Mailer's testimony... the letter was in a letterbox next to the victim's head.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah yes, it's in the sketch as well. The letterbox is on the far side of the shelf.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The point of note is the location of that letterbox.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">U-unbelievable!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As Inquisitor Barnham seems to have noticed, the letterbox is within reach... of the small portal conjured by the witch, behind the painting on the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, indeed it is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And, as Sir Belduke's butler... you would have known exactly where he keeps his letters!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ Indeed, Master Belduke would always keep his letters... in that letterbox, before posting them.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You...you mentioned no such thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Greyerl! You created a portal with Godoor... not with the intention of killing Sir Belduke. You were after this letter, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That's...merely wild conjecture. I didn't even know about that letter at the time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You didn't? Now that's very strange.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When Ms Mailer came by that night, Sir Belduke was busy writing that letter. And that's when you entered. Carrying a bottle of tomato juice.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no way you wouldn't have known that you master was writing a letter to someone! And you could've known even more than that... For instance, perhaps you knew what he was writing about.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That's enough! I served Master Belduke as his butler. I never would have pried into his private affairs! Whatever it was he wrote about in his final letter to the Storyteller... it is no concern of mine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, defence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd like Ms Greyerl's last statement to be added to her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Any objections, Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ No, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Witness, include what you just told us in your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">As you wish, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Can you repeat that last bit? I'm afraid I misheard.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Even I have never used a catchpenny line like that.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, I trembled a little! All those chilling stares are giving me the shivers.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright, no matter how cold everyone else might be towards you, I'll always stay on your side.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Presenting that evidence was a big mistake. Trying to show off was an even bigger one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The one who ought to tremble is you, Sir Blue Knight!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arghhhhhhhh! <thought>Well, guess I'd better revise my theory.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright, I just thought of something... We might be basing our theory on a wrong assumption.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wrong assumption?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't come up with any reason why Greyerl would want to kill Belduke. I'd better wait until I have some more information to go on...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">I think... we've heard everything the witnesses had to tell us. We won't get any more out of them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Miss Greyerl wouldn't kill Sir Belduke!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But...he's dead. And when you think about who could have killed him... ............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Are you all right, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The murder happened. Nothing's going to change that. But... was murder really the culprit's primary objective?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Uhm, what are you thinking about, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm. I think I may need to consider some other possibilities after all. <thought>Rather than try to get any more info, maybe I'll be better off changing my perspective.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, I've been thinking...maybe we've been making the wrong assumptions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What if Greyerl's aim wasn't to get Belduke out of the picture...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However, there was another incident that night, which is related to this case... And I have an idea what it was.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">"Another incident"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm referring to this letter. Sir Belduke wrote a letter shortly before his death, yet all we have here are some blank sheets of parchment.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Fascinating. Are you saying maybe a witch used some kind of ink-removing magic on that letter, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No. The spell used by the witch was, of course, Godoor.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's go over the state of the crime scene one more time. As we know from Ms Mailer's testimony...the letter was in a letterbox next to the victim's head.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah yes, it's in the sketch as well. The letterbox is on the far side of the shelf.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The point of note is the location of that letterbox.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">U-unbelievable!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As Inquisitor Barnham seems to have noticed, the letterbox is within reach...of the small portal conjured by the witch, behind the painting on the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, indeed it is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And, as Sir Belduke's butler...you would have known exactly where he keeps his letters!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ Indeed, Master Belduke would always keep his letters...in that letterbox, before posting them.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You...you mentioned no such thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Greyerl! You created a portal with Godoor...not with the intention of killing Sir Belduke. You were after this letter, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That's...merely wild conjecture. I didn't even know about that letter at the time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You didn't? Now that's very strange.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When Ms Mailer came by that night, Sir Belduke was busy writing that letter. And that's when you entered. Carrying a bottle of tomato juice.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no way you wouldn't have known that you master was writing a letter to someone! And you could've known even more than that... For instance, perhaps you knew what he was writing about.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That's enough! I served Master Belduke as his butler. I never would have pried into his private affairs! Whatever it was he wrote about in his final letter to the Storyteller...it is no concern of mine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, defence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd like Ms Greyerl's last statement to be added to her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Any objections, Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ No, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Witness, include what you just told us in your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">As you wish, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I had no reason to take his life nor steal his letter to the Storyteller.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That's right. I believe I have said as much already.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then...how did you know? How did you know it was addressed to the Storyteller?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah... Indeed!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Why don't you answer his question, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's true this letter is addressed to the Storyteller. But when did you find out about it?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ I have spoken about the murder with many people over the past three months. Everyone has been very kind to me. They have also told me all sorts of things. I must have heard about it... From someone, at some point.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Ms Mailer.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">............ Oh! Siiiiiiiirrr!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I thought I caught her off guard...but it's her screech that's caught me off guard...</thought> Is there perhaps anything you'd like to add to Ms Greyerl's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">............ Uhm... No, not really.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In that case, let me ask you a different question. Did you tell Ms Greyerl about Sir Belduke's letter?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">............ I dunno... ............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Do not beat about the bush, witness! Answer the question!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">If I may briefly interrupt...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I am testifying right now. If you wish to question Miss Mailer, please do so once you have finished interrogating me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's not going to let me question Mailer, from the looks of it. And if she's so keen to prevent her from answering... this might just be a critical point in the testimony. I've got to find another way of fishing for that information!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witnesses, continue testifying.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Well, that incident was certainly much talked about. Would you not agree, defence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Does her testimony hold together?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's nothing odd in her testimony. <thought>To be honest, something she said doesn't quite feel right, but... I can't come up with anything to prove there's a contradiction.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's good, then. Let us continue the interrogation.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Excuse me, Mr Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm? What's up, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Contradictions can be exposed without the need for evidence... The professor said something like that back when Espella was on trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>Now that I think about it... The professor did talk about a different kind of weapon that I could use in court. Maybe I should keep that in mind and give it another try.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witnesses, continue testifying!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is a huge contradiction in Ms Greyerl's testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You are becoming very predictable, Sir Blue Knight. If there is a contradiction, I hope you have the evidence to prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Here's my chance. There's only one way to expose this contradiction...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defence is ready to present evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The defence shall present evidence of a different nature. What does the defence believe to contradict Miss Greyerl's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Can you repeat that last bit? I'm afraid I misheard.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Even I have never used a catchpenny line like that.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, I trembled a little! All those chilling stares are giving me the shivers.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright, no matter how cold everyone else might be towards you, I'll always stay on your side.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Presenting that evidence was a big mistake. Trying to show off was an even bigger one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The one who ought to tremble is you, Sir Blue Knight!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arghhhhh! <thought>Ughh... That didn't go well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Excuse me, Mr Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm? What's up, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Contradictions can be exposed without the need for evidence... The professor said something to this effect when Espella was on trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>Now that I think about it... The professor did talk about a different kind of weapon that I could use in court. Maybe I should keep that in mind and give it another try.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witnesses, continue testifying!</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Sir Belduke was a wonderful man! He's the one who recommended this line of work to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">That's right. I was also a, what do you call it... An orphan. I'd been stealing bread or apples and such from stalls and shops to survive. I was known far and wide among the traders in the shopping area. I was famous...or rather, infamous.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Was she stealing from Mrs Eclaire, too?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mailer">And one day, Miss Greyerl took me there. To Sir Belduke's residence, I mean. Sir Belduke helped me. He helped me to find a suitable job.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And so you became a courier?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Yes. See, I only had one real skill... I'm light-footed! At first I didn't take it seriously. The job, I mean. I didn't care about work. But then I realised it. That it's not so bad to be useful. You know, to other people. So, I owe him a lot too, you see. Sir Belduke, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. What a heart-warming story.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think the judge just wiped away a tear with the rim of his hood...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The more you hear about Sir Belduke, the more obvious it will become that no one had any reason to want to kill him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It sure does seem that way...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mailer">And he's the one who told me about it. The confidentiality obligation, I mean. I've never once broken it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Yes! A courier must not disclose the contents of a letter, nor the names nor addresses of its sender and recipient! But I'll tell you confidentially that, uhm... I love gossiping. Bad-mouthing people, especially. So I wasn't confident I could keep it. The confidentiality obligation, I mean. I was tempted to talk about this and that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>To think that Belduke trusted her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mailer">But then, Sir Belduke spoke to me. He told me this: "think [sic] about how you'd feel in that person's place". And that got me thinking. I really, really like to gossip. But when it comes to being gossiped about... People's messages are their secrets. And secrets must be kept!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. No one would want their letters to be publicly known.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's certainly determined when it comes to confidentiality... That's why she doesn't want to disclose the addressee of Belduke's letter. I'm not going to get it out of her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mailer">I promised Sir Belduke. And I'm going to keep it, no matter what! The promise, I mean. It's something I can pride myself on! ...Right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>End of the road for testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Everyone knows that Miss Greyerl respected Sir Belduke. That's why...it seems so inconceivable that she could be the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">She doesn't have any motive...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But that crime did take place.</thought> At this point what we probably need to do... is look at this case from a different angle. Change the perspective, so to speak.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...We just need to look at it from another angle? I wonder...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I feel we're getting close to the truth here. Now I just need to follow it through. That's an attorney's duty.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm sure you can do it, Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Greyerl may not have had a motive to murder Belduke. But... what if she used the portal spell to obtain that letter? Depending on the contents of the letter, that might prove to have been her motive!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">I wonder what Sir Belduke wrote about in that letter...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's only one way to find out... <thought>I need to get Greyerl to admit that she got hold of that letter.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm worried, Mr Wright...of what's lying ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The feeling's mutual... But I have to see it through. I've got to pursue the truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defence has no intention of presenting evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wh-what?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The proof that there is a contradiction... cannot be found in the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">What... What is the meaning of this, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The professor pointed it out to me in the previous witch trial... In this court, an attorney's arsenal isn't limited to the Court Record.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Each of the witnesses in this trial has given their own account of what occurred. Therefore...whenever one witness has testified, the other remaining witnesses have listened. Should one witness' [sic] testimony differ from another's testimony, then... I suppose that in itself can also be considered a contradiction, can it not...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Juxtaposing contradictory testimonies from different witnesses is the key!</thought> Ms Greyerl...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your testimony contradicts another one that we've heard in this court today!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I had no reason to take his life nor steal his letter to the Storyteller.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix/Espella/Luke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix/Espella/Luke">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Luke">M-Mr Wright, please hold on a moment! Were you just, as they say, trying to wing it by saying something random?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph... I'm not sure I follow what the defence is trying to say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm very sorry, Your Honour! The Golden Professor here seemed to be pointing out a contradiction there. I, uhh...guess he was wrong. Ha ha.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Don't try to pin the blame on the professor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm sure there was a piece of testimony that contradicted Greyerl's... I just need to put them side by side in my head and see which ones don't match up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">A little slip up is no reason to give in. Come on, let's try again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The testimony that contradicts what Ms Greyerl said is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was a single word that gave you away, Ms Greyerl.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">What...what do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The name of the recipient. There were only a few people who knew the intended recipient of that letter. Four people, to be precise.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Only...four people?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">First was Sir Belduke, the author of the letter. Then there was Ms Mailer, who delivered it. And of course the Storyteller, its recipient. As well as...one more person. The one who stole the letter, using a portal spell, and swapped it with the blank sheets of parchment...the witch.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Siiiiiiiirrr!!!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You did what?!</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Uhm. Well, because, you see...me and the butler are sort of friends. And it was about our dear Sir Belduke. I feel like I might've told her about it after all! See? If I did, that's how she knew! About the recipient, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Huh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Remember your testimony. You told us about the courier's duty to keep the details of letters confidential. And you have also testified... that you have never broken that obligation. Remember?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Ah... Siiiiiiiiiiiiiiiirrr!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When Ms Mailer came with the delivery, Sir Belduke was still writing that letter. In fact, he was in the middle of it. At that time, the letter had not been addressed yet. And the next morning, when the body was discovered, that letter was already in the letterbox. Keep in mind that Ms Greyerl would have had no opportunity to see it then, either.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Is that...so...? She went to report the crime without even setting foot in the study...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And then, Ms Mailer appeared and retrieved the letter. Needless to say, Ms Greyerl couldn't have learned of the letter's recipient afterwards.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Or maybe you have a good explanation, Ms Greyerl? I'd very much like to hear one. Can you please tell the court how you found out the recipient's name?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ Mr Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhm, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Do you remember what I said when I was called to the witness stand?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">At the heart of alchemy lies the pursuit of the rules and logic that govern nature. You have demonstrated the power of your own logic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Greyerl...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are...are you saying...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes. I confess. The abhorrent witch who used the spell Godoor to swap the contents of that letter... and who took the life of Master Belduke... It was none other than I.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That day, I suddenly remembered about [sic] the witch's sceptre that I had hidden.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The Goldor spell...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I thought I'd try it, just once...casting the spell. But at the time, I had no idea what an irreversible mistake that would be.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Even though no one told me... I knew from the very beginning what magic I was able to use.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">But...it wasn't the right thing to do after all. ...I was terribly punished for using magic, even just the once.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Punished?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...In what way were you punished?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I placed the leaf down in the back garden and cast the spell. But then... Margaret suddenly walked in front of me.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Margaret?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">My...closest childhood friend. Margaret... Right before my eyes, she... She was turned into gold!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, dear me!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I screamed and cried but...I knew I couldn't ask anyone for help. If anyone had seen it, they would have known it was the work of magic. And I knew...Margaret wasn't coming back.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That...that's terrible...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Then, my mother and father's faces flashed before my eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Master Belduke met with my parents and explained everything to them. They were very sad...but they agreed it would be best if I didn't return home.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Poor Miss Greyerl... That must have been so awful for her...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Master bought the house for my parents, so they wouldn't have to worry about paying rent any more. As for Margaret, turned into gold...he brought her to his residence. He knew that if anyone saw her, they would report an incident of witchcraft.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And this Miss Margaret, is she...still in that golden state?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes...she is.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Hmm, that's strange. We have received no reports of anyone by that name having gone missing.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Margaret is...being kept in the basement under Master's study.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The...basement? Correct me if I'm wrong, but this Margaret... Is she a...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes. My dear friend...was a goat that we were keeping at our house.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...Goat.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Until then, Master Belduke had mainly been researching medicine... but since the incident with Margaret, he became known as an alchemist.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's when he became an alchemist... I was wondering why the goat was the only thing not covered in dust...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That's how I started a new life as Master Belduke's butler.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Sir Belduke would sometimes work as a physician, curing the townspeople of their illnesses. As his assistant, you have also shown commitment to helping the townspeople through your work.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I forgot about being a witch and was able to live happily, at peace with everyone... I thought it could stay like that forever... ............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...But those peaceful days came to an abrupt end. Tell us...what in the world was the cause?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ Even I am not quite sure what led to this. However... it all started three months ago, with that lightning strike.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">But the expression on Master Belduke's face was unlike anything I'd seen before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">His face went pale and twisted in sheer terror. He was shaking violently...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Perhaps Sir Belduke saw something that others couldn't.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">He cancelled his experiments for that night and began writing a letter to someone.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A letter...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I found out about it when I brought him his bottle of tomato juice.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Everything went black in front of my eyes. I will never forget the feeling... that overwhelmed me at that moment.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is that when you decided to commit the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">What I did first was "accidentally" singe a part of the wall in my room. It was an excuse to repaint that section of the wall...green.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Then you also painted the wall behind that painting in Sir Belduke's study.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">And when that fateful night came...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">"Storyteller".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I would like you to believe me... that the thought of taking Master Belduke's life never once occurred to me. I only planned to steal that letter and then disappear. But...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">There is just one thing I fail to understand.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You said you wanted to run away once you had stolen the letter. Yet despite that, you continued to live in Sir Belduke's residence. And now, here you stand. Why did you not run away?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ My life had been thrown into disarray due to the absurdity of magic. I had learned all about alchemy, living at Master's residence. Alchemy is concerned with the logic that governs the world. I...wanted to believe that there truly was such a thing. So I stayed in that place hoping to one day see the irrational nature of magic overcome by the power of reason.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Magic being overcome by reason...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That night... I swapped the letter with blank sheets of parchment and waited for the sun to rise. I resolved to wait for the day when my true identity could be exposed through reason and logic. Master's death remained a mystery for three months. And people started to lose interest. And then you appeared, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">On the day you visited the residence... I was listening to your conversation from the other room. "Has the time finally come for me?" My heart was racing with anticipation. Then... a few minutes after everyone entered that room, an unbelievable incident took place.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That incident...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">A witch appeared...in Master's study.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wh-what?!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I wanted to get a look at the witch, so I created a portal in the wall behind the painting. Precisely at that moment...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I knew at the time what kind of a witch the Inquisition would be looking for.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A witch that can use Famalia and Goldor.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">It occurred to me that I only needed to change one of the magic gems. I had previously found out that the Famalia gem was purple. I realised that if I swapped the Godoor magic gem for my amethyst... I could pin the blame for my crime on that other witch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you changed one of the gems and threw the witch's sceptre into that room, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...Exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How so, Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes...you are right.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Can someone explain to me what this is about?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I am a witch, indeed. A sinful creature that killed the person to whom she owed her life. However... regarding the gentleman standing next to you, Mr Wright... He may have fallen victim to a witch... But that witch was not me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ohhh... Wait, whaaaaat?! Order! Order! Order in the court! What...in the... What is the meaning of this?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Jean Greyerl admits killing Sir Belduke, but not to turning Sir Layton into gold. That is the gist of it, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-but lying about it is meaningless!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lying?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Just being a witch is a crime in itself. And the punishment for that crime is the same, regardless of whether she took one person's life or two. That's why there's no point in lying about it. I'm sure that's what the judge is thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Greyerl is still claiming she never laid a finger on the professor... But if there's no point in lying...does that mean she must be telling us the truth?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">So in that case, who's responsible for what happened to the professor? If it wasn't her, then who was it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="???">...Uhm.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Mind if I say somethin'?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ Take a hint, witness. Does it feel like this is the right moment for you to talk?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Yeah, well. That's kinda why I was stayin' quiet until now. But... I either say it now or never. ............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Don't simply fall silent after saying that! It only makes it weigh on my mind more! Whatever did you want to say?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">............ Oi, Bluey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh... Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">The alchemist's butler...uhm, lady butler. She slipped sleep medicine into his drink?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's correct. She laced his tomato juice with it.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">And then he...uhm, she strangled the alchemist afterwards?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. Sir Belduke was unconscious from the sleep medicine, so he didn't resist.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">And that explains why we found no signs of a struggle at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Yeah... About that... I let it slip earlier about what I did at the crime scene, right? I told you that...uhm...I had a few sips of that juice.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...And the sleep medicine mixed in made you sleep like a log. Yes, we remember.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Yeah, well... Here's the thing... This is just between us, okay? Y'see, when I appropriated that juice... the juice bottle was, well...still unopened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was unopened?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Har har har. Me throat was parched, and I wasn't thinking straight. That brand new bottle was just there, waitin' for me, with a corkscrew conveniently laid next to it. I couldn't just let that go to waste. I swiftly pulled out the cork and got to drinkin'.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wh-what...?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">So, in case you don't get what I'm gettin' at, the alchemist... didn't have a single drop of the juice with the sleep medicine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh... Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-witness! You... You... ...went to the trouble of opening a bottle found at a crime scene just to drink its suspicious contents?!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">That's what I've been tellin' ya, I was dyin' of thirst!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That doesn't justify what you've done!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Indeed, you are right, Inquisitor. Her role in the Sir Layton incident is not entirely clear... but a person who kills her protector, to whom she owes her very life, can be nothing other than a witch. The court has sufficient grounds to sentence her as such.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Belduke didn't drink the juice that night... And if that's true, there's one thing here that doesn't add up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Wright! I have to say, there's something about this that's bothering me. I'm sure there's a contradiction lurking in that man's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">You think so, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Can I really turn a blind eye to that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If the judge passes his verdict now, Maya should be found innocent. Getting her cleared of charges should be my priority as her attorney, I guess.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>That's Maya's voice!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, you've already helped me out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maya...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But... You haven't uncovered the whole truth just yet. It's not like you to leave this stuff unfinished!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>My role here... is to trust my client and fight to the end. I need to find the truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mister, you're saying you opened the tomato juice bottle... But that claim contradicts a certain piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wh-what?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ Defence, I'd like a word with you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honour?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">At this point. your client's innocence has already been established. Therefore, whether there is a contradiction in that man's testimony or not should no longer be any of your concern.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That may be so, Your Honour. But, even though I'm here to defend the accused... the true duty of any attorney is to uncover the truth behind what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My job's not done until there are no more contradictions left!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ Very well. Sir Blue Knight, let us hear about this contradiction you have discovered.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The bottle was first opened by that guy, meaning Belduke didn't drink any of it... That means there's one piece of evidence that should be very difficult to explain!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I would like to hear about this contradiction, too. The defence shall present evidence. Where is the contradiction in this witness having been the one who opened the tomato juice bottle?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Hey, Bluey! Would you like some too? Some tomato juice...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Have a drink. It helps you think better when your mind's all mushy. *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Tomato juice! A marvellous drink! Helps you concentrate, helps you think!♪</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait, I thought the bard left already... I really wish he did...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Luke">The important part of his statement is that he opened the bottle... and that Mr Belduke didn't drink any of the tomato juice, isn't it, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You got it, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">To put it another way, he didn't consume any of the sleep medicine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And that makes one particular piece of evidence seem really strange...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The contradiction can be seen in one of the sketches of the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In one of the sketches?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please take a look at Sir Belduke's mouth. We can see a line of red liquid trickling down from his mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, well. We have already established that it was the tomato jui- Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly, Your Honour. Sir Belduke didn't drink any of the tomato juice that night...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">"Earlier"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If the victim had put up a fight... then there should have been traces of a struggle at the crime scene. And yet, no such traces were found. That's what made you assume the witch must have used Famalia.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Ngh...! Y-yes, that is so...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">As I explained before... Master Belduke didn't struggle at all at the time. But when I think about it now, in light of the new information, it was very unnatural...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The victim didn't drink the soporific, yet didn't struggle...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">But...what in the... What does this mean? If it's not tomato juice, nor blood brought about through a struggle with the murderer... then what else could it be?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Since it's not tomato juice, we have to assume it's blood, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Yeah, right? It's gotta be that!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">We have ruled out the possibility that the victim bit his tongue while struggling with the attacker.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Then there's got to be a different reason for that blood being there... He must have suffered internal bleeding that was somehow connected to his death... But what could have caused it?</thought> ...Your Honour. If I may ask one question...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A question? To whom?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I just clarify this one suspicion, I may be able to explain the blood shown in the sketch. That's why I need to question one person in particular...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I'd like to ask...Inquisitor Barnham...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What, me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhm... Do you have any idea who I should question?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Why are you asking me?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh...I knew he'd get mad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">If it's about the incident, then it would make sense to ask one of the witnesses, do you not think?!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">He may have yelled at you, but at least he answered your question, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yeah, Mr Wright. You know...maybe there's a human heart beating under all that armour, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A witness, huh... Who should I ask?</thought> Your Honour! Please let me ask just one more question!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hope that this time you will think about what to say before opening your mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well then, I have a question for Ms Greyerl!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the day of the crime... did anything go missing from the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Missing? Such as... the tomato juice that a certain person drank, do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yeah, something like that... But, was there anything else?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Hmm, I'm afraid I cannot say. You may remember that I didn't enter Master's study that day. Not even once. If I may be so bold as to make a suggestion, perhaps it would be wiser to ask someone who went into Master's study.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's right... I'll try again.</thought> Your Honour! Please let me ask just one more question!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hope that this time you will think about what to say before opening your mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mister, can I ask you something?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Y-yeah? Don't give me that scary look, Bluey! I...I know nothin'! Nothin' at all. I've got nothin' to tell!</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Emeer's as innocent as a little lamb. But is his confidence more than a sham?♪</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>He'd be better off without that bard.</thought> You drank the tomato juice that was at the crime scene, right?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">D-d-don't keep askin' me about that over and over again! S-so what if I did?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then...I have another question for you. Did anything else disappear from the crime scene that day?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">............ ............ ............ Nah...I didn't notice anythin'.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Wh-wh-wh-wh-why're you l-l-l-lookin' at me like that?! I dunno about anythin' goin' missin'! I'm innocent! Please believe me!</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪Truth could drown in his swimming eyes. Some tell lies well, others cannot tell lies♪</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like my gut feeling was right. He took something from the crime scene... Something that could be directly connected to that red liquid around Belduke's mouth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What on earth did that man steal from the crime scene?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A certain item disappeared from the crime scene that day... And, at this very moment...it's highly likely that item is right in front of our very eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What...? It's here?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't that right, mister?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Is...is it? I, uhm, I have no idea!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defender! I order you to show us what this item is. The item that this witness took from the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's too vague.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaaaat? <thought>Whoa, that was fast...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">This witness...is covered in jewels, in a manner that defies good taste. Surely he could conceal countless magic gems about his person.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Wait, what?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But...Inquisitor Barnham, this witness is of a rather masculine persuasion!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">For all we know, he may be a master of disguise. We have been calling him "mister" all this while... But he may actually be a "missus"!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">............ Uhm, Bluey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">If you've got somethin' to show the judge, please hurry up with it... I feel this trial is takin' a bad turn for me...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I don't come up with the right answer now, Barnham will personally slay that poor guy!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's this bottle!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The bottle?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Greyerl, I'd like you to clarify something for me.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">What would that be, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sir Belduke was working on creating certain medicines... He had various dangerous substances in his possession, as well. How were they stored?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Master kept them in a locked medicine cabinet. The bottles were labelled so that it was clear that they were dangerous. They have all been confiscated.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As for those labels... Did they resemble... the label on that guy's bottle?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...! Mister... What are you doing with a product of Master's research?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">It's not what you think! I didn't have any evil intentions, or nothin'!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That bottle belonged to Master. And it was used... to store strong poison. Poison strong enough to kill...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">P-poison...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Wh-what?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The red liquid trickling down Sir Belduke's mouth was definitely blood. Now, as for what caused him to bleed like that from his mouth... it was the deadly poison from the bottle this guy stole from the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">This is...outrageous!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whaaaaaaaaaaaat! Order! Order! Orderrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! D'ya expect me to just keep quiet?! It was poison?! Poison! Am I...gonna die?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Y-yeah, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">More importantly, I want to know why you have that bottle!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Huh? Uhm. Well, that's... Uhh. Remember how I told you I drank the alchemist's tomato juice?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. It's not something easy to forget... Especially having heard it several times.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Well...that was when I saw it on the floor. This bottle right here. It was totally empty. And I thought, y'know, it's such a fancy-lookin' bottle and all. I'm a bit of a skull-fancier. They have this air of danger about them, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They certainly do.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">So, since it was there, and I was there too, I felt we were kinda meant for each other. I thought, "This bottle's so classy I could die for it!"</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Had any poison been left in the bottle, you would have died instantly. But if it was empty, it was probably harmless.</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Ooooh! Hear that? I'm gonna live! Good thing I rinsed it well before use! *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But if the victim was killed by poison... that raises a new question, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Who could have poisoned him...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Considering all the evidence and the testimonies we've heard today, the answer is so close, I can taste it.</thought> Sir Belduke was poisoned by...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It could've been no one else but... Ms Greyerl!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, yeah, but...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Had she intended to poison Sir Belduke, surely she would have had no reason to use any sleep medicine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ That's...a good point. <thought>Easy, Phoenix. You sure didn't think that one through properly.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Keep pointing that finger at others without solid reasoning, defender... you may just get your fingers burnt!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arghhhhhhh! <thought>Coming from Barnham, I don't think that's a metaphor...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was...that guy!</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">What's got into you, Bluey?! Me, poisonin' someone? I nearly poisoned meself! If anythin'...I'm a victim too!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">Well...maybe not quite on the same level as the alchemist...but still. Anyway, how d'ya think someone like poor old me could've poisoned him?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Easy, Phoenix. You sure didn't think that one through properly.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Keep pointing that finger at others without solid reasoning, defender... you may just get your fingers burnt!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arghhhhhhh! <thought>Coming from Barnham, I don't think that's a metaphor...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was, of course, Sir Belduke himself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Sir...Belduke himself?!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sir Belduke took that poison of his own will. His death was suicide!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The most unnatural aspect?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Greyerl, when you were strangling Sir Belduke... he put up no fight whatsoever, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes, it is. Until today, I was convinced it was due to the sleep medicine...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It wasn't. Because he didn't take any. The truth is, when you gripped his throat, Sir Belduke... was already dead. He had poisoned himself!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Nghhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-but would the poison have caused him to bleed from his mouth?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I personally know of no poison that works instantly and causes such symptoms.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... Y-you don't? <thought>I can't just tell them that it happens on TV all the time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">There are certain plants in this area that contain a highly poisonous substance. In the course of his research, Master Belduke found a way to extract that poison.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What am I hearing?! Is there really such a dangerous plant in Labyrinthia?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">The poison is very bitter to taste, so it would be impossible to secretly slip it into someone's food or drink... And it would cause internal damage. It is a very powerful poison... Drinking it would induce a most painful death.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">And to think Sir Belduke could...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... did Sir Belduke really choose such an agonising death for himself? It doesn't seem like he suffered that much.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...I would like to know that too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Greyerl...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">You mean to say Master killed himself after exposing me as a witch? I...I cannot believe it! He...he just wouldn't commit suicide!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Indeed, we cannot take such a theory at face value! Had he committed suicide, I dare say he would have left a suicide note!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ I can't say why Sir Belduke committed suicide, but... I think there's a piece of evidence that can confirm his suicide was a possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">There...is a piece of evidence like that?!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you have such evidence, you ought to present it to the court immediately. Present the evidence indicating that Sir Belduke's death could have been suicide!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I have a single piece of advice for you, Sir Blue Knight. Should you choose to end your life out of shame from showing such pitifully inappropriate evidence... make sure you do not forget to write a will.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is to say... showing that evidence was somewhat ill-judged.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... That was a bad slip-up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">How can we know why Sir Belduke would take his own life?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Only Mr Belduke himself could know the reason why he did it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, yeah... <thought>If only he'd left some kind of message explaining why... Unless... Could he have left behind a suicide note after all?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's...Sir Belduke's letter. Let's see...it was addressed to the Storyteller, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the last letter written by Sir Belduke. Now, if his death was a suicide... then this letter may well be his suicide note!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Barnham:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. But there is one person who knows whether this letter was really a suicide note.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You mean...the person who swapped its contents... In other words... You...Jean Greyerl.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, you stole Sir Belduke's letter on the night of the crime. Tell us, what was written in it?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ I don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what? You don't know?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I did steal the letter, yes. But...I don't know what its contents were.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You mean you have not read it...?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I couldn't bring myself to read it. It seemed that if I did... everything that had happened since Master Belduke saved my life would be ruined in an instant. I've taken it out and held it in my hands many times... But no matter what, I just couldn't...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Miss Greyerl...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you tell us where that letter is now?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ I have it here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... You're...carrying it around with you?! If you were searched, you would've been done for!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That night...having killed Master Belduke, I decided to stay in his residence. I knew my identity would be revealed sooner or later, and I was ready for it.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">...!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">So, until that time... I decided to always keep the letter with me. ...Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">If you don't mind, could you please read it aloud?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Now that I'm here, in this place of judgement... I think I'm finally ready to hear what Master wrote.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...Me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sir Belduke wrote this letter to the Storyteller as he was preparing to die. I think it's only right his last words should be read by you.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ Yes, you're right...I see. I understand. Please allow me to read the letter aloud.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A daughter...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Hmm? I was not aware that Sir Belduke had a daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mr Belduke seemed to know a lot about this town... This town's "secret"... And the "truth" about the witch...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Truth about the witch... Somehow I don't think he was talking about Ms Greyerl.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ The second matter weighing heavily on my mind... is that Jean will be left on her own. Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Master... Master Belduke...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...This...this letter...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Master Belduke cared about you... until the very end.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...Yes... ...How could I have forgotten...? I'm sure...I knew it all along... So why did I... How could I have done that to him?* <thought>Voice-over only</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Miss Greyerl...</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">I think it is about time. ...For the guilty verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">G-guilty...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The inquisition withdraws the charges against Maya Fey... and charges Jean Greyerl with being a witch.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">All the evidence corroborates this accusation, and she even admits her guilt. Hence, the inquisition asks that the witch be found guilty and punished immediately.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What do you want now, Sir Blue Knight?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Admittedly, Ms Greyerl did attempt to strangle Sir Belduke... but he had consumed a deadly poison and was already dead at the time! Therefore, she is not guilty of murder!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And one more thing! It also wasn't Ms Greyerl who turned Professor Layton into gold. There was another witch present at the crime scene. The defendant, Maya, saw her too! To put it simply... Ms Greyerl didn't kill anyone!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, she didn't kill anyone! And yet... you still want to burn her?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you even know how it feels to be put in this cage? It's like everyone's against you and it's super frightening! I'm not a witch... but I've been thrown into this cage and almost sentenced for something I didn't do! And now you're about to do the same to another person?! That's just not right!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ Is that all you have to say?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The one who's in the wrong is not me, but you, Sir Blue Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Whether the witch committed a crime or not is completely irrelevant. This is the Witches' Court. All witches must be punished by fire!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But...that's crazy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why...why, Barnham?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Inquisitor Barnham is absolutely right. Being a witch is a crime. You understand that, don't you, Miss Greyerl?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well then. The court is ready to issue the final verdict. Maya Fey is found innocent! And in her place...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nooooo, you caaaaaan't!</line>
<line speaker="???">Espella:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What is it now, Espella Cantabella?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There is nothing else we can do. This is the course of things, and you should know it well.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Indeed. "All witches shall be cast into the flames." That is the law of this town... A law that was written by your very own father. And furthermore, a law that has always been obeyed in the town of Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">A town like this...should never exist in the first place!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Trials in which innocent people are sentenced to death by fire... I shall make sure this is the last one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Since you're all so keen on the rules created by the Storyteller, you should know exactly what I mean. The stipulation for ending the witch trials: "Once the Great Witch Bezella is burned, the witch trials will end." At present... I am under suspicion. You know very well why that is, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You...you don't mean that you're...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I am guilty. I am the Great Witch Bezella!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Now, cast me into the flames! And let Miss Greyerl free!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...! Miss Cantabella...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">This shall be the last of the witch trials! No one else need be burned hereafter!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella, just what are you saying?! I can't let you do that!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Please, Mr Wright! Let me do as I wish. I'm sorry, but this is a problem concerning the people of Labyrinthia!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No, please don't do it!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There must be another way! You don't need to do this!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's all right. Luke, Maya... Mr Wright...and Mr Layton. I truly appreciate all you have done for me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This can't be happening!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Miss Cantabella... Your confession will have very serious... or rather, fatal consequences for you. May we assume that you fully understand those consequences and are willing to accept them?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ I am Espella Cantabella, the Storyteller's daughter. But I also have another name... I am the Great Witch Bezella. I have lived hidden in the dark pages of my father's Story, deceiving all of you. Many lives have been sacrificed because of me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court attendants! Seize that woman! She is the Great Witch Bezella!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Espella, this just isn't right! Let's go! Nick, gimme a hand! Jump! Jump over there!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">B-but...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hurry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Help me, Niiiiiick!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Espella! Quick...in here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Stop! You've got to stop! Mayaaaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think not, defender.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If anything here is strange, I'd say it was you, defender.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Indeed, Milord. A baker turned defender, clad in such an outlandish outfit...is the very epitome of "strange"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uwaaaaaaahhh! Th-the defence abstains from commenting on the inquisition's fashion sense, Your Honour...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm...? I don't see anything odd...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a...um...contradiction... somewhere in there...I think...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">From the look on your face, I can see you are not convinced. Hearing such a weak objection has put me in foul spirits... I think a penalty is in order.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come on, is that really enough reason to punish me...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's rather hopeless. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's...hopeless?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes. Entirely so. In fact, it's so hopeless it doesn't merit talking about it. And here is the punishment for your hopeless performance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Saying everything I do is "hopeless" feels like sufficient punishment, to be honest...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">May I have your attention, Mr Emeer?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">*gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* C'mon, let me finish me drink first, Bluey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you...done yet?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">*gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp* *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Haven't you had enough?</line>
<line speaker="Emeer">*glug* *glug* *glug* *glug* *glug* *glug* *glug* *glug*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, I get the hint... Forget I asked.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In that case, let us continue with the interrogation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">May I ask you a question, Ms Primstone?</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Dearie, dearie me! Oh dearie, dearie me! My dear, do not frighten me so! I feel like a schoolgirl caught napping during class...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you have something to say about the testimony we've just been hearing?</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Ms Primstone's lesson number one! "Asking questions leads to nothing but trouble!" As soon as people learned to speak, they began to get themselves into trouble with silly questions! This will be on the exam!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I feel sorry for her pupils, having to learn about her gloomy outlook on the world.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Quite frankly, I feel more sorry for US, Espella...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Carry on with the interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr Birdly, can I ask you something?</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">♪So many questions for Birdly the bard! But most of them I shall disregard!♪</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh... The statement you heard earlier... Was there anything you'd like to comment on?</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">Hmm, I wonder if there was. My peerless companion, what do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Cracker">Hang on! Hang on! Hang on! Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, Mr Wright! He's imitating you perfectly! How adorable...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't say I share your love for the bird, Espella. It feels like it's mocking me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Carry on with the interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Luke, I have a question.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Shh! Please don't disturb me right now, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm busy...thinking about whether there's something suspicious in the other witnesses' testimonies!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So, that means...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">You haven't noticed anything yet...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh well... Guess I'd better leave him to his thinking.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Carry on with the interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd like to ask Sir Belduke's butler a question...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">What is it, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did anything in the statement you've just heard catch your attentio-</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">No, there was nothing in particular.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I have nothing to say about it, Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Cutting straight to the point without even letting me finish...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Unlike you, Mr Wright, Sir Belduke's butler is always ready to go.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Um... I'm sure you didn't mean it like that, Espella... At least I hope you didn't...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Carry on with the interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you mind if I ask you something, Ms Mailer?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Siiiiiiiirrr!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">So? You wanted something? What was it? What did you want to ask about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks to that brain-piercing scream... I can't remember what it was now.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">There are witnesses whom you should not bother without reason. Keep that in mind, Sir Blue Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please don't badger that witness unless you absolutely need to...or we will all go deaf.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd say it was her screech that was badgering our ears, Your Honour...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Carry on with the cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There is no need for this trial to go any further. It has been proven beyond all doubt what the accused truly is. The court is ready to issue its verdict regarding Maya Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Being a witch is a crime in itself. Such evil beings must be purged from this world. Now, you despicable witch! Prepare to meet your fate in the flames!</line>
</xml>