<xml>
<title>The First Turnabout</title>

<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Boy am I nervous!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, h-hiya, Chief.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Whew, I'm glad I made it on time. Well, I have to say Phoenix, I'm impressed! Not everyone takes on a murder trial right off the bat like this. It says a lot about you... and your client as well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... thanks. Actually, it's because I owe him a favor.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">A favor? You mean, you knew the defendant before this case?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. Actually, I kind of owe my current job to him. He's one of the reasons I became an attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, that's news to me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I want to help him out any way I can! I just... really want to help him, I owe him that much.</line>
<line speaker="???"><thought>It's over! My life, everything, it's all over!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">... Isn't that your client screaming over there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... that's him.</line>
<line speaker="???"><thought>Death! Despair! Ohhhh! I'm gonna do it, I'm gonna die!!!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">It sounds like he wants to die...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, yeah. *sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Nick!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey. Hey there, Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Dude, I'm so guilty!! Tell them I'm guilty!!! Gimme the death sentence! I ain't afraid to die!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!? What's wrong, Larry?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh, it's all over... I... I'm finished. Finished! I can't live in a world without her! I can't! Who... who took her away from me, Nick? Who did this!? Aww, Nick, ya gotta tell me! Who took my baby away!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... The person responsible for your girlfriend's death? The newspapers say it was you...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My name is Phoenix Wright. Here's the story: My first case is a fairly simple one. A young woman was killed in her apartment. The guy they arrested was the unlucky sap dating her: Larry Butz... my best friend since grade school. Our school had a saying: "When something smells, it's usually the Butz." In the 23 years I've known him, it's usually been true. He has a knack for getting himself in trouble. One thing I can say though: it's usually not his fault. He just has terrible luck. But I know better than anyone, that he's a good guy at heart. That and I owe him one. Which is why I took the case... to clear his name. And that's just what I'm going to do!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court is now in session for the trial of Mr. Larry Butz.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The prosecution is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The, um, defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem. Mr. Wright? This is your first trial, is it not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor. I'm, um, a little nervous.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your conduct during this trial will decide the fate of your client. Murder is a serious charge. For your client's sake, I hope you can control your nerves.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank... thank you, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Mr. Wright, given the circumstances... I think we should have a test to ascertain your readiness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Your Honor. <thought>Gulp... Hands shaking... Eyesight... fading...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This test will consist of a few simple questions. Answer them clearly and concisely. Please state the name of the defendant in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... the defendant... is me, right?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wright! Have you completely lost your mind? Focus! The defendant is the person on trial! You're his lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, er, eh? Oh yeah, right! Eh heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">This is no laughing matter! You did pass the bar, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Sorry, I couldn't hear your answer. I'll ask once more:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The, um, defendant? That's... er... Mia Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wrong, Wright. Look, I have to leave. I have to go home. I'm... I'm expecting a delivery.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aw, c'mon Chief. There's no need to be going so soon, is there?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wright! Listen: the defendant is the one on trial--your client! I mean, that's about as basic as you can get!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've put my foot in it this time! I've got to relax!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Sorry, I couldn't hear your answer. I'll ask once more:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defendant? Well, that's Larry Butz, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Correct. Just keep your wits about you and you'll do fine. Next question: This is a murder trial. Tell me, what's the victim's name?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whew, I know this one! Glad I read the case report cover to cover so many times. It's... wait... Uh-oh! No... no way! I forgot! I'm drawing a total blank here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix! Are you absolutely SURE you're up to this? You don't even know the victim's name!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, the victim! O-Of course I know the victim's name! I, um, just forgot. ... Temporarily.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I think I feel a migraine coming on. Look, the victim's name is listed in the Court Record. Just touch the Court Record button to check it at anytime, okay? Remember to check it often. Do it for me, please. I'm begging you.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Who is the victim in this case?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Mia Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">W-W-What!? How can I be the victim!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh! Right! Sorry! I, er, it was the first name that popped into my head, and--</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The Court Record button! Remember to use it when you are in a pinch.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let me ask that one again:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, um, wasn't it Ms. Block? Ms. Cinder Block?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The person in question was a victim of murder, not ill-conceived naming, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wright? If you forget something, just touch the Court Record button to help you remember. A mistake in court could cost you the case.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I ask you again:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... the victim's name is Cindy Stone.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Correct. Now, tell me, what was the cause of death? She died because she was...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right! Wasn't she, um, poisoned by er... poison?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're asking me!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Chief! Help me out!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Check the court record. The Court Record button... remember?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Geez. Give a guy a break!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let me ask again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right... she was strangled, wasn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Please tell me that was you talking to yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you wish to hang yourself, Mr. Wright, you're welcome to, but not inside my courtroom. I suppose there's nothing to do but give you another try:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She was struck once, by a blunt object.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Correct. You've answered all my questions. I see no reason why we shouldn't proceed. You seem much more relaxed, Mr. Wright. Good for you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Your Honor. <thought>Because I don't FEEL relaxed, that's for sure.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, then... First, a question for the prosecution. Mr. Payne?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As Mr. Wright just told us, the victim was struck with a blunt object. Would you explain to the court just what that "object" was?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The murder weapon was this statue of "The Thinker." It was found lying on the floor, next to the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... the court accepts it into evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wright... Be sure to pay attention to any evidence added during the trial. That evidence is the only ammunition you have in court. Touch the Court Record button to check the Court Record frequently.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Payne, the prosecution may call its first witness.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The prosecution calls the defendant, Mr. Butz, to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Chief, what do I do now?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Pay attention. You don't want to miss any information that might help your client's case. You'll get your chance to respond to the prosecution later, so be ready! Let's just hope he doesn't say anything... unfortunate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh, Larry gets excited easily... this could be bad.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ahem. Mr. Butz. Is it not true that the victim had recently dumped you?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey, watch it buddy! We were great together! We were Romeo and Juliet, Cleopatra and Mark Anthony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Um... didn't they all die?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">I wasn't dumped! She just wasn't taking my phone calls. Or seeing me... Ever. WHAT'S IT TO YOU, ANYWAY!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Mr. Butz, what you describe is generally what we mean by "dumped." In fact, she had completely abandoned you... and was seeing other men! She had just returned from overseas with one of them the day before the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Whaddya mean, "one of them"!? Lies! All of it, lies! I don't believe a word of it!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Honor, the victim's passport. According to this, she was in Paris until the day before she died.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Indeed, she appears to have returned the day before the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Dude... no way...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The victim was a model, but did not have a large income. It appears that she had several "Sugar Daddies."</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Daddies? Sugar?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes. Older men, who gave her money and gifts. She took their money and used it to support her lifestyle.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Duuude!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">We can clearly see what kind of woman this Ms. Stone was. Tell me, Mr. Butz, what do you think of her now?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wright... I don't think you want him to answer that question.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah... Larry has a way of running his mouth in all the wrong directions. Should I...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Might be better not to get involved in this one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Well, Mr. Butz?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Dude, no way! That cheatin' she-dog!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My client had no idea the victim was seeing other men! That question is irrelevant to this case!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Oof! *wince*</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Dude! Nick! Whaddya mean, "irrelevant"!? That cheatin' she-dog!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I'm gonna die. I'm just gonna drop dead! Yeah, and when I meet her in the afterlife... I'm going to get to the bottom of this!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's continue with the trial, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I believe the accused's motive is clear to everyone.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, quite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh boy. This is so not looking good.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Next question! You went to the victim's apartment on the day of the murder, did you not?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Gulp!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Well, did you, or did you not?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Heh? Heh heh. Well, maybe I did, and maybe I didn't!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh. He went. What do I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I know! I'll send him a signal...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Er... Yeah! Yeah! I was there! I went!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Well, Mr. Butz?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Dude, chill! She wasn't home, man... So, like, I didn't see her.</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Honor, the defendant is lying.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Lying?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The prosecution would like to call a witness who can prove Mr. Butz is lying.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll send him a signal...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Um, well, see, it's like this: I don't remember.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">You "don't remember"? Well then, we'll just have to remind you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I got a bad feeling about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">We have a witness that can prove he DID go to the victim's apartment that day!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, that simplifies matters. Who is your witness?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The man who found the victim's body. Just before making the gruesome discovery... He saw the defendant fleeing the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court! Mr. Payne, the prosecution may call its witness.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is bad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">On the day of the murder, my witness was selling newspapers at the victim's building. Please bring Mr. Frank Sahwit to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Mr. Sahwit, you sell newspaper subscriptions, is this correct?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Oh, oh yes! Newspapers, yes!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Sahwit, you may proceed with your testimony. Please tell the court what you saw on the day of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I was going door-to-door, selling subscriptions when I saw a man fleeing an apartment.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Larry! Why didn't you tell the truth? I can't defend you against a testimony like that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Incidentally, why wasn't the phone in the victim's apartment working?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Honor, at the time of the murder, there was a blackout in the building.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aren't phones supposed to work during a blackout?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes, Your Honor... However, some cordless phones do not function normally. The phone that Mr. Sahwit used was one of those. Your Honor... I have a record of the blackout, for your perusal.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes! Er... yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You may begin your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">C-Cross-examination, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Alright, Wright, this is it. The real deal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... what exactly am I supposed to do?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Why, you expose the lies in the testimony the witness just gave!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lies! What?! He was lying!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your client is innocent, right? Then that witness must have lied in his testimony! Or is your client really... guilty?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">!!! How do I prove he's not?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You hold the key! It's in the evidence! Compare the witness's testimony to the evidence at hand. There's bound to be a contradiction in there! First, find contradictions between the Court Record and the witness's testimony. Then, once you've found the contradicting evidence... present it and rub it in the witness's face!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... okay.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Touch the Court Record button and point out contradictions in the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I was going door-to-door, selling subscriptions when I saw a man fleeing an apartment.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't a man leaving an apartment a common sight? I find it odd you would take notice of him...</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Er... heh. I don't know. He just seemed strange to me, that's all. Like he was mad, and yet frightened at the same time. Just like... a criminal fleeing the scene of a crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense requests that the witness refrain from conjecture!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Of course. What the witness means is that the man he saw looked suspicious. So, what happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I thought he must be in a hurry because he left the door half-open behind him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Half-open... you say?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yes, yes, the door was open halfway. Yes. I watched for a moment, but no one came to close the door. "That's odd, in a big city like this," I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I see. And what happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Thinking it strange, I looked inside the apartment.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What gave you the idea to do that?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Well, the door was half-open, you see. Isn't it only human to want to... peek? We climb mountains because they are there! It's the same thing.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Truer words have never been spoken! Anyone would look inside!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... why did Payne cut him off so quickly?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">So you looked into the apartment. What happened then?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Then I saw her lying there... A woman... not moving... dead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure she was dead?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">W-Well, no, I guess I wasn't. But, she wasn't moving at all, and there was blood everywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess that would look fatal to anyone...</thought> Very well, what happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I quailed in fright and found myself unable to go inside.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you didn't touch ANYTHING in the apartment?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Um, yes. I mean no! Nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay. What happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I thought to call the police immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You "thought" to call the police? Does that mean you didn't actually call them!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Please, please... Listen to the rest of the testimony. You thought to call the police... What happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">However, the phone in her apartment wasn't working.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The phone in her apartment wasn't working?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yes. I mean, no, no it wasn't. Right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you said you didn't go into the apartment... or did you!?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Oh, oh, that? I can explain that! There was a cordless phone on a shelf in the entranceway. I reached inside and tried using that to call...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">And the phone wasn't working, correct? What happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I went to a nearby park and found a public phone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why use a public phone?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Well, you see, I don't have a cell phone. And, being the middle of the afternoon, there was no answer at the nearby apartments.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, right... what time did you call again?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I remember the time exactly: It was 1:00 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">1:00 PM! Are you certain?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yes. Absolutely.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... He seems really confident.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">1:00 PM? Wright. Doesn't that seem strange to you? Present some evidence to contradict him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">The man who ran was, without a doubt, the defendant sitting right over there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you absolutely, 100% positive?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yes, it was him. No mistake about it.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The witness says he's certain!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's all of it. There must be a contradiction in there somewhere. Examine the Court Record button if something strikes you as being suspicious. Then, find the evidence that contradicts his testimony, and present it to him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You found the body at 1:00 PM. You're sure?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yes. It was 1:00 PM, for certain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Frankly, I find that hard to believe! Your statement directly contradicts the autopsy report. The autopsy notes the time of death at sometime after 4PM. There was nobody to... er... no "body" to find at 1:00 PM! How do you explain this three-hour gap?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">!!! Oh, that! Oh, er...</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">This is trivial! The witness merely forgot the time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">After his testimony, I find that hard to believe. Mr. Sahwit... Why were you so certain that you found the body at 1:00 PM?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I.. er... well, I... Gee, that's a really good question!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Great job, Wright! Way to put him on the spot! That's all you have to do: point out contradictions! Lies always beget more lies! See through one, and their whole story falls apart!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Wait! I remember now!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Would you care to give your testimony again?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">You see, when I found the body, I heard the time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see. You heard a voice saying the time on a taped program. Mr. Wright, you may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wright! You know what to do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've got this one.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">You see, when I found the body, I heard the time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You said "heard"... Not "saw"?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yes, heard. All I saw was the body lying there... I didn't think to look at anything else, least of all my watch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Isn't that a little strange? So you're saying you "heard" something. But if you were so shocked by the body, you wouldn't hear anything at all!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">The witness did say he actually heard the time. It's ludicrous to suggest he "wouldn't hear anything"!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I have to agree with the prosecution. Witness, continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">There was a voice saying the time... It was probably coming from the television.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure it was a television and not... a radio?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Well, no, I guess it might have been a radio.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Incidentally, there was no radio on the premises. There was only one large television.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wright! I can't put my finger on it, but something about this seems fishy. Something about "hearing" the television...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The witness has testified. He heard the time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Oh, but it was three hours off, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How do you explain the gap!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, witness? Can you explain this?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I guess the victim must have been watching a video of a taped program!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A.. video?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yes, that would explain why the time was wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">True, true...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wright! I think the problem lies someplace else...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We're agreed that you heard the time at the scene, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">That's why I thought it was 1:00 PM!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure the voice you heard said it was 1:00 PM?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yes, I can practically hear it now. It was quite clear.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Payne, has the prosecution verified this testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">My apologies, Your Honor. I, too, have only just learned that the witness "heard" the time.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Oh, I'm really sorry. I only remembered it just now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Terribly sorry about the misunderstanding...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, you just watch it! <thought>Hmm... Not much point pressing him on that one, was there?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Notice anything suspicious?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hold it right there! The prosecution has said there was a blackout at the time of the discovery! And this record proves it!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You couldn't have heard a television... or a video!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Gah!!! I... well... urk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense has a point. Do you have an explanation for this, Mr. Sahwit?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">No, I... I find it quite puzzling myself! Quite! ... Aah! W-wait! I remember now!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Sahwit? The court would prefer to hear an accurate testimony from the very beginning. These constant corrections are harming your credibility. That, and you seem rather... distraught.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">...! M-my apologies, Your Honor! It... er, it must have been the shock of finding the body!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Sahwit. Let's hear your testimony once more please.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Actually, I didn't "hear" the time... I "saw" it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You saw a clock? I guess that would explain it. The defense may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gladly.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Actually, I didn't "hear" the time... I "saw" it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That strikes me as a very suspicious mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yes, I can see how you'd be a little doubtful... I'm really sorry. I only just remembered that table clock!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A "table clock"?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">There was a table clock in the apartment, wasn't there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A "table clock"? Was there a clock at the scene?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is the first I've heard of it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yeah, the murder weapon! The killer used it to hit the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The... murder weapon?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Yes, the table clock that was used as a weapon! That's what I just said. Did you doze off in the middle of my testimony or something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something's fishy here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">That must have been what I saw.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why didn't you tell us that in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I guess it just slipped my mind! I'm not really sure how it happened myself...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The witness says he saw the table clock. End of story.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Now, find the contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait just a moment! The murder weapon wasn't a clock. It was this statue! Now how is this supposed to be a clock?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Whaa!? Y-you with your "objections," and your "evidence"... Just who do you think you are!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just answer the question, Mr. Sahwit.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Hey, I... I saw it there, okay! That's a clock!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Honor! If I may...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Mr. Payne?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">As the witness stated, this statue is indeed a clock. The neck is a switch. You just tilt it, and it says the time out loud. As it doesn't look like a clock, I submitted it as a statue. My apologies.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. So the murder weapon was a table clock after all. Well, Mr. Wright? It appears that the witness's testimony was correct. This is a clock. Do you have any problems with his testimony now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess not. There was a clock on the scene, so, no problem.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wright! Are you out of your mind!? That clock doesn't look like a clock at all! The witness couldn't have possibly known it was a clock just by seeing it! He said himself, he never entered the apartment! It was in his testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is something the matter? Does the defense have anything to add?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... Yes I do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor, there is a gaping hole in the witness's testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The only way he could have known the weapon was a clock is to hold it in his hand. Yet the witness testified that he never entered the apartment! Clearly, a contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... indeed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness knew it was a clock, because he...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me, isn't it true that you knew the victim? In fact, you were one of her "sugar daddies"! Be frank with us, Mr. Sahwit!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Hmph. "Frank"? I'm always "Frank"!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Honor. We have complete records of the victim's relationships. Mr. Frank Sahwit does not appear anywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Oh, really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please, Mr. Wright... Is "Huh" the best response you can muster up? Try to refrain from making off-the-cuff accusations in the future.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, Your Honor. Let me think this over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're lying! You were inside the apartment on the day of the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Oh yeah? Prove it! Prove I went in there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll do better than that! I can prove you were the one who killed her! You struck her with the clock, and the shock of the blow triggered the clock's voice! That was the sound you heard!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order in the court! Intriguing. Please continue, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. Mr. Sahwit. The sound must have left quite an impression on you. Understandable, since the murder weapon spoke just as you hit the victim! That voice was burned into your mind. That's why you were so certain about the time!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">W-w-what's the meaning of this? This is all baseless conjecture!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Baseless...? Just look at the witness's face!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Ngh... grrrah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Would the witness care to elaborate? Did you strike the victim with the clock?</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I... I...! That... that day... I... I never! Look... I... the clock... I heard, no! I mean, I saw...Saw... nggg! Gwaaaaaaaaaaaaah! Shutupshutupshutup! I hate you! I-it was him, I tell you! I saw him! H-he killed her and he should burn! Burn! Give him death!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court I say!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Honor, a-a moment please! There isn't a shred of evidence supporting the defense's claims!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You claim the sound the witness heard came from the clock... Do you have any evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The whole case is riding on this! I'd better think it through carefully!</thought> Yes, Your Honor. The sound Mr. Sahwit heard was definitely this clock. A fact which is clear if you simply...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All you have to do is examine the batteries!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed? The batteries are... in the right way. The clock seems to be working fine. What exactly did you mean, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, the clock was working fine!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes, and...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Umm, I'm sorry, I think I got confused back there with all those testimonies.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! I expect more from a lawyer in this court. Even if it is your first day. I'm afraid I have to penalize you! Try to think things through more carefully.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, Your Honor. As I was saying...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All you have to do is talk to the victim's neighbors!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Talk to the neighbors...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure one of them heard the clock tell the time when the incident occurred!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... Does the prosecution have anything to say, Mr. Payne?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">We have already made all the necessary inquiries. Everyone living near the victim's apartment was out at the time of the murder. Furthermore, even if a neighbor had heard the clock, that would not prove that Mr. Sahwit had heard anything.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That is true. I believe you may be wrong, Mr. Wright. You'll receive a penalty for that, unfortunately.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm sorry, Your Honor! Let me think about it again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's sound the clock now, here in this court. Your Honor, may I have the clock? I ask the court to listen very carefully...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That certainly is a strange way to announce the time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, he is "The Thinker," after all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, we've heard the clock. What are your conclusions, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Payne... can you tell me what time it is now?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">It's 11:25... Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As you can see, this clock is exactly three hours slow! Precisely the discrepancy between what Mr. Sahwit heard and the actual time of death! So, Mr. Sahwit... Try to talk your way out of this one!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">... ...Hah! Hah hah! You forgot one thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh... what's he talking about...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">While it may seem like that clock IS running three hours slow... It proves nothing! How do you know it was running three days slow on the day of the murder!? If you can't prove that, you don't have a case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>He's right! How am I going to prove that!? Dammit! I was so close!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright? It seems you lack the critical evidence to support your claim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This means I cannot let you indict the witness. Unfortunately... This ends the cross-examination of Mr. Frank Sahwit.</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">I come all the way down here to testify, and look what happens! You treat me like a criminal! A criminal! You lawyers are all slime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grr! I almost had him! Sorry, Larry... I failed you. There's nothing I can do about it now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Not so fast, Mr. Sahwit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia! I mean, Chief!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Listen up, Wright! Don't throw this one away, not like this! Think!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, Chief, it's over. I can't prove the clock was slow the day of the murder! Nobody can prove that!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Um... well, yes. But that doesn't mean you can't still win! Try thinking out of the box! Don't waste time doubting the facts. Assume the clock was three hours slow and... Think through it! Ask yourself, "Why was the clock three hours slow"? Figure out the reason, and you'll have your proof! Right, Wright? Can you think of a reason as to why the clock would be three hours slow?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Wait! Maybe I can prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You must have evidence somewhere that can prove it, Wright! Find it and let them have it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright? You say the clock was already running slow on the day of the murder... Have you found evidence to support this claim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course. There is a piece of evidence in the Court Record that can prove my claim beyond a doubt!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Hah! Tough words! Let's see you pull this one off!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-how am I supposed to know that!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I know you can figure it out! There must be some evidence in the Court Record... Something that can show why that clock was three hours slow! Find it, and he won't have a foot to stand on!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-y-yes, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You say the clock was already running slow on the day of the murder... Do you have evidence to prove this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is it... all or nothing!</thought> Yes, Your Honor. I believe I have the evidence that can prove my claim!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Hah hah! I'd like to see THAT!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's see this evidence that proves why the clock was running slow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Um, excuse me. This proves your claim... how? I can't see what that evidence has to do with the clock.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>D'oh! That wasn't it!</thought> One more chance... Give me just one more chance!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Alright, Mr. Wright, but time is not on your side. Be quick about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim had just returned home from abroad the day before the murder. As we all know, the time difference between here and Paris is nine hours! When it's 4:00 PM here, it's 1:00 AM the next day there. The clock wasn't three hours slow, it was nine hours fast! The victim hadn't reset her clock since returning home! That's why the time you heard when you struck her dead in her apartment was wrong! Proof enough for you, Mr. Sahwit? Or should I say... Mr. Did It!</line>
<line speaker="Sahwit">Ngh! ...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-order! Order, I say!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... This case has certainly turned out differently than we all expected. Mr. Payne... your witness?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">He... er... he was arrested and has been taken away, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I have to say, I'm impressed. I don't think I've ever seen someone complete a defense so quickly... and find the true culprit at the same time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">At this point, this is only a formality, but... This court finds the defendant, Mr. Larry Butz...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And with that... The court is adjourned.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It turns out that Frank Sahwit was a common burglar! He posed as a newspaper sales-man to check and see when people were out of the house! That day... When Larry went to her apartment, the victim wasn't home. After he left, Mr. Sahwit let himself in to do his dirty work! While he was searching her place, the victim returned! Flustered, Mr. Sahwit grabbed the nearest blunt object he could find...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whew... I still can't believe we won!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wright! Good job in there! Congratulations!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-thanks, Chief. I owe it all to you.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Not at all, not at all! You fought your own battles in there. It's been a while since I've seen a trial end on such a satisfying note!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've never seen the chief looking this happy... If she's this glad, imagine how Larry must feel!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">My life is over...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry! You're supposed to be happy! What's wrong now!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Aww, Nick... Don't worry 'bout me! I'll be dead and gone soon!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good! Wait, no! I mean... Bad! Bad bad bad! Larry, you're innocent! The case is closed.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... But... but my Cindy-windy's gone, man! Gone forever!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Larry, she was a... Nah... Never mind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Congratulations, Harry!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">H-Harry...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes, you! I can practically see the headlines now: "Harry Butz, Innocent!"</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Heh... um... thanks! I really owe you one. I won't forget this, ever! Let's celebrate! Dinner? Movie? My treat!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oh, no, I couldn't.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey, I was the one who got you off the hook!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh, hey! H-here, take this! It's a present!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">A present? For me? Wait... Wasn't this the evidence that...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Actually, I made this clock for her! I made one for her and one for me.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">R-really? You? You made this? ... Well, thank you. I'll keep it as a memento.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yo, Nick... Can you believe it? I was so into that chick... And... and she was just playing me for a fool! Don't that make you wanna just cry? *sob*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... Are you so sure?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Ex-squeeze me?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I think she thought quite a lot of you, in her own way.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Nah, you don't gotta sympathize with me, 'sokay.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oh, I'm not just sympathizing, really. Isn't that right, Wright? Don't you have something to show your friend? Something that proves how she felt about him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-huh? Oh, yeah, right! <thought>What the heck is she talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Check this out, Larry. Proof Positive you weren't just some chump to her.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh...? What about that clock?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the clock YOU made for her, Larry! And she took it with her when she traveled.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Whatever. She probably just needed a clock, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You think so? It's a pretty heavy clock to take traveling.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, make of it what you will.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... Hey, Nick. I'm glad I asked you to be my lawyer. Really, I am. Thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hope that made him feel a little better...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here you go, Larry. Proof.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... Eh... heh heh? It's okay, Nick. Don't worry about me. I'll forget about her soon enough. Look, I'm gonna head home. Thanks a ton, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess that wasn't the right thing to show him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wright? I hope you see the importance of evidence now. Also, hopefully you realize, things change depending on how you look at them. People, too. We never really know if our clients are guilty or innocent. All we can do is believe in them. And in order to believe in them, you have to believe in yourself. Wright... Listen. Learn. Grow strong. Never let go of what you believe in. Never.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, I think our work here is done! Shall we be off?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I guess so!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Say, how about dinner. On me? We'll drink a toast to innocent Butz!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oh, speaking of Harry... You were saying part of why you became a lawyer was because of him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Er, yeah. Part, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You'll have to tell me more about it sometime! Maybe... over drinks?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And so, my first trial came to a close. Larry slapped me on the back and said, "Gee, Nick, it's good to have friends!" But I'm pretty sure he's not going to pay us. Unless you count the clock he gave Mia. ... I didn't know it then... but that clock was soon going to be at the center of another incident. And my promise to tell the chief about me and Larry... would be one promise that I wouldn't be able to keep.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't sound very convinced, Mr. Wright. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This evidence clearly reveals the contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are that evidence and the statement just now related...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They aren't, are they...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Wright, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness's statement is clearly faulty, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry, but I can see nothing faulty. Unfortunately, I will have to penalize you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh. I must be on the wrong track?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! This court see no reason to further prolong the trial. The defense has failed to give the court sufficient reason to doubt the prosecution's claim. This court find the defendant, Mr. Larry Butz...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accused will surrender to the court immediately, to be held pending trial at a higher court within a month from today's date. That is all. This court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>