<xml>
<title>The Inherited Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Ray">This program sure brings back memories. Gregory... Tomorrow, I'm heading towards that fateful place with your son. To find out the truth of 18 years ago...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This badge's design is said to reflect the relentlessness and discipline of law enforcement. It comes from the authority vested in us as strict protectors of the law... ...and executors of sentences, much like harsh winter frosts and blazing summer days. To wear it is to identify oneself as a prosecutor, but I have no interest in doing so.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Each Prosecutor's Badge is engraved with the number of its owner on the back. Hmph. Numbers. As if we're not human on the inside like everyone else!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Shields, isn't it about time you told me what this is all about? Why did you bring me to this museum with you?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">You're not busy now, are you Miles? I thought it would be nice if we could share the romance of the constellations together.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I beg your pardon, but I would like to leave.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Sorry, sorry. It was just a joke. Do you know about the final case your father worked on? The "IS-7 Incident"?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... Manfred von Karma showed it to me immediately after I became a prosecutor. I reviewed the case file again last night, after you invited me here. And... while I don't remember it very well, I also had been in attendance at the trial back then. <thought>When I was young... I loved watching my father do battle in the courtroom. During that trial, it was my father, the defense attorney Gregory Edgeworth against... ...my former mentor, Prosecutor Manfred von Karma. And while the trial ended with the defendant being declared guilty...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">I see... So you were there too, at Gregory's final trial. In that case, I'll cut to the chase and tell you what you want to know. The truth about the "IS-7 Incident". It happened 18 years ago, during the winter... All the buildings were covered in snow, coating the entire town like a layer of frosting. And it was in this very place, that the incident occurred. This was all before Uncle Ray became a defense attorney...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">The defense attorney's badge is shaped like a sunflower. Does the shape have any special meaning?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Well. A sunflower always points towards the sun, right? From there, it's said to represent "freedom" and "justice".</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Then, I'll also aim towards becoming a defense attorney, just like a sunflower!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">He he... I look forward to it.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">The number engraved on the back, is it like the badge's ID number?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Yes. However, the number itself has no special meaning.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I'd like to see a badge with matching numbers.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>That... would be a rare sight indeed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Mr. Edgeworth. This request sure was sudden, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Indeed. We were contacted immediately after the client was arrested.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">My name is Gregory Edgeworth. I am a defense attorney. I brought my assistant, Raymond, with me to meet our client, but...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">A murder on Christmas Eve! This is just too much!</line>
<line speaker="???">♪ Ahh... In the darkneeeess... A miraculous meetiiiiiing... ♬ ♬ Welcome one and aaaall to the visitor's roooom! ♪</line>
<line speaker="Ray">A-Amazning! So this is what meeting a client is like! It all happened so suddenly, I was completely surprised!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...I'm also surprised.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">A thousand pardons for startling you. I am merely expressing my happiness through song. Welcome one and all... I greatly appreciate you coming.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">So you're the client for this case...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">My name is Gregory Edgeworth. I'm a defense attorney. I will be representing you in court. This is my assistant, Raymond Shields.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">N-Nice to meet you! I... um...! I'll do my best to help you!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Relax, Raymond. ...Please excuse his jitters. He's working part time at my office as an apprentice. I thought I'd let him assist me in this investigation.</line>
<line speaker="???">So, Mr. Gregory and Raymond, correct? I'm pleased to make your acquaintance.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>My job involves saving my clients from crimes in which they were falsely accused. First, I should determine if he is truly innocent.</thought> First, I would like to know more about you.</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, I have forgotten to introduce myself. My name is Jeffrey Master.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">What!? You mean you're... "Master Jeff"!? "The World's Greatest Pastry Chef" Jeff Master the Master Chef...?</line>
<line speaker="Master">Yes... I am honored that you have heard of me. All my fans call me "Master Jeff".</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Wowzers! I'm totally star-struck! I can't believe I get to meet Master Jeff!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Raymond seems to know quite a bit about Mr. Master.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Master Jeff makes fantastic desserts while putting on a song and dance show!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Macaroons and waffles ♬ Light and fluffy chiffon cake!</line>
<line speaker="Master">Happiness for one and all ♪ The sweetest temptations... There!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Where?</line>
<line speaker="Master">Over there! ♬ Take a peek inside the oven!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...! <thought>I got caught up in their song myself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Wahooo! I'm so happy that I got to sing with Master Jeff! It's my dream come true!</line>
<line speaker="Master">Ho ho... Thank you. I am happy to hear that as well.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...Mr. Master. Raymond. Shall we return to the matter at hand?</line>
<line speaker="Master">Yes, of course. My sincerest apologies for making you wait. Now, where should we start?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">You are the world's greatest pastry chef, but you are also skilled in song and dance?</line>
<line speaker="Master">Yes! When I'm having a good time, my body just moves to the rhythm by itself.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">You seem to enjoy making desserts from the bottom of your heart.</line>
<line speaker="Master">Ho ho... If you don't have a good time making desserts, you won't make anything good. Creating desserts that bring happiness to one and all is my purpose in life.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Master Jeff's desserts are practically works of art! They sparkle and look so delicious... He's so famous for his dreamlike desserts!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Bringing happiness to all with his dreamlike desserts, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">The incident occurred in your estate, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Master">Yes... That's where the "Great Dessert Contest" was being held... It seems that the body was discovered in one of my creations.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">They found it in one of your desserts!?</line>
<line speaker="Master">For that reason, I was arrested by the detective in charge of the initial investigation. ...I would never do something as vile as robbing someone of their life. I am certain that the police will also realize that they have made a mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">R-Really...?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Hmm... Do you know anything about the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Master">He was a man named... Isaac Dover. He was one of the competitors in the contest. He was a wonderful man who made desserts of the highest beauty. Why did he have to die...?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...I see. <thought>He truly seems to be grieving over the victim's death...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Master">Thank you very much for accepting my request to serve as my defense attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...The scale engraved on this badge represents "truth" and "fairness". As long as you are innocent, I will see to it that you receive a fair verdict. So please, entrust your faith to me and wait patiently.</line>
<line speaker="Master">Yes...! Thank you for your assistance.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...I believe I have a sufficient understanding of Mr. Master's personality.</thought> Mr. Master, before I accept your request, there is one final matter I must confirm. You did not kill Mr. Dover. ...Can I take your word for it?</line>
<line speaker="Master">Yes. That is correct. I did not kill him. No matter what happens, I would never take another person's life.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">..... <thought>Those aren't the eyes of a liar.</thought> I understand. I believe you. Thank you very much for taking the time to talk with us.</line>
<line speaker="Master">The pleasure is all mine. I am grateful to speak with someone other than a detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Next, we shall begin our investigation of the crime scene. ...We will report back with our findings once we have finished.</line>
<line speaker="Master">Mr. Gregory, Raymond. I wish you good luck.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Whew, it sure is cold outside. I didn't expect it to be snowing this hard.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Indeed. A blizzard like this will probably not clear up for a while.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">But even so, this mansion is ginormous! So this is what Master Jeff's place is like, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">If you're going to hold a contest in your own home, you would need this much space, after all.</line>
<line speaker="???">♬ La, la, laaa~ Welcome! Thank you for coming! Eek! Oh my! Are you okay? I-I'm so very sorry! Would you happen to be Monsieur Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Yes, I am Gregory Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">And I'm his assistant, Raymond Shields!</line>
<line speaker="Kate">Greetings and welcome, Monsieur Edgeworth and Monsieur Shields. Please call me Katherine Hall! I am in charge of the household affairs of this estate, and am also Monsieur Master's assistant.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ahhh! No way! You're the famous "Kate", aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Kate">You know of me?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Of course I do! I see you on TV all the time! I'm a big fan of "Piece of Cake"!</line>
<line speaker="Kate">Oh, goodness! I'm glad to hear that you're a fan!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...Tell me, what is this "Piece of Cake"?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">It's a TV show that's hugely popular with the kids! Master Jeff and Kate sing and dance while they make delicious treats. Just like this!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">♪ Cookies and caramel ♬ Rich and feathery cream puffs!</line>
<line speaker="Kate">Let's make it together! ♪ A delectable paradise... Here!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">There!</line>
<line speaker="Kate">Everywhere! ♬ ♪ You just open up the oven!</line>
<line speaker="Kate">Oh, Monsieur Shields! That was incredible!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">He he he! I always practice along with the show.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">..... <thought>Maybe I should tell my son about this show.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">But man, doing this dance repeatedly sure works up your appetite.</line>
<line speaker="Kate">Ah! Pardon my inconsideration! I've forgotten to take care of our guests! Please relax and have some tea.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Oh... This is some fine Ceylon tea... I hear the aroma of citrus does wonders for your concentration.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I see... So this is what Ceylon tea smells like.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Oh? These saucers are chilled.</line>
<line speaker="Kate">Yes. They help cool the tea more quickly for people who are bad with hot beverages.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">I see... These tea cups also have a wonderful design.</line>
<line speaker="Kate">Oh, thank you very much! They are one of the few pride and joys of our estate, ordered directly from France! They were made by the famed sculptor Pierre Hoquet. They are my absolute favorite articles of tableware.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...You seem to greatly appreciate this man's works.</line>
<line speaker="Kate">Yes! They are like treasures to me.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>She appears to be very honest about what she likes.</thought> Thank you, Ms. Hall, but it's time for us to move on to business. Are there any details that you can give us about the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Kate">Ah... You're right. I sometimes get so distracted welcoming guests that I forget myself. To tell the truth, I was the one who discovered Monsieur Dover's body.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">So you were the first one to discover the body? It is true that the body was discovered in one of Mr. Master's desserts?</line>
<line speaker="Kate">Yes... It was during the judging of the Great Dessert Contest. I heard the sound of something breaking from Monsieur Master's room.</line>
<line speaker="Kate">...Monsieur Master? Are you in here? Eek...!</line>
<line speaker="Kate">When I looked inside the room, I saw Monsieur Dover's body inside the treasure chest...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...Thank you very much. I'm sorry to have made you recall such painful memories.</line>
<line speaker="Kate">No... I should be the one apologizing for not being much help.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Now then, I believe it's time for us to start investigating the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Kate">Monsieur Edgeworth, Monsieur Shields. Please find some way to save Monsieur Master. Monsieur Master is not someone who could commit murder!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...Yes. Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Just leave it to us!</line>
<line speaker="Kate">Then I shall entrust it to you. If you'll excuse me, I have to continue serving tea to the other inspectors.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Raymond, let's head to the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Yes, sir! Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Wow! This whole thing is made of chocolate! I can't believe I'm actually seeing Master Jeff's desserts up close!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Were this not the scene of a murder, I admit, I too would have delighted in this occasion.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Uuugh... Now that you've reminded me it's a murder scene, I'm getting shivers down my spine.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...Perhaps it's because this room is cold to begin with?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Now that you mention it, this room really is cold. *A-ACHOO*</line>
<line speaker="???">...Never expected the defense attorney to show up so early.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Pleased to meet you. I'm Jeff Master's defense attorney, Gregory Edgeworth. This is my assistant, Raymond.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">How do you do!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Detective Tyrell Badd. Homicide.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Mr. Badd, the detective in charge of this case... A man of few words... Mmm... Tastes kinda bitter...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">He ate... the paper...!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">He likes to digest his memos in his stomach as well as in his mind... It's just a strange habit of his. Please don't be too concerned. <thought>It would probably be too much to ask him not to be concerned at all...</thought> More importantly... Detective Badd. Will you give us permission to participate in the investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Permission denied.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Wh-Why!? Mr. Edgeworth is Master Jeff's defense attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Defense attorneys... plant false evidence... to try and get their "Not Guilty" verdict. I don't want... their kind to disturb the crime scene...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Mr. Edgeworth would never use false evidence to defend his client!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Heh... I can't trust that, coming from a defense attorney...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Do the police still suspect Mr. Master, even after the investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.....If we didn't, we wouldn't have arrested him...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">I believe that Mr. Master is innocent. That's why I have come to investigate.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Believing in his innocence... without investigating the crime scene... How naïve...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...That's why I would like your permission to investigate. By investigating the crime scene, I want to ascertain if my thinking was naïve or not.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Hmph. ...So you don't intend to leave until you've investigated the crime scene...?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Tch... Fine then... I will give you permission to investigate the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">! Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">But, I'll be accompanying you. ...I can't trust you defense attorneys, after all! ...If you understand that, you... can begin your investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">That's... a lollipop?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...I'm a little surprised myself.</thought> Alright, let's begin the investigation. Raymond, be sure to take notes on the case.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Leave it to me, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Just... begin already...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Due to the broken stand, the ship lost its balance... It would seem Ms. Hall entered the room upon hearing the ship collapse.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yeah... When Ms. Hall entered the room, the ship had already fallen over...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">At any rate, I wonder why the stand broke <thought>Why the stand broke? - The ship fell over because the stand broke. Why did it break?</thought>?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Maybe there was something wrong with the ship's balance in the first place...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Is that really true...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Each of Mr. Master's works had a piece that was missing. Add to that the fact that the ship's chocolate stand was broken... I think we can surmise that someone ransacked this room.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">And, the one who did it could be the true culprit!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...That I don't know. But I think it's safe to say that the ship stand got broken when the room was ransacked. <thought>And, when the ship fell over it broke the treasure chest lid... I expect that the lid of the treasure chest was originally closed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Your way of investigating is... to soft. An investigation is like a popsicle... Walk around the crime scene... and investigate. ...Talk with... the people involved. If you do that... little by little, you'll lick it down to its core... And the truth will be written... on the end of the popsicle stick.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...I pray that it doesn't say, "The truth was lost for all eternity."</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Is it safe to assume that the state of the crime scene has been preserved?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Crime scene preservation... Is the most important rule of an investigation. The body has been recovered, but... besides that... it's been left untouched...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">If possible, could you tell me about the condition of the body in more detail?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Ms. Hall... took a photo of it. ...Be content with that, defense attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Does this detective have a grudge against defense attorneys? I guess I have no choice but to investigate the contradictions of the crime scene myself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Working with defense attorneys... isn't worth it... They go through the crime scene as they please... and interpret their findings to their favor.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Do you also feel that way about me?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Hmm.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...He didn't confirm or deny it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...It's a strange seal. If this were a stamp, it would imprint "PH"...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Perhaps it's meant to be seen as it is. In that case, it would read "H9"...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Hits... Nine hits... An explosive batter... No, that's not it...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Does Detective Badd like baseball...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">There are several... puzzling points... in this case...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">I would like a little more information on the state of the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">You have... your own two feet. Why don't you go investigate yourself... That's how... a detective does things...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">We may be in different positions, but we both want to know the truth of this case. Wouldn't it be better if you cooperated a bit more?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.....</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>He's fallen silent as a stone. A rather large stone. ...Is that also how a detective does things?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">It seems the culprit... prepared gloves in advance... That's why only fingermarks... and no fingerprints were left behind...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Could you get any information from the size of the fingers?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...That would be difficult. In other words... this evidence is meaningless.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It's a bit early to decide that. This could also become a clue. It tells us, the culprit "did not leave fingerprints."</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Hmph... You always have a comeback. It's because you're a defense attorney...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Heh... I'll take that as a compliment.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">I would like to ask your opinion about this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I refuse... I hate... pointless chatter...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I guess he's not interested in things that he doesn't think are related to the case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">What are you investigating?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Sir! I'm checking the temperature of the stream!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...What have you learned?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Sir! This stream... has warm water! The stream is connected to the fountain in the patio, and runs through every room.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It's an unusual construction for a room.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">The minds of the rich... I'll never understand.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...What about over here? Was there nothing suspicious in the cupboard?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">No, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...So there was something?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Oh, uh... No. Only things like cooking burners and tableware were placed here!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I see. Defense attorney, was there nothing that you noticed?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">No.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...So you did notice something?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Oh, no... I didn't notice anything.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Everyone's always giving replies that are difficult to understand...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I think it's your way of asking that's bad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It appears to be a display of sailing equipment.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">There's also the possibility... that one of these is the murder weapon...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">No... It looks like these pieces were all made out of chocolate. You can't beat someone to death with these.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Tch...! Misleading...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>At any rate, they all have such good workmanship that they look just like the real thing. It really speaks about the level of skill Mr. Master has in his craft.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">So this was where the body was discovered?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yeah... The body has been removed... but otherwise... the crime scene has remained untouched.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">To build such a large ship out of chocolate is magnificent.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">As expected of Master Jeff! I want to try eating it... Although I have no idea where to start eating it from...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Anywhere should be fine, but if you start eating the crime scene... I'll make you leave...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Uwaah! Don't glare at me! Can't you tell it was a joke?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...I'd like Raymond to be just a little bit calmer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It seems that the body was discovered inside this chocolate treasure chest.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...The person who discovered it was Ms. Hall...</line>
<line speaker="Kate">...Monsieur Master? Are you in here? Eek...!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">She heard the sound of something breaking <thought>Breaking sound - What was the sound that came from Mr. Master's room?</thought>... inside this room... and came in.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...I would like a little more information about this.</thought> Hm. What's this? Something has been dropped inside the treasure chest. Hm. This is...? It seems to be some kind of seal, with a design and initials carved into it.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">It looks like a signet crest. Was it the victim's?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I don't know if it was the victim's, but we should take it for now...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It seems that the stand supporting the ship has been broken <thought>Broken stand - The stand that supported the ship was broken and caused the ship to tip over.</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">The ship tipped over and broke the treasure chest, didn't it? Ah! M-Maybe! Could the victim have been crushed by the ship and killed?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...If that were the case, this would have been an accidental death.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...You two... aren't serious about that, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Well. We were only discussing one of the possibilities.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">...I was being pretty serious though.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">"The Voyage of the Good Ship Red Rum" is written here...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">"It sailed... the Seven Seas and in the end finally found... a huge treasure. Modeled after... the glory of an ancient adventurer." ...It's written here...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">So he failed six times... What an unlucky captain.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...No matter how many times he went on a fool's errand... In the end he reached the truth... ...It's just like... a detective's spirit...!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Did detectives even exist... during the ancient times?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Detective Badd. I would like you to tell me about the state of the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">If you mean a photo of the body... Here. Look at it... all you like. It seems the victim... was beaten to death <thought>Beaten to death - The victim appears to have been beaten to death with a blunt object.</thought> with a blunt object.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Has the murder weapon been found?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...You... should try asking the prosecutor in charge later...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...It seems he doesn't intend to tell me frankly.</thought> So... May I borrow this photograph?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Sure... It's not a photo that was taken by the police... Ms. Hall took a photo of the body with an instant camera when she discovered it.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">An instant camera... Is that like a disposable camera?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">An instant camera is a camera that can develop its film right after taking a picture.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Eh! Such a convenient camera exists!?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Anyway, let's go over the state of the crime scene a bit. This photo... upon closer examination, contradicts the state of the crime scene. I'll have to deduce the contradiction to resolve this matter.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Is this spot somehow connected to any of the evidence I hold...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">This part is contradictory... It contradicts this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">This ship is "confectionery"... How sweet. Otherwise... we could board the ship... and sail down the chocolate river.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>What an unpleasant dismissal... Let's calm down, and inspect the crime scene once more. It feels like something that was here before isn't anymore...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Are you sure the only thing the police removed from the crime scene was the body?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Ah... They also took away the piece of cloth the body was wrapped in.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">In that case, a major "contradiction" has been created at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Contradiction...?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Detective Badd. Please look at the crime scene carefully once more. The bloodstain that should have remained at the crime scene has disappeared!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...! I definitely... didn't get any reports about the bloodstain being cleaned up... I'll check... with forensics.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Mr. Edgeworth. What happened?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Comparing the photo and the crime scene, something struck me as being out of place. In the photo, the chocolate underneath the body remained intact inside the treasure chest. ...however, in the actual crime scene, it's missing.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">! The chocolate with the bloodstain has completely vanished.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Yes. Did the police remove it, or was this the work of the criminal...?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">According to forensics... no one has cleaned upo any bloodstains...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...I see. Well, that would mean someone erased the bloodstain.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Who knows...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">This is an actual crime scene! I'm so excited!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">This isn't a game, Raymond. Please be more serious.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Yes, sir! I'm taking a memo right now!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Oh... What exactly are you writing?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I'm copying down this dessert recipe over here!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...Raymond. Please be more serious.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Yes, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Excuse me, but you are...?</line>
<line speaker="???">..... Nnph. My apologies. I was meditating. What did you ask, Sir Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Actually, I'm a defense attorney. My name is Gregory Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I'm his assistant, Raymond!</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">Pardon my late introduction. My name is Dane Gustavia. I am one of the pastry chefs participating in this contest.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">What kind of desserts do you make, Mr. Gustavia?</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">...My specialty is making desserts out of candy.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Awww! What a cute seahorse!</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">It was meant to be a "dragon" dancing in the sky...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Eh! Th-This is a "dragon"...?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I think it would fit better in the ocean than in the sky...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">I know all too well that design is my weak point! ...I plan to study design and undergo training in Zheng Fa once things settle down here.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I probably shouldn't touch the subject of design any further.</thought> Mr. Gustavia, if you aren't related to the investigation, why are you in this room...?</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">Sir Detective wanted to know more about the desserts in this room, so he asked me to come.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Since he's one of the contestants, he might know something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Mr. Gustavia, those instruments you use are quite unusual.</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">These instruments are called "candy pumps", and they pump air into the candy.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">They kinda look like swords. They're so cool!</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">Indeed. Ever since I began using them, no day has gone by where I didn't receive a burn or wound! That's why I wear red clothes! So that not a single stain will ever show on me! Making desserts is serious business... I am always training!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...Does he injure himself because he hasn't trained enough?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Can you tell me about the Great Dessert Contest that was held here? From the looks of this room, it seems the desserts weren't just for eating.</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">The exhibition Sir Master held was a "contest in the art of dessert."</line>
<line speaker="Ray">The art of... dessert?</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">"Desserts that are true works of art," made solely out of edible materials! The works of art in this room are all made from desserts.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Now that you mention it, the whole room is filled with the smell of chocolate.</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">Sir Master exhibits great talent in both flavor and design. If you are not able to surpass Sir Master in flavor and design, you will not be able to win.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Beating the world's greatest pastry chef is pretty hard, isn't it...?</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">...In other words, if I can surpass Sir Master, I shall become the world's greatest pastry chef. That was the prize of this contest!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">The prize is the "Title of the World's Greatest"...?</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">In addition to that, there is also Sir Master's treasured "Angel's Recipe". If you want to learn more about the contest, just look at this piece of paper. These were the rules that were given to the participants of the contest.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Is it safe to assume that the state of the crime scene has been preserved?</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">Sorry, but I do not know much about the incident. I only learned about the incident after the judging had finished.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">How was the contest judging carried out?</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">Let's see... Sir Master started judging at 3 PM. Starting from my room, the judging proceeded in a clockwise direction. I used the room to the right of Sir Master's room, which is the room we're in now. Next, the room of a female pastry chef named Delicia was judged.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">A female pastry chef... What kind of person is she?</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">...She is a frightening woman who would do anything to achieve her goal. I heard she used lots of cream to make a fantasy-themed dessert. ...And lastly, Sir Dover's room was judged. His works were frozen statues made from sherbet.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Hall discovered the body... in the middle of... Gustavia's judging. She panicked... and because she immediately notified the police... Master... continued judging... without knowledge that the body has been discovered. As a result, Master... judged Dover's room... in Dover's absence. Hmph... It seems we have plenty of room to suspect Master...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...I'm lacking in information. It's probably too early to object.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">...That badge has a rather artistic design. My craftman's spirit is shaking! Mind if I borrow it for a while?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">S-Sorry... This is rather important to me. <thought>It would be unbearable if it got hurt in the candy making process...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">The title of "World's Greatest Pastry Chef"... I intend to achieve it through this contest. Afterwards, if I am able to master my design training in Zheng Fa... I shall be recognized as a first-class pastry chef in both cooking and design!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...I would think the order would be reversed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">.....Nnph. My apologies. I was meditating. What did you ask, Sir Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">I'm a defense attorney. And about this piece of evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">.....</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>M-Meditating again...? I guess if it doesn't catch his interest greatly, he won't even give it a glance.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">By the way, Detective Badd. What were you talking to Mr. Gustavia earlier?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I was asking him about... the chocolate frame hanging on that wall... I thought... something was missing... I thought... if I asked someone who knew a lot about desserts... I could get an answer. ...Although thanks to your arrival, I still haven't gotten my answer yet...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Well then, since you've been waiting for so long, we can ask him about it, right now.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I guess you don't understand sarcasm...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Mr. Gustavia, can you assist us with this matter?</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">I train in the arts of desserts everyday. If you have a question about desserts, please do not hesitate to ask.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Thank you very much.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">You can make such a beautiful picture out of chocolate!? As expected of Master Jeff!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...Is this really chocolate? It looks like an actual picture to me.</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">Impressive, Sir Attorney! You noticed well. This picture of an angel is not a dessert, but rather the "Angel's Recipe".</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">The "Angel's Recipe"... The prize for the contest.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ehh!? This picture isn't made of chocolate!?</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">Indeed. Within this chocolate frame lies a recipe book. Sir Master told everyone when he explained the rules of the contest to us in this room.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>So the contestants knew the recipe was here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">How about it...? This frame... Don't you think it's missing something...?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>This must be what Detective Badd was asking Mr. Gustavia about earlier.</thought> This chocolate frame, there does seem to be a part that's missing.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">That's... what's been bothering me as well...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Eh? ...What's missing?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Let me show Raymond the part of the chocolate frame that's missing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Raymond. Don't you think there is something missing here?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">...Sorry. I don't know much about art. I thought this was one of those "artistic expressions" though.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...My glasses slipped, and I pointed to the wrong spot.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Um... There's something missing from the chocolate frame, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">That's right. Even if you don't know the first thing about art, you should understand this.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Look closely at this part with the decorations. Can you see that one of them is missing?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">It's true! It's different from the other decorations.</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">Hm... This imperfect balance in the decorations is not like Sir Master.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Upon closer examination, it seems this frame is not the only one with missing parts. ...We need to investigate further.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">All the desserts in this room each have one part missing...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Whoa... The candle holder and the sailing tools are all damaged as well! So someone tampered with the crime scene <thought>Tampered desserts - The desserts Mr. Master made were damaged in several places.</thought>?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...Perhaps.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Maybe... Master vandalized the room himself to fool us...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Master Jeff wouldn't do that sort of thing to his desserts!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Tampered desserts... I wonder if they are connected to the incident?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">This picture of an angel is not a dessert, but rather the "Angel's Recipe".</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">The "Angel's Recipe"... The prize for the contest.</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">Indeed. Within this chocolate frame lies a recipe book. Sir Master told everyone when he explained the rules of the contest to us in this room.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>So the contestants knew the recipe was here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...These fingermarks are?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">These are... unidentified fingermarks. ...We don't know who they belong to. Since... no fingerprints were left behind...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Fingermarks without fingerprints... These might be related to the case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hmmm. It's a mystery!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">He was probably wearing gloves...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ugh... Detective Badd lacks dreams and romance.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I don't think there are dreams or romance at a murder scene...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It seems the title of this work is written here.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">"Angel Caught by Thorns"... It's an enchanting dessert, isn't it! It feels like my heart has also been caught...!</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">Quite...! It seems Sir Assistant has a sense of beauty. Speaking of which, I too have had my heart caught by this dessert.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Mr. Edgeworth! Mr. Gustavia praised me!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Raymond... That's not the sort of thing you'd want to blow your own "thorn" about.</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">Hmph...! Sir Defense Attorney, it seems your sense of words is lacking.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Mr. Edgeworth made a joke! I'd better make a memo about this!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...Exactly which part of what I said was a joke?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">The Captain's log... of a chocolate ship... which is also made out of chocolate... It seems its title is... "Journal of Regret"...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">"Running out of rum while drifting at the Red Sea has really made me red with regret..." it reads. I don't know what kind of voyage it was, but it doesn't seem very regretful.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">A dessert... in the shape of a candle holder... huh... It's titled... "Light of Life"...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>It seems that... one of these important lights isn't lit. Is it symbolic, or...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">This is a fire alarm.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Ah... Let me say in advance... That's not a dessert... It's the real deal. If you press that... an alarm will sound, and security will be contacted... I understand that you want to press it to see what happens... but please refrain yourself...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">No, I didn't particularly feel like pressing it.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Tch! It's because you're a defense attorney...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I don't think being a defense attorney has anything to do with it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">A... A... Achoo!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Are you alright, Raymond?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ugh... This room is way too cold!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">The Fountain Patio wasn't very warm, either... This room certainly is cold. Do you want to wear my coat?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Nope! I'm fine! Because that's something that you promised to give me when I become a defense attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Heh... That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Why is the temperature turned down so low...?</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">It's been turned down in order to maintain the chocolate's temperature. ...Why don't you try opening the panel cover on that wall?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Panel cover...?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Whoa! There's a secret panel hidden there!</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">This control panel is installed in all the rooms Sir Master prepared. So as not to detract from the dessert's presentation, the cover was closed to conceal it.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">What does the panel do?</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">It allows you to change the temperature and the lighting in the room. In order to preserve any type of dessert, it can go down to about -22℉.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...The room would be like a freezer.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">It's set to 59℉! No wonder I thought it was cold. Detective Badd. I'm not allowed to change the temperature... Am I?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Preserving the crime scene... is the foundation of being a detective...!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">But, I'm not a detective...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">A defense attorney can't recklessly damage a crime scene either.</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">Indeed, Sir Assistant. Enduring hardship is also a part of training. In order to preserve chocolate, 59℉ to 64℉ is the ideal temperature.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Hm... The ideal temperature for chocolate. As expected of the dessert chef...</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">No, it is but a trifle. This is basic knowledge that anyone should know if they're a dessert chef.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...So, what's the ideal temperature for candy and fresh cream?</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">As long as you watch out for humidity and hot temperatures, candy shouldn't melt. For fresh cream, around 50℉ is the ideal temperature.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...You need to watch out for the humidity and hot temperatures for candy... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Detective Badd. He seemed a bit happy when they were talking about candy.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Is candy one of his favorite things...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It seems this control panel can change the temperature and the color of the lights in this room.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">The colors are red, yellow, green, blue, cyan, and white... That sure is a lot.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">This room's temperature is 59℉... And the lights are set to white.</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">It's because the works in this room are made of chocolate. By using white light, the chocolate can stand out.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>For Mr. Master, everything in this room is probably a piece of art.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Elegant tableware and cookware are placed on the counter. It looks like the same tea set Ms. Hall was using earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Was Master Jeff drinking this black tea?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">On this tea set... only Jeff Master's fingerprints were found.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Were his fingerprints found on any of the other cookware?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">The cookware was washed... Nobody's fingerprints... remained.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Or he might have been cooking with gloves on... It seems the only thing here with his fingerprints is the tea set.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">Master... used these gloves while making his desserts... They hid his fingerprints...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Certainly, it's possible that they were used for that purpose... But wouldn't you agree that finding cooking gloves in the kitchen is perfectly natural?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Doubt everything... That's my job...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Hm... This is a rather splendid design.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">...You think so? It seems a little eccentric to me... I'm not even sure how you'd pour tea out of it.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Rather than the practicality of the design, focus on its artistic merits.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hmm. Mr. Edgeworth's art sense is too high for me to understand!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">There's an engraving on the bottom! It says "PH".</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It's the initials of the creator, "Pierre Hoquet". Ms. Hall and Mr. Master seem to be big fans of this sculptor's works.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Initials, huh... If it were mine, it'd be "RS"!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...Why don't you try carving your initials on your own belongings?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It seems our investigation of this room is just about over.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">This should make it clear... Jeff Master is the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">! Wh-Why!?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">All the rooms in this mansion... were locked from the inside. And... the only way to open them from the outside, was to use this key to the mansion...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...Do you know who had the key?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Master... was the only one with the key. ...There were no spare keys.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">By using the mansion key... Master... could enter all the contestants' rooms. Of course... the key could also lock his room from the outside...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">However, Mr. Master's room is currently unlocked.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yeah... That's why I suspect Master is the culprit...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...I'd like to hear your reasoning in more detail.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">If the body had been found in a locked room... Master would've been the prime suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Contrary to his expectations... the body was discovered by Ms. Hall... ...That's my reason for suspecting Master. Got that, Ace Attorney?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...So you also think it was Mr. Master himself who vandalized this room?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yeah... You defense attorneys believe that justice lies in trusting your clients... But I'm a detective. If I believed every poor sap's story... I'd let the suspicious ones get away...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...I understand your reasoning thoroughly. However... I'd like you to hear my thoughts on the subjects now.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Hmph. Fine.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Detective Badd believes that he is right, but I won't give up so easily. I can't accept his reasoning... I'll have to show him evidence that contradicts it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">If the body had been found in a locked room... Master would've been the prime suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Isn't it a little premature to suspect Mr. Master on those grounds alone?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">It's a little premature... for you to be objecting...! ...Just wait... until I'm done...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">That's why Master made sure to leave the door to his own room unlocked...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">He left it unlocked?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">If the door had been locked... Master would be the only one who could commit the crime...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Well... maybe the door just happened to be unlocked?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Then... maybe the body just happened to be lying in the open, waiting to be discovered... ...Runt... Do you think you can become a good detective with logic like that?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Uugh... But, I don't wanna be a detective, I wanna be a defense attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...I hope he isn't trying to steal my apprentice.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">Master had... a reason... to leave the door unlocked.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">And to ensure that the body would be seen... Master broke the lid on the treasure chest.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">You believe the broken lid was Mr. Master's doing?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yes... If he hadn't done that, the body... wouldn't have been found.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...It doesn't seem likely that he would break his own work while he was judging the contest.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">That's right! Master Jeff would never waste a good dessert! On "Piece of Cake", he even eats them while dancing!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">That TV show is irrelevant here...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">! Detective Badd, you know about "Piece of Cake"? <thought>When I didn't even know of it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Whaaat! This is a surprise! So... do you sing the song too?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...That's... irrelevant. Anyway... The one who broke the lid on the treasure chest was Master...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Badd">After the judging... everyone was scheduled to meet in Master's room...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">The judging began in Mr. Gustavia's room, right?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yeah... I, too, was looking forward to seeing his candy craft.</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">...Mm? If you would like, I can put on a display of my candy craft for you right now! ...What do you think? It represents Sir Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Umm... Is that supposed to be a police dog?</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">No, no, no...! This is a wolf!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Hmm... a lone wolf... .....Not bad.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...What would my candy form be? I'm kind of curious myself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Moving on...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">That would have created the impression... that the murder had occurred... while he was away.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Do you know the time of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...We're still... waiting on... the autopsy report...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Without the autopsy report, how could you have arrested Mr. Master?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...We don't know the time of death... but we do know... when the body was discovered. It was discovered... while Master was judging Dane Gustavia's room. I believe... he let the body be discovered... to create an alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">But that alone is not enough to arrest Mr. Master, right?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Who knows. That's all... I intend to say.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Detective Badd, are you hiding something...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Detective Badd seems adamant that Mr. Master is the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I don't think Master Jeff would have broken his own creations! But... why was the treasure chest broken then?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Hmm... Just think back to the situation in which the body was found. In doing so, we should be able to see the contradiction in Badd's reasoning.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Originally, the victim's body was hidden inside the chocolate treasure chest. Ms. Hall entered the room when she heard a sound. I think it is likely that this was the sound of the chocolate ship falling over.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yeah... That's what you would think... just by looking at the crime scene...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">You said that Mr. Master broke the treasure chest lid himself... ...but, this photo shows that the ship's fall caused the lid to break.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.....</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">If the lid broke just before Ms. Hall found the body... ...then Mr. Master, who was in the middle of judging, could not have broken it!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I... never said that Master broke the lid directly... The ship was set up to fall during the judging... I believe he tampered with the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Do you have proof he tampered with it?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">No... but the investigation isn't completely over yet...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>It seems they still haven't found anything conclusive...</thought> Have you found any other fingerprints, other than Mr. Master's, in this room?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Yeah. There were some left on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">But... the victim, Dover, and Master were also among the fingerprints left behind.</line>
<line speaker="Gustavia">Before we made our desserts, we all gathered here to have the judging explained to us. Perhaps that was when we left those fingerprints?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...But, you didn't find any fingerprints on the works in this room?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...What...?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Someone tampered with the chocolate in this room. So perhaps there are other fingerprints on it, apart from Mr. Master's.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Hmph. No matter what we find, it won't clear Master of suspicion...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.....Labbie! Hurry up and dust the chocolate for fingerprints!</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Roger that, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Detective Badd! We found another person's fingerprints... on all the chocolates in the room!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.....! Whose... fingerprints...?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">They belong to a pastry chef by the name of Delicia!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Good work... Return to the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It would seem that there are other suspicious people besides Mr. Master, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Hmph. I don't need a defense attorney to tell me that... I'm not stopping my investigation... We will just... go and listen to what this Delicia has to say.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Delicia... Gustavia told us about her not long ago. Is she really a "frightening woman who would do anything to achieve her goal"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Mr. Edgeworth, this Delicia lady sounds mighty suspicious to me!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Mmm. It seems that it will be necessary for us to speak with her directly, as well. Detective Badd. Would you allow us to accompany you?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I'm not obligated to do that.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">What...!?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">But... you were the one who discovered the truth of the crime scene... Fine, have it your way. Follow me...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Detective Badd...! Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">D-Detective Badd, sir! Are you sure about that? Right now, that prosecutor is in the room...!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Doesn't matter. Him and I... don't see eye to eye.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">"Him"...? Who's the prosecutor in charge of this case anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Manfred von Karma...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">WHAAAAAA! Von Karma is in charge!? That guy hasn't lost a case in 25 years...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Manfred von Karma... The "living legend" of the prosecutor's office...? If the rumors of his courtroom performance are to be believed... ...he's a man who would do anything for a guilty verdict. ...No matter what kind of prosecutor he is, I can only hold true to the path I believe in.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Wow! A candy castle! And there are even some fairies over there!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">This room... seems to be structured in the same way as Master's room...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">But it's nowhere near as cold!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">This room... also seems to have been fitted with a temperature control panel...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ah, it's over by that that orange lamp, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Indeed. Let's not forget to investigate it later. <thought>Even so... this room is like something out of a fairy tale. Is this cream-covered castle Delicia's work?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Where is Delicia...?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Oi! Can I help you? Hullo boys! I'm Delicia Scones. In my native England, I'm known as "Ms. Delicious"!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Being called a "boy" even though I'm already 34... It's certainly a rare experience.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">B-Boys? I understand you calling me that, but... Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">As far as I'm concerned, you're all boys to me, even that detective over there.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...My name is... Badd. Not "boy"...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Just how old is this woman?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Mr. Attorney. Let's just finish our business here.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Hmm... Right.</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="???">You! What do you think you're doing!? Conversing with a mere attorney!?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Mr. Edgeworth! A-A scary man came out of the candy castle...!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Von Karma...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Eh! This man is, Prosecutor von Karma...?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Eep! Manny!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>So he's Von Karma...</thought> Pleased to meet you, Prosecutor von Karma. My name is Gregory Edgeworth, defense attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...What a rude man.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">That piercing gaze and furrowed brow...! Uugh... He's even scarier than the rumors say.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Although that statement was also very rude.</thought> Prosecutor von Karma. Would you allow us to investigate too?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>As I thought, it won't be that simple...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">! <thought>Why did he change his mind so quickly?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Don't call me that. ...My name is... Badd.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Why... me...!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Tch... I'm babysitting again...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I wonder why he and Von Karma aren't investigating together? Instead of being on bad terms, it seems like they hardly know each other...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Mr. Edgeworth, now that we've got Von Karma's permission, we can continue investigating!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Yes. His manner bothers me, but I am glad we can at least continue the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Hold it. I also need to investigate this room... I don't want you disturbing the room... So you'll investigate... after me.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">What!? Aren't you the detective in charge of this case? Why haven't you investigated this room yet?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...The detective in charge of the initial investigation was a close colleague of Von Karma. I came to take over for him, so I only got to this mansion just recently.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>So that's why he and Von Karma aren't investigating together...</thought> Detective Badd. Will you allow us to investigate with you like before? In doing so, you'll be able to supervise us and also ensure we don't tamper with anything.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">You want me to watch you? ...You're a strange lawyer. ...Hmph. I'll let you stick around... a little longer.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Yay! You did it, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Thank you, Detective Badd.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...But if I decide you're holding up the investigation, you'll have to leave...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Yes... I understand. Well then, let's begin the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">The rock's pedestal has a similar shape to the recesses on the castle's pillars. Perhaps the rock is meant to be placed on top of the pillars?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Oh, that's right! They're both hexagonal.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I wonder why they were hidden inside the castle, though?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">The reason the fresh cream is so fragile is due to the temperature in this room.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">So my shoes got creamed... because the room temperature is set at 68℉...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Speaking of which... When you opened the castle door, the doorknob didn't break.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yeah... it was stronger than I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Strong? ...A dessert? Detective Badd. Could you have a closer look at that doorknob?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.....? ...This is...!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It would seem this doorknob isn't a dessert.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...And it's not just the doorknob. This castle and the fairies... Are just plastic molds coated in fresh cream.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Eeh! Then, this isn't a dessert piece at all...!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It would seem they're just fake desserts <thought>Fake desserts - Delicia made fake desserts. What are her true intentions...?</thought> covered in fresh cream...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">This room... has the same design as Master's room...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Is something bothering you?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Von Karma ...was investigating ...inside the candy castle... ...I wonder... why...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Detective Badd, do you suspect Delicia?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">That woman... is hiding something. ...My detective's spirit... is telling me so...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Is that his detective's intuition? Something about this room definitely troubles me as well. I should listen to what Delicia has to say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">There's a burner and some chemicals over here. They were probably used to make desserts. What are these chemicals? The writing on the labels say... "No. 1: Punchout!"... and "No. 9: Sufferin"...!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Are... they... poisons?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">No, they are both used to make desserts. Seems to be artificial flavoring and coloring. "Punchout!" is a catchy name for a fruit punch essence.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Tch... Very misleading...!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>What bothers me is what "Sufferin" stands for...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Don't turn around, don't turn around... If you do, you're only gonna eat that castle!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...This forensics officer seems to be on a diet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">There's a cover on the wall, just like in Mr. Master's room.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Let's open it up...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hmm. The room temperature is 68℉, and the lights are set to green...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Gustavia said... that 50℉ is the ideal temperature for fresh cream... This room's temperature is too high <thought>High room temperature - The temperature in Delicia's room is too high for fresh cream.</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>This is... intriguing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It's a cute candy fairy sitting on a tree stump. Hmm. The cream decorations are melting. The fairy seems to be well made, but... something feels slightly off.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...I can't believe this amazing castle is made entirely out of confectionery.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I know! What a work of fantasy. It's like a fairy tale world!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">You like all this fairy tale stuff, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ah... sorry! I got a bit too excited, didn't I?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">No... It's interesting to me since you're so enthusiastic about it, unlike my son.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Your... son?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">He's only in grade school, yet he prefers to read law books instead of fairy tales. ...I am worried that he won't be able to make any friends that he can talk to.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Heh! What an interesting kid. I'd like to be his friend!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Ha ha... I think you'd be more of an "older brother" to him.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">He he he. An older brother, huh... Well, I've got some growing up to do then!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Yes, and that's why we have to continue with the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Hm. This pillar... has a hexagonal recess.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">It looks like a pedestal... but... it has nothing in it.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">A hexagonal recess <thought>Hexagonal recess - The two pillars have a hexagonal recess on top. What were they for?</thought>, huh. I wonder what would have been put in there?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...A giant strawberry... would fit with the fresh cream.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Detective Badd. I don't think strawberries are hexagonal.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I was just... hoping...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Then, I hope it's a banana!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...I think I'd prefer blueberries.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">The castle doors are open...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">When someone opens a door, they really should remember to close it afterwards.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Would he say that directly to Prosecutor von Karma though?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Huh? Looks like there's some stuff inside. Hmm, let's see...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Wait... I'll examine it. Stay out of the way. Tch... This fresh cream melts too easily <thought>Fragile desserts - The cream is melting. A single touch can cause it to break.</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Seems like Detective Badd's shoes got covered in cream... ...Why were these objects kept inside the candy castle?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...If there's anything you want to investigate... you better speak up now.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...There are rolls of blue cloth here. Looks like there's four of them in all...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">They certainly don't look like desserts.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yeah... I don't know what the cloth is for... It almost seems like... it was hidden here inside the castle...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...Also, the color of this cloth looks familiar somehow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">Two big rocks... are placed here. It's like a... storage room.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Yeah, the inside of the candy castle isn't so dreamy. ...Hey! Maybe they're raw gemstones? Who knew that there were such treasures hidden within the castle!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Seems like a rather careless way to handle treasure... Hm...? It looks like there's something underneath the rocks.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Seems there's a... pedestal <thought>Pedestal of rock - The rocks in the castle have a pedestal attached to them for some reason.</thought> attached to both of the rocks...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Of course! It's a pedestal for displaying the gems!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Well... in any case, this is no ordinary object.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">The sicky sweet smell of cream. Yes, this truly is a fairy tale world. And yet, here in this sugary sweet room, there was one with such a sour face... He doesn't belong in this room... That scary old man.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Raymond, mind what you say. You're being a bit rude.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">S-Sorry... It won't happen again. He reminded me of my old school teacher who used to get mad at me a lot...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>A school teacher. I definitely... ...don't want to think of my son being taught by such a man.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It says, "The Four Fairies and the Curious Candy Castle." It seems that this was the theme for Delicia's works.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">But, it's not just the candy castle that I'm curious about...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Here are all the tools used to make desserts.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Everything from a bucket of fresh cream... to a brush and a trowel... Looks more like a construction worker's tools...</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Hey now, boys. Don't undersweetmate the work of a pastry chef! It's completely different from construction work, where they cover the walls with cement. We use the trowel to smear the cream, and the brush to clean any uneven parts...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...How is that different from construction work...?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">*sigh*...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Huh? Ms. Delicious. You don't seem as energetic as you were earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...Delicia. Can I just ask, did something happen with Von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yessie! N-Nothing of the sort!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">But, you just said, "Yessie"...</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Ha ha ha ha! That "Yessie" just now was only a greeting. You're a cute boy! I like you. What's your first name?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Eh? It's Raymond, but...</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Well, Ray Ray! I think you'll make a good man of yourself someday!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">R-Ray Ray...?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">How about that. I think you have a way with British ladies.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">She's a little different from my image of a "lady"...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Why don't we listen to what she has to say.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Could you tell me about your actions during the contest?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yessie! We began making desserts for the contest around 10 o'clock. Basically, I was in here making my desserts the whole time. At half past one, I joined the afternoon tea for about an hour or so.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Afternoon tea?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It's a social occasion, where conversation is had over black tea and cakes.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">...Umm. So, it's pretty much a tea party!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Well... I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Ha ha ha ha! Oh, Greggy, you're a smart boy, aren't you!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>When did I become "Greggy"...?</thought> Where was the afternoon tea held?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">It took place in the gardens, outside of the Fountain Patio. It's our customary break time during the contest. It's always held at the same time. Today there were just three of us who took part. Jeffy, Katie and me. Since Jeffy had already finished his creations, he was there from beginning to end. Icy and Gusty didn't join in because they hadn't finished their desserts yet.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...So, everyone other than Mr. Dover and Mr. Gustavia participated.</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yes. Actually, I hadn't finished my dessert yet either. I just wanted to try some of Jeffy's handmade pastries and Katie's fresh-brewed tea. So... after I had eaten my fill, I returned before everyone else.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">During the contest, did you enter any of the other contestants' rooms?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Eh! Wh-What are you saying?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">We found your fingerprints on the desserts at the crime scene...</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Eep! You found them...!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Are you... admitting that you went to the scene of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">*sob* ...I admit it. But, I'm not the murderer! It's the honest truth, please hear me out!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">What were you doing in Mr. Master's room?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">The truth is... I was studying his desserts.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Studying...?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Because Jeffy's so talented at making sweets! Well... Nobody was in his room at the time, so I just decided to study <thought>Desserts study - Delicia went to Mr. Master's room to study his desserts.</thought> his works for a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...But, if you were just looking, you wouldn't have left your fingerprints behind...?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yessie! It's natural that I left fingerprints on the desserts! For the sake of research, I ate some of his desserts.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Eeh! Isn't that like stealing food?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It couldn't be... The one who wrecked Mr. Master's room was...</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">*sob* ...I'm sorry. It wasn't my intention to vandalize the room, but... I did eat a few parts of the desserts in his room. ...I secretly ate little bits and pieces so Jeffy wouldn't find out.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">So... Did you you[sic] eat the ship stand as well?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yessie! I did.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">The chocolate ship broke... because of you...</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Eep! I'm sorry...!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">So, the reason she left the afternoon tea early... ...was to preserve her appetite...</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">B-But! You've got to believe me on this! I'm not the murderer!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Her actions are sufficiently suspicious, but... I won't press on it yet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Oi! What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">This badge is proof that I'm a defense attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Hoi! I'll show you mine too. This chef's hat is proof that I'm a pastry chef.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Is that so...? But aren't those sold in stores?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Hey! It's not the hat that's important, it's the spirit you wear the hat with that matters!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>So then, wouldn't that mean just about anyone can become a pastry chef...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Oi! That thing you've got there is rather cute, Greggy. But, the color is rather unappealing. Now, if I were to coat it with fresh cream...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">S-Stop it!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...What is it, Mr. Attorney? Something about that ladder bothering you..?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Detective Badd. It's actually a stepladder.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...They're both the same to me...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">They're completely different. Look at their basic nature.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Yeah, Mr. Edgeworth... You tell him!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>The "blue cloth" and the "rocks" inside the castle... I wonder if they belong to Delicia?</thought> Delicia. Those things in the castle, what are they used for?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Ah... uhh, those? I'm afraid I can't tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Looks like Von Karma is... keeping her silent...</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Eep! I've been found out... He'll get made at me if I talk.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Prosecutor von Karma... doesn't intend on being upfront with his information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Aww... it's such a shame. We finally figured out where the rocks are supposed to go.</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">! Could it be that you're interested in my goods?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Eh? Your "goods"...?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Those are my popular relaxation goods.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">You mean... the rocks and the cloth?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yessie! That's right! You see, they're not actually rocks, but special lamps made from rock salt.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Wow! So those are lamps!</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Ha ha ha ha! It gets even more exciting! Because, this cloth also has an amazing secret!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>As soon as we showed interest in her goods, she became quite talkative.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Since we've got them out, come experience the therapy, boys. Baddie! Could you put everything up!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">It's... not Baddie, it's Badd...</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">...So you won't do it? Is Baddie being a bad boy?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">.......</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Labbie! Are you done photographing this room?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Yes, sir! I am!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Then go help Delicia...</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Yes, sir! I'm on it!</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Ha ha ha ha! Thanks! I knew you were a good boy underneath, Baddie!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ms. Delicious... That was amazing. You even persuaded Detective Badd!</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Thanks a lot, Baddie! And you too, Forensies!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">...She even gave the forensics a nickname.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">I think that's her way of showing she cares.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">What's so... therapeutic... about these things anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">We don't have time for that now, Baddie! The show's about to begin! Forensies! Finishing touches, please!</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Yes, ma'am!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">It's...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Wow, It's so beautiful!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It really is... <thought>I wish my son could see this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Oi! I told you so, right? "The Four Fairies and the Curious Candy Castle" was the theme of my work. It's so sparkly and cute, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>It seems like... one of them is missing something.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Delicia">The truth is, I had planned to unveil it during the contest. Well, I'm glad I got to show it to you boys!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Huh? But it doesn't look like the rock salt lamps are lighting up.</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">H-Huh? I wonder why...?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I think I'll need to examine... the rocks and the fairies again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">There is evidence that the victim was beaten to death with a blunt object... What's more, there's a bloodstain on one of the broken rock salt lamps. Could this lamp have been the murder weapon?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">You're right! It could have been used as a weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Labbie. Is the blood analysis on this rock salt lamp finished?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Yes, sir! It finished just a few moments ago! The bloodstain on that lamp belonged to the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...You heard what he said.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>The murder weapon was hidden in Delicia's room... We need to consider her as one of the suspects as well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Using decorations that were against the rules and making fake desserts... A lot of Delicia's actions seem suspicious.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yeah... It doesn't seem like she's aiming to be the world's greatest pastry chef...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Also, the temperature of this room is way too high. Is there a reason for that?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">I wonder. ...I think we should ask Delicia directly.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Delicia's knowledge in the art of dessert making is lacking in fundamental areas. And she claimed she went into Mr. Master's room in order to "study his desserts"... These actions and ideas are not fitting of someone aiming to be the world's greatest pastry chef.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yeah... They don't sounds like the words of a pro. It's like she doesn't even realize it, or...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Or, maybe she isn't a real pastry chef...</thought> Perhaps she had some other intention. ...It's possible that she didn't go into the room to study desserts.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">So, then... Are you saying Ms. Delicious is the criminal?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...We can't say that for sure yet. <thought>But, I know she's hiding something from us...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Since the circumstances have changed, we should investigate the scene once more...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Yes. The fluorescent cloth behind the fairy dolls... and the rock salt lamp concerns me.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Why were they in the castle... No... why were they hidden inside the castle. I knew it, that woman... smells. But not a sugary sweet smell...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">We need to have another look, to see if there are any problems at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">This desserts here... are all fake. ...What a... phony...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">This is the contest to decide the world's greatest pastry chef. Why did she do something like that, which would immediately give her away?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I guess she was naïve enough that she thought she could get away with it, or perhaps...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Her true goal... I feel like I know what it is. I hold the fragmented pieces of information. Now, all I have to do is combine them...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">There's no mistaking it, this is what took the victim's life.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Chossing a weapon like this... perhaps the murder wasn't premeditated. If that's so... that woman... hit the victim with this lamp on a sudden impulse. It feels like the sweet smell of desserts has been tainted by the smell of something fishy.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Delicia... Are you hiding something...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It's a cute candy fairy sitting on a tree stump. The cloth in the back along with the decorations really give it a magical atmosphere. When you look at it, it almost feels like you're spellbound.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">What we need to look for... is the hidden truths of the real world... Don't be fooled...by the fairies...!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It looks like both the lamps in the pillars are broken.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Both of their light bulbs... are broken...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Maybe they were dropped on the floor. There's some sort of red stain on this lamp's surface.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">This stain... could it be...!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...That smell... There's no mistaking it. It's a bloodstain <thought>Bloodstained rock salt lamp - Someone's bloodstain was left on the rock salt lamp.</thought>...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ehhhh! Th-That's a bloodstain...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Why is there a bloodstain on this lamp? I wonder if this has something to do with the lamp bulb being broken... I should also take a look at the other lamp here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">The castle door is adorned with a beautiful cloth. I think this was the cloth that was in the castle.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Entrance ways are always beautiful... that's what a detective thinks.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Yes, after Detective Badd's shoes have trampled all over it... But, this is no time for snide remarks.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...This dessert made my shoes all dirty... If you come any closer... your shoes will be covered in cream too...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>We've already seen what's behind the door. There's no need to look again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">So this is where Delicia originally intended to put the lamps.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I don't get why she put them in the castle...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Since they're broken and don't light up, maybe she decided to put them out of the way?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...If she wanted them out of the way... There are many other places to store them.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">It's like that old saying, "Hide the salt in the sugar bag!"</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...I think the saying goes, "Hide a tree in the forest." If Delicia intended to use these lamps as decorations during the contest... It creates a contradiction with that piece of evidence. I need to deduce the contradiction at the scene...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Is this spot somehow connected to any of the evidence I hold...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Detective Badd, look at this. Don't you think it's strange?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I think what's strange... is your deduction.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Urgh...!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">If your brain isn't working right... then it's due to the lack of sugar... ...I'll sell you one of my lollipops... for two bucks.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>That sounds a tad high... Is there no evidence of a contradiction with the castle decorations?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Detective Badd. Please read the contest leaflet.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">....."Any decorations not made from desserts are prohibited." ...Huh.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">These rock salt lamps and the fluorescent cloths go against the rules <thought>Delicia broke the rules - Delicia used other objects besides desserts for her decorations.</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">So, maybe that's why they were hidden in the castle?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">I wonder about that... I think we should investigate further into Delicia's actions.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Unlike the other fairies, this one doesn't have a fluorescent cloth.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ms. Delicious! It's not right to leave one out!</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">I don't like it either. But... one fluorescent cloth and a machine has gone missing!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">You've lost a cloth... and a machine? What sort of machine is it?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Oi! Let me tell you! Each piece of fluorescent cloth is hooked up to one of these machines. The machine is called a rainbow light device... Light is sent through the cable and into the cloth, which is made of optic fibers. Just fiddle around with the settings a bit, and it will turn into all sorts of colors! When it glows red, it's like a raging inferno! And when it glows blue, you can almost feel the glittering cool ice! It's powered by a long-lasting battery that's resistant to changes in the temperature!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Um, I'm not very familiar with these kinds of devices...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Mr. Edgeworth. She's saying it's a machine that transmits light to the special cloth.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...I see. It's amazing what they come up with these days.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">So, one rainbow light device... and one fluorescent cloth are missing...?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yessie, that's right. Wherever could they be...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>This fluorescent cloth... could it be related to the case?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>One rainbow light device and one fluorescent cloth have gone missing. Could there be some connection to the case...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Delicia, why is the room temperature set to 68℉?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">The cold doesn't agree with me. Plus, it's bad for the body! This figure doesn't just maintain itself, you know! Naturally, as a lady, I want to look young forever.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I wonder... how old Ms. Delicious really is.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Raymond. A true gentleman never asks a woman her age.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">This room... is mainly filled with cream... And 50℉ is the recommended temperature for preserving fresh cream.</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">What, really? Now it's all gone to waste!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">It looks like Ms. Delicious didn't know <thought>Knowledge was lacking - Delicia seems lacking in the basic knowledge of dessert making.</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Hmph. I thought she was supposed to be a first-class pastry chef...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>The fake desserts and the rule violations. And now... her lack of basic knowledge. Looks like she keeps many secrets...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Oi! Looks like this caught your eye. The way this cloth works... Ah, I wonder if it's OK for me to tell you about it.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">...Sorry, I can't talk about this cloth!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>What...? That was strange. I wonder if Von Karma told her to say quiet about it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">A blue cloth... I like this relaxing color.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">As expected of Mr. Edgeworth! That's so old school! C'mon, let's hurry and make it glow!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Y... Yes. <thought>Does he mean I'm old-fashioned...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">The rainbow light device has made the cloth glow with light blue aura.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Speaking of which, one set of this cloth and device has gone missing. I wonder where it went to?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">I don't have the answer to that... but it could be related to the case.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ah! There are some switches over here!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">They probably control the color of the cloth. Raymond, try pressing one. The cloth has started to glow.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">It's so mesmerizing... I could look at it all day...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">This rock salt lamp doesn't light up.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Hm... It's a shame, but it appears to be broken.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Aww, I really wanted to see it light up... I wanted to experience the calming glow too!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Maybe I should try putting one in the office.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ugh... A vivid bloodstain was left behind... I can't believe the murder weapon came from inside the candy castle...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Raymond. If it's too difficult, you don't have to look at it.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I-I'm fine! I'm going to become a lawyer after all!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Heh... I see. <thought>You have a promising future...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">This rock salt lamp has a hexagonal base.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">The recess in the pillars must have been made to match this shape.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">After all, they fit the pillars in the candy castle perfectly!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">That's enough... investigating...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Hmph... We've found much more than I expected. <thought>And yet, something from before still bothers me. Prosecutor von Karma must have found the murder weapon in this room... So then, why did he let Delicia be? First, I must ascertain Von Karma's true motives...!</thought> Detective Badd. I would like to ask Prosecutor von Karma something.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I've also got business with him... And Delicia there too...</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Eep! What's the idea, Baddie? Don't glare at me like that.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>It seems Detective Badd also has his doubts about Delicia and Von Karma.</thought> Delicia, would you come with us for a moment?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yessie! That's... fine. What for?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...We have to find Von Karma. There are some things we need to talk about.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Prosecutor von Karma. We need to talk about the case.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Yes... We discovered the murder weapon in Delicia's room. ...It would seem Mr. Master isn't the only suspect in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Why is Von Karma so sure of himself...?</thought> Well then, aren't you going to explain? Why the murder weapon was in Delicia's room!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Mr. Master took the rock salt lamp...?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Do you have evidence that he moved it?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Wha...!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">He took the rock salt lamp from Delicia's room...?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">But, the murder weapon was found in Delicia's room. Doesn't that place suspicion on Delicia too?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">So, the murder weapon was the rock salt lamp hidden inside the candy castle?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...Why was it necessary for you to enter the castle?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ah! Maybe he's interested in candy castles?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...! I wasn't in charge of... the initial investigation...!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Detective Badd joined the investigation halfway through...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Wouldn't the body left behind in his room also be cause for suspicion? Moreover...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...That's exactly... what I'd like to say to you.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Are you saying that Mr. Master removed the murder weapon, and hid the body in the chest?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Eep! So savory!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Don't you mean... "so sorry"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">She shows no sign... of remorse.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">How can you conclude that Mr. Master is the killer without any evidence!?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Is there really no evidence pointing to anyone else at the crime scene? Surely there's room for further investigation...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Think back to the crime scene. If Mr. Master isn't the killer... There must have been something there incriminating someone else!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>It seems Von Karma won't be shaken easily. I'll just have to present evidence that contradicts his reasoning...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It's true that the murder weapon and bloodstains disappeared from the vicinity. However, there was still one piece of incriminating evidence left behind! Have a look at this photograph, which was taken when the body was first discovered. This cloth was used to wrap the body... Doesn't it remind you of the fluorescent cloth from Delicia's room?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Eep! My fluorescent cloth was at the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I guess Von Karma doesn't know about this cloth's secret.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">It looks like a normal cloth at first glance, but if you use this rainbow light device... ...you can make it glow!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Prosecutor von Karma... seems a little surprised.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I don't think it was the cloth's ability to glow that surprised him...</thought> ...One sheet of this fluorescent cloth is currently unaccounted for. Now, I'd like you to look at the color of the cloth in this photo. Don't you think it looks like the color of the fluorescent cloth before it's been lit up?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Both the rock salt lamp and the fluorescent cloth originally belonged to Delicia. Wouldn't it be natural to assume that this cloth was used to wrap the body?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...Prosecutor von Karma. I believe the present conditions give us much reason to suspect Delicia.</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Eep! Hold it, Greggy! Do you really suspect me?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">I don't yet know if you are the culprit. But, it is true that you're hiding something. Am I right?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Uu... That's...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...What's so funny?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...! <thought>What does he mean...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Wha...!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">..... <thought>Ngh... What's this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Wh-What? Was all our investigating for nothing... Ms. Delicious! Why didn't you tell us about your confiscated items?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Uuh... Well... Manny said I'd look suspicious if I did!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Prosecutor von Karma...?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">And it's true, you all suspect me, don't you!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Von Karma...! So that's why he let us investigate Delicia's room!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Two...?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">.....</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> I still have some doubts about the fluorescent cloth found in Mr. Master's room.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...Ngh...! <thought>I don't have enough information to refute Von Karma's reasoning...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Th-That's!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I can't give up yet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">There are still... some doubts left in our investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Detective Badd...!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">It's not my nature... to leave any doubts behind. There is still one piece of evidence... that has yet to be identified.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">.....! <thought>That's right... there are still the traces someone left behind!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">No. I also have some doubts about one piece of evidence. It's likely... That I have the same doubts Detective Badd has.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>This is the piece of evidence left in Mr. Master's room that has yet to be identified!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">We still do not know the true nature of this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...This is not... the same doubt I had...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>It wasn't this...!</thought> Please wait. I still have some doubts left.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Somebody left gloved fingermarks on one of Mr. Master's desserts.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">If these were the killer's fingermarks... ...then it's possible that the killer also didn't leave any fingerprints on the murder weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I gave them... permission to investigate...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I don't recall... you telling me not to let them in...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">*gulp*...!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">...This isn't good for Badd. I'm so glad I have a kind boss like Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Your salary review depends on how you perform here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Do you have evidence that those fingermarks were left by Master? And moreover... there are still a few points of suspicion surrounding Delicia.</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Uuh... Greggy. You still suspect me? I've already apologized for stealing a few bites...!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...I don't want to suspect you. However, I can't easily trust those who tell lies. You must still be hiding something!</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Uuh... Greggy is a bully...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Don't you know the temperature fresh cream must be kept at? You call yourself a dessert chef, but you lack even the most basic knowledge.</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Uuh... I'm sorry. For my lack of knowledge...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">In your case, it's not even about the lack of knowledge. In truth... you don't even know how to make desserts, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">We're not in court yet, but... very well. This evidence shows that Delicia can't make desserts.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">This is the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">That doesn't prove anything! What a rude boy!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Really... You are a rude boy.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Nnghhoooh!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">It's alright! Young people are allowed to make mistakes!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I'm nowhere near your age... Good grief.</thought> Well... Will you allow me to try again?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">The only things Delicia made were those that broke the rules.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Those were not the only fake desserts she made.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Her desserts may look like something out of a fairy tale at first glance... ...but in reality, they are nothing but mannequins, decorated with cream. Apart from the cream, they're all fake!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">This is not something one aiming to become the world's greatest pastry chef would do.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yes... My shoes... can attest to that...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Will that be enough to convince Prosecutor von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Once he sees what Delicia has done, he'll have no choice but to be convinced.</thought> Delicia... The fact that your actions could lead to you being a suspect is no laughing matter.</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Th-That's! I didn't murder...!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...Isn't it time you told us the whole truth? Who are you? And why were you indulging yourself in another contestant's work!?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">...Yessie... I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">The truth is... I'm not really a dessert chef, like I led you to believe. I'm actually a pharmacist.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">What! A pharmacist?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>That's a completely different occupation... It's no wonder he couldn't hide his surprise.</thought> Why is a pharmacist like you participating in this contest?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">...I just love eating desserts. I joined because I thought I'd be able to eat some of Jeffy's desserts. I never thought I'd end up making it to the finals.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...Even Prosecutor von Karma is at a loss for words.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">S-So that's the real reason why you entered the contest?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yessie... As expected, Jeffy's desserts were oh-so-good.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">So... The gloved fingermarks on the picture frame... were your doing?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Eep! No way! I never wore gloves!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Delicia's fingerprints were found on Mr. Master's chocolates. So it is true that she wasn't wearing gloves.</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yessie! Exactly! You do believe me, Greggy!</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Eep! Sorry, Manny.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...I think it's her belly that's stuffed.</thought> Were Master's desserts all that you ate?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">...Actually, no. After the afternoon tea, I also ate Icy's desserts...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">! You mean you entered the victim's room?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yessie! Exactly. The room was empty after all.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Perhaps the victim was already dead by then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Delicia">But my first bite tasted way too salty and I couldn't eat it! So, I ate the delicious star-shaped dessert that was nearby.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ms. Delicious... You really are a glutton.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Is it rare you see a woman with this kind of appetite.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Delicia">That's all I did. Greggy, Manny, everyone... I'm sorry I caused you trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Now that you've told us the truth, everything's fine. There's no need to apologize.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Prosecutor von Karma. I'd like to go as well. I also need to ascertain whether my reasoning up until now has been correct.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...That's enough for me.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">The desserts adorning the victim's room had disappeared without a trace. Was this the true killer's doing? A body that was hidden inside a dessert, and a murder weapon that was moved... Further investigation would be required to arrive at the truth of this case.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">...Oops, I guess I went on for a little too long there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Something like that... happened? I had no idea. None of the case files I read went into such detail.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Well, I doubt there would be anything in there that would be inconvenient to the prosecution. Especially with that Von Karma at the head.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How did the investigation go from there?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">The desserts had disappeared from the victim's room, so the investigation hit a rough patch. Thanks to that, it took about a whole year before a verdict was handed down.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">One whole year...?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">This was before the whole 3-day pre-trial system was established. Trial didn't need to finish in the short amount of time that they do now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I see. Did they ever find out why the victim's dessert disappeared?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Well, kinda... His dessert was like a candy ice sculpture, made from sherbet... Since it was made from ice, the general consensus was that it had melted. ...However, that might not quite be the case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">This museum used to be Mr. Master's mansion.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The stage of the IS-7 Incident...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">And in this very place, they're exhibiting the "Sherbet Salon" from 18 years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! The victim's dessert...?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Yep. Though it could be just a replica of the original. That's why Uncle Ray had to come today, to check it out. ...And for your old man, too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.....</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Now then! Let's get a move on and check out the room! I'm pretty sure it's over in the "Winter Palace." Hmm... The Winter Palace should be... Huh? It's... locked up. That's odd. They've already opened the museum.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Mr. Shields. According to the pamphlet we received at the entrance, the Winter Palace is over here.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Really? I could've sworn it was this one. Alright, let's scoot. We gotta confirm the truth of what happened 18 years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Man... It's still as cold as ever. Uncle Ray's gonna freeze solid.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems the "Winter Palace" lives up to its name. It's like a freezer in here. <thought>With the light dimmed like this, it's almost as if the room itself is made of ice...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">I think the control panel for the room temperature is on the back wall. Miles, why don't you check what temperature it's set at for me? Uncle Ray's gonna give the curator a piece of his mind later. It's way too cold in here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm... Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">But if you want to look around the room a bit, feel free to stay, or freeze, to your heart's content. I'll get the camera ready. I want to take some pictures of this place and show it to your old man.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Understood.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>For some reason, a giant block of ice is on display. There's a description written on the surface... Castor and Pollux. Every December, large meteor showers appear in the direction of these two stars...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woman">.....And so, Mask☆DeMasque...</line>
<line speaker="Man">...And then, I...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Those two are being rather noisy and distracting. It can't be helped. I should go look at another exhibit.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woman">...Well, how about this? I'll yell out... "Mask☆DeMasque is here!"</line>
<line speaker="Man">Yes! It's meeeeeeee! I'm Mask☆DeMasque!</line>
<line speaker="Woman">Good, good... Wait, Ronnie! If you say that, you'll get arrested! C'mon, if we don't plan properly, we won't be able to sell it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What are these two talking about...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hmm. Mr. Shields. I can't find the temperature control panel.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ah, right. They keep it where it's hard to find. Just one moment. Huh? It's locked. Makes sense. They wouldn't want the guests changing the temperature themselves.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">According to the pamphlet, the Winter Palace has a temperature of 27℉.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Brrrr! Now that is cold. Uncle Ray's going to freeze to death! Guess I'll need to find someone to share body heat with. Preferably a beautiful lady.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.....</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Oh! Are you trying to freeze me to death as well with those cold eyes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course not.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">...Miles. Can I ask you something?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Is it okay... to take photos in this room?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What! Haven't you checked? ...But, if you haven't gotten any warnings about it, then it should be fine.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ah, sorry. Well, to be honest, I would've taken some anyway. Your old man had always wanted to investigate this "Winter Palace" after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...If my father had seen this room, would he have found something? If he had, the results of the trial might have also... No, there's no point in thinking that now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There are two sculptures displayed here...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">These sculptures are replicas of the desserts that vanished 18 years ago. ...Impressive, huh. These sculptures made of ice.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... <thought>My father never got to see these ice sculptures. And now... 18 years later, I'm standing before them.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">...Miles. Sorry to bother you while you're deep in thought. Could you turn this way a little?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...? Like this?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Yes, yes. Like that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! Mr Shields, you're not...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Say "cheese!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Mr Shields, please don't take pictures of me.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">He he he. Sorry, my bad. I just wanted to make sure the camera works okay.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That camera... looks quite old.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Yeah, well, that's because it's an old-fashioned camera. You know, an instant camera. It automatically develops the photos after shooting. Pretty cool, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I know... Though I've never used one.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">He he he. You're quite the know-it-all. You really are the old man's son. Er, could you move a bit? I want to take some more photos of the room.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>His face has taken on an unusually serious expression. He's probably thinking about the IS-7 Incident...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Man. I snapped a bunch! And they're already developed, see?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...He shoved them in my face before I could reply.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Well, I have one more question for you, Mr. Know-It-All! Do you know what these two sculptures represent?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They're sculptures of Taurus and Gemini from the "winter constellations".</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ooh! Bingo! Not bad, Miles. That's probably why they call this room the "Winter Palace". Uncle Ray is feeling generous today, so I'll give you a copy of this photo too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Uh... Th-Thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Are these replicas of the constellation desserts that were made 18 years ago?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Yeah. It looks like these two sculptures are also made out of sherbet. Uncle Ray's only seen the real sculptures in photos... ...but these sculptures look like the real deal.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This was what you wanted to show me?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Yeah... I think your old man would have wanted you to see it as well. I'm sorry. Uncle Ray didn't have the courage to come here alone.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Don't apologize. This was a good opportunity to learn about my father's case.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">That means a lot to me. So, you want me to take another commemorative photo?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To create something like this out of sherbet... Even reproducing it would require considerable technique. The glass case seems to be lit up from the inside. If those stanchions weren't there, I could get a closer look.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This rock salt lamp is lighting up the constellation chart. I see... Gemini and Taurus are constellations that can be seen in the winter. Since this is the Winter Palace, perhaps that explains the winter constellations made of sherbet. According to the pamphlet, the other palaces are made of crystal. But for the Summer Palace, I think it'd be more fitting if it were made out of shaved ice... Well, no, that would make it exactly the same as this room... Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Miles, since we came all the way here, why don't you take a look around?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, since this room is so cold, I thought I'd go to a warmer room...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">If you're that cold, why don't you borrow my clothes? And in exchange, I'll borrow your jacket.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...No thanks. <thought>Let's try enduring this for just a little longer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's a boy with a school bag. Did he come to the art gallery... by himself?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Hmm... She even quit her job in order to run this museum. I don't really get it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Perhaps... one of his parents knows the curator?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A giant block of ice is being displayed here. It appears to be quite heavy... No, the inside must be hollow. On the surface, there is an image of the stars and a written description. The Pleiades... also known as the Seven Sisters. A star cluster that comprises a part of Taurus.</thought> But, for all these stars to be grouped together as a cluster... The ways of the ancient people must have been very imprecise.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Alrighty, now that I've got some pictures of this room, let's check out the other places. Might as well see them all, since we're already here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I suppose you're right.</line>
<line speaker="???">AAAAAAAAAAHHHHH!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! That yell just now...!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">It came from the Fountain Patio! Let's go, Miles!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's someone passed out on the floor! And that man there is...!</thought> Larry! What are you doing here!? No, I'm getting ahead of myself. What exactly happened here?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">E-Edgeyyyyy! I... I saw something that no one should ever have to see! Agaaain!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Larry, calm down! Why is there someone passed out here?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I-I didn't do anything! He just fell down all of a sudden!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">! This man... He can't be...!</line>
<line speaker="???">Excuse me, but what is the matter here?</line>
<line speaker="???">You can't raise such a ruckus in the museum, boys.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? This scent is...!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Seems like he's still breathing, but this is a bad situation...! Miles, it's not safe here! Get everyone out of here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Everyone, get away from that room right now! There's... poison gas coming out from it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm. Mr. Shields. How is the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">It looks like he breathed in a little too much of that poison gas... He's still unconscious. According to the doctor in the ambulance, there are no external injuries or any other wounds. Thanks to our fortunate timing, we were able to save him before he was too far gone... ...but he's not out of the woods yet. He's currently being treated by a specialist in the infirmary.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... Mr. Shields, is he an acquaintance of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Yeah, you could say that. He's Dane Gustavia. He was involved in the IS-7 Incident.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The pastry chef? <thought>So he was involved in the case 18 years ago.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">At least the other guy is doing alright. Is he a friend of yours, Miles?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes, you could say that. It is unfortunate you were not hurt, Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">What's "you could say that" supposed to mean, Edgey!? How could you treat a childhood friend like that? That's just cruel! And also, when I'm dressed like this, I'm called Laurice Deauxnim, y'know. So don't call me "Larry," It's "Laurice!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This man is Larry Butz. He's nothing but trouble, but he's been one of my friends since grade school. Some time ago, he awakened to the calling of art and assumed the alias "Laurice Deauxnim"... ...but a Butz by any other name would smell just as much.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Really? You two are childhood friends? I better report that to your old man, too. I'm sure it will bring him joy. He was always worried about you not being able to make friends.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Good for you, Edgey! Aren't you glad to have a bosom buddy like me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>My father was worried about something like that...?</thought> But anyway, what are you doing in a place like this, Larry?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">How many times do I have to tell you, Edgey!? I'm "Laurice"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What. Are you doing. In a place. Like this!?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yikes! Don't glare at me when you talk!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So are you going to tell me?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Isn't it obvious? I've come here to study art! I'm going to take Mandy on a date here, so I was just doing some scouting beforehand!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Aren't you just using art as an excuse to go on a date...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Not bad, Laurice! Maybe you can introduce some pretty girls to me next time.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Oh, now you're talkin' my language, dude!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I think I'm getting a headache.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">By the way, Laurice... Did you notice anything strange when you found the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Nah... not really.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nothing that would make you say, "I saw something that no one should ever have to see"?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Oh, yeah... That. I was just surprised when I saw that old dude fall down out of nowhere like that. I didn't do anything this time, for once!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Is that anything to brag about!?</line>
<line speaker="???">Visitors, we wish to deeply apologize for the disturbance. I am the curator of this museum. My name is Katherine Hall.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She's also one of the people involved in the IS-7 Incident...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hello there, Ms. Kate.</line>
<line speaker="Kate">Monsieur Shields, thank you for your continued assistance.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She was the woman we saw at the reception. So she's the curator here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kate">We apologize for the inconvenience, especially since it's the opening day...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">No, no. You don't have to apologize for a thing, Ms. Kate. Ah... I almost forgot. Let me introduce you to someone. This is Miles Edgeworth. ...He's Gregory Edgeworth's son.</line>
<line speaker="Kate">Oh! Monsieur Edgeworth's...! ♬ Oh! How wonderfuuuuuul! I meeeet the soooooon... Afteeer eighteeeeen years...! ♪ ♪ It is an honor to meet youuu! Deefeensee attooorneyyyy Miles Edgewooooooorth! ♬</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Wow, that was amazing! You still got that golden voice, Ms. Kate.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Actually, I'm a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Kate">Oh, so you are a prosecutor? My most sincere apologies, Monsieur Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This woman is very polite, but... slightly odd.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">U-Uh... Katey! Could I get your autograph right here, pretty please?</line>
<line speaker="Kate">Yes... if you so desire.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why do you want her autograph?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Hey! Don't tell me... You don't know who she is?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">My, my. You really don't keep up with the entertainment news, do you, Miles?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What...? What is this unbearable atmosphere!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">She's a superstar actress who's been in tons of musicals and movies. She's a great singer too.</line>
<line speaker="Kate">*giggle*... Currently, I am the curator of this museum. I have already retired from the stage. I finished filming my role for my last movie a few days ago. My costars also said that they would come here once I opened the doors. ...And here you are, Monsieur Artiste. I return this to you.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Thanks a bunch, Katey! I'll treasure it for the rest of my life!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Well, well. Looks like me and Laurice share the same interests.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...So I gathered.</thought> Larry, you said you're here to study art. Why don't you practice drawing as well? ...Since you're here at Ms. Hall's art museum.</line>
<line speaker="Kate">Oh! It would be an honor to have Monsieur Artiste sketch our exhibits.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Oh, I guess even you have some good ideas every now and then, Edgey! I'll do a bit of sketching for Katey here!</line>
<line speaker="Kate">Hee hee... what an amusing person.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Forgive the disturbance. Incidentally, who was the woman that was with you earlier?</line>
<line speaker="Kate">That was Madame Delicia Scones. She is currently assisting in the treatment of Monsieur Gustavia in the infirmary. Even though I said "infirmary", since this is an art museum now, it is only provisional. As I am the only staff member working here, I cannot take a leave of my duties for too long.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Delicia Scones... I believe we have heard that name before, Mr. Shields.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Yep. Looks like the whole gang from the IS-7 Incident is here. Well. ...I doubt that's a coincidence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Kate">...Monsieur Shields. Monsieur Edgeworth. Would you care for some hot tea?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Oh! Ms. Kate's tea. That takes me back.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Kate">Now, I must take my leave. I must explain the situation to the other visitors.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Alright, thanks for everything.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This smells like... Ceylon tea. I should drink it before it cools.</thought> Oh... This Ceylon tea is of very high quality. And this aroma of citrus...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">"Does wonders for your concentration," right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">He he he, your old man said the exact same thing 18 years ago. But the saucers back then were chilled. Today they're warm.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hmm. A-Anyway... Don't you think this current situation is rather unusual?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">You mean how everyone involved in the case 18 years ago has gathered at this museum?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. I would like to be in charge of this case, if at all possible...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth, sir! Are you OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! Mr. Shields! I came here as fast as I could when I heard that you were done in by the poison gas!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ohh! My sweet honey Kay! How about a hug after being parted for so long?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">No. Geez! So you're perfectly fine? I can't believe you made us worry so much!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe... What is the meaning of bringing Kay here?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-I'm sorry, sir! I knew the gas was dangerous, so I tried to stop her... But no matter how much I ran and ran and and ran and ran, I couldn't gain any ground...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...He he heh, when it comes to running away, no one is faster than the Yatagarasu!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>But you weren't running away from here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth, I'm all set, sir! I'll start investigating the crime scene! Since there might still be traces of gas in the room, I'll have to ask everyone to wait here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very well. I'm counting on you.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Good luck in there, flatfoot!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow. Gummy's so cool! He's just like a detective!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...But that's what he is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes, Edgeworth here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! It looks like the poison gas has dissipated, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective, calmly explain the state of the Autumn Palace.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yessir! I'll start with the exhibits. On the left, there's a statue with two people. And on the right, there's a statue of an animal with two horns.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A statue of two people and a statue of an animal with horns... Isn't that the exact same thing I saw in the Winter Palace just a while ago...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Also, the room is wet with water thanks to the sprinkler system! That also prevented the gas from harming everyone else.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The sprinkler system... Was there a fire in the room?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There are no signs of a fire, and the fire alarm hasn't gone off either, sir. The sprinklers in this museum are the kind that detects both smoke and fire. If it detects smoke, it will send an alert to the security room. I think the poison gas might have set off the alarm in the security room, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Was there anyone in the security room at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The only one working here is the curator, Ms. Katherine Hall, sir. She has been in the reception booth, opposite the security room ever since the museum opened.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Did Ms. Hall turn on the sprinklers?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The sprinkler system can only be operated manually from the security room, sir. If it had been automatic, it would have sprayed water all over the exhibits. Since the system is manual, the situation can be examined and the exhibits moved if need be.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I guess there would be more priority over the exhibits than the building. Only at a museum.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Brrrr... But it's way too cold in this room, sir! Isn't this supposed to be the Autumn Palace? It feels more like the dead of winter in here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Autumn Palace... is "cold"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I checked the thermostat earlier, and it was set to 27℉! I couldn't believe it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why would the Autumn Palace be set to the same temperature as the Winter Palace...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's about all I know for now, sir. If I figure out anything else, I'll give you another call!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. I'm counting on you, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What did Gummy say?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...He said it feels more like winter in the Autumn Palace.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">? I don't get it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I haven't been able to enter the room personally... ...but it should be possible to look inside ater the police have finished investigating.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hmm. I'd like to know what it's like in there myself.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Isn't there anyone else who knows about the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Aah! There is someone! Miles' friend, right!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Friend...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Though he's such a nuisance, we have no choice but to listen to what he has to say for now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wait, you mean...!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Oh! You're here too Kay! You're looking as cute as ever!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eheheh. Long time no see! It's Larry... isn't it!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">...Kay, right now my name is "Laurice"... I'm an artist, that's why.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah, so that's your pen name! Laurice, the artist formerly known as Larry!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Wow, you really are a good girl, Kay! ...Nothing like Edgey here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..... Larry. I have many things I need to ask you.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">What's this! Don't tell me you suspect me again! You're gonna say because I was first on the scene, I must be the culprit, aren't you!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I never said anything like that. I only want you to tell me what you saw. You said you "saw something that no one should ever have to see", did you not?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">BUUUUT! Now I'm saying I didn't see nothing, and I didn't do nothing! ....Probably.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Oh my, he didn't seem so confident at the end there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...There are somewhat troublesome circumstances surrounding this man. The saying "When something smells, it's usually the Butz" still holds true, 26 years on. One could say his tendency to attract trouble is legendary. <thought>It seems he's done something troublesome, without even realizing it himself... ...I'll just have to try and extract the truth from him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">My goal is to expose whatever Larry is hiding. However...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I didn't see nothing, I didn't do nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Larry is an extremely restless and troublesome man. Until he cools down, I'll just wait and see.</thought> First, I'll ask him about his goal. This isn't something I can't handle. I'll finish this quickly.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What was your purpose for coming to the art gallery?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">What!? Are you saying that I don't belong in an art gallery!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Larry! The statement you just made is full of problems!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">What's with you Edgey? Isn't that the case... with all my statements!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">H-He's suddenly serious...! <thought>That was an unnecessary statement.</thought> I must read my opponent's reactions and feelings, and strike with the right words!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Hey! If you're not gonna talk, hold that pose so I can paint your portrait! And then, I'll scribble all over the portrait I drew of you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Larry! The statement you just made is full of problems!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">What's with you Edgey? Isn't that the case... with all my statements!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">H-He's suddenly serious...! <thought>That was an unnecessary statement.</thought> I must read my opponent's reactions and feelings, and strike with the right words!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I-I was just joking. I would never scribble over my paintings, of course. They're works of art, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't think any of your works would qualify as "art".</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Don't look down on me! There are people who recognize my skills as an artist!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Larry! The statement you just made is full of problems!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">What's with you Edgey? Isn't that the case... with all my statements!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">H-He's suddenly serious...! <thought>That was an unnecessary statement.</thought> I must read my opponent's reactions and feelings, and strike with the right words!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Mandy is my girlfriend, but it's really my paintings she fell in love with! That's why, I'll sketch anything my girlfriend likes!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then, why are you here on your own today?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">So what! Can't a guy with a girlfriend spend some time alone!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Larry! The statement you just made is full of problems!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">What's with you Edgey? Isn't that the case... with all my statements!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">H-He's suddenly serious...! <thought>That was an unnecessary statement.</thought> I must read my opponent's reactions and feelings, and strike with the right words!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Mandy said she's a Gemini. I thought she'd be happy if I showed her a sketch of it on our next date.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you really have that much confidence in the sketch?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Well... I'm not so confident about this one. But I thought she would be happy... if I did a sketch of her astrological sign.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...........</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Huh? What? If you're not gonna talk, I'm going back to my sketching!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait! <thought>I was too passive there...</thought> I must read my opponent's reactions and feelings, and strike with the right words!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... I see. That's just like you. To impress Mandy, you came here to see the Gemini Sculpture, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">WH-WHAAAAAAAAAT! How'd you find out!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Because you just unknowingly told me everything!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">W-Well then, I'm not saying another word from now on!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He's finally decided to remain silent. In that case, I'll be more relentless in my questioning. I'll try to find out what he was doing here at the art gallery. I'll expose his true motives. This shouldn't take long!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You... just what did you do in this art gallery!?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Wh-What's with that glare...!? I-I don't really remember anything. I didn't have a pamphlet... so I just loitered around the Fountain Patio.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...........</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Huh? What? If you're not gonna talk, I'm going back to my sketching!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait! <thought>I was too passive there...</thought> I must read my opponent's reactions and feelings, and strike with the right words!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't they give you a pamphlet at the reception booth after you pay the admission fee?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Huh? Oh... is that right? So... the admission wasn't free, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...........</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Huh? What? If you're not gonna talk, I'm going back to my sketching!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait! <thought>I was too passive there...</thought> I must read my opponent's reactions and feelings, and strike with the right words!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't tell me... you sneaked in here without paying!?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I'm sooooooooorry! I-I didn't mean to do anything bad! I-It's just... there was no one at the reception booth... That's why... I thought you could come in here for free!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...........</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Huh? What? If you're not gonna talk, I'm going back to my sketching!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait! <thought>I was too passive there...</thought> I must read my opponent's reactions and feelings, and strike with the right words!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Hall wasn't at the reception booth?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yeah. It didn't look like there was anyone on the other side of the desk.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Come to think of it... Gumshoe did say something about that. Ms. Hall was busy activating the sprinklers from the security room. Because of the incident, she had to leave the reception booth.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Poor Katey... She went to all that trouble to open up the palace. And now, the art gallery's star attraction, the "Winter Palace" is completely ruined...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...........</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Huh? What? If you're not gonna talk, I'm going back to my sketching!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait! <thought>I was too passive there...</thought> I must read my opponent's reactions and feelings, and strike with the right words!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're certainly well-informed about the Winter Palace, for someone without a pamphlet. The Winter Palace is where your goal, the Gemini Sculpture, is located... You had your sights set on the Winter Palace from the beginning, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Whaaaaaaaat? H-How'd you find me out again!? That's right! My goal was to see the Gemini Sculpture! From the very beginning, the Winter Palace was the very reason why I came here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He confessed quite easily... You can never tell anything with this man. Next, I'll ask for further information regarding the Winter Palace. ...He may still have some fight left in him. I'll watch his reactions, and extract the information I need!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Larry... Did you also enter the Winter Palace?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Wh-What's with... that look of distrust...!? Sure, I tried going in, but...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...........</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Huh? What? If you're not gonna talk, I'm going back to my sketching!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait! <thought>I was too passive there...</thought> I must read my opponent's reactions and feelings, and strike with the right words!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You tried to go in... but you weren't actually able to, right?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yeah... that's about right. I wanted to go in, but... Then that old geezer collapsed... I was a little freaked out.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...........</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Huh? What? If you're not gonna talk, I'm going back to my sketching!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait! <thought>I was too passive there...</thought> I must read my opponent's reactions and feelings, and strike with the right words!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you couldn't get in because the victim of the poison gas collapsed?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yeah. He fell right out of the Winter Palace.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm? I'm sure the victim emerged from the Autumn Palace...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">If it weren't for that poison gas incident... ...I'd be in there sketching the Gemini Sculpture right now!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Larry must have mistaken the Autumn Palace for the Winter Palace... That aside, it seems his goal was to sketch the sculpture. Heh... this should be a useful clue.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've run this line of questioning to its conclusion... Let's try another line of attack.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Larry. Did you see anything in the Winter Palace?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">You're still hung up on that? Didn't I say that I didn't see anything? I started to think that it wasn't such a good idea to come to the art gallery. I needed to leave soon to meet with my girlfriend.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hmm. I don't have enough clues to proceed with this line of questioning. Maybe I should try another line of attack...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have no more use for you... Leave, now!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">...Huh? Really? You're actually letting me go? Well, I need to go to meet Mandy anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait! That was a mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Edgey! You need to take responsibility for what you say!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnghhooooooh! <thought>I'm being lectured by HIM!</thought> Please... I'd like to ask you a few more questions.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">...Fine. But you'll have to treat me to dinner.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh... <thought>I need to be careful not to make careless statements...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps I should try using that clue...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...........</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Huh? What? If you're not gonna talk, I'm going back to my sketching!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait! <thought>I was too passive there...</thought> I must read my opponent's reactions and feelings, and strike with the right words!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You came here to sketch the sculpture for your girlfriend, did you not? I don't think you would give up that easily! Even after the victim collapsed, you could still see inside the room from the outside, right?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">W-Well, I may have gotten a tiny glimpse, but... ...there's no evidence... that I saw something scary in there, right...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Larry! The statement you just made is full of problems!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">What's with you Edgey? Isn't that the case... with all my statements!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">H-He's suddenly serious...! <thought>That was an unnecessary statement.</thought> I must read my opponent's reactions and feelings, and strike with the right words!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...........</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Huh? What? If you're not gonna talk, I'm going back to my sketching!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait! <thought>I was too passive there...</thought> I must read my opponent's reactions and feelings, and strike with the right words!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">My, my... I'm disappointed it turned out to be this simple. Larry. You saw "something scary" at the crime scene, didn't you!?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">U-Uw-waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah! Edgey! You! Can you read my mind!? In that case... there's no point in keeping any more secrets from you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You just told me everything of your own accord. That was a complete waste of time, but, finally... It's checkmate.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I had my eyes fixed on the Gemini Sculpture...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You've mentioned the Gemini Sculpture many times now, but... I don't believe the sculpture you saw was the Gemini one.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Wh-What!? Was it a mirage then?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Larry mistakenly thought he saw the Winter Palace.</thought> This piece of evidence shows what Larry really saw!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence shows what you really saw!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">...Y'know, you really shouldn't put that much faith in your sense of aesthetics. If you'd like, I could teach you a thing or two about art.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh...! I-It's fine! <thought>So it's not this piece of evidence... Larry mistakenly thought he saw the Winter Palace. But what he saw was not the Gemini Sculpture from the Winter Palace! I must have evidence that proves that...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Take a look at this pamphlet. In the Autumn Palace... The Pisces, Capricorn, Aries, and Aquarius sculptures are displayed. Incidentally, I can confirm that the Gemini Sculpture is located in the Winter Palace. Therefore, the sculpture you saw could not have been the Gemini one!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">......I knew it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Hm. I expected him to be a bit more shocked at the news...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">I thought it was kinda strange. I know I saw a single goddess. ...And that transformation was no mirage.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..."Transformation", you say?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Oh! You're curious too, Edgey? Well, nothing for it, guess I'll have to show you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Show me? What, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I drew a picture of the very scene I saw back then! But, I really can't believe what I drew.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Picture, what picture?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">This one, right here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh... What! What is this disturbing picture!? Is that sculpture weeping tears of blood?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Laurice! ...This picture is scary!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Kay! It scared me too! This Gemini Sculpture suddenly transformed into a goddess right before my eyes. I couldn't help but scream.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...So the victim collapsing wasn't what surprised him.</thought> What do you mean when you say "transformed"?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I don't really understand it myself! The lower half of its body just turned into a fish!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">A fish goddess... That would be the Pisces Sculpture, wouldn't it. In mythology, Pisces represents the fish that a goddess and her son transform into.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Really! So Pisces isn't just a couple of ordinary fish?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Edgey... you don't think that sculpture is cursed, do you? Those tears of blood turned the Gemini Sculpture into a fish.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Preposterous. You simply mistook the Pisces Sculpture for the Gemini one.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh. You put the sketch in your Organizer?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Even a sketch like this can be used as scrap paper, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">How could you!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">But, it's strange. Why did only the lower half of the sculpture transform? Uncle Ray is a bit curious about what went on in the Autumn Palace.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Indeed... I wonder if someone tampered with the Pisces Sculpture.</thought> Yes. Edgeworth here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! We've finished searching the room! The poison gas isn't a threat anymore, so you can enter the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Right. Good work, Detective. ...It seems we can enter the Autumn Palace now.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Nice timing, Mr. Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Let's go right now! I wanna see the Pisces Sculpture!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">If Kay's going, I'm going too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I was planning on bringing him along anyway.</thought> Right then, let's proceed to the Autumn Palace.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So this is the Autumn Palace... <thought>It certainly does resemble the Winter Palace.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I've been waiting, sir! ...Huh? Aren't you... that Harry Butz guy!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Wrong! I'm Laurice Deauxnim!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.....Never mind that, Detective. Your report, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Roger that, sir! Err... We discovered a used gas burner during our investigation. The nozzle was still warm when we found it, so it may be related to the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hmm. <thought>Was it used to heat something?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Was that ladder always there on the ground?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It was probably used by the person who set off the poison gas. The poison gas was released when someone lifted the lid off that glass case, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm...?&#160;! The Pisces Sculpture...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? Seems like you know about it, sir. Well then, do you know what the sculpture next to it is?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Since we're in the Autumn Palace, it would probably be the Capricorn Sculpture.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">As expected of Mr. Edgeworth! I thought it was Taurus myself. I was thrown off as it was covered by this weird cloth!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">The fluorescent cloth! I wonder what it's doing here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Evidence from the IS-7 Incident...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No matter what it is or how it got here... The sculptures in this room are all covered with this fluorescent cloth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A blue cloth... I guess this kind of relaxing color is nice once in awhile.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Miles. You're starting to sound like your old man.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I don't want to hear that from Mr. Shields...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The cloth is glowing with a light blue aura.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">According to the detective's report, it was wrapped around the statue like this.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...So it would seem. <thought>How is this related to our case?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">According to Mr. Shields, this allows you to change the color of the cloth. Let me try it out. Hmm. The cloth has started to glow.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And because they're hidden, it makes me want to see them even more.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Let's take a look! I'll just get this cloth off.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow! They're beautiful!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You don't think... the "transformation" Larry saw... Was, in fact, the moment the cloth wrapped around the lower half of Pisces fell...?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">See, Edgey! It wasn't a mirage or a mistake after all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hey... Miles. There sure is something strange about this room. It looks exactly the same as the Winter Palace we were in just a moment ago.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes. I agree. Perhaps the sculptures were hidden to make it look like the Winter Palace. If you wrap the cloth around the lower half of the Pisces Sculpture, it looks like Gemini.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Capricorn is a half-fish too. Hide the lower half and it resembles Taurus. The remaining two, which couldn't be altered with trickery, were covered up.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Autumn Palace was made to look like the Winter Palace. So it seems... Mr. Shields. It looks like we'll need to conduct an investigation of the Autumn Palace too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Debeste and Judge Courtney...!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Hey, hey, hey! You guys again!? This is a problem. You see, this is MY crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Mr. Edgeworth... it seems my power is insufficient. If you're here, then it would appear that you still haven't understood my warnings.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Furthermore... you know full well your reckless actions will cause trouble for that detective. In the name of the Goddess of Law, I must pass judgement.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You've got it all wrong, pal! I was the one who asked Mr. Edgeworth to investigate!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Really? Well then, flatfoot, I'll have to do "that".</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">"That"...?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Yeah, "that"... err. Right! Cut your salary! Looking forward to your next payday!? I've always wanted to say that!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Uugh... You're the last person I want cutting my salary, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hold it, Debeste. I am only cooperating with the police as a witness to this incident. ...Detective Gumshoe is not to blame.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Hmmm. So that's how it is. Well then, should I be raising his salary?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...No, that's not what I meant.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But, it would be really nice to get my salary raised.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Your mercy is deeply moving, Sebastian. But past transgressions must lead to future judgement. Prosecutor Edgeworth, and all in his company. Depart at once from this holy site.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">B-But that's! We only just got here!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">The one given the Goddess of Law's blessing for this incident was Sebastian.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In other words, Mr. Debeste is the prosecutor in charge of this case...</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">That's right, Mr. Edgeworth. Your opening performance is over! Besides, I've already got my eyes set on the culprit!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whaaaaaaat!? Wh-Who, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Well, naturally! ...That artist!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">M... Me? Hey! What's going on Edgey!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't ask me. I can't understand his reasoning.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Tsk tsk tsk... If you can't understand how the best prosecutor thinks, it simply shows how inculpable you are.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It seems he doesn't know what "inculpable" even means...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...That's right, Sebastian. Prosecutor Edgeworth is quite "incapable".</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Umm. Yes! He's incapable!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...She just nonchalantly corrected him.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Don't underestimate my intelligence gathering skills! I just came from the infirmary and asked the doctor there... ...about the cause of the poison gas!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...And what was the cause?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Err. Some "normal" substance... What was its name again? H-Hold on a second. I'll call the doctor to make sure.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Since Sebastian is on the phone, I'll answer for him.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...In that case why didn't you tell us before he called?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">The poison gas was caused by the mixing of two different types of chemicals. Their names are Normallium and Fatallium.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So, what are those chemicals exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Normallium is a red liquid that's commonly used in everyday products. It can be found in paint and detergent, among other things, but it is not toxic by itself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...So you're saying that it's a substance readily available to anyone.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Yes. But Fatallium, on the other hand, is not so easy to obtain.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Its name sure sounds dangerous. What's it used for?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">It is the active ingredient of a white pesticide known as Megatoxin X. Fatallium itself also has a deep white color, but it's not readily sold in stores. It's nearly impossible to obtain domestically. Right now, we are looking into how this chemical was obtained.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">OK! I've finally found out the names of those chemicals!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Judge Courtney has already told us. We don't need to hear it again.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Eh. ...Fine, then. I'll cut to the chase! You know that Normallium from the poison gas is also used in paint, right? Today, out of everyone who visited the art gallery, the only one carrying paint... ...was that artist!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Y-You're treating me as the culprit just because of that!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">I object... to the red paint on the palette you're carrying!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Hey, Edgey... Don't you think this prosecutor is kind of an idiot?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. Although I've known him for a short time, his logic is always absurd.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Hey! Don't ignore me!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">It's alright, Sebastian. They're only doing it because they're afraid of you. Like the first star to appear at night, show us reasoning that shines the best.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">The first star shines best... Not bad. Hey, you guys better listen up too!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">That artist was the "first" to discover the victim, so naturally he's the "best" suspect!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">...So! What do you think, Justine?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...We cannot ignore the possibility. Well then, Mr. Artist. Please tell us the truth. Did you leave red paint at the crime scene? Or else... Did you cause the poison gas to go off?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">The only thing I leave behind is my "bond of love" with you...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...Please watch what you say. My gavel is already prepared to declare you guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please pay no heed to this man's statements.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Hey, hey, you guys! Ignoring my reasoning just because it's flawless won't do you any good. Mr. Edgeworth, if you've already admitted defeat, you should take your leave!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Even though I don't really have time to deal with your ridiculous reasoning...</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">That artist was the "first" to discover the victim, so naturally he's the "best" suspect!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed, at first glance this man seems suspicious, however...</line>
<line speaker="Debeste"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">At "first" glance...? Ugh... What's with that "first" all of a sudden! You! Are you trying to steal my spot as the star that shines "best"!?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Huh? Would that make me the "best" artist?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Larry! Don't make this any more confusing than it already is! Mr. Debeste, continue your reasoning, now!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">The poison gas was caused by Normallium, a chemical found in paint, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Apparently, Normallium is used in many everyday products.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Right! So the red paint is definitely suspicious!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But, it's also used in things other than paint, right?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Hm. I guess you have a point. ...What do you think, Justine?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">That's right. Normallium is also used in detergent, for example.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In other words... it might not have been paint that caused the gas.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Th-That's not true! Let me finish my reasoning!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">As he was carrying paint near the victim, he would've had the "best" chance.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even if paint is the cause of the poison gas, that does not mean he is guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Ha ha! Well then, if the paint is NOT the cause, that doesn't mean he's innocent either!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Now he's just trying to sound clever. Mimicking what Mr. Edgeworth says won't make you look cool at all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Kay, please don't make my statements look bad.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Now then! It's about time... to wrap up my shining logic!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">The paint, along with being the first witness! ...That pretty much proves he's the culprit!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you truly claim that Larry is the culprit based on just that?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Huh? You got a problem with that? ...If you have a problem, then present evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth. It looks like he really wants you to do that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. Then I will do as he wishes and present evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems he doesn't pay much attention to what other people are saying. There is a clear contradiction in Mr. Debeste's logic.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Why'd he even bother making the phone call?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'll finish this quickly. ...This is a waste of time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Debeste. Your logic is more akin to a shooting star than a shining star.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">He heh. It shines the best like a shooting star, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It may shine brightly for a brief moment, but then it burns itself out. The poison gas originated from inside the glass case of the Pisces Sculpture.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Exactly! So that's where the artist set off the gas, right? He used the Normallium in his red paint!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As your senior, let me give you one piece of advice. Listen to the explanations of others. The poison gas was caused by mixing both Normallium and Fatallium together. The Normallium contained in the red paint is not enough by itself.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">.....Really? But I thought I heard that "Normallium caused the fatality"...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Don't tell me you just misheard the forensic report!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">D-Darn it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">By the time Larry discovered the victim, the room was already filled with poison gas. It is time for you to realize how incapable you really are!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Hey! What do you mean by "incapable"!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You tried to use that word earlier, and you still don't know what it means...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">He means to say... you are lacking in ability.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Incidetally, "inculpable" has a completely different meaning.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">.....I get it! You're making fun of me again, aren't you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I am merely saying you were incapable in your investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Before you insult Sebastian, I still have some doubts about your own statement.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...What kind of doubts?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">For all we know, Mr. Artist could have simply entered the Autumn Palace at an earlier time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Moreover, do you have evidence that the red paint is unrelated to the case?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...The most important thing now is not the red paint. The red Normallium and the white Fatallium... Exactly how were these two substances mixed? I believe that is our main concern.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Naturally. It was Sebastian's job to investigate that. ...Were it not for your interference, we would have found that out by now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I never intended to interfere. On the contrary... I'd like to cooperate.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Don't tell me you're going to say you know the cause of the poison gas?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How the poison gas started... I have something that may shed some light on this matter.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Sebastian, do not fall for his bluff.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Come now, it's fine really. Let's hear what he's come up with.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">.......If you say so, Sebastian.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Come on, show us! How did the poison gas start?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Can you see this piece of evidence? It has traces of the poison gas's origin!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...Sebastian, don't get too close to Mr. Edgeworth. His foolish logic will make you dizzy... I find it poisonous, and even guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">.....</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He actually backed off...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Don't give up, Mr. Edgeworth! Keep using your poison tongue like you always do!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I must have evidence that shows how the Normallium and Fatallium were mixed. Red Normallium and white Fatallium were mixed, huh.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Surely you're not saying that this was the cause of poison gas?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... It seems even you've noticed it.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Duh! It really stands out!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Those red tears that Larry saw were undoubtedly Normallium.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Huh? Wait a second! If those were chemicals... Does that mean a ghost set off the poison gas?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I don't have time to play along with him.</thought> The red tears of Normallium... could not have triggered the poison gas by itself. That red liquid was mixed inside the case to create the poison gas.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">What!? Just where do you see evidence that the chemicals were mixed!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That can also be seen in this sketch. Here is the evidence! <thought>Show evidence that the two chemicals were mixed!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The proof... is right here!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">...It seems the truth has been made as clear as black and white. You really are just a bluffing fool!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh...! <thought>To be called that by Mr. Debeste of all people... As clear as black and white... it's not quite that simple. If you mixed white and red, naturally... their color should change.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A pink liquid can be seen flowing out from under the case of the Pisces Sculpture. This is proof that the two chemicals were mixed!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">H-Hold on a second! I still don't get it. How does this show that Normallium and Fatallium were mixed?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Since we have a self-proclaimed artist here, I'll let him explain. Larry. You fancy yourself an artist, so you should know about mixing paint, right? ...What do you add to red to make pink?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Don't take me for a fool, Edgey! I'll have you know I graduated from middle school! You add white to red to make pink, it's common knowledge! Well, technically there's "rose pink", "baby pink" and several others...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's enough. Now do you understand, Mr. Debeste?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Ah! ...That's how it is! By mixing red Normallium with white Fatallium... ...you get a pink liquid!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, exactly. <thought>Took him long enough...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Hmmm. .....I see.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It looks like Mr. Debeste finally gets it.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Prosecutor Edgeworth. You have merely presented one possibility... Do we really know if the color was the result of the two chemicals mixed together? Furthermore, this sketch was drawn by the suspect. I cannot put much faith into it.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I just painted what I saw! How could that be a lie!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Mr. Artist. I did not permit you to speak.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Ugh... So cold... But that's part of her charm!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Of course, I intend to bring the truth to light immediately.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">It would not be wise to jeopardize your position even further. Aren't you going to answer my question from before? How do you know that Mr. Artist did not enter the Autumn Palace? If you cannot prove this, there is no room for you to argue any further.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! Couldn't we find that out if we talked to the victim, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...The victim, Dane Gustavia, remains unconscious and in critical condition.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Ah, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Well then, Sebastian will be investigating the crime scene now. All of you, please vacate the premises.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...If you were to take a stand in court, you'd cause a lot of trouble for the presiding judge. Is there something you would like to say? .....Mr. Artist?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Hold your horses, Ms. Cool Beauty!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...My name is Justine Courtney. Please don't address me by such a strange title.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Oh, you finally told me your name. Pleased to meet you, Justy! I'm Laurice Deauxnim! But you can call me Laurice!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...Mr. Artist. Please get to the point.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I just remembered something I haven't had a chance to say yet! When I first got to this room, it was locked, so I couldn't go in. But then, that old dude just suddenly fell through the door!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...It would appear that the palace rooms can be locked from the inside. But... just because you say it was so, doesn't mean the door was locked. Without proof, your statement holds no value.</line>
<line speaker="Ray"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Well, why not let Uncle Ray prove it for you.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Wha...!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">After all, we can confirm the room was locked too. Right, Miles?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes. I remember as well.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hmm... The Winter Palace should be... Huh? It's... locked up. That's odd. They've already opened the museum.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Until the gas outbreak, no one could have entered this room.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Perhaps the suspect entered the room with the victim during the gas outbreak?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As you can see, this man did not inhale any of the gas. If you examine his belongings, you'll find he wasn't carrying a gas mask either.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">.....Is that so? Well then, I have no choice but to agree.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...? That was easier than I expected.</thought> Anyway... I presume this clears up any suspicion surrounding Larry? ...It seems Mr. Debeste's logic was off once again.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Wah hah hah. Not exactly. I just didn't have enough information, that's all. Therefore, my reasoning was just "before its time"!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He sure has a grand way of saying that things didn't work out for him.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">In that case, there is one more suspect who has yet to take the stand. ...Mr. Artist, you are free to go.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Huh! But I wanted to talk to you a little more, Justy.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...Overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Your cold demeanor leaves me mesmerized all the more!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This other suspect is...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...a pharmacist by the name of Delicia Scones. It would have been difficult for this artist to obtain the Fatallium from Megatoxin X. ...But a pharmacist may have knowledge of how to do that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">The court will now take a 10 minute recess. Sebastian. It would be best if we brought her in quickly.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">"Best" if we brought her quickly? Heh heh. Sounds good, leave it to me! Hey, Flatfoot! Keep up the investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ugh... Got it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't tell me... Judge Courtney suspected her from the very beginning?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So Mr. Debeste's logic wasn't any help at all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Judge Courtney... Just what is she thinking?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">She said it would only be a 10 minute recess. They sure are taking an awfully long time.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Ahem. Sorry to keep you waiting! Prosecutor Debeste presents Ms. Delicia Scones.</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yessie! You called, so here I am! It is I, Delicia Scones, the pharmacist who makes delicious drugs. But you can call me, Ms. Delicious!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">And you can call me, "Mr. DeBestest."</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Oi! Nice to meet you, Besty!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>They've gone straight to nicknames...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Huh? That boy... reminds me of someone.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">He he he. This is Miles Edgeworth. ...He's Gregory's son.</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yessie! Nice to meet you, Miley.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Could you please not call me "Miley."</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Ha ha ha! Meeting Greggy's boy... I guess it's a sign that I'm getting old.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>How old is this woman...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Sebastian. isn't there something you'd like to ask Ms. Pharmacist?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Oh. Right, yeah! Ms. Delicious, could you tell us the reason why you came to the gallery?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yessie! I came to see the curator, Katey! I've been friends with her for 17 years, so I visit her quite often.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Is it true, Ms. Pharmacist, that you also assisted in the treatment of Mr. Gustavia?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">I guess you could say that, although I only made the antidote for the doctor.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow! You made the antidote on the spot?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yessie! As long as I have the right ingredients, I can make any drug easily. The infirmary here is well equipped, you see. Instead of sending him to the hospital in critical condition, we treated him right away. I did all I could do. The rest... depends upon his body's ability to recover.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Do you know the victim, Ms. Delicious?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yessie... although it's been 18 years since I last saw him. I only knew that he had become a world-famous pastry chef.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Eh! Is the victim that famous?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">I heard on the news that he had won a competition for designing desserts.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">That reminds me, I do remember him mentioning something about studying design in Zheng Fa.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Now, let's get down to business. ...Ms. Pharmacist. Are you familiar with the drug, Megatoxin X?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yessie! It's the drug that's used to kill "those things". It's "mega effective"! Because the effects are so potent, it's not avaliable to the general public.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What are "those things" you're referring to?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">It's a drug for vanquishing the creatures that strike fear into the heart of a lady! ...The ones that often infest kitchens and the like.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah... I think I know what she's talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">So, Ms. Pharmacist. May I ask you one more thing? Do you know what happens when you mix Normallium with Fatallium?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yessie... I know. It's even written on the warning label for Megatoxin X: "Hazardous when mixed." When the two drugs are mixed together, a chemical reaction occurs and a gas is released. Inhaling a large amount of this gas can cause breathing difficulties... and even death. From the amount of poison gas Gusty breathed in, I think... ...there was probably at least 500 millilitres of each chemical in the gas.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>As expected of a pharmacist, she's very well informed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Normallium is an adhesive liquid that becomes hot as soon as heat is applied. It also has a red color and a minty fragrance. Due to its low cost, it's used everywhere! Fatallium is a white, watery liquid.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">That's enough for now. ...As expected of a pharmacist. You're very knowledgeable.</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yessie! Of course I am. Megatoxin X is one of the chemicals that the company I work for produces!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Ah... But! Not just anyone has access to it! It's so potent as a poison that it couldn't be sold to the public, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Thank you... I think that's all I need to hear.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Does Judge Courtney suspect her? What is she hiding behind that smile...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Oh? Flatfoot. Have you made progress in the investigation or something?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah... Let me tell you. The glass case that contained the sculptures can be opened by a mechanism in the lid.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Hmm. What strange cases.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The temperature in the cases can be lowered down to 0℉. The inside of the Pisces case was set to 27℉, so my hand nearly got stuck to the ice!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Good thing it didn't! ...So then?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">From the lid of the Pisces case... ...we detected slight traces of Normallium!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Ehh! Not bad!</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Huh? If the Normallium was in a glass case at a temperature of 27℉, then... ...it would have been frozen to the lid.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Ehh. Really? So... What happened?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Mr. Debeste. Why don't we try borrowing the power of Kay's Little Thief? I think the circumstances will be easier to understand if we use our "Mr. Thief."</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Hmph. So you really want to help me out that much? Fine! I'm not really sure how this all works, but... You, get on with it!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I hate being bossed around by this guy, but to arrive at the truth, I'll do it!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...Stop acting as you please. The Goddess of Law has no need of your power.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Don't be such a stick-in-the-mud, Courtney-pie! We have approval of the prosecutor in charge, so what's the problem? Could it be, there's something the P.I.C. doesn't want us to find out?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">......That's none of your concern. If you insist on participating in the investigation... ...then, let me check if you're qualified by asking you a question.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...What is she planning?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Who set off the poison gas? ...If you can answer me that, I'll allow you to work with us.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">...Well then, Miles. The person who opened the Pisces case and set off the gas... When you think about the circumstances, there's only one person it could have been.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... Considering the circumstances, it's clear who it was.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">So, please give me your answer. Who set off the poison gas?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The one who set off the gas is clearly... this person!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Clearly overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No...!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">As I suspected, you just aren't qualifi...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Please wait, Courtney-pie! He was just joking. If you think about it carefully, it's obvious who caused the poison gas. Only "that person" was in the room at that time. ...Right, Miles?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">U-Um, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...So, I'll ask again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There was no one in the Autumn Palace, other than the victim, Dane Gustavia. It's hard to believe it could have been anyone but him.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...It seems that way. Very well, I'll allow you to participate this time. However... If I feel you are a hindrance, I will have to ask you to leave.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Understood. <thought>But, what I don't understand is why the victim opened that case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">So, Mr. Edgeworth. What shall I re-create?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Based on the information we've gathered so far, let's re-create the scene before the gas.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Uwaaaah! D-Don't scare me like that!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">So, this is the true power of "Sir Thief"...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's investigate the Pisces Sculpture posthaste. There's frozen Normallium on the lid of the Pisces Sculpture's glass case.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's frozen so thick you can't even open the lid!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">On the actual glass case, the lid was heavily cracked... It was like someone had it out for the Pisces Sculpture, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Do you have any idea how it came to be cracked like this?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm... Well, the damage didn't seem to have come from outside of the glass case, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. So the inside of the case was below freezing point, and the case had developed cracks. There are no signs of external damage... From this we can deduce...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Below freezing...? Like Mr. Edgeworth's cold stare...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And cracked...? Like Mr. Edgeworth's furrowed brow...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thermal fracturing! The cold glass case was heated from the outside, causing it to crack.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hmm. But why did thermal fracturing occur here, and what caused it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Inside the thermally fractured glass case, there was frozen Normallium...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Oh? That face means you've probably thought of something, Miles.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed I have. I know how Mr. Gustavia was able to open the glass case.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">WHAT! How can you possibly know something I don't!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'd say the things he DOES know are in the minority...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Hey! Aren't you going to LET me know? How did Dane Gustavia open the glass case?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Gustavia used this to open the case.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">......? Uhh, Justine...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Do not worry, Sebastian. I cannot understand it either. I'm certain that no one but Mr. Edgeworth is able to comperehend such logic.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Mmph... it can't be this. The fractured case and the frozen Normallium... The cause of the thermal fracturing must tie these two together!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Hmph. If your explanation isn't "the best", then don't bother giving it to me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This gas burner, that was found in the Autumn Palace, shows signs of recent use. I believe this was the cause of the thermal fracturing in the Pisces Sculpture's glass case.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">A gas burner...? Why would he use something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! I got it! The lid was frozen shut, so he had to use the burner to melt the ice!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed, that is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Ngh... I just had a late start. I-I'm still "the best", y'know!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Late start... you didn't even understand a single thing, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Well, that's just because Mr. Edgeworth's explanation was too hard to follow!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Kay, why don't you update the Little Thief so that he can understand it.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">If you say so. Right, let's restart the re-creation!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The victim, Dane Gustavia, was the only one to enter the Autumn Palace. If he used the gas burner then... ...the Normallium in the glass case would have melted.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">...Uh huh, uh huh. And then?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The melted Normallium would have come into contact with the Fatallium inside the case... ...and produced the poison gas! The moment Mr. Gustavia opened the lid, he would have begun to inhale the gas. He managed to drag himself out to the Fountain Patio just before his strength ran out.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">...So he inhaled the gas when he opened the lid...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It seems he finally understands.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">But why did Mr. Gustavia open the glass case of the Pisces Sculpture?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The victim's goal... That, I do not yet know.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Perhaps he had the same reason as Uncle Ray. Maybe he actually came to see the Winter Palace, not the Autumn one.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Uncle Ray also thought that this was the Winter Palace at first.</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Oi! You too, Ray Ray? Actually, I thought so too! It looks just like Icy's room from 18 years ago. It's even got the exact same plants in front of the door.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It seems everyone involved with the IS-7 Incident made the same mistake. It is imperative that we investigate the real Winter Palace immediately. I should suggest that to Mr. Debeste.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">I get it now...! Yeah. That's how it was!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Huh... Did you think of something?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">The victim committed suicide! He thought he would look refined if he died in an art gallery!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.....</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Have you even been listening?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Well, if you're as smart as me, just hearing half of the story will be enough.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Sebastian. I'll explain it from the top later.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">"Top"...! That means "best", right? Alright, I'll leave it to you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Yes, it would indeed be "best" to let Judge Courtney handle him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Courtney">That aside, don't you have some information to inform everyone of?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Aah! I totally forgot!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">He heh. We did a little checking on that pharmacist. "We" meaning me, "The Best" Prosecutor's... subordinate!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's not something to brag about.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">S-Shut up, you! Quiet down and listen! Suicide is... um... Off the table for now, yeah. That's because, umm... in short... That pharmacist is the culprit! She set up the gas as a trap!</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Eeep! N-No!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">It's a terrible shame, ...Ms. Pharmacist. How could one in the profession of saving lives stoop to extinguishing them!</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Huh? Wh-What are you saying? I... I would never do such a thing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Debeste. Do you have a basis for these accusations?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Hmph! Of course! This is my basis! Her pharmacist's license. It would permit her to handle Megatoxin X, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.....And its active ingredient Fatallium was one of the components of the poison gas.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Exactly! That chemical is almost impossible for ordinary people to obtain! But, that pharmacist is another story altogether!</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">I-It wasn't me! You've got it all wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">And that's not all! A bottle of Megatoxin X was found in the victim's pocket. And on the bottle... we found clear fingerprints, yours!</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">E... EEEEEEEEEEP!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">You and the curator took the victim to the infirmary, right? That would have given you the perfect opportunity to plant the bottle on him!</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Th-That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">You are the only pharmacist on the premises who could have handled Megatoxin X. Furthermore, as for the curator of this art gallery, you're an acquaintance of hers. You would've had access to the gallery at any time, in order to prepare the poison gas trap.</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">P-Please wait! That Megatoxin X, it was stolen!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...Trying to lie your way out of this won't go well with me.</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">It's true! Look, I've got the proof right here in my bag...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...What is she searching for?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Not this... Not this either...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Hm? I remember seeing cloth like that recently...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Ah! Here! Please take a look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? It's some sort of paper...?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">What's it say?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"April 1st Theft Report Accepted. Stolen Item: Megatoxin X" This... is a theft report acceptance certificate.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yessie! Truth is... one week ago, my Megatoxin X was stolen.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">One week ago...? That means, you didn't have it with you today?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Yessie... That bottle you just found is probably the one that was stolen from me. I normally carry that bottle of Megatoxin X in my bag at all times. Even though I often forget to keep it locked up... I would never even think about mixing it with Normallium!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But... Why in the world would you carry such a dangerous substance on your person?</line>
<line speaker="Delicia">Well, you never know when those things will appear. Those... those...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">..."Those creatures that infest the kitchen, striking fear into the heart of a lady," right? Although if you had a rolled-up newspaper, you could just squash them with one blow.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">...Justine, what do we do now?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Well then... Can we really accept this theft report? Let's ask for confirmation. That should clearly tell us whether or not she's lying.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Right! Well then, I'll just call and confirm it.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It looks like Ms. Delicious isn't the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. If she really did set up the poison gas as a trap... I don't believe she would do it in the way that incriminates her the most.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">...So Miles, who do you think is the culprit?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Predicting the actions of the victim would require a fair amount of advance planning... And there's only one person here capable of that.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Huh? Uncle Ray would like to know too. ...Who do you suspect?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The one who stole the Megatoxin X and prepared the room in advance was...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was, this person... probably.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">...Ahh. Hmmm, I see. Miles, you're feeling tired, aren't you? Instead of an alarm clock, let me tell you a funny story from when you were small. During your second year of grade school, you were as tired as you are right now...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I'm awake! Please don't say any more!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aww, I kinda wanted to hear the rest of that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Someone who could predict the victim's actions, and could prepare in advance. It can only be that person!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It had to be the curator of the Zodiac Art Gallery... Ms. Katherine Hall. However, I still don't have any evidence that she is the criminal yet...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I see... She is... .....</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...? The way he said that just now sounded like he had been expecting it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hmm. Good job Miles! As expected from Uncle Ray's future apprentice!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I have no intention of becoming your apprentice.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Aaaand I will now announce the results of my verification! I can confirm that her theft report was indeed accepted! Therefore... it's a little too early to come to a decision!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... that means your logic was completely faulty.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Ngh... Y-You're wrong! My real performance is still to come!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Really...? And how do you plan to proceed with your investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Th-That's... First, we need to speak with the curator.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And after that?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Ugh... W-We'll cross that bridge when we come to it!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Sebastian. Mr. Gustavia may have had business in the Winter Palace. I believe we should send an investigator there as well.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Oh! That's good too! Detective Gumshoe! Investigate the Winter Palace at once!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Uugh... Got it, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Justine! Let's go talk to the curator!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Yes, let us proceed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...We should go and listen to what Ms. Hall has to say as well.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Alright, I want you guys to listen to what the curator has to say.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Mr. Debeste, weren't you going to go and talk to her yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Nah. That's a job for my subordinates. All I have to do is wait for their report. ...I'm "The Best" Prosecutor, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Such arrogance...!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, this is anticlimactic. I'm gonna chill for a bit. Huh? What's that in the fountain...! A-AAAAAAAAAAHHH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">WAAAAAAAHH! Th-There's a dead body in the fountaaain!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What... is the meaning of this...!?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">.....!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Silence, everyone! Forensics! Identify this body at once...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-It's terrible, paaaal!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Please be quiet, Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The ice sculptures in the W-Winter Palace... They've all melted, paaaaal!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Wha?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wha?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Wha?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">WHAAAAAAAAAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's going on here!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">There are two victims now...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">This is all... just like 18 years ago. Once again, the ice sculptures have melted.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Again...?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">...And everyone related to the incident 18 years ago is gathered here now. This is no mere coincidence. Don't you think so, Miles?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. The key to finding the truth of this case lies in this IS-7 Incident. ...This is what I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">He he heh. That's right. Uncle Ray thinks so too. Looks like it's time once again for Uncle Ray to tell you about the IS-7 Incident.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I don't think these pieces will fit together... Looks like I'll have to start over.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>It seems these two pieces of information aren't connected... It seems I was a bit too hasty in jumping to conclusions.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Hmm... no good. That line of logic seems too unreasonable.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">This piece of evidence holds the key to the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...You know what this lollipop... and your reasoning have in common...?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...They're both so sugary they make me sick!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>...In that case, why don't you stop licking that lollipop?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">I'd suggest... you try a more tangy line of logic...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">This piece of evidence will make the contradiction clear!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">......Rubbish!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>He shot that down with one stroke.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">I'd like to... hear sharper reasoning... than that...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">I understand. My next strike will settle this!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">I believe your statement contradicts this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">..You know what detectives... and lollipops have in common?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Chew them out for too long... and you'll lose your teeth! ...Next time you make a mistake, this lollipop might come flying at your head...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>I should watch out for cavities and any further mistakes in my reasoning...</thought> I would like one more chance.</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">What do you think of this piece of evidence, Prosecutor von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">I-I am a defense attorney...!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Ngh...! He really looks down on me...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Have a look at this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Uugh...!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><thought>Ngh... He's laughing at me...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">That statement is strange. It contradicts this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Ngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Debeste. What do you think about this piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Why are you asking for my opinion?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't you see? This evidence contradicts your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">WH-WHAAAAAAAAAT!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">I don't believe this evidence has that kind of meaning.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Eh! Is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... <thought>With Judge Courtney here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Also, you don't need to yell ><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Debeste. There is a contradiction in your statement!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Eh! Is that true, Justine?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">It is not, Sebastian. It is Prosecutor Edgeworth's statement that is contradictory.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Of course! There's no way there could be a contradiction in my argument!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh! <thought>Isn't it full of contradictions!? My real problem is her rather than Mr. Debeste...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Ngh! To come this far, only to lose hold of the truth...! But... it seems all hope is lost...</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">Thus the truth was lost for all time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh! To come this far, only to lose the truth...! But... it seems there's nothing I can do now...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Edgey! I'm not gonna talk if you keep bullying me like this!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sh-Shoot... I messed up!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can't give up now. I have to stand my ground... Now... Let's try this again!</line>
<line speaker="Gregory">There aren't any clues here.</line>
</xml>