<xml>
<title>The Stolen Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, I'm glad we found the urn and all, but poor Mr. DeLite got arrested again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, supposedly, Mr. DeLite was in the CEO's office when the murder occurred.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No way, Jose! I don't buy it!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But the one who proved that Mr. DeLite was there... It was Mr. Nick himself... ...At least, from what I can understand.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Looks like you did too good of a job this time, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, ah... well, how about we get started looking into the KB Security murder?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I think I'm going to head back to Kurain Village for a little while, if that's alright.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sure. But why?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm going to bring the Sacred Urn back and have some people take a look at it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, that's a good idea! I think I'll go with--</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">No! Mystic Maya! You should stay here! I want you to spend some special quality time together, full of love and happiness!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Maybe Pearls is so caught up in her fantasy she forgot there's a murder to solve.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Now remember! No fighting, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...She's gone.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">OK, Nick! Time to get doing on this murder investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what do we do now?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Isn't it obvious!? We should get out there and investigate the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well first, we need to find out exactly where KB Security is located.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Hey! Why don't we ask Ms. DeLite! She should know! Besides, I want to ask her some stuff about motorcycles!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Motorcycles...? You're not thinking of getting one, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm not the same little Maya who used to be happy with her dinky little bike, Nicky boy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*sigh*... Speaking of asking around, I've got a few questions of my own for Mr. DeLite...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">OK, well, let's make sure to go to the detention center, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You must be relieved we got the Sacred Urn back, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You bet! ...But there's something a little different about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't "...?" at me! It's pretty obvious, isn't it? I mean, take a look at this. It clearly says, "I AM" on the urn in the poster. But the urn we got back says, "AMI", like it always used to.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh yeah... You're right.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Plus, the vase has pink splotches on it now... ...I'm sure they wasn't there before!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya doesn't know, but 1 year ago... when the urn was broken... ...the repairer accidentally turned Mystic Ami's name into "I AM". And that repairer was one mechanically unskilled little Pearls. But still... I don't remember ever seeing pink splotches on it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is it possible that urn is a fake?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure Pearls'll find out about that once she gets back to Kurain Village.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, I suppose...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that I think about it... Maya hasn't been back to Kurain Village in a long time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... I guess people still go to Kurain Village to do their training, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup. If you want to become a spirit medium, you need to undergo severe training.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So why haven't you been training lately, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well... Lately I've been thinking of heading to a channeling dojo to do just that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A "channeling dojo", huh...? Sounds pretty serious, whatever that is.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If you're going to train, you have to be serious. Otherwise real tragedies can happen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is what happened last year still bothering you...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That murder in her village... It happened because the power of channeling was misused.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">When a medium uses the Kurain Technique, she temporarily loses her own will.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So when an especially strong spirit is summoned... ...the spirit medium can get taken over and even forced to commit terrible crimes. What's worse, in those cases, the spirit medium has no memory of what happened. That murder... it wasn't your fault, Maya. You know that, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I suppose not, but... ...I guess I'm still a bit shaken up. That's all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It sounds like being the Master of Kurain is going to be a heavy responsibility...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm glad we got the Sacred Urn back and all...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So then how come you don't look any happier?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why should I!? I don't know if it should say "AMI" or "I AM" on it anymore... ...and now it's got big pink polka dots on it that weren't there anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't you think you're overreacting just a little?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Overreacting!? Nick! I can't believe you said that! I mean, it's like... like... I got it! It's like if I came in wearing polka dots on my acolyte costume every day and said... "Hi, Nick! I'm Ayam!" Well!? Do you still think it's no big deal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I guess... it would be... um... a real disaster...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You see! You see! Well that's how I feel!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to this data, the thief showed up at the basement warehouse at...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, 1 o'clock in the morning, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, but remember, this data came from Atmey... For all we know, he might have somehow tampered with it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But... But then, what about this photo? It's got the time on it, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, and the security camera belonged to Lordly Tailor. Atmey couldn't have tampered with the photo's timestamp to show the wrong time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess that means this data is accurate after all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So the Mask☆DeMasque in this photo... ...is Detective Atmey in disguise, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks that way. <thought>Atmey knew there was a security camera set up in the basement... So I'm guessing this photo was probably a part of his elaborate plan...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's still bent, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Detective Atmey said it got bent when the thief hit him on the head with it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it looks like he ended up the bent one after he turned out to be the thief. He must have damaged the sword himself to back up his phony story.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah... I guess he really does have a brawny mind, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So Mr. DeLite was being blackmailed, huh? By the CEO of the security company he used to work for.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, it looks like it. <thought>Sounds like we still need to do some more poking around...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You'd better watch yourself and not do anything naughty either, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Was that a threat? Is she trying to blackmail ME now...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This was found in the building where the crime took place on the very night of the murder. And according to the time record on the key card inside...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, it was used right around the time of the murder... Doesn't sound very good, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So Detective Atmey was Mask☆DeMasque after all, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess so... After all, he did admit it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes, but Mr. DeLite still hasn't changed his tune. He's still claiming that he's the real Mask☆DeMasque. You don't think he's just saying that to avoid the murder charge, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I-I'm not sure...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">This was found on the floor of the basement warehouse. So does that mean... Detective Atmey put it there himself?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's the only explanation I can think of. I guess he wanted to make sure it looked like he'd struggled with the thief that night.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're not very photogenic, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>Maybe I shouldn't show this picture to too many people... And yet... I've walked around my whole life, showing this face of mine to the world... I wonder if I've just been making a fool of myself with this silly face...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, I was only joking, Nick... Don't make such a sad face. You're making me feel guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pearly sure is a good kid.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. But she tends to let her imagination get the best of her, though.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's one of the things I like about her, silly! Slapping you the way she did! She's a tough one alright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're telling me! I think she knocked a few teeth loose. <thought>Pearls is only 9, but it's amazing how emotionally strong she is. After all... the only "family" she has left is her only cousin, Maya.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can hardly believe that guy was really the thief in disguise! I never saw that coming! Then again, I stink at spotting those "plot twist" things.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Atmey seemed to really enjoy himself today. Maybe a little too much.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ha ha, yeah. Today was pretty wild. Like the plot of some crazy comic book!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Great, glad you had fun while I was getting abused by the prosecutor... as always.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, it's Larry. He's your childhood friend, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I've known him since elementary school.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow...! That's even longer than I've known Pearly. You two must have lots of good memories together!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess so. But I can hardly remember them... They've been erased by all the traumatic ones.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Say, Nick... What do you think that thing attached to his face is anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't ask me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why not? You know him, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've never met that guy before in my life! And believe me, he's not exactly forgettable.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, but at the trial today, he said...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">So we finally meet... Mr. Phoenix Trite!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I've returned from the depths of Hell... To do battle with you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're right about one thing. He sure acts like he knows me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick? I was just thinking... Maybe you should try to stop making people you've never met before into your enemies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trust me, I'd like to stop doing that, too. My poor body can only take so much. <thought>Who is that guy anyway? And what's his story? I wonder if I'll ever find out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">The Treasures of Kurain exhibit is all ruined now...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm sorry, it's just so sad... This was our big chance for everyone to learn about spirit channeling...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe I can cheer her up somehow...</thought> Well, now that we've got the Sacred Urn back, maybe they can reopen it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">R-Really...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure! Maybe we can label it, "The Urn of Mask☆DeMasque's Desires"! That would probably attract a lot of attention!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Whoa. Whoa. Whoa!! That's brilliant, Nick! We could clean up! And be filthy rich! Woohoo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, that was surprisingly easy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Oh...! It's you, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Andrews... <thought>What's she still hanging around down here for?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Um, so! How is it going!? What about the Sacred Urn...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The urn...? Oh, that. It's been taken care of already.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you mean, "Oh, that"!?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">"Taken care of"...? Do you mean... It's been found!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes! It was brought in during the trial today!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Wow! Really!? You really are the greatest, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Mr. Wright" had nothing to do with it. It was Mask☆DeMasque's wife that found it!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Well, anyway, I'm... I'm so relieved!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is the camera and computer that Detective Atmey set up, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what he said.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And yet he still let it take a picture of him. I guess he's not as smart as he pretends to be!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The camera belonged to Lordly Tailor, so he knew he couldn't tamper with it... So then why would Atmey, I mean, Mask☆DeMasque, allow that to happen...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Detective Atmey said he got hit on the back of the head with this by the thief. But that was obviously a lie.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Because it turned out that Atmey was the real thief... It's still hard to believe...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looks like Adrian feels really bad about it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I'm going to take full responsibility and fix that sword myself! I know I don't look it, but I have complete confidence that I can fix it right up! I promise I'll fix it so you never knew it was bent in the first place!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">P-Please be gentle with it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like the door to the actual storeroom. I can see lots of big boxes and stuff back there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess that's where they were keeping the Sacred Urn.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Remember, Maya. Ms. Andrews said we're not allowed in there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The statue wasn't where it is now when we first came here, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, it was right next to the door, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, if someone moved it, it was probably Mask☆DeMasque.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe he didn't like being watched by Mystic Ami while he stole the urn.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Hey! Cut it out! You're giving me the creeps with that kind of talk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It says "ORGANI".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No it doesn't, Nick! It says, "ORGANIZE"! You just can't see the last two letters.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, well I guess no one else could read it either, because this place is a mess.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. So you should feel right at home, right?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I just heard all about it on the news... So that detective was actually the thief all along!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks that way right now.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It-It's my fault. I'm the one who ended up hiring DeMasque to guard the treasures...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't blame yourself. You were just doing your job.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick, if she wants to apologize, you should let her. So... When was it that you hired Detective Atmey again...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">About 20 days ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And when was it that Mask☆DeMasque's calling card arrived?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">That was about 10 days ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So he sent a calling card to the very place he was hired to guard...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess that's it then. Detective Atmey must have really wanted the Sacred Urn after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess so...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">What!? So Mask☆DeMasque m-murdered someone as well...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, that's how things look right now.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes, but... I thought that he was here stealing the urn at the time...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... We're talking about a criminal mastermind, so anything is possible.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, let's get down to business already. On the night of the theft, did you notice anything suspicious about Detective Atmey?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">No... I couldn't have. After all, he was hidden the entire time. I never even caught a glimpse of him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He claims that's the way he always operates...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's just what he says so he can have an alibi while he commits the thefts himself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, he was caught on the crime scene photo dressed up as Mask☆DeMasque pretty well.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I'm so glad that you got your Sacred Urn back...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... But there's still something that bothers me about it.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Wh-What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not exactly sure... But somehow the urn that came back seems different...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">R-Really...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You wouldn't know anything about that, would you Ms. Andrews?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">N-No, I don't know anything! Wh-Why would I?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A Psyche-Lock...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you think this means, Nick!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It means the person that holds the secret to the mystery of the Sacred Urn... ...is our very own Ms. Andrews!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... Do you know anything about the Sacred Urn?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Wh-Who? M-Me?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">In court today, Ms. DeLite brought the urn back... But... It's a little different from the urn I remember.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So Adrian does know something that she's not telling us...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, I want to find out about the murder, but I also want to know about the urn.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd like to know myself. Another loose end to tie up, I guess.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">The Treasures of Kurain exhibit is my first job after last year's ordeal. And I really wanted it to be a success!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've got an idea! Why don't you redo the whole poster?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You could put something like, "Voted Best Treasure Exhibit by Mask☆DeMasque"!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...Why Maya! That's a fantastic idea!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I heard Detective Atmey for security before we even received a calling card... I suppose that was a mistake...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Atmey... I mean, Mask☆DeMasque... He sent a calling card to the very exhibit he was hired to guard...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder if it was because he knew it would be easy to steal.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes, but he should have also known that he could easily become a suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I thought the whole exhibit would be brightened up by something shiny and gold. That's why I went to the trouble of borrowing it from a branch family training hall.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A gold statue is totally cool in my book.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It arrived rather late, so I thought I wouldn't be able to put it on display.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By the way, it looks like this statue was moved on the night of the theft... Do you know anything about that?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Huh! N-No! It-It certainly wasn't me that moved it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why is she so flustered all of a sudden...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">The security camera was provided by Lordly Tailor Department Store. I took a close look at it on the day after the theft... The timestamp on the photo is definitely real.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Detective Atmey said he got hit on the back of the head with this by the thief. But that was obviously a lie.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Because it turned out that Atmey was the real thief... It's still hard to believe...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looks like Adrian feels really bad about it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I'm going to take full responsibility and fix that sword myself! I know I don't look it, but I have complete confidence that I can fix it right up! I promise I'll fix it so you never knew it was bent in the first place!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">P-Please be gentle with it...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Ms. Fey, I'd love to introduce you at the exhibit, if you don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? I'd really happy to do whatever I can to help! Oh, I have an idea! Maybe I could sing a song? "The Master of Kurain" or "The Spirit Song" or perhaps "Maya's Theme"?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">That sounds wonderful! I had no idea such songs actually existed.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well they don't... yet. I was going to make Nick write them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Be serious.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">She's such a cute little girl. I'm deeply in her debt for what she did 7 months ago.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Her name is Pearl. She's training to be a spirit medium!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Training at such a young age... That's very impressive. Well, as a fellow career woman, I salute her!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Career woman, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess that's one way to look at spirit mediums... since they're all woman...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Now I realize I should have called the police. As soon as I got that calling card from Mask☆DeMasque, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I guess you should have.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, now Detective Gumshoe has one more failure to add to his list.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Oh? You mean he's not a very good detective?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's a good thing he's not here to hear us talking about him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">So Detective Atmey was actually Mask☆DeMasque... ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She really seems depressed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't say I blame her. She's the one who hired the fox to guard the henhouse.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...I'm really terrible at judging people, I guess. I should have learned my lesson after what happened 7 months ago... But I didn't! I got taken in by this... this... flimflam detective!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't feel so sad. After we're here to help!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Yes! Mr. Wright is a really wonderful man, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That should've made me happy. but she just admitted she's terrible at judging people...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, come on... I can tell you're happy anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I'm sorry I can't help more, but I'm so busy taking care of everything in front of me. I still haven't given up on the Treasures of Kurain exhibit.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, Ms. Andrews! I'm so happy to hear you say that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like the Treasure Exhibit is the only thing she has on her mind...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa, this place is literally crawling with cops!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What did you expect? Now that they know he was actually Mask☆DeMasque... This must be incredibly embarrassing for them, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I guess they're trying to make up for it by tearing the place apart. Hey, I just noticed... Gumshoe is nowhere to be seen.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, he is a homicide detective. He's probably working on the murder case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But wasn't he in charge of the Mask☆DeMasque investigation all the way up to yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, a murder case is a lot more exciting, isn't it? He'd say something like: "There's nothin' like a good murder case, pal."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Points for the quality of the impression, but I'm not sure Gumshoe has bloodlust, Maya.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Officer">Hey! You guys!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eeek!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">We're investigating this place! So keep your hands to yourselves!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Boy! These policemen sure are a bunch of sourpusses!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Mr. Ace Detective did make complete and utter fools out of them...</line>
<line speaker="Officer">What's all this now! Move it along! The show's over!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww... It doesn't look like they're going to let us investigate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess we might as well call it a day for this place and go look somewhere else.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">I already told you! It's not meeeeeeeee</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A sad, pitiful whine that tapers into silence...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sounds like they're interrogating Mr. DeLite right now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Man, and we don't have enough time as it is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, well, I guess the police are going crazy just like we are. Yesterday they thought he was just a thief, but now they got a murder case on their hands.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess you're right... That guard over there looks a bit on edge, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come on. We'll just have to come back later.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">OK! Let's go check out some other place, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Oh! Nicky boy! Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. DeLite...</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">All I wanted to do was help my dear Ronnie...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... but I guess it ended up hurting his case...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't say that, Nick! She don't need your help beating herself up.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Hey, Nicky boy! Please! Please help Ronnie! He's not a killer, I swear! My Ronnie wouldn't hurt a fly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Alright. I'll poke around and see what I can find out.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Really! Are you serious!? Oh, I'm so happy! I knew asking for your help was the right thing to do. I... I don't know what I can do to help anymore...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I had no idea Ms. DeLite had such a vulnerable side.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a whole bunch of stuff piled up over here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are these rolls of paper stuck in the trash can? "Theft of the Mazarin Stone: The Great Albatross Strategy" "Theft of the Immortal Goddess Statue: The Great Knucklebomber Strategy"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Did the police even investigate this place...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">The police took a look at all of that, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really!? Did they say anything?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">They said it wasn't important.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Don't worry about it, Nicky boy. After all, my Ronnie is just an amateur.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Amateur or not, this is cool! "Knucklebomber"! How cool is that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a bunch of cheap costume pieces arranged inside a nice frame.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">L-Look, Nick! It's a fake beard!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's also a mask made out of cardboard...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Try on this fake beard! Come on! Try it on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Hey! Cut it out...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now put on the mask! ... Aha ha ha ha ha ha! It's Phoenix☆DeMasque!</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">If you like it, feel free to take it home with you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, but no thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmmm... This thing looks vaguely familiar.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I know! It's a fishbowl! Well, an upside-down one, anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think it's a helmet. ...An alien helmet.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And that looks like a tape recorder or something next to it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think it's a transceiver. ...An alien transceiver.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Oh, that. Ronnie brought that home one day. He asked one of his friends from work if he could have it. It's a Space Ranger uniform. I've never seen Ronnie happier in his whole time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, man... Now I want one, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if KB Security was in charge of security at the event from that old case?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's Mask☆DeMasque!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a tape recorder hanging from his neck.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let me see that!</line>
<line speaker="DeMasque">Aha ha ha ha ha ha ha... I'll be taking this crown now! Better luck next time, gentlemen! Aha ha ha ha ha ha ha...</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Ronnie used to say that "a happy laugh is the lifeblood of a thief".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, that certainly is a happy-sounding laugh alright.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Yes, and laughing isn't as easy as it sounds. The harder you try, the more fake it sounds.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. Mr. DeLite really works hard at his craft, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are a bunch of books lying here. They're all romantic-sounding novels about famous heists and fantastic thieves.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Look at all the bookmarks and notes stuck into them!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see here... "Note: Must remember this thief's way of laughing. Very useful." "Note: A calling card is an important part of any good thief's modus operandi!"</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">It was always Ronnie's dream to become a thief.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I guess you can chalk that one down as fulfilled...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder why Mr. DeLite never talked to his wife about it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, well I think she deserves some of the blame for not bringing it up either.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Listen carefully, Nicky boy! My Ronnie would never, ever kill anyone! It's just not in him!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...I don't think he would either, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, but you have to admit he's got a bit of a temper to him. It's not that hard to imagine him just snapping and screaming, "Please diiiiie!"</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He would never say that! Anyway, Ms. DeLite, he might not be a killer... ...but he's still going around saying that he's a "thief"...</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">I already told you, that's just a fantasy for him...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. DeLite, I hate to say it, but you're the one living in a fantasy world.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Wh-Wh-What!? How dare you say that to me, Nicky boy! I know everything about my Ronnie! We don't have any secrets between us! Ronnie isn't the thief type! He's so honest that he wouldn't even sneak a nap! He-He's so honest that he wouldn't even steal a glance! Thief! Ha! The very idea...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... I guess I just don't get it...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Get what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I just can't understand how they can be so different, and yet, be such a happy couple!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, they sure are different.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Come on now, Nicky boy! It's not that mysterious, is it? It was love at first sight! ...For me, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? F-For you?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">I hate these kinds of people more than anything!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... You mean Ace Detectives?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">No, I'm fine with Ace Detectives.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh... So then you must mean thieves?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">No, they're alright, too. I just hate thieves that pretend to be Ace Detectives! There's nothing I hate more than cowardly men!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">By the way, why did you go to Detective Atmey's office anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Well, as the trial went on, I started to get more and more nervous. I went there to try to find out more about the "real criminal".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The "real criminal"...?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Yes! Obviously, the real Mask☆DeMasque is not my Ronnie, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-Yeah...?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">And Detective Atmey knew more about Mask☆DeMasque than anyone else... They mentioned him on the "Great People of the Town" segment on TV.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So then... you went there to ask him some questions?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">That's right. I'll do whatever it takes to save my man! His secretary said, "The Ace Detective isn't in right now!" But I forced my way past her and into his hideout.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wouldn't exactly call that office of his a "hideout"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">That bag was sitting right there on top of the table.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh yeah, we saw that bag there yesterday, too.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">There's nothing lower than someone who would try to pin a crime on someone else.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ms. DeLite, do you know about KB Security?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Don't be silly, of course I do. That's where my Ronnie works.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So she thinks he still works there, huh... Oh, that's right. According to what we heard today...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Come on! Don't tell me you didn't know it! Ron DeLite was once an employee of KB Security... He was a professional security guard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...But he quit. He doesn't work there anymore.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It looks like Ms. DeLite doesn't know...</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">KB Security is only about 20 minutes away. By motorcycle, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry told me it takes 30 minutes by car...</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Well, I have to admit I tend to fly pretty fast on my bike.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>To make it to KB Security that fast, are you sure you aren't literally flying...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Why don't I give you a ride sometime? Or better yet, how about now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, ahh... N-No...! I'll pass, th-thanks! Wh-Why don't you just tell us where it is and we'll go ourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ha ha, what a scaredy-cat you are, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ms. DeLite told us the location of KB Security.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">OK. Let's head over there right away, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... So was it really love at first sight when you first met Mr. DeLite?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Well, maybe not at first sight, but Ronnie saved my life.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Saved your life...?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">I was at work one day when two robbers suddenly rushed in. Well, I'm not the kind to just curl into a little ball in a corner, so I fought back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Robbers?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Yes, they took me hostage. I was so frightened. They were both carrying these huge knives and... I-I broke down into tears.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah... I would too, if I were in that situation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! I think I get it! Did Mr. DeLite come running to save you?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Yes! Exactly! I remember he looked so handsome in that guard uniform of his! He went right up to those two knife-wielding robbers... and screamed in their faces! "PLEASE, STOP IIIIIIIIIIT!" he screamed. I could see the robbers' faces turn pale...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That high-pitched shriek of his does have a surprisingly strong effect on people...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Then, crying and swinging his arms like crazy, he attacked the two robbers. All by himself... He came to save me, a total stranger, all by himself... He was so scared that he was crying and shaking, but he still risked his life for me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Wow. That's a great story...</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Yes. He may not look it, but in a tough situation, there's no one better... ...That's why I fell in love with him like I did.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*sniff sniff* Th-That's so romantic... I'd fall in love too, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, I hope you'll do the same for me if I ever get taken hostage...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>With Maya, that possibility always seems to loom in the not so distant future. *gulp*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">I'm so happy that you got your Sacred Urn back.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, I have you to thank for that, Ms. DeLite! ...A-And I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Huh...? What are you apologizing for?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Because I mistakenly blamed your husband for taking it...</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Ha! I told you, didn't I? My Ronnie could never do such a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Do you know about this?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Oh, is that a letter addressed to my Ronnie? Sorry, but I hate it when people poke their noses into other people's business.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It looks like Ms. DeLite doesn't know about it... Which means she has no idea that her husband was being blackmailed...</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Huh...? What are you apologizing for?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Because I mistakenly blamed your husband for taking it...</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Ha! I told you, didn't I? My Ronnie could never do such a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">That's Ronnie's wallet.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It was found at KB Security on the night of the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Ronnie and I went out to dinner early that evening... I'm sure he had his wallet with him then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So it's true then. He must have dropped it at the crime scene...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Ah! I know what that is! That's one of those key cards from Ronnie's company. ...Come to think of it, it's been a long time since I've seen one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's probably because Ron doesn't work there anymore...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">So this is Mask☆DeMasque, huh? I wonder what kind of a house he lives in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who knows... Maybe it's exactly like this house.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Ha ha ha, you're so funny sometimes, Nicky boy. But if I was a famous thief, I'd live in a great big, gorgeous mansion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'll be sure to tell that to your husband.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Oh, this girl. I saw her slap Nicky boy right across the face.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, ah, yeah, she did... <thought>Of all the ways she could remember Pearls by... Why?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">She's such a little cutie. If you could bring her by, I'd love to meet her.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sure! Of course!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great... I can tell I'm in for a reprise of the "Hundred Hand Slap"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">I know he doesn't look it... But he can really get things done when he puts his mind to it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? So when exactly does he put his mind to it?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">...Well. Not very often, I admit. ...But I'll never forget the first time we met as long as I live.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It must be nice to have such a fond memory like that...</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">I'll never forgive this man. He tried to pin his own crimes on my Ronnie.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't blame you!</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">All criminals are the same! They're nothing but filthy, sneaking liars! I hate their guts!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*gulp* OK, I think I get it... ...And I think I can see why Ron didn't tell her how he was earning that money.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Oh, this is the guy who delivered Ronnie's wallet. He's got some "issues". doesn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Let's just say his flirting style is pretty obvious. ...Pretty stale too, actually. It's pretty sad when the only thing you remember about a man are his lame pick-up lines.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's even more sad is said man probably believes in those like they're his life-lines.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Looks like he blew it again, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Grrr, I don't like this man one bit. He's had it in for my Ronnie from the very beginning. It's his fault that Ronnie is under suspicion of committing murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Plus, he lobbed a coffee grenade at me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You looked pretty silly wearing that mug on your head like a birthday hat... Oh, I know! We can get him back tomorrow by returning fire with a milk grenade!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So I guess this is where it all went down, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The walls in here look thick... just you'd expect in a CEO's office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What has that got to do with anything...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! It's you guys!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, it's Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Today was a real train wreck for you guys, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sure was, pal! That prosecutor made real fools out of us...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah... I feel for you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, that's not like you at all... I thought you'd be more like... "Oh, that was great! You guys got what you deserved, pal! Ho ho ho ho!" Or something to that effect.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">D-Do I really sound like that to you, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If the Gumshoe fits...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um... Well, anyway... The point is I can tell when someone puts their heart into their jobs. And I can sympathize when things don't go your way. ...Sometimes, I feel like "wrong" is the only way things go for us detectives.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, I had no idea Detective Gumshoe was such a nice guy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now if this little love-fest is over, maybe we can start investigating...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! This safe is unbelievable...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet four Pearls would fit in there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And it's got a bunch of doohickeys attached to it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's pretty amazing alright. Motion sensors, heat sensors, weight sensors...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick. Come on! Let's open it and take a look!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If I broke into one of these, wouldn't that set me down the path to hoodlumville?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This rope... You think it fell out of the safe when it was opened?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I don't think so.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I think this string shows where and how the corpse was lying.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-Y-You mean... The victim... H-He was killed by being crushed by the safe door?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sh-She can't be serious... Can she...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Look at that huge framed photo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tall mountains rising majestically against a dark and cloudy sky...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's a title written at the bottom of the photo. "The Greatest Sunrise of My Life"... This is it? This was his best sunrise?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Either this guy didn't get out enough or he had really rotten luck with the weather.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe if he had lived a little longer, he would have seen some better days.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be the CEO's desk. It's a lot simpler than I would have thought.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, that looks like a super soft chair. Let me try it out, just for a second... Ooh. Nice... I feel just like a CEO. Hey, you! Whip me up a cup of some really expensive import tea and some scones! Move it! ...Ahhh, this is the life.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, the victim sat in that chair just before he was brutally killed, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">EEEEEEEK!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Check out this big, thick binder here...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Leave the heavy lifting to me, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Reading a file isn't exactly back-breaking work, just a little hard on the eyes...</thought> ...Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-What did you find out, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This file... It's not about any sort of security operations or anything! This huge file is all about Mask☆DeMasque! It's filled with info on him!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? What kind of info?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's filled with incredibly detailed information about his methods and the crime scenes.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...? Hey, Nick. Look at the last page!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a list. Let's see... "Tear of Emanon... $100,000" ...This looks like a list of all the treasures that Mask☆DeMasque stole.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So then "$100,000" is the value of the stolen item?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I don't know, that number sounds kind of low to me. <thought>I think I'd better secretly make a copy of this list.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, there's a button here. Let's see...</line>
<line speaker="Buzzer">*BEEP BEEP BEEEEEEEEEP!!*</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! Cut it out! Don't press that!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ha ha ha! That was pretty funny. I never knew Detective Gumshoe could jump like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is that button anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's an emergency buzzer! It says it right there on the panel!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oops, you're right! It's written right there! Nick, how many times have I told you to read the instructions first!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This alarm's connected to the basement guard room. It's used to summon security up here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Really? Then it's possible on the night of the crime...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh! So when the CEO was attacked... ...do you think that maybe he pressed the buzzer...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, I thought about that, so I asked around down there... ...but they said that the buzzer never went off that night. Also, we couldn't find any fingerprints on the buzzer. Mr. Bullard, the victim, wasn't wearing any gloves, by the way. Just so you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I think we'd better go and talk to that guard about this emergency buzzer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These look like some kind of bookshelf/rolling cabinet hybrid.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Nnnnnf! I can't get in between these two shelves!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't strain yourself trying. It looks like the shelves are controlled by a special panel.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So I guess it's one shelf at a time, huh? Looks like they're filled with bunches of files.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, files filled with data about security jobs they were hired to handle.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It'd be a good night's reading. ...If you've got insomnia. I was hoping for something a little bit more exciting... Like UFOs or something.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Detective Gumshoe. Tell us what you know about the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm, OK. But the thing is, I'm really not supposed to...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, come on! What about how we "put our hearts into our work"? Things are really "working against us" right now and we need help...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OK, OK! I tell you! Just don't start crying on me, OK pal?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">OK. I won't cry on you, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The victim's name is Kane Bullard. He was the CEO of KB Security and a pretty big fella in his own right. His corpse was discovered at 9:00 this morning... His estimated time of death was 1:00 in the morning on October 12th. Cause of death was blunt force trauma to the head. Probably an object in this room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It happened at exactly the same time that Mask☆DeMasque was stealing the urn, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So why did it take almost an entire day to discover the body?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's a good explanation for that one. Bullard's body was stashed away inside the safe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Safe...? <thought>Well, it is pretty big...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nobody had heard from him, and when they opened the safe this morning, out he came...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, so the body fell out... <thought>That white string must be the shape from when he fell out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I think we still need some more information about Mr. Billiard...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe you could start by getting the man's name right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, umm... What happened to Mask☆DeMasque?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He's at the detention center screaming like a madman... "Investigate me agaaaaain!" he keeps yelling.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, no no. I didn't mean him. He's not the real thief anyway, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, you mean that "Detective" Atmey? Ho ho ho ho ho... Oh, that was great! That guy got what he deserved! Ho ho ho ho!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now that's the Detective I know and love.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Think about it... Atmey was always around when a calling card showed up. But he always mysteriously disappeared when the heists took place! "I was hiding at the crime scene"... Heh! Yeah right! That's the lamest thing I've ever heard! That's how you just knew he was the thief!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That would explain how he was able to retrieve the stolen item he keeps bragging about.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, he just did that to make himself look like a great detective. That's all. ...But there's this one thing I can't figure out about his first heist...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His first heist...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, the "Tear of Emanon" case. There was a witness on that one.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A witness...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Here, I saved the newspaper clipping... Since the thief is already under arrest, you guys can keep it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, this guard here... Haven't I seen him somewhere before?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's pretty small so it's kind of hard to see, but now that she mentions it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh! That prosecutor! I really don't like that guy! The way he used our own evidence to do that to Mr. DeLite...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, I think he did it that way just 'cause he knew it'd hurt more... That's what my gut tells me anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So who is that java addicted, masked maniac anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Prosecutor Godot? He's quite the enigma, huh? The thing is, pal... I never even heard of the guy before. He just showed up one day at the prosecutor's office. ...Came outta nowhere.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right, he said this was his first case as a prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And it's true... According to the records, anyway. But! No way he's an amateur. He's an iceman in court, a maverick that give [sic] me goosebumps.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Goosebumps...? You?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. I knew something was off about him, so I asked around... Nobody would talk to me... They all just turned the other way.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Poor Detective Gumshoe... I had no idea you were so unpopular...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah, no. That's not what I meant...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That Godot guy acts like he knows me and has a grudge against me... I get the feeling he's hiding some kind of dark secret...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you tell us some more about Mr. Bullard?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He was the CEO of KB Security, right? What kind of company is it anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, the company basically sends security teams out to buildings to guard them. Mr. Bullard must've had the chance to learn a lot of secrets doing this kinda work.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? And?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And... I don't know how to put this, but the guy was kind of a moneygrubber.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? Me too! I just love money! I can't ever get enough!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Please stop leaning in towards me like that... You aren't getting to my wallet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Anyway, it looks like he did some pretty shifty stuff to earn his millions.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! So that's my problem! I think I need to be shifter!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Lemme go already...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Apparently he was involved in selling trade secrets between rival companies.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh, that's pretty dirty and underhanded.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. Oh! KB Security used to head security operations against Mask☆DeMasque.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, and after screwing up so many times... ...the company's reputation really took a nosedive.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So it really was Bullard who sent Ron the blackmail letter, huh...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm, so about this...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! Thanks, pal! How did you know I had a sore throat anyway? ...*chomp*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! What are you doing!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ack! Sorry, that thing's all smooth and shiny, so I thought it was a piece of candy or something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't believe you ate the whole thing in one go...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I almost swallowed it too, pal...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ohh... My poor Magatama...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I still got no idea why Mask☆DeMasque would go after a broken old pot like...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">*glare*</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah, I mean this tasteful, old family heirloom...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good point. Why go after a worthless piece of junk like...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">*glare*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, um... I mean worthless in a good way I mean, this is a first for the guy... <thought>Adrian Andrews hired Atmey as security before the calling card even came... I wonder if that has anything to do with how things played out...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The thief in the photo taken by the security camera is missing his broach...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup. The thing is, there's no evidence that the photo was tampered with. It was definitely taken at 12:58 AM.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I turned the tables at the trial today with the mystery of this missing broach. I wonder if there's something more to this missing piece of costume jewelry?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So Detective Atmey wasn't hit in the back of the head after all?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's right. Because he was the real thief! He wanted it to look like he was knocked out... So he bent it on purpose. I'd stake my reputation on it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Grrr... What kind of a creep would ruin an antique for that...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About this blackmail letter...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, I've been thinking a lot about it, too, pal. Why would Kane Bullard have been blackmailing Ron DeLite anyway...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Mr. DeLite used to work at KB Security, right? But what was it that made him quit?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, that's it! Maybe that's the same reason he's being blackmailed!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well... I'm in the middle of investigating that right now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh... Alright.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is proof that Ron DeLite was here at the crime scene when the murder happened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>His wallet... and this key card, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I think we need to ask Mr. DeLite some more about those two things.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm, so about this...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! Wait a minute, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We copied that data without permission... Don't show it to him. He might get mad at us.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So? What are you whispering about?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Err... Oh, it's nothing. It's just my billfold.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's a pretty thick billfold you got there, pal. ...Now I really want you to show it to me.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This was his first heist, and I guess I underestimated him. I was sure I was going to get him, so I was careless and lost the info on the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By witness, do you mean the guard in this photo?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, he and the detective worked together to try catching Mask☆DeMasque...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But, he got away anyway, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That guard... I got the weird feeling that I've seen him around lately.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! That's Ms. Mia Fey! She was a truly beautiful person, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? You knew her? You knew my sis?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure. Everybody in the police force knew her. ...We all lost a great friend that day... I-I just got something in my eye...! ...I'm not crying!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You're such a familiar face to me now, you know? And now that I think about it, you're the real victim in this case, right? But for some strange reason, it's hard to think of you as a victim, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're darn right I'm the victim! That was our most precious treasure!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ha ha. You know, pal... I think I know why I can't think of you as a victim, ever.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I kind of feel sorry for him. He's kind of a sad young guy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, and he seems to have a habit of always getting arrested prematurely.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, it's just my personal opinion, but... I think the police should've investigated the whole thing more carefully.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But weren't YOU the one that arrested him with a giant goofy smile on your face...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come on, we don't have time to start with that. Let's just leave it alone.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I know I look a little rough around the edges. But the truth is, I'm a lot more "detective-like" than I used to be.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? Like what part?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Like the color of my coat.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, but what about what's inside the coat...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I always knew there was something suspicious about this guy! And I was right! It turned out that DeMasque was really that "Ace Detective" in disguise!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You really thought that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? Of course! It's the stone-cold truth! Sooner or later, a guy like that always shows his true colors...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, well I think we saw a little too much of his colors today...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah... I gotta agree with you on that one.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The guy is a real puzzle, if you ask me. Then maybe I should be asking you! Do YOU know something about him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why would I know something?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, it sure sounded like you two each other from the way you acted today.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's Mr. Godot that acts like he knows Nick, not the other way around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Exactly. You'd think I'd remember someone like him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I still say the whole thing's a bit suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Detective Gumshoe! Tell us more about Mr. Shane Bluebard!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's "Kane Bullard", not "Shane Bluebard", pal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh yeah... The victim in this case just doesn't make much of an impression on me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, you were the victim up until Mr. Bullard was found dead.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, and his body wasn't discovered until this morning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anyway, we don't have enough information yet. Can you help us out?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry... I'm actually a little confused myself. For some reason, I'm just blabbing like an idiot right now...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">OK, Nick! Now is our chance to get more info about the victim, so hurry up and ask!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Detective Gumshoe... About this right here...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry... It's hard to believe, but there's a limit to how much my brain can hold. I got two ears and two eyes, but I only got one brain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can see your eyes and the years... ...but the jury is still out on the brain thing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick, if you have something to say, just come out and say it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Detective Gumshoe. What about this person?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry, pal... To be honest, my head is so full right now it feels like it's gonna burst.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Note to self: Keep hair away from Gumshoe's head.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's the victim in this case. "Lame Blowhard"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, it's "Kane Bullard"!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I know, but he looks so ugly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, why don't you remember at least the "Bull" part of his name and riff off of that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Now that you mention it, I guess he does kinda look like an ugly old bull.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... We still don't know very much about this victim.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, he's the one who sent the blackmail letter to Mr. DeLite, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks that way. <thought>But we still need to look into this guy some more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Oh, I know him... This is Ronnie's boss, the CEO guy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, now he's an ex-boss. Someone killed him last night.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Naturally, I know that. He was a pretty sly man, let me tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh really...?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">You bet he was. He made Ronnie "Chief" of one of the security teams. But that was just so he could work him like a slave.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Did Mr. DeLite ever have a problem with Mr. Bullard himself?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even if he did, you think she'd ever tell you about it...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Well Ronnie isn't the type to complain about that kind of thing. I tried to get him to talk to me about work, but he never would.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow... This is really something else.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">For a security guard office, it sure doesn't feel very secure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"KB Security Guard"...! Uh oh, I just remembered... Larry might be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey, Nick! Wassup!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh! So he IS here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yo! How's it hanging, dude? And you got my sweet little Maya with you, too!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hi, Larry!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Here I was working my fingers to the bone... And in walks an angel! I've got no problems with a daytime date. It's all good!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, that's not what we're here for. We're investigating the Bullard murder case.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...Huh? Oh yeah! That's right! You're a lawyer, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's so hopelessly clueless.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, if it's about the murder case, boy have I got some good info for you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really!? What is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hmm... Well, I don't mind sharing with my sweet little Maya. But Nick here is a different story!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But Larry, I thought you two were old school buddies...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That was then and this is now.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's my partner's seat.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your... partner?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, that's what I call her. She's my superior, actually. ...Kind of a weird old lady.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... There's tea spilled all over that machine, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh, don't worry about it. Just the other day, I spilled some chocolate milk on mine. It still works fine, more or less. They really know how to build them, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something is written on this poster in fine print.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"A Guard's 5 Commandments" ...Wow, this sounds serious. Let's see what it says... #1: Obey thy superior #2: Respect thy superior #3: Smile at thy superior #4: Salute thy superior #5: Buy donuts for thy superior upon command It's signed, "Wendy Oldbag, Head Supervisor".</line>
<line speaker="Butz">She's one tough old bird, let me tell you. Cross her and you come face-to-face with her real, genuine ray gun!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, sounds scary alright.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, fortunately she's on vacation. That's why I'm so relaxed right now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Hey, Larry. That's your jacket, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... Did you know you hung it right on top of some kind of lever?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah, sure. I was told to never, ever, touch that lever. She scowled and huffed at me, "Something terrible will happen if you do! Got it, greenhorn?"</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...So why hang your jacket on such an important lever?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Because it got me curious. If the jacket's weight pulls the lever down, that's what they call an "accident". Doesn't the suspense just kill you? Don't you want to know what'll happen? Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's true... It's killing me, too! What about you, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, but for a different reason...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Take a look at these things here! Hey! Hey, Larry! What are they!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you say, "Hmm"?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey, man. It's not like I have to know what they are to do my job. I... I always thought they were just some kind of decoration or something.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh boy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How did this guy ever get a job here anyway...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Those screens there show what's going on all over the building. Everywhere. And it's my job to keep a steady eye on them. All of them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wouldn't sound so smug if I were you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Can you watch regular TV on these, too?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If anyone would sit here and watch TV instead of working, it's Larry.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey, Maya, I'm a pro. OK? Besides, you can't get regular TV on it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And how do you know that, Larry?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Because that was my first bit of investigation, if you know what I mean. ... I know what you're thinking! It was a professional investigation, alright!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's my workstation. Pretty cool, huh? I keep a steady eye on the monitors and use that mic for communicating.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look at all this equipment. It must be hard to operate.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">No biggie. I think there's an instruction manual somewhere in this room.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Somewhere"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Instruction manual"...? What are you going to do in an emergency?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, I guess I'd start by calmly looking for the instruction manual. During that time, my partner, the old lady, would calmly look for her reading glasses. That's what us security professionals call "teamwork".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even Maya and Pearls could run this place better.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! What's that supposed to mean!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what's this "good info" you were talking about, Larry?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey! I'm a guard! A pro! I can't just give away information for free!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He wants a bribe? I thought professionals were more, I don't know... HONEST!?</thought> ...Can you talk to him, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Larry! Tell us already! What's the "good info"!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey, I like that! This kitten has got some claws! OK, you really want to know?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes, yes! So tell me!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">OK. So the thing is... Ron DeLite was an employee here. And naturally since I'm a pro, I looked into his background. Follow me?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes, you're a pro! I follow you! Go on!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well one year ago, Ron DeLite was fired! And there was no warning at all! It just happened all of a sudden! I know this is a small company, but I think that was pretty awful.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess he must have done something bad to have gotten fired like that.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Like maybe skipping out of work to go pick up hot chicks or something...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No, that's just you...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what is it like to be a part-time security guard?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Lemme tell you, it's tough. Well, you know me... I get by alright, I guess. First, I have to keep my eye on those monitors. All the time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Monitors?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">There are security cameras set in each room around the building. It's really hard! Sometimes I feel like my eyes are gonna fell out!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">And if I see something suspicious, I have to contact one of the teams.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What "teams"?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">The security teams for this company. They're supposedly the best in the business. But I'm no amateur either, so if it's something small, I don't bother calling them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So in other words, you basically watch TV screens all day long...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were in this office when the murder took place, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wh-Why do you say that? This is just a part-time job for me! And I can't operate the equipment! And I'm dumb!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even if it is part-time and you are dumb, you're still in charge of security here!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey gimme a break! Don't try to pin the whole thing on me! That's not fair, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't think you can expect someone like him to take any responsibility.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anyway, the point is you were here that night, right?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh no, I knew something smelled bad, and it was the Butz after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, it's like I always say. That was then and this is now. OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looks like I'm going to have to break his Psyche-Lock after all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Larry, I want you to tell me about the night of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Aw, man. Why do we have to talk about that?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wh-Why don't we talk about what we're gonna do tonight instead, Maya!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh... I won't get anywhere if I can't break this Psyche-Lock... I think I have to present Maya's Magatama to get the ball rolling here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Larry, there's something I want you to look at...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey, Nick. I told you. I'm a pro. And you don't interrupt a pro when he's working. I don't have time to sit and chat with you, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, is that right...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh! Heh heh, naturally I've got time for YOU though, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We're gonna have to squeeze this guy if we want to get more info out of him, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the night of the crime, were you working hard like you were supposed to?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What? Huh? Of-Of-Of Of course I was! Why wouldn't I have been?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But didn't you sneak out of work just yesterday to go see Ms. DeLite?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Ah...! B-But that was that... and-and this is this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is there any chance that you snuck out of work last night, too...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Never! I didn't sneak out! I tell you what! I'll even bet you a dollar!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A dollar, wow! Now that's confidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">What's with that drenched in the rain puppy look on your face!? Do you have evidence that I left my position or are you just pulling my chain!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The evidence that Larry was not manning his station when the murder happened is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the key card to the CEO's office, right?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Y-Yeah, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This key card was found inside a wallet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Whew... I was scared for a minute...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmmm... Larry seems pretty relieved...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">But I tell you I'm not relieved! I'll even bet you 70 cents!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm going to break this Psyche-Lock if it's the last thing I do!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">What's with that baby who had his favorite toy taken away from him look on your face?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This wallet... You know about this, right?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I've never seen it before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Liar! You hand delivered this wallet to Ms. DeLite just yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Gimme a break! You can't just expect me to remember every little thing that happens!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I do expect you to remember something that happened just yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What time was it when you found this last night?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I guess it was around 1:00 in the morning on the first floor of our company building.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">1 o'clock... In the morning...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. In other words, Larry... At the time the of the murder, you were away from the security guard office!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">AAAAAAAAH!!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Y-Y-Yeah, B-B-But! th-there's something you didn't think about!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">My shift that day didn't start until 10:00 PM! The murderer might have snuck in before then!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">If the murderer had snuck in before 10:00 PM... ...then it wasn't my fault! It was the fault of the guy whose shift was before mine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I have the feeling that he still doesn't get the seriousness of this...?</thought> Listen up, Larry. We know beyond a shadow of a doubt that... the killer "snuck" into the CEO's office after 10:00 PM, during your shift!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Whew... Boy, you really had me scared!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've never seen anyone look so relieved in my whole life...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">What's with that little lamb that can't get to sleep look on your face?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I'm gonna have to rattle his cage a little bit more...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry... When you use this key card, does it leave a record?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah, it does. But I can't show the record to just anyone you know...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That key card data was already made public in the trial today.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What!? I didn't know that! Any kind of request for info like that is supposed to go through me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Boy does that sound a bit arrogant coming from a part time guard...</thought> Anyway, according to the data, the door to the CEO's office was opened with this card... Furthermore, it was most definitely used at 1 AM, the time of the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">No way!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, someone used this to get into the CEO's office. That happened at 1 AM on the night of the crime. Right in the middle of your shift!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Ooooh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry, you can't duck your responsibility this time!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">GYYYYYAAAAAAR! NOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oooh... I knew it...! It's all my fault! It's my fault that the Boss was killed! My fault!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Larry...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">There was nothing I could do! I have important issues to deal with too, man!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What happened that night anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Aaah... My Donna happened.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Your Donna?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I got a bad feeling about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah, my Donna called and said, "I have to talk to you right away..." So I went to see her and... he was standing right there next to her!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, who was?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Her new boyfriend! It was like some horrible joke! Before I knew what was going on, the guy socked me right in the kisser! Normally I'm the one that does the punching! Isn't that right, Maya!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-So is that why you left the security guard office?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">WAAAAAAH!! I'M SORRRRY! It-It-It's all my faaaaault! H-How can I ever make up for it, Nick!? What can I do!? Whaaat!? Wah haa waa...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's curled up on the floor, crying like a baby.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh boy...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...Nick! Is there anything I can do!? Anything! Just name it! I'll do whatever I have to do to make up for it! I swear I will!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey Nick, as long as he's offering, why don't you show him the evidence we've got?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's right. Maybe we'll get at least one bit of useful information from him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Niiiiiick...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm, I accidentally pressed the buzzer earlier...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah, I heard it. So that was you, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're a security guard, aren't you? Why didn't you come to the CEO's office!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, this is the 3rd floor of the basement. The CEO's office is on the 1st floor... I thought it would be a good idea to, um... adopt a wait and see approach. Plus, there's a police detective here, right!? I just didn't think it was necessary!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's as if he's trying to win an award for the laziest person on the planet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... Let's get back to talking about the night of the murder, OK? Is it true that the buzzer didn't go off that night?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There must be a record, right? You must have had a look at it, right?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Of course I did! And I couldn't possibly have made a mistake either!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you think you could take just one more look for me? Pretty please?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh, OK... I just can't say no to you, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you think, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's probably right... I don't think even Larry could make a mistake like that...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">WAAAAAAAAAAH!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-What is it? What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I-I made a mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? B-But how...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">It can't be... It's impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK, enough already! What about the records?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That night... It went off just once... In the morning... At around 1 AM...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">1 AM...? Th-That's when the m-murder happened!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">R-Really? Are you serious!? That's terrible! It can't be!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's not necessary, Nick. You don't have to threaten me. I'll tell you what I know. I know it's tough to tell, but I'm really sorry about what happened...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow, I've never seen Larry look so serious. I actually believe him...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah... He's like a totally different person...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">In that case, maybe you and I should get reacquainted.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is one of Kurain's greatest treasures.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I used to have zero interest in all of this old, junky stuff... But, now that I'm a new person, well... I can kinda see the appeal. Hey! I got it! Why don't we all go visit one of those musty old temples next time? </line>
<line speaker="Maya">...I think I could actually learn to like this new Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, but he still hasn't told us anything useful.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Umm... Listen carefully, OK, Nick? I know you don't think much of me as a person... But I'm no thief. And I would never wear a goofy getup like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Nobody ever accused you of being a thief.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">It's too much work for me. Making plans, writing calling cards, etc., etc... I'd rather just pull a dine and dash at a burger joint.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Burgers!? I love burgers, too!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Really? Well, how about it? Wanna go on a burger date tonight?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...At least pay for the food, because I'm not defending you again.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm, so what about for this...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh!? Maya, you shouldn't have! A love letter for me!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh, no. Sorry. This is a blackmail letter.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Whaaaaat!? How do you know about that, Maya!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">How much is Alexis demanding this time!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Who is this "Alexis"?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Didn't we show him this letter yesterday, too? I'm pretty sure we did...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Ah! That's the wallet I found!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You found it when you snuck out of work to get socked in the kisser, right?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...I didn't "sneak out of work to get socked in the kisser". If only I had been more responsible at work... I might have spotted the murderer on the monitor like I was supposed to...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Larry... You really do feel bad, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah, well... Maybe it's all for the best. ...I think it's brought Dessie and I closer together. Just like they say, "Every cloud has a silver lining". "You gotta see that old water glass as half-full", Am I right...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Now he's starting to sound like the Larry I know.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't forget, Nick! Half-full!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So was this the card that was used by the culprit that night...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, going off the serial number, then yeah. This card was used to open the CEO's office door at 1:00 in the morning. Your client had this card, right? Then it's a no-brainer. He's the killer, man.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... The buzzer in the CEO's office is directly connected to this room, right?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's right! Just like my heart is connected to yours, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Go ahead. Maya. Press the buzzer in your heart! I promise I'll come running to your rescue, like the professional guard I am!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow... That was pretty good.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Heh heh, thanks. I try!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you think you could tell us about the buzzer now?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes, please! Please tell us!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">OK... I guess so. Prepare to be wowed!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">You guys have really made me reflect on the way I've been living... But, the only problem is, with all this reflecting... Where is the time for love? Frankly, I think reflecting is a bit overrated, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-What are you going on about, Larry!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Plus, do you honestly have any new info on the buzzer record?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh? The record? Ah, no... Nothing at all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This guy reflects about as much as a piece of black carpeting...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">You're 26 years old, right? Don't you think it's about time you took a long, hard look at your life?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh, sure.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">The only time you can really screw up and hope to recover from it is when you're young!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Well, I guess so...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Naturally I'm not talking about you, Maya! You're already perfect!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's hard to imagine Larry not screwing up at any age.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Seeing her makes me remember how important it is to stay young at heart! Even when you grow up, you gotta keep the part of your heart that's still pure...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're so right about that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm impressed that you can still think like that, Larry. After all, you went through some pretty tough times as a kid...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh? I did?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something tells me it's more about self-induced amnesia than having a pure heart...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh, this guy? The detective? He was here before, drilling me with a ton of questions.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? Like, what did he ask?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Um, let's see... I can't remember.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, you know... just a bunch of boring stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Detective Gumshoe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">WHOA! WHO is this! Come on, man, don't hold out on me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Forget about it. You don't need to know and I'm not telling you.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey now! I thought we were pals! I got a MAJOR thing for girls with black sleeveless shirts and glasses!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How do you know that!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">And if they have an orange-colored memo pad, I really lose my cool!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He has to be making that up... He can't really know Adrian... Can he...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">I'm 25 now. It's about time I started giving some serious thought to my life.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good! That's the way you be! ...What exactly are you thinking about, though?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, you know... My future, my dreams...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Larry, when exactly does this "future" of yours start?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">A man's life begins at 30! ...That's my theory anyway. I figure I got another 5 years of guilt-free screw-ups before I have to buckle down.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry, I think... Forget it. We're just gonna have to have a nice long talk next time...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">The CEO of our company. He was a pretty good guy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah, you bet! You know how I'm not very good about working hard, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, yeah, I kinda noticed...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, guess what the boss said to me about that? "I don't expect much work from you, Larry. In return, just don't expect much pay."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I guess he had to follow some kind of dumb law about having security here in the building.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So, in order to pay the lowest wage possible, he went to the bottom of the barrel.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">To be honest, I really looked up to the boss. If I ever grow up to be a CEO, I wanna be just like him! And don't worry, Nick! I promise I'll hire you for security!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Umm... I think you know how much I want to help you guy, but... I really don't know what to say about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What is it, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's just that he seems so... I don't know... "pleasant".</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I'm really sorry, Nick! I swear I want to change my ways. But the thing is... I just don't have any interest in men.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This guy really needs to get his mind out of the gutter...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Larry's your stereotypical guy, alright.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Ah! M-Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mr. DeLite... Did they finish their interrogation?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Yes, but...! P-Please don't leave me alone anymoooooore!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Mr. DeLite, you lied to us before, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">W-Well... Err, you see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the same night the Sacred Urn was stolen from Lordly Tailor Department Store... ...a blackmail letter you got summoned you to KB Security to hand over some money. And then, that's where the CEO, Kane Bullard, was murdered. But... there's only one Ron DeLite, am I right? So the only question is... Where were you that night? This time I want to hear the whole truth... Your life depends on it.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">O-OK...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitors the visitor's room. He looks pretty nervous... ...standing near someone who went from thief to murderer overnight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. DeLite, do you still insist that you are Mask☆DeMasque...?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Isn't that what I've been saying since yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That was a quick response...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me about it. To be honest, it's starting to get irritating.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-But listen, Mr. DeLite! At the trial today, we learned the true identity of the thief, didn't we!?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Hee hee hee ha ha ha Aha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Ho ho ho hee hee! Take a good look, everyone! Unable to find a rival worthy of my genius, I was forced to create one by myself! Here I am! The tragic clown...</line>
<line speaker="Ron">I guess it's true... I wasn't the one who stole that urn...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Of course not. After all, you were at KB Security at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So then the person dressed up as Mask☆DeMasque in this photo...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...It's gotta be Detective Atmey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that night, you didn't go to Lordly Tailor, you went to KB Security, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Yes... I went to KB Security at the time the blackmail note said I should.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Alright... What happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Well, I used to work there, so I knew where the CEO's office was. I knocked... but there was no answer. So then I used the key card to unlock the door.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's probably when he dropped his wallet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">When I went into the CEO's office... someone was in there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Someone"...?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Then suddenly they bashed me over the head! Bam!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Was it Kane Bullard that hit you...?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">I don't know. The person ran away while I was still stunned. When I came to my senses, the sight I saw left me speechless. The dead body of the CEO was right there in front of me! I thought I'd die myself! Anyway, I thought I should do something with the body...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that's why you put it in the safe...?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">...Yes, that's right. I used to be the chief of one of the security teams, so I knew how to open it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">OK... And what did you do after that?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Well, I got out of there, for starters! I was the one who set up the security cameras in that building... ...so I knew how to avoid being spotted by them!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... All of a sudden, Mr. DeLite kinda sounds like the murderer to me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Please don't say that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mr. DeLite, is it true that one year ago... ...you were forced to quit KB Security?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Ah! H-How did you...!? I-I'm begging you! Please don't tell Dessie! Pleeeease!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">D-Don't worry. We haven't told anyone yet...</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Whew! Thank goodness... Err, no.. I umm... But I suppose I'll have to tell her sometime... She'll find out eventually.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why have you been hiding it from her anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Dessie would despise me if she ever found out I was living a life of crime. A criminal, a thief... She'd never forgive me! My marriage would be over!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Knowing that, why did you become a thief in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Because Dessie spends money like it's water. There's no job in the world that could bring in enough money... Except being a thief. At least, that's what I thought anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So he became Mask☆DeMasque for Desirée, huh...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">This blackmail letter... Is this the first one you got?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">No, of course not! But this is the first one that ever called me out to a specific location.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, did you start receiving blackmail letters after this incident...?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Yes. Just a few days after the "Tear of Emanon" heist... That first letter... It said, "I know you did it".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So someone found out about your true identity? Just like that?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Ah, it's not easy being a master thief, you know! "I've got proof that it was you, so give up!" it went on to say. So in the end, I had to give up the treasure I went through all that trouble to steal...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that right... Hey! Hang on a second! What do you mean you had to "give it up"?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Oh, don't worry. After I put the jewel in the safe-deposit box the letter specified... ...someone sent me $10,000!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No one said anything about me being worried, you know...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">After that, I started getting the plans in the mail.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">P-Plans...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are these "plans" you're talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">They were instructions on how to steal a crown or painting or some other rare treasure. They showed security blind spots, escape routes and even suggested training methods.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So you mean that the one who planned the heists wasn't you...?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">No, it wasn't. I only planned the very first one. After that, I received plans from some very kind person! Incredibly detailed plans!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It sounds like Mr. DeLite is thankful to the person that was blackmailing him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So Ron DeLite was Mask☆DeMasque after all...? But... Someone else is behind the thefts. Someone who planned it all out in detail!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">All I had to do was deposit the treasures I stole into the safe-deposit box. Then I just waited for the cash to come in the mail.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Could you try not to look so gleeful about it...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So you went after the Sacred Urn because of one of those plans, too?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Well, see... truth is, I've never seen the urn. All I did was follow the instructions and steal what I was told to steal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. DeLite... Is everything you've just told me the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Yes... B-But please don't tell Dessie. OK?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">That's kind of strange...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What is?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Up until now, Mask☆DeMasque has gone after famous works of art or treasures. Why did he suddenly decide to steal this plain-looking urn that nobody would want?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You make it sound like you had nothing to do with the theft.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Well... It wasn't me that chose to steal this urn.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This calling card... Did you send this?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">No...! Err, that is... I don't know anything about that. I mean, I had other plans for that night already...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's true... He did get that blackmail letter, after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What about Detective Atmey...? Could he be the one that sent it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks that way. I can't think of anyone else.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Yeah... That night, because of the letter, I had no choice but to go to KB Security.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Wow, this is cool! I'm really into this kind of stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh yeah? It's one of our most valuable treasures!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">If I ever get out of here, me and Dessie will go to Lordly Tailor... ...to check out the whole Treasures of Kurain Exhibit!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, OK, I guess... Just promise me you won't steal anything, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Oh don't worry! We'd going when I'm not on the job as Mask☆DeMasque.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, that's reassuring...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">This photo... This has got to be the real Mask☆DeMasque!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">I'm sure it is. I know Mask☆DeMasque when I see him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, but... This isn't you, right Mr. DeLite?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Well, err... No... I was at KB Security then.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So then... I guess it really is Detective Atmey, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So was this blackmail letter written by KB Security's CEO, Kane Bullard?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">I-I think so... Probably. You can only get into the CEO's office if you have a key card.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The blackmail letter said to meet at KB Security...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">The no one else other than Mr. Bullard could've have written the letter...</line>
<line speaker="Ron">I was at KB Security at around 1 o'clock that night... I took out my wallet to open the door with the key card...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So is that when you dropped it?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">I-I'm so sorry... I should have told you the truth earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you still doing with this key card anyway? Didn't you return it when you left your job at KB Security?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Of course I returned it! Don't be silly! Umm... But it got sent back to me along with the blackmail letter.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">With the blackmail letter...?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Yes, it said... "Use this to enter the CEO's office".</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Oh! I didn't know Mask☆DeMasque had become so famous!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, I actually bought this publicity photo!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Really? Well, I'd be happy to sign it if you like! I'll even add, "Behind Bars!"</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes! Please! Please!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looks like Ron had totally forgotten about what happened at the trial today... That he was declared "not guilty" of being Mask☆DeMasque...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This list... We found it in the office of the CEO, Mr. Bullard.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Hey! This is a list of all the things Mask☆DeMasque stole!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's the value of each item listed next to them. "100,000 dollars"... "150,000 dollars"...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Are you sure that's the value of the stolen items?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Hmm... The numbers seem a little low to me. Even on the black market, the prices should be at least three times higher than that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess he knows about that stuff because he used to be a security guard...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">That's the emergency buzzer from the CEO's office. Don't press it! It makes a terrible racket!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hee hee. Sorry. I just love making a lot of noise.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Err, umm... Does this buzzer have something to do with this case?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, at this point, I don't really know yet. <thought>After all, there were no prints on it, or anything else for that matter.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">Hey! This is an article about my debut heist! Boy, that was a tough one. Before I knew it, they were hot on my trail.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But Mask☆DeMasque... He must have gotten away, right? It says in the article that he "disappeared"...</line>
<line speaker="Ron">That's right! I got a sudden burst of inspiration! I hid my Mask☆DeMasque costume in a nearby plastic bucket... Then I quickly changed into my security guard uniform. ...Pretty clever, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow... Awesome! ...Hey, hold the phone! The guard in this photo... Is that you, Mr. DeLite?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Hee hee. That's right. Nice trick if I do say so myself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nice and easy to figure out! Even Pearls could see through that in a heartbeat.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">But as you might expect, Detective Atmey found the disguise... He truly deserves the title of "Ace Detective".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Atmey found the Mask☆DeMasque disguise? <thought>Hmm, that's interesting...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">Yes, and I heard that he brought it home with him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's it... That's when Atmey got his hands on this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">Thanks to that, I got the chance to remake my costume.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That must have been really time-consuming, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Yes, it took quite a while to complete. Anyway, a few days after that... I received the first of the blackmail letters...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-Blackmail letters!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What are you talking about? Hurry! Tell me what you mean!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">H-Hey, calm down...! Don't get so worked up...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The buzzer went off just once around the time that Bullard was killed.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Oooh! Th-That's scary!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know anything about that, Mr. DeLite?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">...Sorry, I'm afraid I don't.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why am I not surprised by how clueless he is anymore...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. DeLite, are you absolutely sure about this testimony? That you stole the treasures as you were directed by a series of blackmail letters...</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Yes, and I got money for them in return. It seemed like a good deal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He doesn't look like he's lying...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So then how do you explain Detective Atmey's crazy confession...?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">A great lawyer and so young! You really are an inspiration! I bet you make lots and lots of money, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That doesn't sound right coming from a thief, if you know what I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Ron">... I'm sorry... I suppose you could say I'm nothing but a terrible lowlife</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-Why do you say that?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">...This is the first time I've ever had to actually face a victim of one of my crimes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess he's talking about the Sacred Urn...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, but I thought that you weren't the one who stole my urn...</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Th-That's true about the urn, I guess... Maybe I should give up this life of crime and try becoming a professional cowbell player</line>
<line speaker="Ron">I'm ashamed to admit it... ...but sometimes I wonder if I'm really cut out to be a thief.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, isn't that obvious?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It doesn't suit you at all!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Uuugh... I knew it... I guess I'm not the only one who came to that conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">This is the detective that was in charge of the Mask☆DeMasque investigations. He was so happy when I surrendered yesterday that he actually shed tears of joy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What? Gumshoe cried!? Really!? Was it a single manly tear or did he let loose and sob?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Sobbed. I started weeping myself, too. It was truly infectious! A truly moving moment, if I do say so myself.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...That must've been one heck of a beautiful scene.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If beauty is in the eye of the beholder, I'm convinced that these two are blind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">Once I decided to become a thief, I started studying like crazy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Studying!? Like what? Pretty Larceny 101? The History of Pilfering?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Ha. No, but I watched a lot of movies and read a lot of novels about great thieves.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh yeah? I admire you for doing your homework, if for nothing else.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">All the great ones had their own trademarks. Flashy costumes, calling cards... ...unique laughs, and catchy slogans, like, "Farewell, my friends!" I figured I needed to do a good job with that if I was going to make a splash.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, I guess you really can't say goofy stuff like that unless you're a master thief. "Farewell" or "We shall meet again"... You know, hokey stuff like that.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">He's an Ace Detective, alright. He's been hot on my trail ever since the first heist.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes, but... He made a pretty stunning confession in court today. "It was me all along! I am Mask☆DeMasque!"...</line>
<line speaker="Ron">I don't know what to say... I guess he's just delusional.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's exactly what your wife said about you...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">Dessie... She really has a thing against criminals.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you have any idea why that is, Mr. DeLite?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Well... if you want to know the details, you'll have to ask her. But the thing is, after I lost my job at KB Security... I needed to earn money to keep Dessie satisfied... Lots of money. But... I just couldn't seem to find a good job. That's why I wound up becoming the thing that Dessie hates most... A thief.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Isn't he great! I wish I could be half as cool as him! Besides, he's the only one that really believed me when I said I was the thief!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, hang on a second! This is the guy that had you arrested for murder!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Well, I still don't think that makes him a bad person...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What in the world do you see in that coffee-crazed prosecutor!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">Mr. Bullard... my old boss. It's so sad...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you have any idea what might have happened? Was there anyone that might have wanted him dead?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Oh yeah, sure... Mr. Bullard was the type of guy who made lots of enemies. He did lots of threatening things to people...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, wait, do you mean he scared people, or that he threaten them with blackmail?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Well, I guess they're kind of the same, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think about this?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Hmm... I don't really think I can help you with that. Err, no, that's not it... It's just that the thing is I don't really know if I can say one way or the other</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I didn't really catch that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry, you didn't miss anything.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Y-Yes...? B-But please don't hurt me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Kane Bullard... Do you swear that it wasn't you who killed him?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Y-Yes, of course! I could never...! I-I'm not lying! All I did was hide his body in the safe! But then I was afraid they'd discover what I did. So I turned myself in yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, why?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Well, if the judge had ruled that I was guilty of robbery, then I'd have an alibi, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... I guess so. You're really clever, Mr. DeLite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I have no choice but to take Mr. DeLite at his word.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Mystic Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey...! Pearly!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey Pearls. So what have you been up to this whole time...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">The Sacred Urn, Mr. Nick! I took it back to Kurain Village to have it examined!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And? And? What did you find out?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Well there's no need to worry! They said it's the real urn!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whew! That's a relief! I was really worried!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But there's one small problem.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Problem?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, these cute little pink splotches... They said that it's paint... And that they were put on the urn recently!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why are we talking about the pink splotches again? What's the big deal?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's the big deal!? We've gotta find out how they got there! That's the big deal!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes, Mr. Nick! We've gotta find out how they got there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-OK, OK! We'll go find out how they got there!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">P-Please don't forget about me...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Oh, Pearl. How nice to see you.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">H-Hello there!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I haven't seen you around lately. What have you been up to?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Well, actually... I was having this urn examined!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">! O-Oh... I see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe if we take another good look at this urn... ...we can figure out the mystery of what actually happened here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Let's look around one more time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This box, there's something about it that's bothering me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's the box that the Sacred Urn was in!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It looks like there's some pink paint on it, too...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And it's definitely the same color as the stuff on the urn!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think I know how the paint got on it now...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Alright! Let's investigate again, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks to me like it's been dry for several days.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's something suspicious about this paint mark. The bottom left part of it is shaped oddly and it's shocking pink.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">This is the same color as the paint splotches on the urn!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So then the question is... What's the cause of the odd shape...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Let's look around here carefully, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks to me like it's been dry for several days.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's something suspicious about this paint mark. The bottom left part of it is shaped oddly and it's shocking pink.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! Could it be that this odd shape is...!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I'm pretty sure this is it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! That's the box the Sacred Urn was in...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you look here, there's a little bit of paint on the box as well!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, you're right! Look! It matches!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What is it, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is all turning out exactly as I thought it would...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think it's all starting to become clear... We're that much closer to solving the mystery of what happened to the urn...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks to me like it's been dry for several days.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's something suspicious about this paint mark. The bottom left part of it is shaped oddly and it's shocking pink.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! Could it be that this odd shape is...!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I'm pretty sure this is it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! That's the box the Sacred Urn was in...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you look here, there's a little bit of paint on the box as well!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, you're right! Look! It matches!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What is it, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is all turning out exactly as I thought it would...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">See? We got our Sacred Urn back.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">That's really wonderful.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... We're not entirely convinced it's the same urn. Ms. Andrews, we want you to cooperate with us.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Nnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">What a magnificent box!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're not going to throw is off the trail with flattery. I want to know about the paint on this box...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Well I... I'm sure I don't know anything about that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Some people just have a natural gift for lying... Adrian's not one of them.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Andrews, about the paint that's all over the wall...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Oh! Look at that! It looks like paint alright! Is-Isn't that funny!? I never noticed that before!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... That has to be the most pathetic acting I have ever seen in my life.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm beginning to get very frustrated.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh. I'd better do something to calm them down, and fast!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Andrews, do you know anything about the Sacred Urn?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">D-Do I know "anything"!? I'm in charge of the entire Treasure Exhibit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The urn that was submitted before the court today... ...It's obviously not the same urn as before!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">W-Well, that's... That's um... ...True! Maybe it isn't the same! It could be... It could be a fake!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...A fake?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">You're the one who said it wasn't the same! So that's the most obvious explanation! Do you have any evidence the urn that was submitted at the trial was genuine?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Ms. Andrews?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">She, look! It was a fake after all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I mean, your evidence is fake too, as I expected!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oops, I guess this isn't going to help me much...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">So I have convinced you? Or...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry to break it to you, but the urn is the genuine article. Pearls went back to Kurain Village and had it examined.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Is-Is that right? That's nice, but I don't see how...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What she discovered was that the vase was broken... again.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">D-Did you say... "again"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. It was broken once a year ago. And now it looks like the same thing has happened. And quite recently, too...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">R-Recently!? Are you saying that this urn was broken recently!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. That's exactly what I'm saying.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Why do you think it was broken recently? How do you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">... So, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Why do you think it was broken recently again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, well... B-Because... ...Umm, I just think so.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Sorry, but that's not a valid explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grr... The hunter has become the hunted!</thought> W-Well it was! It was broken recently! Come on! You know it! I'm not willing to yield to you on this point!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">G-Get a grip, please! ...Now. I'll ask you one more time, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This poster... It was made recently, right?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Poster...? Ah! The poster for the exhibit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At the time when this photo was taken, the urn said, "I AM" on it. But now, for some mysterious reason, it says, "AMI"! When the urn was fixed, the letters were transposed!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">AAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">"I AM"...? What does that ever mean? I don't know anything about that! I wasn't even there when the photo for this poster was taken.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was a mistake. Now... Tell the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Ah! W-Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">For?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Ev-Even if the urn was broken, I had nothing to do with it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Y-Yes, that's it! It must have been one of the people at the photo shoot! They probably dropped it! I'm sure that's what happened!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... It looks like I still haven't broken the entire Psyche-Lock...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Do you have any proof the urn was broken here at Lordly Tailor?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Ms. Andrews?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Umm... What is this supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This urn has these pretty little pink paint splotches on it.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And there's some on the box the urn was stored in, too! No matter how you look at it, the paint seems to be exactly the same, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">S-So? What does that prove?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That the urn was dropped along with the box! That's when they both got paint on them. ...Are you with me so far?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Y-Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The rest of story is obvious. "This box was dropped right here in Lordly Tailor's basement warehouse." ...If I can prove that, it means that the urn was broken here, too.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">So can you prove that? Can you prove that box was dropped here in the basement warehouse?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Ms. Andrews!?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Um... Actually, I think I should be the one asking the questions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Are you feeling ill, Mr. Wright? Have you been getting enough sleep? Are you sure you haven't been working yourself too hard?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh, she's turning this thing around on me now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">You really should take some time off and try to relax.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I can relax later, after I've solved this mystery! <thought>Argh! The answer is right here! I know it! Maybe I need to investigate the warehouse some more...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think you already know where I'm going to this, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Y-Yes... More or less...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's pink paint splattered on the floor and walls of this basement warehouse. But there's an odd shape imprinted into a part of the paint satin, am I right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Ms. Andrews?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Umm... What is this supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is pink paint all over this urn.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And there is pink paint all over the floor and walls of this basement warehouse. In other words... This urn was broken there!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can't weasel out of this one, Ms. Andrews.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">B-But...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh-oh. She's trying to make her escape...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">B-But you can get pink paint anywhere!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well there's none in my office, that's for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">W-Well there is in my room!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Liar!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">An-Anyway...! The paint on the urn and the paint on the floor... There's no proof that it's the same paint!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come on! This is getting ridiculous!</thought> The proof linking the paint on the urn to the paint on the floor is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Ms. Andrews!?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Um... Actually, I think I should be the one asking the questions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Are you feeling ill, Mr. Wright? Have you been getting enough sleep? Are you sure you haven't been working yourself too hard?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh, she's turning this thing around on me now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">You really should take some time off and try to relax.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I can relax later, after I've solved this mystery! <thought>Argh! The answer is right here! I know it! Maybe I need to investigate the warehouse some more...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This box... The urn was stored in this, right?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Y-Yes... That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, there's pink paint on this box as well.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think you already know where I'm going with this, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Y-Yes... More or less...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The paint on the floor has an odd shape imprinted in it, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Ms. Andrews?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I knew I was right about you, Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">You're a softie at heart, aren't you...? I knew you'd never hurt me on purpose. What a relief...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grrr, I guess that wasn't the right piece of evidence.</thought> I-I think you're mixing up the me of a year ago and the me of today, Ms. Andrews!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Well then... Prove me wrong by coming up with the right answer!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Y-Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you put this box into the impression in the paint, you can see it fits perfectly.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which means this box was dropped right here! And that... is when the urn was broken!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Your name does justice, Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I'm so sorry... I was the one... The one who broke the urn.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Boy does this make me feel like some sort of evil school teacher.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I'm a terrible person! Not only did I break it, but I tried to hide what I did!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well... That's not so hard to understand. Is it, Pearly?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">N-No, not at all! I... know just how she feels!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">It happened about 2 weeks ago. Just after the poster photo was taken, on the same day the urn arrived here... ...I thought I'd put it away down here for safe-keeping. I was carrying it in the box... ...when I tripped on a paint can and lost my balance! The box I was carrying crashed to the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I heard a terrible noise and I thought my heart was going to stop... Fearing the worst, I opened the lid of the box and that's when it happened! The broken pieces of the urn fell out of the box and landed right in the paint! I... I... I was in shock... And let out a huge scream!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Hmm. I can totally see how that could've happened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, as clumsy as she is, I'm sure Maya understands...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Well, I knew it was the most important treasure in all of Kurain Village... ...so I tried as hard as I could to fix it. Fortunately, the shards were pretty big.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And that's when the "I AM" got changed to "AMI"?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I-I didn't know how it was originally written. But any sane person fixing it would have assumed it said, "AMI"...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">A-Any sane person...? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, Pearls... She said she wasn't very good at spelling...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Anyway, I put the urn into the storeroom and no one had seen it since then.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But... There's something I don't get... When we first came here, I didn't see any paint stains.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Well, that's because it was so ugly and embarrassing. I used the golden statue to cover it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The Ami Fey statue... Aha!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The first time that we came down here... It was on the night that the Sacred Urn was stolen.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But Mr. Nick... There were no paint marks on the walls or floor of the warehouse when we were here.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Well, there's a good reason for that. On the day of the crime, around noon... ...that golden statue just happened to arrive from the mountain training hall.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A-And?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I realized that the statue would be the perfect size for covering up the paint stains. That's why... I put it where you first saw it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see... Now it makes perfect sense.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, but there's still one thing I find strange...</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">What is it, Pearl?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">The day after the urn was stolen, we came here again... At that time, the statue had been moved and the paint was clearly visible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's right about that...</thought> Well, Ms. Andrews?</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">Huh! What? I, err... I don't know anything about that! I placed it there to cover the paint, so why would I move it again?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well then who was it? Who would have done it and why...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>On the day before the theft, the statue was definitely closer to the door! Then the next day, it was moved. But why...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like... ...there's some connection between the Sacred Urn and the murder case.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-Why? Why do you think so, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because that night... the real thief, Ron DeLite, was at KB Security. ...So then why did another Mask☆DeMasque show up here? A lot of different things are pointing to one undeniable fact.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">One undeniable fact...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The murder trial is starting tomorrow... It looks like that thief is going to be making another appearance...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think I have enough evidence yet... I should investigate and gather some more clues before I try again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nnrgh! I've made too many mistakes!</thought></line>
</xml>