<xml>
<title>The Great Witch</title>
<line speaker="Layton">...The Great Witch Bezella. The legendary witch from ancient times. She is the source of all evil, and the one who gives rise to all other witches. As long as the Great Witch Bezella is alive, there will always be witches in Labyrinthia. Apparently, that is the commonly held belief. Therefore, if Bezella were to be put to the fire, there would be no further need for these trials.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In other words: no Bezella, no witches, right? But...how does all that implicate Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">By the way, Professor. You seem to know a lot about all this.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The professor and I discovered a mural of the Great Witch Bezella in a room below the library... And it looked like it was painted a long time ago, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean like a wall painting...of Bezella?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. There were some historical remains hidden beneath the library. We found it there. At any rate, I'd very much like to investigate Bezella in greater detail. I'm afraid my knowledge extends no further than the legend known to the townspeople.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">In that case, I guess we have no choice but to ask Espella. Maybe she can tell us why she's accused of being Bezella...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, yeah, but... Didn't they tell us we can't see her for a while?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">C'mon, we've never let that stop us before!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urgh... And that, Maya, is how we always end up in all sorts of trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, fine! Just leave it to me. It's nothing that a little sweet talking can't fix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, I'm not so sure that's a good idea...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Look, pal! We need to see Espella! It's a matter of life and death!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm not sure I would qualify that as "sweet talk", but rather more of a full-on assault.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Did you not hear what Inquisitor Barnham said? Espella Cantabella is currently undergoing questioning... And while that's taking place, no one is permitted entry.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Can't you do something?!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">H-hey, keep it down, will you?! Orders are orders! No matter how many times you ask, the answer will still be no. Now be on your way, will you? Go on...go!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Access denied.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That much is obvious, Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I can't believe Mr Barnham took Espella into custody just because of that outburst.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That reminds me, something Inquisitor Barnham said has been bothering me... "It was not I who made the decision". ...I believe that's how he put it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, yeah...that's right. So in other words... there's someone of higher authority than Inquisitor Barnham, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's it! We'll just go and ask that person instead!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But who in Labyrinthia could have more authority than Inquisitor Barnham?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, I know how to find out. Let's ask around, Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Not you again... You don't give up, do you? Like I said before, you cannot see...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, it's not Espella. There's someone else we'd like to see.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's right, we'd like you to take us to see the person ranked above Inquisitor Barnham.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Above Inquisitor Barnham...? You...you're not telling me that you want to see the High Inquisitor?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............! So they're called the High Inquisitor, then?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">What's this? Are you seriously suggesting that you don't even know of High Inquisitor Darklaw?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">High Inquisitor Darklaw?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's weird, I can't help but feel I've heard that name somewhere before.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm sorry, but could you tell us where we can find that person?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">P-please, do me a favour and don't ask. She's not the sort of person you can just drop in and see, believe me!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But there's something of importance we wish to discuss with her.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">You people really are fearless. Well, don't say I didn't warn you. To meet High Inquisitor Darklaw, you must go to the Inquisitors' Hall. Just be careful not to upset her.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We understand. Thank you for your assistance.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Is the High Inquisitor really so fearsome?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Of course not! Not our High Inquisitor. She's wonderful, beautiful, intelligent... just a little strict. You don't have to go mentioning what I said about upsetting her, understood?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Don't worry...you can rely on us...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">High Inquisitor...that title sounds really high up on the food chain, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Apparently, if we go to the Inquisitors' Hall, we can see her there.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, we won't achieve anything standing here. Let's go and see her.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">High Inquisitor Darklaw is in the Inquisitors' Hall. Even if you go there, I doubt she'll see you, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The guards are watching us. Or should I say, staring at us with an unspoken threat in their eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The doors to the courthouse are shut and guarded. We cannot gain entry now.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">These knights must have seen all the witch trials. Do they enjoy them or find them distressing?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So many candles, and yet it's so dark in here. Let's light some more!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The ceiling may catch fire...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This chandelier is very simple compared to the Great Archive's.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know...the candle maker must be the richest person in this town.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An old wooden bench that many woodworms would call "home" if they could speak.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Those awaiting trial sit here, on these uncomfortable, worn-out benches.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Uhm, cheers, I'd rather stand. That bench is bristling with splinters.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe this bench is a torture tool? Shall we try it out on you, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah, I can see Inquisitor Barnham over there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay. Which means that woman standing next to him must be...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">High Inquisitor Darklaw.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They look so...serious. It might be difficult to butt in. Perhaps we should wait until they've finished their conversation.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">We have prepared for the questioning of Espella Cantabella. She's in the Deathknell Dungeon. Would you like to see her now?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Barnham, I intend to leave the questioning of the girl to you.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">B-but...if she is indeed the Great Witch, shouldn't the High Inquisitor be there?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">It is not necessary that I be present, and I have much faith in your abilities.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Understood. I will not let you down.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I intend to visit the scene of the crime. You take care of things here while I'm away.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The scene of the crime? You mean...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">That's right. It's unlikely there are any clues left, though. Anyway, the questioning is yours, Barnham.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Yes, Milady.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks like they've finished talking. Um...uh, Inquisitor Barnham!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............! You...how did you get in here?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">S-sorry, sir, we didn't intend to eavesdrop.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh...Inquisitor Barnham? There's something we'd like to ask you.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ I've no time right now. You'd best leave.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's gone!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gone to question Espella...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would appear that we have to find what we need to know from the High Inquisitor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's Barnham's armour. It makes quite an impression.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It must be difficult to walk in heavy armour like that. And imagine the heat in summer!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The armour and cape are made from the finest materials, far better than what regular knights wear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A drawing of someone's scary face. Barnham has a gift for caricatures.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's Inquisitor Darklaw! The picture looks like it's used for dagger-throwing practice.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Uhm...I hope Mr Barnham and Miss Darklaw have a good work relationship...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So many memos. Magic crime is on the rise, from the looks of it.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Does Mr Barnham really need all these notes? Maybe he's just a hoarder.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww, a picture of smiling Barnham with his doggie! They look cute together.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look at that! What a sweet quill stand! I want it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It's cute. Wait, Maya, put it back where it was!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Barnham uses a dumbbell as a paper weight. I guess it makes sense when you have that many papers...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's as if Mr Barnham wanted to say, "I've got a heavy workload today."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can picture him slowly making his way through all this while Darklaw stares at him from across the room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Does Barnham use his own desk to practise swordplay on? It's badly damaged.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's amazing...that this desk hasn't collapsed yet. It's full of cracks, and bits are chipped off.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What a stark contrast with the tidy desk on the other side of the room. It reminds me of my own...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">All these notes and documents piled up on the desk... The inquisitors have a lot on their plates, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What a pretty lady...with a ruthless face and a scary sword ready to cut someone's head off...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It may symbolise the inquisitors' harsh but just judgement.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Labyrinthians seem to be fond of statues. They put them everywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A normal-looking painting. It feels like it doesn't belong here.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's a landscape painting of a house by the lake surrounded by beautiful red flowers.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I wonder if it's a real place somewhere in Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the kind of chair you can sit in all night long and not fall asleep.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The chair is elegant and of high quality, but not extravagant.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Your comments are not half as smart as the professor's, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's a splendid writing quill.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Miss Darklaw is taking very good care of that quill. It looks as good as new.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">So you are the High Inquisitor?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">From the way you talk, one would think we had already met.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm certain we have never met before. But I did have the opportunity of seeing you at the Storyteller's parade.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's right, Professor! During that parade, she was... standing right next to the Storyteller!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Storyteller... Isn't he the one who...err...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">He's known as "the Creator" in this town.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So any person who gets to stand by his side has to be someone important, right?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Did you all just come here to stand around speculating? If so, then there's a quiet cell in the dungeon which has just become vacant... You can speculate all you want in there.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Just a moment, Miss Darklaw. We have come here to talk to you.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Talk to me?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's right. It's about this trial... We'd like to ask you about it.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Inquisitors do not make a habit of discussing the details of trials with just anyone.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Just anyone? We...or in particular, he... acted as Espella's attorney. That is hardly "just anyone"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh...that's me, all right! I'm Phoenix Wright, attorney at law.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">So...you're the one. You're the Knight of the Court who opposed Inquisitor Barnham, aren't you? I received a detailed report. Yes, indeed...most interesting. Hmm... So what would you like to know?</line>
<line speaker="Layton"><thought>I should ask Darklaw about...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella was proven innocent at the last trial. Despite that, she's now been accused of being Bezella, even though there's no decisive evidence to support that claim.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Just a moment. Before we discuss that, there is one thing I need to make clear. While it's true that you acted as Espella's defender in the last trial, that does not necessarily mean to say you will be defending her again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what do you mean? Just because the trial is different, that doesn't change the fact that I'm her attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The charge against Espella Cantabella is of the gravest nature.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean the charge that she's the Great Witch Bezella?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What makes you think the accused wants you to defend her again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Does that mean that if Espella doesn't ask Nick to defend her again... then he can't request to be her defence attorney?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Correct. The Great Witch Bezella is the source of all other witches. Her defender could, by their own words, place themselves in great danger.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Knowing Espella's kind nature...I don't think she'd want to subject anyone to that risk! That's why she kept quiet earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ However, Espella is, at this very moment, undergoing questioning, is she not? And there's a possibility that she may be cleared of the suspicion of being a witch.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's right! There can't possibly be evidence of Espella actually being a witch! So how could anyone prove she is?!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Just how well do you people really think you know Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Eh?!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">On what grounds can you say that she's not a witch or that there's no evidence? I'd be glad to have you explain that to me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's not...fair.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We are certainly not experts when it comes to the Great Witch Bezella. So could you perhaps tell us more about this particular witch?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">To begin with, is the Great Witch not just a figure of legend?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The Great Witch Bezella does exist. That is a fact accepted by all of the townsfolk. In the past, the Great Witch Bezella used her evil power to burn the entire town.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...she burned the town...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, we saw that witch in the picture in the library. She was burning the town...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">If the Great Witch Bezella uses her powers, this town could burn again as it did long ago. We have to capture Bezella before that can happen.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But there's no way Espella would ever do something like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One thing I'd really like to know is... why Espella, of all people, is suspected of being Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ Of course, there is one reason...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One reason?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">From what you've told us so far, it seems there's something about Espella that we do not yet know. Something which makes the townsfolk, and you yourself, believe that she is the Great Witch Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell us...what that reason is?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">That's something you will have to investigate. As the High Inquisitor, do you think it would be in my best interests to provide you with that information?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh, please! If you could just tell us a little more!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I don't have to tell you anything! If you really want to know, find out for yourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then at least let us SEE Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, Inquisitor Barnham is questioning Espella right now, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Yes, he is. So seeing her tonight would be difficult. Try coming back tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tomorrow... All right, fine. We'll try again tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That we will!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I hope you all realise how this will look to the people of this town, when they see you all supporting the person suspected of being the Great Witch Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When it comes to rescuing Espella, I'm not worried about what people think.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And I feel the same way as Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...That is what I was hoping to hear. At the very least, you should investigate. And I pray I don't see disappointment in your eyes the next time we meet. Now, if you will excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick. I was thinking... We've met her before, haven't we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, we have. In that trial back in England.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh?! Then who on earth is she?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not entirely sure. But at that time she was a teacher from a boarding school for girls.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Was she indeed? It would seem Labyrinthia is packed full of puzzles. And this is one puzzle that I would really like to solve.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Okay then! Leave it to me. I'll give it my best shot! Uhm...where shall we begin?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">While I appreciate your enthusiasm, Luke, I wonder if it might be better to first return to the bakery. Mrs Eclaire is no doubt worried about us. We should let her know the situation.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right! We need to tell her all about the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh...I have a feeling that's not going to go too well...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I think you did very well, Mr Wright. I'm sure she'll understand.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She's like a mother to Espella. She must be worried sick about her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, everyone. Let's head back and tell her everything.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ How the court proceedings went, and the way the townspeople reacted... Espella, it would seem you do indeed have a secret...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Phew...I feel like it's been a while since we've been out here in the fresh air.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. Shall we head back to the bakery? ...Hmm?</line>
<line speaker="???">Woof-woof! Woof!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yikes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa! He's one frisky little puppy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's a cute little guy, huh? You're just begging to be petted, aren't you, boy?! Good boy, good little doggy...</line>
<line speaker="???">Ruff, ruff...ruff, ruff, woof!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">See...see! Look, Nick, he's so happy he's showing his teeth, like he's smiling!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not so sure dogs show their teeth when they're happy...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't be such a spoilsport. Come on, try petting him!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ruff-ruff...woof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right...let me give this a shot. C'mon! Here boy!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">M-Mr Wright! Don't... Don't pet him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Grrrrr... Wooof, wooof-wooof-ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah! Owwwww! Oooooh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess...even cute little puppies have a bite worse than their bark...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Are you all right, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I tried to warn you...</line>
<line speaker="???">Woof-woof, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm...I guess you can't always judge a dog by its looks.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">He may look cute, but what he was saying wasn't cute at all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-what do you mean... by what he was saying, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's right, Miss Fey. Luke can understand what animals are saying.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">WOOOOOOW! That's amazing! It's like...magic! Luke, you have magic powers just like the witches do!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Umm...given the current circumstances... I'm not so sure that's a good thing!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wish I could talk to animals... I'd love to talk to a puppy! Or even to Espella's cat, Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That puppy's way of talking reminded me a lot of Inquisitor Barnham. He said something like: "I'll only say this once, Sir Blue Knight! I, Constantine, do not permit you to stroke me!" Or words to that effect...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... So the dog's name is Constantine, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...perhaps that could have been Inquisitor Barnham's dog.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm sure of it. He ran off in the direction of the Inquisitors' Hall. Maybe he's going to meet his master.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That dog is just like his owner...constant. Constantly barking, constantly biting Nick... and constantly adorable!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So, Maya, you mean you really believe in my ability?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Trust me, Luke, when it comes to people and their special abilities, nothing surprises me. I have a few myself, you know... Okay then, let's get back to the bakery. Come on, Nick, let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah...I guess so. I think I've been bitten enough for one night... By dog...and by his owner.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Witches' Court is like a cross-breed of a courthouse and an execution place.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder why it was built so far away from the rest of the town?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This deep in the forest, no one can hear the screams of burning witches...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">However magnificent this courthouse looks, the trials that take place inside are an ugly matter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, another owl flew by.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, I saw another owl.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Owls are nocturnal animals. This forest seems to sustain quite a large population.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This adorable pup is a courageous, loyal companion. He's wearing his armour with pride.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Constantine is a smart dog. He only bites his master's rivals and enemies.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...? Did you see the leaves moving in that tree over there?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yes, I did. I wonder what it could be. Perhaps there's a bird up there. ............ ........................ Good grief!</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">Wah-dee-dah...fwoooooating down. Hu-hu...hu!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I must say, this is a surprise! I didn't expect you to drop in like that.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What were you doing up there in that tree?</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">Hu-hu...I can't tell you that. It's a maiden's secwet!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I-is that so?</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">...Do you want to know why?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um...no, it's okay.</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">Well I suppose I can tell you anyway... I was searching for fwowers.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You climbed up that tree to find flowers? You certainly are an active young lady.</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">I thought of a good way to appeal to the man of my dweams, you see. I'm going to cweate a fwower bouquet like ones the faiwies would make! ............ Am I head over heels?!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">If I give him a bouquet such as this... would he ever fall head over heels for me? Oh...I can't wait for the day when I can meet him again!</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">Oh...I'm so looking forward to the day when I next see Inquisitor Barnham and hand over the bouquet!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is very dark in there. It should not be dangerous, but we had better be careful.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">To think that a big forest like that's just outside the town!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Do you think this forest is infested with witches?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a sizeable candle inside. It can probably last all night.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The stone lantern's design is quite to my liking.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Who put that here? It totally doesn't match the style of anything else in this town.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pretty, huh? Now, try coming here at night on your own... The lone lantern would be a scary sight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The letters on the signpost are so worn out by the elements that it's almost impossible to read it.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This way goes to the courthouse, that one to the shopping district... but what about the other one?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Let's find out where that path leads some other time.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's bright here even after dusk.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps the light helps dispel Labyrinthians' fear of the witches.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Is it just my imagination, or are there fewer people around? Have they all gone home because of that story?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The opposite side is not very well lit, so it's hard to see anything from here.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The Great Archive, towering above us against the dark skies, looks truly imposing.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">At night, it looks more like a place to test your courage at rather than read books.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Unlike in the other parts of the town, buildings here are tall and magnificent.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks quite posh.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Many of the houses have shops on the ground floor and living quarters above.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can see why they chose to do the parade here. Just look at these fancy houses!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks even taller when you see it up close! I can't even see the top!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It requires a lot of architectural knowledge to construct a building of this size.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Awesome. But looking up at it gave me neck pain. Nick, can you make it go away?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It makes me feel giddy just looking up at it!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This seems to be related to the mural we saw in the Great Archive cellar.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The librarian said the fire was caused by a fire dragon summoned by Bezella, the Great Witch.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Those symbols were in the Great Archive, too.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">These flags serve to constantly remind the townspeople that their creator is watching them.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's a bit unsettling, although I can't really say why.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Labyrinthia seems surrounded by cliffs and woods. In the distance there's nothing but fog.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The fog is so thick, I can't see far.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Did someone just say something? I was miles away...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This place looks so mysterious, surrounded by the misty forest.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There are two identical statues, one on each side.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The statues portray people reading. Maybe that's supposed to motivate those who come here to read more.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe we should put a statue of someone eating bread in our bakery to boost sales.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This appears to be documentation on accidents and criminal cases.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The professor would be itching to dig up any hidden puzzles buried in those books...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There's nothing on magic or witches in here.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">An owl statue. This is a frequently used motif in this town.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah, that's right! The flags also have an owl symbol on them!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aztec tribes associated owls with witchcraft and evil...but I don't think that's the case here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A candle chandelier. How do they light the candles?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I would venture a guess that they light them from the second floor, with the aid of a long stick.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I'd love to give it a try! Think they'll let me light it up?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Reading by candlelight can ruin your eyesight.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh, these colours and the brush strokes...this wasn't painted by some amateur!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">An abstract painting in soft colours. It reminds me of a meadow in spring.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? If you look at it from a distance, it resembles an animal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It looks kinda like a hippo...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's locked. I can't even peek inside.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A cabinet that cannot be opened... This smells like a puzzle to me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Something really important or valuable must be inside.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It won't open no matter how much I push or pull. Maybe it's locked with a puzzle?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Oh, it appears we could not open it simply because the door was not fitted properly.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A lively picture of children playing.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There's a woman in this picture. Is this someone famous in Labyrinthia?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The author's signature is on the bottom. It seems to be a self-portrait.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So this archive isn't only about books. There are some paintings, too.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks like candles are the only source of light at night in the Great Archive.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The quiet Great Archive, bathed in warm candlelight, looks very peaceful.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All these candles are making the room so hot. Isn't this a fire hazard?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks very nice, but I wouldn't want to be the one who replaces all these candles when they burn out.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Few lights are on at night around here, giving this place a very different atmosphere.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">These are some fancy street lights. What's that burning inside?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">London street lights used to be powered by gas, but that is not the case here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You can hear hammer strikes even at night.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">He may have received an urgent order. You can tell from the sound that he's very keen on the work.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The town feels somewhat desolate at night, so seeing shops like this brightens up the mood a little.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, that's a super-cute helm! It would look awesome on the professor!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The middle of the road is paved with white cobblestones.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">These cobblestones surround the shopping district. This must be the main street.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">If you follow the white line, you won't get lost.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The windows are closed, but the first floor lights are on.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Very few people are out and about at this hour. Streets empty out as night sets in.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Witches found their way even into the professor's office! Doors and shutters won't keep them out.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's a water fountain. The water looks very clear. It may be suitable for drinking.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There must be a spring somewhere nearby.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I used to draw water from this water fountain back in the olden days when I was a baker.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A pile of discarded wooden crates.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They're just crates. Nothing to see.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Time for a treasure hunt! Let's see what's inside these crates! Uhm... they're all empty...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The fountain looks marvellous illuminated by the lights.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">They don't seem to use electricity for light. There must be torches on the inside of the trough at the base.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The statue has a different air about it at night.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The cat that was here earlier has gone off somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It might have gone for a patrol around its territory.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Cats sleep so much during the day that they're full of energy at night.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It doesn't seem to be open for business at night, either.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The lights are on upstairs, but maybe the shopkeeper's unwell?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We should put our time to better use than waiting for this shop to open. Let us go back.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I was staring at that flag for so long that I started to make out a face in the pattern...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The coat of arms is unlike anything I have seen in books on the topic.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Those flags are all over the place, so they've got to be important, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The shop's closed. The owner must have gone home already.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The shop staff may have just gone to purchase fresh produce.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I am not averse to admiring implements of this sort.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">These things don't have anything to do with witches or magic.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Archaeologists learn about ancient cultures by examining sundries like these.</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Phoenix! Maya! Why are you back so late! [sic]</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh...yeah, sorry we're so late. It's just that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well...we, um... About Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Ha-ha-ha-ha... What are you two looking so glum about? I was so surprised!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Just how is it...that you could do such a brilliant job as a defender?! It was wonderful the way you proved Espella innocent. Thank you...from the bottom of my heart.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not at all...no need to thank me. After all, Espella is still...</line>
<line speaker="Patty">I know, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, were you...watching the trial?</line>
<line speaker="Patty">I certainly was, Maya. There's no reason for you to look so glum. The way you stood up to the inquisition... In all my life I've never seen anything like it! That outstretched arm... That pointing finger... It was truly a sight to behold, Phoenix!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Boss...</line>
<line speaker="Patty">That's why I'm not at all worried.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Because I believe in you, Phoenix. And I know you'll rescue Espella again. You will rescue her, won't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I will. I'll be there for her, no matter what! Right to the very end.</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Ha-ha-ha...that's a promise now, you hear? Now, then... You must both be tired after all you've been through. You must have a good rest! And that means you two gentlemen as well!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh...do you mean us?</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Of course! Why, if it hadn't been for you two, Phoenix couldn't have done what he did.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Thank you, madam.</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Perhaps I should bring out another extra large loaf for our young apprentice here!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">No! I mean, I'm fine...really... But thanks for the offer!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, we have to give it all we've got! For the boss' [sic] sake!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've got that right.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It might be difficult to rest right after a trial like that. But tonight, perhaps we should all try to get a good rest, as Mrs Eclaire suggests.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I agree, Professor. Tomorrow's a new day, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Let's go inside, then. If we don't take that rest, we won't be able to do our best tomorrow! I hope Espella is able to rest for tonight as well...</line>
<line speaker="Patty">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There's a butcher next to the fishmonger. It's still open.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Extended opening hours? That's convenient. Do you think they take pounds and pennies?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I think we've all got a bit hungry. We seem to be noticing only food.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ooooh! Phosphorescent anglerfish!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And that would be octopus over there. It looks belligerent and ready to spray the potential buyer with ink.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They've sold out of most of their products today.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This is the entrance to the bakery. Shall we go in?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Let's stay the night here and resume our investigation tomorrow morning.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Calming moonlight is pouring into the room through the roof window.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It must be very nice to lie down in bed with a view of the starry skies above!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Thick volumes are lined up on the shelf.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Labyrinthian books...interesting. I would like to read some when we have time.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They're all very thick. It would take you some time to read them, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They all have bor...difficult titles. I'm impressed by this...studiousness. Hey, is that a word?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Jars with...jam, perhaps? They all have vibrant colours.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They look scrumptious.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I am sure this jam would be even more delicious on Mrs Eclaire's freshly baked bread.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, Espella's home-made jam! Of course I'd love to try some!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well then, let's all turn in for the night.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Ah! Is that you, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Luke. What's the matter? Can't sleep?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I kind of woke up... But then, I guess you did too, right? You're worried about Espella, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">After all, you were living here together. She must be like a member of the family. But you and Mr Wright found yourselves here in Labyrinthia, just like me and the professor, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Seems that way... Even though we've supposedly been living here for five years now... But those memories... didn't exactly turn out to be real. I've got no idea how I even had that kind of memory in the first place... On top of that, even the boss seemed to have the exact same memory of us... She's done so much to take care of us. When I think about it, I can't help but feel like we were deceiving her, y'know?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I don't think you have any reason to feel that way, Maya. It's not your fault that your memories have changed. And even if the memories are different, I'm sure your feelings for Mrs Eclaire and Espella are real.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're so right, Luke! Thanks, Luke! I feel way better now!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Not at all...it's nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aaaaaaall right! I'm gonna try real hard and get my beauty sleep! I'll be out faster than you can say "good night"!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm not so sure beauty is achieved by sleeping, or that sleep is something you can try hard at, but I'm definitely ready to sleep! Um...Maya, did you just say something?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Me? I didn't say anything...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But I'm sure I heard something. Maybe it was from outside.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder what it was...? Let's go and have a look, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, isn't that Patty over there?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks like she's searching for something.</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Eve... Coooeeeee... Eve! Goodness me, where could that cat have gone? She doesn't normally go wandering off at this time of the night... I suppose you're worried about Espella too, aren't you? ...Espella... I wonder what she's doing right now... Is she crying herself to sleep? Don't worry, Espella! You've got friends here, and we're going to make sure you come home to us safely! And when you do, we'll all sit down and have a nice dinner together!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Boss...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">She's worrying so much about Espella... She looks so sad...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She really does... This must be so hard for her. ............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">...Maya! I've got a great idea! Let's go and find Eve for her. If Eve still isn't back by the time Espella comes home... she'd miss her for sure! And Mrs Eclaire could relax a little too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Luke, you're a little genius! Let's go and find Eve for Espella and Patty! But I wonder where she could've gone?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We'll probably find her quicker if we ask around a bit. Eve is easy to recognise. She looks quite distinctive and has that scarf around her neck. I'm sure someone must have seen her.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Correction, you're not just a "little" genius, you're a super-mega-huge genius!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's nothing! I mean, I am the professor's apprentice!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's get this show on the road. How about we start by looking around the town centre?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are, Maya! But we'd better take care, since we'll be in the streets at night. Don't worry though! If anything happens, you can rely on me! It's the job of every gentleman to protect a lady! Let's go, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">As the grown-up here, I can't help but feel it should be me who's doing the protecting...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eve isn't at the butcher's.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Maybe she went farther away. Let's check some other places.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eve is so lucky to live next to the fishmonger!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Eve's not here now. Where can she be?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess...we really weren't bakers.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mrs Eclaire looked very concerned. I'd like to help her out as much as possible.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, the bread I baked has sold!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yeah! It was somewhat misshaped and a bit burnt, but it didn't taste that bad, it seems!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Luke, what matters is that you put your heart into baking those loaves, not how they turn out in the end!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's chuck in some more logs and see them burn!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">No, that's too much! The bakery will burn down if you stuff so much wood into the oven!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick brings the water from the well near the town square.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There's not much water left in this one. Let's go get some more tomorrow morning.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe Eve will just come back on her own?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We should be looking for her, not hoping she'll just come back at some point!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe Eve is hiding behind the bookshelf?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">She's not there. She must have gone outside.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I secretly had a few spoonfuls earlier. It's so rich and yummy!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Why not sell your bread and jam together? That'd be an irresistible combo!</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof, woof, ruff, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look, it's Constantine! I wonder what he's doing here this late...</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Ruff, woof, woof, woof!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It seems he's on his evening patrol. Looks like Constantine's a member of the order of knights too.</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Ruff, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, really? So I guess that makes him a "Dog of the Order" then.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hmm...Dog of the Order...Order of the Dog, eye of the needle...knee of the idol... Constance of the Order!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What is it, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why don't you ask Constantine if he's seen Eve?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right! Let's see what he's got to say. Hey, Constantine, what's up, boy? Have you seen Eve?</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Ruff, ruff...grrr...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-I wonder what's wrong? He seems to be upset.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Apparently Constantine doesn't like Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof, woof, grrr...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">"What makes you think I have even the slightest interest in a feline like that?!" ...Is what he said.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Feline...? I guess this must be a cats and dogs thing. Hey, Luke, ask him why he doesn't like Eve!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um...okay. But we're getting a little personal now...</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof, woof, ruff! Ruff, woof, woof, woof, woof!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">"It's nothing to do with liking or disliking. I just have no interest in her, that's all!" ...Is how he put it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, I think Constantine actually likes Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Rrrrr...ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">"I'm not patrolling to chase after some furry feline!" ...He says.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah? Well, I think it's just the mysterious male psyche at work here...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Just imagine dropping a book from the top! It could kill someone! Especially a hardcover edition.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Miss Maya, why do you always think about such horrible things...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The librarian said the fire was caused by a fire dragon summoned by Bezella, the Great Witch.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You get used to seeing it everywhere after a while.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe it's an occult symbol, with some hidden scary power!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eve wouldn't have got this far, right?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I don't think Eve would have gone all the way over there.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Well, good evening! What brings you here at this late hour? It's past our closing time, you know. We can't lend you any books, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">No, no... We're not here to borrow books. We were just wondering if you've seen a black cat around here, by any chance...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">A black cat...? No, I'm afraid I've been working late here in the library.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So you haven't seen her, huh? I wonder where Eve could have gone...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">If the cat is a pet, surely it will find its own way home.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yes, but we want to find her. Someone's feeling downhearted, and we're trying to help.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">How admirable. Well, I wish you both luck. But remember to take care...especially after that incident.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yes...yes, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">By the way... since you're here... Why not take a look at a puzzle or two before leaving?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">I'm afraid I haven't seen your black cat... but I have seen a lot of puzzles. Why not take a look at one or two before you go?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They went to so much trouble to make these statues look identical. Amazing.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, must've been hard to make them look the same! The bread I bake looks different every time!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That sure is a lot of books! Has anyone ever read them all?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's closed. The librarian must have locked the door.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Does the door under the owl statue lead to the Special Viewing Room?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Unauthorised access is strictly forbidden!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The Great Archive deserves a great chandelier, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Doesn't melting wax drip on the heads of people below?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If Eve went into the forest, there's no way we can find her.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I doubt she went there. Let's go back and look for her in the town.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It stands there silently, in the middle of the forest.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eve wouldn't have crawled inside, would she?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The path leads deep into the forest. I'd like to follow it with the professor one day and see where it goes.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, I don't think Eve went that way. Let's go back to the town?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No way we're going to get in at this hour.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Miss Maya, why don't we go back to the town for now?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Patty must be worried sick about Eve. Gotta find her quickly!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Miss Maya, I don't think Eve would have come all the way here...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hel-lo! Anyone home? Can I interest you in ordering freshly baked bread from the bakery?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You're so business-minded, Miss Maya! But maybe you shouldn't yell under people's windows at night.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I used to come here with Nick... He'd carry the water pots and I'd cheer him on.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Maya, don't you get those urges to open up all the boxes and see what's inside?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe we could build a cat fort for Eve with these crates and boxes!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I always wanted to chill out at a trendy place like this.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks pricey, but I guess we could step in for a bit, if you want to.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhm, you're right, we'd need deeper pockets to be able to enjoy this place, anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's the Great Archive. Think it's a nice place to work at? Maybe I should apply.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Dewey said it's paradise for book-lovers.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, a bakery is paradise for bread-lovers!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">These tall buildings must be perfect for watching the parade! The view has to be stunning!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Look at how wide the road is here. Maybe this area was designed especially for the parades.</line>
<line speaker="???">Make way... Make way! Letters to be delivered!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah! Sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Phew... Okay. Everything seems to be okay. ...Hmm? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's a little late in the evening to be delivering letters, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Yes! Yes, it is. But I'm the only courier in this town. Which means I'm always busy! Even at this time of day!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What? You're the only one? That must be tough...</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">So...what is it then? What can I do for you?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh, right! Um, you haven't seen a black cat anywhere around here, by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Black...cat...hmm... ...Ah! Siiiiiiiirrr! I do believe I did! I saw it! The cat, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait, really? That's great! Can you tell us about it?</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Well, I could... But I'm wondering. Should I tell you for free...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh... Uhm, we don't have any money on us, if that's what you mean.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">No, no. Not money. It's just, I'm kind of in a bind. I'm sort of not sure. About where to take the next letter, I mean. Do you think you could help me with it?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">If that's all that's troubling you, we'd be glad to help!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">40</line>
<line speaker="Notes">No penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Hey... That's amazing! Now I know where to go! Thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A puzzle like that is a piece of cake.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Now then. A promise is a promise! Let me tell you about that cat. Although... I, um... I didn't actually see it. The cat, I mean. I more heard it. Or rather, about it. The minstrel near the fountain was singing about a black cat.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Near the fountain? That's in the town centre, isn't it!</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">Right! Well, time's ticking. Better get going. These won't deliver themselves, you know! The letters, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow...that's a world-class sprint! Now THAT'S determination! C'mon, Luke! Put the pedal to the metal!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">H-hey, Maya...wait for me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They are so dim. Are you sure they aren't using energy-saving light bulbs?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We're not going to get ambushed by any witches, right? Not that I'm scared...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eve may be sleeping, curled up in one of these pots!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's right. Cats love getting inside narrow spaces, like boxes or pots. I guess they feel cosy.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You seem to be really into helms, Miss Maya. I thought you could only get this enthusiastic about food...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, they're the coolest headgear. Let's get one for the professor! He'll love it!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ugh, I don't think he will... Let's ask him first?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Stop looking down at your feet... Or you won't notice the world around you!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But...we're looking for Eve, so we should keep our eyes on the road...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um, excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Price">What is it, lad? You have something you wish to sell? It must be serious for a young fellow-my-lad like yourself to be visiting my shop at this hour.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um...what kind of store is this anyway? I only see a bunch of pots and junk here...</line>
<line speaker="Price">This is a pawnbroker's shop, madam. So, pray tell, what is it that you're selling?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We're not exactly here on business... We're just looking for a cat.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's a cute black cat called Eve. You haven't seen her, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Price">A black cat, you say... I have a feeling I may have seen it, but then again... Uuuummm...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Price">Um, it's no good. I felt I was about to remember for a moment there, but... I've got things on my mind and am finding it hard to concentrate, you see. If only I could solve this...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...are you talking about a puzzle? Becaaaaause I could totally solve it for you. ZVARRI! Just like that!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'll help too! Maya's still a newbie when it comes to solving puzzles.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, Luke. We can do this, can't we? ZVARRI! Just like that!</line>
<line speaker="Price">Then let's get to it, madam. Recently, the mice have been bothersome. I want to catch the mice that have been causing trouble in the shop and teach them a lesson!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Price">Hehm... I didn't think you'd solve such a difficult puzzle so easily. I'm quite impressed!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All right! That settles it then, I'm the professor's new apprentice!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah, I think not! The professor has only one apprentice, and that's me!</line>
<line speaker="Price">So do you two want to talk about a cat, or don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">O-of course we do. We'd very much like to hear about that cat. So, Mr Pawnbroker, what can you tell us?</line>
<line speaker="Price">Well, I haven't actually seen the cat. But I'm certain I overheard the minstrel near the fountain singing about a black cat.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Near the fountain, got it! Thank you! We'll go and take a look there.</line>
<line speaker="Price">This is a pawnbroker's shop. You two are perhaps a little young to be needing my services.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She's not in the fountain. I thought she could've gone for a swim...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Cats generally hate water, but there may be some that do like it.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A stray cat sleeps here during the day but disappears at night.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe it left because it found the ultimate barrel and this one just doesn't compare any more!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">If it was still here, I could have asked about Eve...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Miss Maya, do you have any idea what kind of a shop this is?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I vaguely remember someone telling me this is where all the bottle enthusiasts gather!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Say again? Bottle enthusiasts? Uhm, that's...weird.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Good evening, sir. There's something we'd like to ask you.</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">............</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What's the matter? You're a bit quiet this evening, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder what's up...a sore throat, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">C'est la vie, c'est la vie...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">C'est la vie?</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">I have no choice but to retire... C'est la vie!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yikes!</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">Alas, now a rival has up and appeared, So how can I sing when I'm so afeared? A simple bard just cannot compete, With a rival that strong, he cannot be beat</line>
<line speaker="Luke">P-please calm down! What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">Hm? Ahem...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It would seem some amazing new rival has appeared.</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">............Woe is me...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, for starters...you could try perking up a little.</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">...Perking up... I need some colour to cheer up my day... I need some colour to replace the grey...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You need...colour?</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">For example, bright colours such as these!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Look at this, Mr Bardly! The colours are beautiful. Come on, cheer up! A minstrel isn't judged by appearances, he's judged by his songs. I'm certain that there are many people who love to hear your songs, Mr Bardly.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Absolutely! I, for one, would love to hear more of your songs!</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">............Really?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes, really!</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">............Really, truly?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yes, truly - really!</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's more like it! At least he's perked up enough to continue singing.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yeah, too right! That's a relief.</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">In return for the cheer that you did bring, Now, more than ever, I'll continue to sing</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You're very welcome!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Still...it seems like there's another minstrel somewhere in town...</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">Oh, oh kindly duo, what could it be? What brings you to Bardly? What would you ask of me?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh! I almost forgot! Mr Bardly, have you seen a black cat anywhere around here?</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">I've seen it, seen it, I've seen a black cat! Since you are asking, I'll sing about that A beautiful black cat with fur so sleek, Chased and chased, ran to the main street Three knights gave chase, but it didn't last, The cat got away, by running so fast</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's it, Luke! Eve must've gone to the main street!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Come on, Maya... Let's go that way!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! He mentioned something about Eve being chased... We'd better hurry!</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">A beautiful black cat with fur so sleek,</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's even a flag here! It's not looking very perky though.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's just because there's no wind right now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This shop's closed. We should've come during business hours.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's so late that the shopkeepers have already gone home.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Stalls like these look more appealing at night rather than during the day.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's the ambience of a stall that makes a difference!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">If we don't hurry up and find that cat, it'll get away from us.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Come on, give me a break. Just how long do you intend to chase after a cat?!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">If we don't get back to our posts, the captain's going to blow his top!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Even so, I'm sure that cat was a stray. Surely it's part of the code of chivalry to rescue people and animals without distinction?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">But we've done nothing but chase it around. Sheesh, why did you have to be in our squad?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Did you hear that, Maya? Those knights are talking about a cat!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yep, and I bet they're talking about Eve!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Let's ask them! Um, excuse me, sir. We're looking for a black cat... and we overheard you talking about a cat.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We're looking for a black cat wearing a purple neck scarf.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Eh? A cat, you say? That must be...</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Hey, wait a minute! Aren't those two the ones... who gave Inquisitor Barnham such a hard time at the trial?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Aha! These are the ones, all right. They were with that defender.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">What business could you possibly have with us? Be off with you! Or feel our wrath!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">I know nothing of this cat you seek.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Eh? But I heard you... You were talking about chasing a cat.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, I heard you too. You were worried about her escaping.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">E-even so, I don't know what I don't know and can't tell what I can't tell!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Come on, just tell us! We need to find her.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">You can ask as much as you like... but we know nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Saw nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Heard nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">20</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Seen nothing, heard nothing, know nothing! And we're not going to tell! ...Hmm?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We've worked out where Eve is, Maya! And you know where she's going, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I sure do. It looks like she ran off toward the town square.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Nooo! We didn't even tell you, how did you work it out? Did you read our minds?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">No, the answer was in the puzzle!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Say, shouldn't you be getting back before your captain goes ballistic?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Touch!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We're close to finding Eve, Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right, let's go and find her before she goes running off somewhere else.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! Hey, you know what? I could really get used to this whole puzzle-solving thing! You know, it's like the moment I saw the answer it just felt so right...and I was right!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey, I was right too, you know?! Anyway, let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">......... It's...it's you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">High Inquisitor...Darklaw!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">......... Oh...if it isn't you two. Isn't it a bit late for you to be out here strolling around?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aren't you tired, Luke? Why don't we take a short break?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm not a little boy! I can walk. And I'm not tired at all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A bell this large can probably be heard throughout the whole town.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Do they ever ring it, though? Miss Maya, have you heard it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhm...nope. Maybe it's broken?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I hope Eve didn't get inside.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Even she wouldn't be able to sneak in unnoticed with those guards around.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Um...so what are you doing here, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">.........</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You seem...a little different, somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Well, well... aren't you quite the inquisitive ones? I'm the inquisitor here, remember? Anyway, I happen to be on duty.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">On duty? This late at night?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">As long as there are witches in this town, there will always be crimes of magic. I'm directing the knights' enquiry into a certain incident involving this bell tower.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A...certain incident?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Three months ago, an alchemist residing not far from here was murdered. Naturally...it was at the hand of a witch.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">D-did you say an alchemist? A witch murdered an alchemist using magic? That's terrible.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Indeed...it was a dreadful incident. And it is the only case to remain unsolved.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The only incident to remain unsolved...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">That's the reason we are working on it through the night. Go home to the comfort of your beds... We wouldn't want you meeting a witch now, would we?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey, I'm no child, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's "we", Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We happen to be searching for a cat. It's a black cat called Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............Eve............?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey...have you seen her?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I have seen no sign of any cat. Not around here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">O-oh...really?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But...she has to be somewhere nearby. Come on, Luke, let's look around a bit more!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yeah...right you are, Maya! Well, thank you, High Inquisitor Darklaw.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ ...Maya Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-yes! What...what is it? Wait... That's weird... I don't remember telling you my name...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">There are witches in the most unlikely of places. You must remain vigilant.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............! Wh-what did she mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey, Maya! Over here! I've found Eve! What's the matter, come on!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um...yeah...okay...I'm coming!</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meeow!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eve! We found you! Finally!</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meeow!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm so glad you're safe. Espella would be so upset if anything happened to you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She sure would, Luke. She said that Eve is "a real friend". Hopefully, the boss will feel better too when we get Eve back home.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm sure she will. Come on then, let's go back to the bakery.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Maya, don't you get those urges to open up all the boxes and see what's inside?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I keep thinking about the incident High Inquisitor Darklaw told us about.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We've found Eve, mission complete. No need to check that area.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meeow!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Ah! It's the black cat! Did you come back to see me? You're so cute, you sweet little pussycat. I'd like to stroke you.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">...Meeow!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">...Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I suggest you keep your hands...or should I say gauntlets, to yourself. Eve seems a little afraid of you.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">A little afraid? How would you know? Don't keep her all to yourself. Come on, let me stroke her too!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Hey, will you cut that out already?!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">It looks like we may have to drag him back to his post...</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Aww, and just when I'd found the cat... No, no...I don't want to go back!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Look, we know you love cute animals, but you're going a little too far.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Seriously though, how can you even call yourself a knight? Why did you join up in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">I was sure there would be cute pets in the order of knights... You know, like Inquisitor Barnham's...</line>
<line speaker="Knight">So it was little Constantine that attracted you to the group?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Luke. I think we should go, while the going is good.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I think you're right, Maya... Before they decide to chase after Eve again.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meeow!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Luke. I think we should go, while the going is good.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I think you're right, Maya... Before they decide to chase after Eve again.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meeow!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Eve the cat is drinking water greedily. She must have been parched.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Looks like the barrel cat has quite an active nightlife.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meeow.</line>
<line speaker="Price">Ho! That's a fine looking cat! A-ha! This must be the cat those three knights were searching for.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meeow.</line>
<line speaker="Price">Does this cat belong to you two?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">No...it belongs to Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Price">Oh, really? Espella's cat... It's not really for me to say, but I feel I must warn you both... Stay away from that girl. You do realise she's being held on suspicion of being the Great Witch Bezella? Of course I would never say it out loud, but I always suspected as much...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Espella is not a witch!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yeah, no way is she a witch! Don't talk like it's a foregone conclusion!</line>
<line speaker="Price">I, uh...I'm sorry. You're right, of course. Although... it's not as unreasonable as you might think.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Why is it that people suspect her so much?</line>
<line speaker="Price">Well...that's because... I'm afraid I cannot say! You should ask her yourself. Now then, I must be going...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why does everyone seem to fear Espella? What are they all so scared of?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I wonder if Espella herself will be able to tell us...</line>
<line speaker="Price">It's getting late, you know. Young boys and girls should be at home.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Stop looking down at your feet... Or you won't notice the world around you!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We've found Eve, so let's hurry back to the bakery!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Shops are still open, but I doubt they'd let us in with a cat.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meeow.</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">............! Ruff, ruff, woof, woof, grrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Constantine sounds a little stressed!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">At this rate we're going to see a fight.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Luke, can't you do something?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Okay...I'll try! Now listen up, you two! I have a proposition for you...</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Grrrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meeow...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look, Luke! I think you've done it!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, I got them both to agree to a suggestion of mine...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A suggestion? What kind of suggestion?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well...a puzzle, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A puzzle?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Yes, I thought that if we all worked on a puzzle together, they could become friends.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Luke! That's genius! That just might work!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm glad you think so! By the way, I need your cooperation too!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Who...? Me...?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Of course you! This is one of those puzzles that needs everyone's input.</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">25</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You see! The four of us working together were able to solve the puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You were right, Luke! It was refreshing solving a puzzle together like that.</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">...Woof, ruff, ruff.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey...Luke, what did he just say?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">"I suppose it won't do any harm to show a little more consideration to this feline." ...Is what he said.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, way to go, Constantine!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, at least we seem to have relieved the tension a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You hear that, Eve? You've got to be nice to Constantine too.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meeow.</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof, woof...ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">"You win. I can hold up my end of this... if it will really please you both so much." ...He said.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meeow.</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof, woof.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, wow, I could've sworn Constantine's little bark had a little extra bounce in it just now. Now c'mon, you two... Try and get along with each other, got it?</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meeow.</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's pitch-black, as always. I can't see what's below.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meeow.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Hm...bringing a cat into the library is not something I encourage. You see, it might damage the books.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">S-sorry, but she's very well behaved.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Well your cat does look very refined. It's obviously not just some stray cat you've picked up somewhere. However, I still ask that you take care. Cats can be temperamental, you know. Don't let her get playful with those claws. By the way... since you're here... Why don't you take a look at a puzzle or two before leaving?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Cats can be very temperamental, you know. Please keep an eye on her at all times. I don't want her scratching the books. By the way... since you're here... Why don't you take a look at a puzzle or two before leaving?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There's nothing on magic or witches in here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't want to be here. It looks as if we might get ambushed by witches at any time!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This place is spooky, and my expert opinion is that it's haunted. Let's go back...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We've found Eve already, so let's head back to the bakery.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All righty! We've got Eve now. At least that will help us cheer Espella up tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's late and everyone's probably worried about us. Let's go back to the bakery.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That took us longer than I thought it would. I wonder if everyone's asleep?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's getting close to daybreak. We should enter quietly and try not to wake anyone.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meeow.</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Where on earth could those two have gone? After what happened earlier, you'd think they'd know better than to go wandering out at night like this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's getting bright out already. I'm starting to worry that they came across a witch...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If they don't show up soon, I suggest we all go looking for them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">After a trial like that...it makes me wonder where they get their energy from.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meeow.</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Oh, Eve! Where were you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah, good morning, everyone!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean, "good morning"? Where have you two been this whole time?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">S-sorry... We didn't expect to be gone for so long.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'd have thought you'd know better, Luke. What were you doing out there at this hour?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Sorry, Professor...we went looking for Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Looking for Eve, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Patty">You mean you were both concerned that Eve was missing?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well... When Espella comes home, she'll want Eve here to meet her, won't she? After all, Eve is like a member of the family.</line>
<line speaker="Patty">Oh, you dears... That's very considerate of you. Thank you. But, I want you to promise me that you won't go wandering around late at night like that again. It's just not safe, what with all those witches out there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We promise... I'm sorry, boss.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm sorry too...</line>
<line speaker="Patty">I should say! It's nearly morning already. Why don't you both go and get yourselves cleaned up? I've already prepared breakfast. So jump to it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes, ma'am! Come to think of it, I'm so hungry I could eat one of Mary's goats! How about you, Luke?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Now that you mention it... I'm definitely ready for breakfast!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You certainly both love your food. Personally, I'd just like a little more sleep...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Right then, let's eat breakfast and make our way to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are, Professor! I'm sure Espella must be feeling lonely.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Oh and, Mr Wright, could you perhaps take something from the bakery for her?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You bet. I'm sure Espella will be glad to get some of Patty's freshly baked bread.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, what are you all waiting for?! Breakfast is ready!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...All right, all right. We're coming...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well then, let's dig in.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">As it seems we are all ready to go, shall we make our way to the court? So does everyone remember how to get there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure...we just head east from here, and it's on the other side of the forest, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Boy, Espella must be feeling so sad and lonely. Let's get a move on!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Welcome, welcome. How about some fresh goat's milk from a freshly milked goat? Well, I'll be... If it isn't you lot! What a coincidence seeing you here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey, Miss Mary, I thought you were selling milk on the outskirts of the market...'</line>
<line speaker="Mary">That's right, I do. But not everyone can get to the market to buy their milk, child. That's why Snowy and I sometimes set up a stall in town like this.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It must be hard having to do it right after the trial like this.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">We have to deliver the milk while it's still fresh, you see. There's no way we can go taking a break! Not only that, but we hardly feel like resting! Not after all of that excitement. We've never experienced a trial like that. Who would have thought that sweet flower seller, Kira, would turn out to be a witch? Such an innocent face, too. You'd never believe she could have done it! Don't you think so, my little Snowy-kins?</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaa...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">At any rate, it was a real shock seeing an execution by fire...</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Maybe so.... But on the other hand, it couldn't be helped. After all, she was a witch!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Anyway, at times like this, a little puzzle can help to clear the air. Isn't that right, my little fluffy dumpling?</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaa...</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">50</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Mary">What do you think? Doesn't it feel dreamy being surrounded by lovely bleating goats?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll be seeing them in my dreams tonight for sure. I'll probably be counting goats instead of sheep...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They certainly do look cute, don't they?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Their cute appearance can be quite relaxing, if only you can block out their bleating.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Fresh goat's milk, straight from the goat! Be quick, or we'll be sold out!</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaa...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Where do the wagons with milk come from?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I haven't seen any cows or goats around here, but there may be a farm outside the town?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Someone left their wagon unsupervised.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The goat lady said that goats give little milk, so it's very expensive.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So many types of fish! Is there a river or a lake nearby?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Interesting. I, too, wonder where they obtain so much fish from.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The fish are very fresh. Some are still alive, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, a sly cat crouching in the shadows is getting ready to pounce on the fish.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mmm...there's a delicious smell coming from the bakery.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There is only one bakery in this area, it would seem.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So many types of bread! Sweet, savoury...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I arranged everything so nicely! It looks too awesome to be sold to unappreciative people!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They're selling fruit and veg. Good place to get your five-a-day.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">They also have fish on the other side. It's a grocery stall.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The open market is much more fun than shops in the town centre.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's a statue of a knight. We've got them in London, too.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is a magnificent statue. We can deduce from it that knights are very respected in this town.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Knights, huh. They're like medieval police officers! ...With swords!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The water's so pure and cold.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just how many knights are in this town?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's comfortably asleep. Just like in our world, cats take it easy here.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Cats used to be valued for catching mice. I wonder if they're kept here for the same reason?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They say cats have nine lives. I wouldn't complain if I had a couple spare ones, myself.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This kitty likes sitting on top of barrels.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The cat seems determined not to get down unless someone makes it an offering of delicious fish.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The shop sign looks very peculiar. What do they sell here, I wonder?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The shop's not open yet. The door's locked.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A sundries shop. Pots and vases of various sizes are lined up on display.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm not sure if you could call it a sundries shop. It looks like they specialise in earthenware?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps it is an antique shop. Although I am not sure if the concept exists here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The wares he's peddling look pretty heavy. I can't believe he can walk carrying all that.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">He looks athletic, but what is physical strength compared to the power of witches?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The trade with the knights seems to be flourishing.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's a caf. Why don't we pop in and take a short break from investigating?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is an expensive residential area, after all. Everything here looks very elegant and refined.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's so spacious and the sky seems so high.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, doesn't that look imposing? Who designed that building?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">An enormous book presides over this town, governed by a story...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I didn't know that medieval people could build things on this scale.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe it's all full of books, piled up all the way to the ceiling!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The symbol from the flag can be found throughout the town.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's an odd symbol. Maybe it's unique to this town.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The quills seem to resemble the Storyteller.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe Nick should have a flag in his office, too. It might raise his image.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm. The door and windows on the ground floor are shut. Could this be so for safety reasons?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">If this was my house, I'd keep the windows open during the day to let fresh air in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At least the windows on the second floor are wide open.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Look at that bench, Professor! Wouldn't it be nice to spend a whole day on it, reading in the sunshine?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Luke, we are carrying out an investigation. This is not the time to be lazing about on a bench.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Lush grass, a fine bench. Should I get my picnic set out?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A single bell hangs in the belfry. Perhaps it is sounded on special occasions.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's one huge bell.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't remember hearing that bell ring, somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Some knights are standing guard at the entrance. I guess we can't go in.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is plausible that the guards are there to make sure no one goes to ring the bell without permission.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe it's just me, but this belfry seems so ominous.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's so sunny. I feel sorry for Espella, imprisoned in a dark cell. We've got to get her out of there soon.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The forest stretches ahead. I hope there are no snakes. I'm not good with snakes...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The weather is so fine that it is hard to believe this town is threatened by witches.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Good weather makes you optimistic, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was lighting our way when we left the Witches' Court last night.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Seen during the day, it has a very intriguing shape.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It was hewn out of one stone, from the looks of it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm sure this lantern attracts a lot of moths and other insects at night. And ghosts.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A signpost. Let's check later where this road leads to.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The path disappears in the forest. Does anyone live there?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The path splits in two directions. We can check where the other branch leads on another occasion.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Coming back here makes me remember yesterday's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Espella's still being held somewhere inside the building.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, and it's up to us to get her out as soon as we can.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The first thing we should do is make sure we're allowed to see her.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">You there! Yes, you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh-oh! There's nothing like a confrontation first thing in the morning to keep you on your toes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...we're here to ah...you know... to, err...visit...our client.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">It's not you we're interested in...it's Dark Hat over there! He's to come with us immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Who, sir, me, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Yes, sir, you, sir! What have you done this time?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">P-Professor! Did you do something?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...I wonder what it could be. Luke, do you have any idea?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">P-Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Don't play innocent with us! The order came from the Storyteller himself! You have been personally summoned to the Audience Room to see the Storyteller!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The Audience Room?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Meeting the Storyteller in person is the highest honour that can be bestowed upon a person. There's no one in all of Labyrinthia who wouldn't be proud to meet him. That goes for us knights too, although such an honour is almost unheard of. Nevertheless, those were the orders... To have Hershel Layton make his way to the Audience Room.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Very well. And in this Audience Room... the Storyteller will be waiting to see me, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Whaat?! Why does the Storyteller want to see you, Professor?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! What's going on here, anyway?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ Would it be possible to go there after having seen Miss Cantabella?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">The Storyteller's order is of the absolute highest priority! Nothing can take precedence!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">B-but!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Not only that, but in any event, you are not permitted to see the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Why would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Permission to see the accused is restricted to Defender Wright and his assistant. Those are the orders!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What do you make of that, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Make of it what you will. Orders are orders!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Very well. Let's go and meet the Storyteller.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">That's more like it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Professor, are you really planning on meeting with the Storyteller? It might be a trap...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...while I do sense the potential for a scheme here, I'd be foolish to pass up the opportunity to meet with this town's "creator". There are rather too many things that I would like to ask him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">If the professor is going, then I'm going too! After all, I am the professor's apprentice!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Be careful, Luke! I'm sure you'll be just fine, as long as you stay with the professor.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I will, and please give Espella our best. Oh and, Maya, could you give Espella the bread from Mrs Eclaire?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sure thing, Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Well, if you've finally finished talking, I would suggest wasting no more time. You'll find the Audience Room beyond the guard post, east of the Great Archive. And, defender, you should see the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, it would seem we must go our separate ways for the time being.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, it looks like it. Well, take care, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And you, Mr Wright. I wish you both luck.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, there they go. Do you think they'll be okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The professor and Luke? I think they can take care of themselves. Anyway, we should hurry up and talk to Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right! Even though she tries to hide it, inside she must be terrified...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What if she's found guilty of being a witch? What would we do then? Last night we saw with our own eyes what they do to witches.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............ It's not right... Any world where things like that are allowed to happen isn't right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know, Maya... But for now, we have no choice. We have to clear Espella of the charges. We need to focus on that and that alone.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The Great Witch Bezella... I wonder why they suspect Espella of being her?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know... But if we're lucky, maybe she'll be able to shed some light on it.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Hey, defender! It's time for you to see the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, this is it, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It sure is. Let's go, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We've got to find the Great Witch before the next parade. Let's go to talk to Espella first.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Get a move on, Nick! I want to see Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We'd better hurry up and go to the Deathknell Dungeon.</line>
<line speaker="Allan">...Hey, it's you two!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... Did you want to speak to us?</line>
<line speaker="Allan">I need to have a word with you both! Thanks to your turning courtroom procedure upside down, we're in a fine mess now! Finding a defendant INNOCENT is unprecedented in the history of the Witches' Court!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you mean?! I'm pretty sure trying innocent people is more of a problem than your precious procedure!</line>
<line speaker="Allan">What are you...trying to say?! That girl...is being held on suspicion of being the Great Witch Bezella! Defending her only invites suspicion upon your own complicity!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a false accusation.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's right! There's not a shred of evidence against Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Allan">Harrumph... No matter what you say, she is the most likely suspect! Anyway... If I stand around talking to you for too long, I'll invite suspicion upon myself! So from now on, I would appreciate it if you would keep your distance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But...you're the one who approached us...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Allan">Harrumph...</line>
<line speaker="Allan">I won't talk to anyone whom I think might be supporting Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Awesome. But looking up at it gave me neck pain. Nick, can you make it go away?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe Nick should have a flag in his office, too. It might raise his image.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Did someone just say something? I was miles away...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">I know you... You're both acquaintances of the professor, aren't you? I was at the trial last night. I saw the whole thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, you were there too? I guess the witch trial really does get the townsfolk interested...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Indeed... Especially last night...on account of the defendant being Espella Cantabella. But I must admit, you amazed me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I did?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Very much. It was the first time I had ever seen a defender fight that way for his client. For example, the way you used the word "contradiction" in the courtroom... It worked almost like...magic.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But that's only natural for a defence attorney...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Until now, the defender was always defeated the moment they stood before Inquisitor Barnham. Not only that... But in this town, there's no one who wants to befriend a witch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-that's just not how a trial should be... That's not justice!</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">I believe Professor Layton made the right decision giving you the Grand Grimoire. And from now on, I hope you will continue to fight for justice in court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, you've got it.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Now then, this conversation has become rather heavy, don't you think? If it's okay with you, I have something to lighten the mood...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... Then that means...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">I have a repository of all the puzzles in Labyrinthia. If you come to me, you can tackle any puzzles you may have missed. As well as puzzles that you previously couldn't solve. Why not occasionally try a puzzle or two to keep your thinking flexible?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">I believe Professor Layton did the right thing when he gave you the Grand Grimoire. Please continue to fight as a just defender. Oh, and be sure to drop by for a look at some puzzles.</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">Oh...it makes me so mad...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's the problem?</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">It's my neighbour... He's got this really annoying habit.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Annoying habit?</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">He just loves stomping around his place all the time. Thanks to him, all the books in my house are now a complete mess. Not to mention, I can't get any sleep!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That does sound like a serious problem...</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">Can you even imagine how loud it is?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, I...uh, not exactly...</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">That's what I thought. I knew you couldn't. So let me just reproduce it for you! You'll truly be amazed!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">40</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Can be solved in five moves</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">So what did you think of that? Wasn't that stomping just ridiculous?! I've had enough already...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then why don't you just pack your things and move out?</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">Move out? Move...out... Hey, that's a great idea! I'll come and stay in the library instead! I could be of more help to Miss Mystere, and I'd be surrounded by all these books! This is the greatest idea ever!</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">No, Dewey. I'm sorry, but I must insist that you leave and go home.</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Maya... Let's just pretend like nothing ever happened and get going ourselves...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Sometimes life doesn't go quite the way you want it to, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">He stomps so hard my entire house shakes! I don't even want to go home...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe we should put a statue of someone eating bread in our bakery to boost sales.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The professor would be itching to dig up any hidden puzzles buried in those books...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aztec tribes associated owls with witchcraft and evil...but I don't think that's the case here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I'd love to give it a try! Think they'll let me light it up?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Knights, huh. They're like medieval police officers! ...With swords!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just how many knights are in this town?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They say cats have nine lives. I wouldn't complain if I had a couple spare ones, myself.</line>
<line speaker="Petal">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's the matter? Are you lost or something?</line>
<line speaker="Petal">...'Course not! How could I be lost?! You listen to me...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...!</line>
<line speaker="Petal">Have you two seen a young boy about the same age as me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm...nope, can't say we have. What's up? Did you get separated?</line>
<line speaker="Petal">Nuh-uh! We haven't been "separated"! More like he went and ran off somewhere on his own!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...I see. Well, if we see him, we'll bring him back here to you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right... He's probably a little worried as well.</line>
<line speaker="Petal">Who said I was worried?! Just that, you know Cecil... He's such a little weakling crybaby! He's probably crying his eyes out somewhere right now... That wimp can't do anything without me by his side! When he feels sick, he can't even go for medicine without me. So...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I get it... It's only natural that you're worried about him. So his name's Cecil, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't worry, we're on it! If we see a crybaby fitting that description, we'll give you a shout.</line>
<line speaker="Petal">Cecil... Why did that wuss have to run off like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The goat lady said that goats give little milk, so it's very expensive.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, a sly cat crouching in the shadows is getting ready to pounce on the fish.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I arranged everything so nicely! It looks too awesome to be sold to unappreciative people!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe it's all full of books, piled up all the way to the ceiling!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can see why they chose to do the parade here. Just look at these fancy houses!</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Boo-hoo...boo-hoo! Waaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! That kid...he must be...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, you're right. He must be the one that little girl was searching for.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, let's talk to him then! Hi there, Cecil!</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Boo-hoo! Wh-who are you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A moment ago we met a little girl who asked us to help her find a missing crybaby. ...You're Cecil, right?</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">My-my sister Petal said that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right, she's been worried about you.</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">............ P-Petal always tells me not to talk to strangers...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">I mean, you might just grab me and take me off somewhere... You might even be...a witch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Well, in that case, there's nothing we can do. See you around, kid.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, come on, Nick! We promised his sister!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Listen...if I'm going to be suspected of being a witch's accomplice... I'd rather just hand this kid over to one of the patrolling knights.</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">............ Um... Okay, okay! Please, could you solve this puzzle for me?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">If you're the kind of people who can solve puzzles, I'll believe in you!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">40</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">That's great! You two aren't strangers after all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! Of course we're not! I mean, do I look like some stranger?</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Well, you don't look strange yourself... But those clothes you wear sure are weird!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Urk...Nick... I think we should go.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya...we can't give up now. After all, we just solved the puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, name one thing strange about my clothes! ONE!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I could give you a laundry list of things. Anyway, we'll go and get your sister... You just wait here for a while, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">O-okay!</line>
<line speaker="Petal">Oi, Cecil! Why'd ya let go of my hand and run off?!</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">I-I'm sorry, sis. I just... At least we're back together now, right? Ha ha ha...</line>
<line speaker="Petal">Pssh, so what?! I couldn't care less one way or the other! B-but anyway, from now on... Don'cha go running off like that, GOT IT?</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Got it, sis!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There you go, problem solved. It feels good helping people out like this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even so, that was a tough puzzle... I was wondering if we'd ever actually solve it for a second there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, but we so have what it takes, Nick! I could see us going pro at this whole puzzle-solving thing. Just like the professor! If we get stuck on a case, we could always consider changing jobs!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll think about it...</line>
<line speaker="Petal">Hey, thanks for what you did there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No problem. You guys stick together now, you hear?</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">Right! I'll hold Petal's hand extra tight, just to be sure she doesn't go running off somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Petal">Hey, you were the one who went missing!</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">...! Waaaaah! Boo-hoo! She hit meeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You two should try and stop arguing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At least the windows on the second floor are wide open.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I used to draw water from this water fountain back in the olden days when I was a baker.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Time for a treasure hunt! Let's see what's inside these crates! Uhm... they're all empty...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Lush grass, a fine bench. Should I get my picnic set out?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't remember hearing that bell ring, somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe it's just me, but this belfry seems so ominous.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's so sunny. I feel sorry for Espella, imprisoned in a dark cell. We've got to get her out of there soon.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Good weather makes you optimistic, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was lighting our way when we left the Witches' Court last night.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm sure this lantern attracts a lot of moths and other insects at night. And ghosts.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A signpost. Let's check later where this road leads to.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The path disappears in the forest. Does anyone live there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Witches' Court is like a cross-breed of a courthouse and an execution place.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder why it was built so far away from the rest of the town?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, another owl flew by.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's Barnham's armour. It makes quite an impression.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A drawing of someone's scary face. Barnham has a gift for caricatures.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's Inquisitor Darklaw! The picture looks like it's used for dagger-throwing practice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So many memos. Magic crime is on the rise, from the looks of it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww, a picture of smiling Barnham with his doggie! They look cute together.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Barnham uses a dumbbell as a paper weight. I guess it makes sense when you have that many papers...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can picture him slowly making his way through all this while Darklaw stares at him from across the room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Does Barnham use his own desk to practise swordplay on? It's badly damaged.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's amazing...that this desk hasn't collapsed yet. It's full of cracks, and bits are chipped off.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What a pretty lady...with a ruthless face and a scary sword ready to cut someone's head off...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A normal-looking painting. It feels like it doesn't belong here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the kind of chair you can sit in all night long and not fall asleep.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Your comments are not half as smart as the professor's, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't like the look of those chains on the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This place looks scary, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............Ah. Mr Wright, Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this is the Deathknell Dungeon... Looks more like solitary confinement to me.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Don't worry, I'm fine...really. I was a little surprised at how hard the bed was, though...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, that's right! I have something for you here! The boss made it for you. Look, it's her special walnut bread. You should try it!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Aunt Patty made that...for me? Thank you, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We'll get you home soon, then we can all sit down and eat Patty's freshly baked bread together!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...that would be nice. We're going to have you out of here soon, so don't you worry, Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ But are you sure you want to do that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you talking about, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Do you really want to continue defending me, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what?! Of course I do! What made you say that?!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">You do both know what I've been charged with, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">S-sure we do. They're accusing you of being Bezella... the source of all witches here in Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That's right... And anyone who defends such a suspect will also come under suspicion themselves. People are likely to criticise you and make you suffer...all on my account. I can't ask you to defend me... I don't want you suffering because of me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Listen to me, Espella. We're already suffering just seeing you here in this prison. Do you honestly think...we'd just stand around not doing anything?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! I think I get it, Espella! I bet you're just worried that Nick will slip up the way he always does.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Trust me. There's nothing to worry about. The professor and Luke are on our side, too.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Huh? No, no...that's not what I meant! I wouldn't think that at all. Mr Wright, you were...just amazing. You and Mr Layton, both... It was like you were working magic together!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, that settles it then, Espella. And don't worry, we're going to be there for you - we'll fight to the very end. The two of us, the professor and Luke. We'll all be working together on this thing... We won't let you down!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">........................</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-what's wrong, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's just that... the only one who's ever been this kind to me before is Aunt Patty... I...I don't know what to say...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Espella...I'm not sure how to say this, but... It seems that the townsfolk are distancing themselves from you. It's as if they fear you for some reason.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah...I can't believe they'd all think a cute girl like you could be the Great Witch.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella, we heard from High Inquisitor Darklaw... that there's a "reason" why people are so suspicious of you.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If it's okay with you...we'd like you to tell us what that reason is. The reason the townsfolk suspect you... and why they are so distant.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ All right. I guess I never had the chance to explain properly.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's true that the townsfolk look at me... "differently". And the reason for that is... because I am...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, Professor, we've reached the library. And the place at which the Storyteller is waiting for us is east of here, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed... According to the knight, the Audience Room is past the guard post.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I wonder what the creator of Labyrinthia wants to talk to you about, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's too soon to assume anything, Luke. But whatever it might be, I have a few things that I would like to ask him, too. We should be thankful that this opportunity has come so soon. Even if it is part of some scheme...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............ Let's go, Professor. To the Audience Room!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Let's go meet the author of all these tomes!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The Storyteller's flag. We will soon meet the Storyteller himself.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Labyrinthia seems surrounded by cliffs and woods. In the distance there's nothing but fog.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The fog is so thick, I can't see far.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This place looks so mysterious, surrounded by the misty forest.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Ah, Professor Layton. It's so good to see you again.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The pleasure is all mine, Miss Mystere. By the way, I've noticed the puzzles in Labyrinthia are of the highest quality.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">It warms my heart to hear you say that, Professor. So then, would you like to see if there are any puzzles you've missed or attempt any puzzles you've put off? How about spending a moment or two with me, just to check some puzzles?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">When you want to tackle a puzzle you've missed or solve a puzzle that you previously put off, just come by and see me. So...would you like to solve a puzzle before you leave?</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">Ah, you're the gentleman from yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hello again, Dewey.</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">Hey, you even remembered my name! Say, are you always so calm and collected? Uh-oh... Ooooooooh!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Please calm down, or you'll drop all those books.</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">Oh, oh... Whoa, whoa, whoa! Phew... I was really surprised when you borrowed the Grand Grimoire in the first place... But then to lend it to someone who works at a bakery!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But the professor did get permission, so there's no problem, is there?</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">I guess not...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">And if not for the Grand Grimoire, an innocent person would have been found guilty already.</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">Well, I suppose so...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">In my opinion, Mr Wright should be well capable of completing Miss Mystere's trials himself. In fact, I'm quite certain of it.</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">I was really surprised watching him perform in yesterday's courtroom... Everyone in the town is talking about it. This is the first time we've ever seen a person accused of being a witch... be proven innocent in the court.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Is that so?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It makes me wonder if the people sent to the fire before now... really were all witches.</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">...! Don't talk like that! You can't go around saying things like that, or you'll have the knights after you!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There are two identical statues, one on each side.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The statues portray people reading. Maybe that's supposed to motivate those who come here to read more.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This appears to be documentation on accidents and criminal cases.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There's nothing on magic or witches in here.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">An owl statue. This is a frequently used motif in this town.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah, that's right! The flags also have an owl symbol on them!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A candle chandelier. How do they light the candles?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I would venture a guess that they light them from the second floor, with the aid of a long stick.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Reading by candlelight can ruin your eyesight.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh, these colours and the brush strokes...this wasn't painted by some amateur!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">An abstract painting in soft colours. It reminds me of a meadow in spring.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? If you look at it from a distance, it resembles an animal.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's locked. I can't even peek inside.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A cabinet that cannot be opened... This smells like a puzzle to me.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It won't open no matter how much I push or pull. Maybe it's locked with a puzzle?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Oh, it appears we could not open it simply because the door was not fitted properly.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A lively picture of children playing.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There's a woman in this picture. Is this someone famous in Labyrinthia?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The author's signature is on the bottom. It seems to be a self-portrait.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks like candles are the only source of light at night in the Great Archive.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The quiet Great Archive, bathed in warm candlelight, looks very peaceful.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks very nice, but I wouldn't want to be the one who replaces all these candles when they burn out.</line>
<line speaker="Old Rootie">Hee, hee, hee... Are you two folks interested in hearing a rumour?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A rumour, you say? Well, I suppose rumours can be a useful source of information... One can learn a lot about a place by simply talking to its people.</line>
<line speaker="Old Rootie">Hee hee! Sounds like you folks are after some juicy gossip, all right!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What kind of rumour can you tell us?</line>
<line speaker="Old Rootie">Hee, hee... That's a silly question, youngster! It's not for me to choose the rumour... You two folks have to guess what it is!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Old Rootie">Take a look at this! One, two... One, two... What's today's vegetable? Hee, hee! Why, it's a puzznip!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">30</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Old Rootie">You folks must love your puzzles to have solved the puzznip. Hee, hee!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What a charming thought, putting a puzzle into a turnip like that.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">She's certainly lively, isn't she, Professor? ...By the way, what about that rumour?</line>
<line speaker="Old Rootie">No more puzznips today, I'm afraid. You folks should come again another day.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's a statue of a knight. We've got them in London, too.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is a magnificent statue. We can deduce from it that knights are very respected in this town.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The water's so pure and cold.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's comfortably asleep. Just like in our world, cats take it easy here.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Cats used to be valued for catching mice. I wonder if they're kept here for the same reason?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This kitty likes sitting on top of barrels.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The cat seems determined not to get down unless someone makes it an offering of delicious fish.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Where do the wagons with milk come from?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I haven't seen any cows or goats around here, but there may be a farm outside the town?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Someone left their wagon unsupervised.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So many types of fish! Is there a river or a lake nearby?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Interesting. I, too, wonder where they obtain so much fish from.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The fish are very fresh. Some are still alive, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Mmm...there's a delicious smell coming from the bakery.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There is only one bakery in this area, it would seem.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So many types of bread! Sweet, savoury...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Well, doesn't that look imposing? Who designed that building?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">An enormous book presides over this town, governed by a story...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I didn't know that medieval people could build things on this scale.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Unlike in the other parts of the town, buildings here are tall and magnificent.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks quite posh.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Many of the houses have shops on the ground floor and living quarters above.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm. The door and windows on the ground floor are shut. Could this be so for safety reasons?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">If this was my house, I'd keep the windows open during the day to let fresh air in.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's a water fountain. The water looks very clear. It may be suitable for drinking.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There must be a spring somewhere nearby.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A pile of discarded wooden crates.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">They're just crates. Nothing to see.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Look at that bench, Professor! Wouldn't it be nice to spend a whole day on it, reading in the sunshine?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Luke, we are carrying out an investigation. This is not the time to be lazing about on a bench.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A single bell hangs in the belfry. Perhaps it is sounded on special occasions.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's one huge bell.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Some knights are standing guard at the entrance. I guess we can't go in.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is plausible that the guards are there to make sure no one goes to ring the bell without permission.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The forest stretches ahead. I hope there are no snakes. I'm not good with snakes...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The weather is so fine that it is hard to believe this town is threatened by witches.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Seen during the day, it has a very intriguing shape.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It was hewn out of one stone, from the looks of it.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The path splits in two directions. We can check where the other branch leads on another occasion.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This deep in the forest, no one can hear the screams of burning witches...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">However magnificent this courthouse looks, the trials that take place inside are an ugly matter.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, I saw another owl.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Owls are nocturnal animals. This forest seems to sustain quite a large population.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There is a current, so this moat has to be connected to a river or some other waterway.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oh, little fish are swimming over there! It's quite pretty for a moat.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The water is very clean. I suppose there is a spring nearby.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Opening and closing that heavy gate behind every visitor must be a bother.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The guards are very alert. We can be certain that this town's creator is nearby.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This area is guarded pretty tight. Maybe the knights are keeping an eye on us.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Limiting the means of access to a bridge, supervised from the keeps, is a good way to keep intruders out.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It feels like they're not only looking out for witches but trying to keep the townspeople out, too.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">............Ah! Aren't you... Hershel Layton, the Hatter?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, I'm not a hatter... Although I certainly am Hershel Layton. I have been told that my presence is requested in the Audience Room.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">I've definitely heard something about that, but it's beyond me why...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">With all due respect, why would the Storyteller invite mere commoners to the Audience Room?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Aren't people normally allowed to visit?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Of course not! Both the Audience Room and the tower in which he resides are areas of strict surveillance. One does not simply... visit the Storyteller.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Did you say...tower?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">The Storyteller's Tower, naturally. Don't tell me you've never heard of it! He only comes out of his tower to appear before the people in his parades. The Audience Room is where the Storyteller comes whenever there is a parade. We, the order of knights, provide his protection from this guard post! We feel honoured by his presence, even if he doesn't speak to us.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I see... Then it would seem we are extremely privileged to have been invited here.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Hurrumph, don't let it get to your head! Wait here while I open the gate.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Come to think of it, during the parade... the Storyteller did seem to be held in high esteem by all the townsfolk.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, Luke. After all, he is the author of this town's story. So he is effectively like some kind of god.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Like...a god?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Nooo! Someone tell me this isn't happening!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............? There seems to be some commotion over there.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It's that knight! He's coming back this way. And he doesn't look too happy...</line>
<line speaker="Knight">This is bad, really bad! What am I going to do?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What's the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Well, actually, Dark Hat, the g-gate won't open! It's broken...and I can't fix it!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">So what happens now?!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">I wish I knew... Wh-what am I to do?! We need to do something... Can't keep the Storyteller waiting! If we do... there goes my career as a knight! Um...unless, aren't you two meant to be good at finding people?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Finding...people? I wouldn't say we're particularly good...</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Don't say that, I need your help here! There is one knight who is able to fix the gates, but he's busy training with the other knights. I'd like to call him back here without disturbing the others... but in armour, they all look the same. The only way to identify him is to look for a knight with an unusually shaped sword.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Unusually shaped sword? How interesting...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor, doesn't that mean...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, my boy. It means we can tackle this the way we would a puzzle.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">So...will you...find him?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Okay, I'll see what I can do.</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">25</line>
<line speaker="Notes">Penalty for an incorrect submission</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Thanks to you, Sir Hatter, I've been able to have it repaired immediately.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm glad you were able to fix it.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A puzzle like that is a piece of cake for the professor!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Hmm...as I suspected all along, you're certainly no ordinary gentleman. Sir Hatter, Hershel Layton, shall henceforth be allowed to pass through this gate freely.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Thank you, kind sir.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Please make your way to the Storyteller as swiftly as possible!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Usually, common townsfolk are not allowed through this gate. Only the knights are permitted to go beyond this guard post into the Storyteller's domain.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wow! No matter where I look, there are knights everywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, indeed. The knights have their guard post on this side of the gate. Given the grandness of the scale, I imagine they are living here too.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But I wonder exactly where around here we're supposed to meet the Storyteller... That knight said to go to the Audience Room, wherever that is... With a name as grand as "Audience Room", you'd think it would be easy to notice.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... Luke, can you see the long flight of stairs over there? I think we should go and take a look.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A flight of stairs? Ah...I see it! There's also a building over there. Looks rather stately... Do you think that's where the Audience Room is?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, my boy. However, there seems to be something going on over there. And from the looks of things, I don't think we'll be able to just ignore it and stroll right by. At any rate, let's go and take a look.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Hmm... Hmm...hmm. Hmm...this is no good! It's been three days and three nights, but still I don't get it...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What is it that you don't understand?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Whoa! Don't frighten me like that! How long have you been there?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We've been here for quite some time now...</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Hmm... Mmm... Well...I suppose I can tell you. See, I've been doing my mind training. Us knights must train...not just physically, but mentally too.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Training of the mind? How delightful. As a gentleman, I always endeavour to keep my thinking flexible, too.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Hmm...your comment exudes confidence! And if you are so self-assured, why not try solving this puzzle? This is a chess puzzle based on a brave fight between knights. The trouble is, no matter how hard I try, I can't defeat the black knight!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">20</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Whoa! You beat the black knight! If I can just remember how you did that... Hmm... Mmm... All right, now if I can beat him, he can keep guard of this area next week instead of me!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Keep guard...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">instead [sic] of you?</line>
<line speaker="Knight">...! N-no! It's, um, purely for mind training, believe me!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Sounds a little fishy to me...</line>
<line speaker="Knight">This kind of chess puzzle is becoming quite popular recently. But naturally, I do this for mind training, not just for the fun of it.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Splendid. I wouldn't mind having a go myself one day.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah, Professor! I think there are mice hiding up there!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Take a closer look, Luke... You may notice that there are not only mice hiding there.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Eh? Ah...I see what you mean, Professor! There's a hidden puzzle there, too! Just leave it to me, Professor! I can handle a puzzle like this, no problem!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This puzzle might prove to be a little tricky. Take a deep breath and do your best! If you think it's too much for you right now, you can always select "Quit" and come back to it later.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">25</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor! That's the Storyteller's chariot from the parade!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">So this is where it's parked when not in use.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We need to save Miss Espella before the next parade...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Enthusiastic shouts and clinking of metal can be heard from the other side. A training session?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Seeing the knights practise has rekindled my passion for fencing. Perhaps I should join them.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But aren't swords useless against witchcraft?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ooh, I can hear the horses in there! I'd like to chat with them.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's a big stable. It just shows how important horses are for getting around here in Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The horses are all in a good mood. They're neighing, "This hay's sooo good!"</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">How many times do I gotta tell you? I ain't this "suspicious guy" you're after!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Hmm... And you expect us to believe you just because you say so, eh? You can save us all time and trouble here. Just admit your guilt and be done with it!</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">You gotta be kiddin' me! This is a false accusation! C'mon, why won't you listen to me? I admit my face might look a li'l scary, sure. But I'm tellin' yer straight... my pals are always sayin' there's no one with a purer heart than good old Cutter!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Oh, spare me...we're getting nowhere here. Hey, knights!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Yessir!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Put this miserable wretch into solitary confinement!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Yessir, Captain!</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">Oi, oi! What're ya doing?! I'm innocent... Innocent, I tell ya!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You seem to have your hands full here. May I ask what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Hey, if it isn't you two! Do you mean to tell me you're the ones that the Storyteller has summoned?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's us, all right! So you can't go chasing us around the way you did before.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Nnngh... Rats...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">By the way, Captain, what has that man been accused of?</line>
<line speaker="Captain">What has he done? He is guilty of carrying out a heinous crime of assault and theft!</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">How many times do I gotta say it? It weren't me...it's a FALSE ACCUSATION. I'm totally innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Silence! Who else could have done it?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm...could you tell me a little more about this?</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Well, I had a feeling you'd want to know... You seem to like poking your nose into other people's business. A series of thefts have been occurring in this town...and at the same time, a suspicious figure has been sighted. Now, I ask you, does this man not look suspicious to you? Clearly it has to be him!</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">You got it all wrong! I heard there was a thief in the area... That's why I teamed up with them townsfolk to keep a lookout for the blighter! And that ain't all! I even found a way to make sure every dang corner of the town was bein' watched. We placed ourselves in positions where we didn't obstruct one another's line of sight! Catch my drift? This suspicious figure you guys mentioned...there ain't no way that was me!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">So you're saying that you watched every part of the town, while at the same time avoiding overlapping each other's search? That's impossible. You committed the crimes and are lying to cover yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I wonder if you're perhaps mistaken... It might just be true. For example, if they positioned themselves like this...</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">40</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Hmm... I would never have guessed such a solution could exist.</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">So d'ya believe me now?! I was tellin' the truth! The real culprit must still be on the loose, goin' around stealing stuff in broad daylight!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Hmm... Men, it looks like we've no choice. Let him go. We'd better head back to the crime scene and go over it again with a fine-toothed comb.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Yes, Captain!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, I'm glad we were able to sort out the misunderstanding.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">I don't know who you two are, but you're a bit too sharp to be some regular townsfolk.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Not at all, we're nothing so special. Just a couple of regular English gentlemen.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Hmm...English, eh? So what is that, your title? Well, whatever it may be...it's not normal to be summoned directly by the Storyteller himself. It would appear that you are indeed something special... The Storyteller is in the Audience Room. I wouldn't keep him waiting if I were you! As for the Audience Room, it's in the building at the top of those stairs.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That building up there...just as we thought. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Just mind your manners when in the presence of the Storyteller, you hear me? If I hear any sign of trouble... you'll regret it!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">W-we'll be on our best behaviour! So please keep your hand off your sword - you're scaring me!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It just goes to show how highly the knights regard the Storyteller. Now then, let's move on, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right. Let's go, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">You did it! You've saved my hide big time, fellas! I won't forget this, believe me! An' I'll tell you two this: my motto is to always return kindness from others! So if you two ever find yerselves in trouble, just gimme a shout and I'll be right there!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The Storyteller should be in here, right? I'm starting to feel a little nervous... ...Hmm, this area is totally deserted. All I can hear is the wind...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It looks as if not even the knights are allowed to come up here.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">He really is treated almost like a god... I wonder what someone like that wants to talk to us about...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What is it, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Have a look at this, Luke. There's a puzzle concealed here. In a situation like this, perhaps solving a puzzle might help to relieve stress.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I think you're right, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">40</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It doesn't seem to be a trap.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What if...once you're in, you can't get out?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We should proceed with caution.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I can make out the outline of a tall building in the fog. This could be the tower the knights spoke of.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It could rival a skyscraper! They didn't have buildings like that in the Middle Ages, surely.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Huh? Professor...the door won't open! Helloooo! Is anybody there? ............ No reply.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It appears there is no key hole... This is no ordinary lock mechanism.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Inviting someone to visit you only to lock them out?! That's a bit rude!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Just a moment, Luke...if you look closely, you'll see there's a puzzle built in there. I believe this may be a test, Luke. A test to determine whether we qualify for an audience with the Storyteller or not.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hmm...that's a bit off, isn't it? But when it comes to puzzles...we'll be glad to oblige, won't we, Professor?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, my boy. Let's show our mettle!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">40</line>
<line speaker="Notes">The puzzle can be solved in four moves, but this is not necessary to clear it.</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Luke">We did it, Professor! That should open the door!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would seem that we have proven ourselves worthy...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Labyrinthia's creator is waiting for us inside...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The creator...of this town. I wonder what he intends to say.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Are you all right, Luke? I imagine you must be a little nervous.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wh-who, me? Well, to be honest...I suppose I am, just a little. But don't worry, Professor, I can do this! Let's go... Let's meet the Storyteller!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Very well. Muster your courage - we're going in!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">...And thus, the guests finally made their appearance! I bid you welcome to Labyrinthia, the town governed by stories.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I've been waiting for you, Hershel Layton.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I believe I should say, it is an honour. Mr Storyteller.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You're the creator of Labyrinthia... But...why did you call the professor here?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I have summoned you... so that I may ask you...why you are here.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I beg your pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wh-what are you talking about?!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............ In writing the story, I provide everything... and in turn, take everything away. I give each person a story... and weave their intertwining webs of fate. However, it would appear that interlopers have found their way into the story. The two of you.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ You mean to say...that my presence here was not written in your story?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">...Precisely. And so, I must ask you...exactly how did you find your way into this world?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">In truth, we found ourselves here somewhat inadvertently. We were brought here by a book... A book called the Historia Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I am led to believe it was you who wrote that book... Surely you cannot deny it.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">It would appear I have found it - the source of the corruption within my story.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Corruption?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">In other words, you consider our presence to be a hindrance to your story, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Not only you... There was another man who tried to change the course of my story.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You mean...Carmine Accidenti?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Carmine... So, there is a connection between him and the two of you after all.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Oops...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Your presence here is, shall I say... a slight inconvenience. The story of Labyrinthia is about to take a turn towards its grand finale.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Grand finale?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Indeed. A conclusion that requires a climax of epic proportions. The identity of the Great Witch Bezella is made public...she is tried in the court and finally...destroyed! At last, peace will be restored to the town... The final scenario is close at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Th-the identity of the Great Witch... Do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's true that the townsfolk look at me in a... different way. And the reason for that is because... I am...the Storyteller's daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're...WHAAAAAAAAAAAT?! Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're the Storyteller's daughter? <thought>I didn't...see that coming...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">When I first came down into the town, everyone was friendly. Perhaps they thought that if they got to know me, things would go well for them. That was the impression I had.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm...that sounds like the kind of thing people would probably do. But obviously not me! I wouldn't do anything like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No one's accusing you of anything, Maya!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">...But unfortunately, things didn't work out the way people hoped they would.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm...well, people should realise that good things don't come easy.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Then one day someone just happened to bump into me in the town... and I was knocked over. Later...that night, that same person was attacked by a witch and killed by her magic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I don't know whether it was just a coincidence or not, but... after that, everyone's attitude towards me changed. They started saying things like "it's best to keep away from her, or you'll have a bad story written about you". All because I'm the Storyteller's daughter...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's the Storyteller thinking?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, he has his daughter stuck in a place like this... And if he didn't write such a bad story, she wouldn't have to suffer like this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>You have a good point there, Maya...</thought> Anyway, the investigation has only just begun. Espella, if it's okay with you...I'd like to ask you a few more questions.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Of course, I'd like to help in any way I can.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've got to gather as much information as I can. I should ask Espella about...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This might be difficult for you to answer, but... Why are you not living with the Storyteller... I mean, with your father?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I did live with him before. We lived together on the edge of the town... in the Storyteller's Tower.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Storyteller's Tower...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">When I was little, he was very kind... And always listened to what I had to say. But then, at some point or other, he started to become distant... If you think about it, I guess it's only natural... because he had to write the Story for every single person in the town.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">As he became busier and busier... I was left alone in the tower. And that's the reason... I decided to leave home with Eve and live in the town. I stayed with Aunt Patty and helped out at the bakery. Now you two are at the shop too... But my dad... ............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's the deal with the Storyteller...? I can't believe he'd write a story where his own daughter is the Great Witch Bezella...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe the professor will be able to find out the Storyteller's true motives...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what about Patty? Does she know anything about your past? Have you ever told her that you're the Storyteller's daughter?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes...she knows. When the other people in town started avoiding me...Aunt Patty was the only one who stood by me that whole time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, Patty's always looking out for you...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">There is so much I have to thank her for... It's been five years since I left my dad and started living with Aunt Patty. She's always been so kind... She's been like a mother to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now that you mention it... what about your real mother, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">She... Actually, I... I can't remember anything about her. According to my dad, she died in an accident when I was still young. And...that's really all I know. He didn't tell me any more than that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella, we believe in you. There's no way you can be the Great Witch Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's right! That's why we'll find the real Great Witch!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">The real...Great Witch... But...the Great Witch is only a character of legend. How could you possibly find her?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, admittedly...at the moment we have no real leads.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Actually, to be honest, we know next to nothing about Labyrinthia. We were supposed to have been living with you for five years now... but that memory turned out to be completely phoney...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you have any ideas at all, Espella? Anything that could give us a clue. I guess it's a lot to ask...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">All magic-related incidents are thoroughly investigated by the Knights of the Inquisition. And if there were any clues as to the whereabouts of the Great Witch, then I believe they would have found them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">As far as I know, there's not a single incident that has remained unsolved by the inquisitors.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............ Wait a minute, that's not right...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The part about there being no unsolved incidents left...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Last night...me and Luke ran into High Inquisitor Darklaw.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, what?! You saw High Inquisitor Darklaw?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup. She said she was investigating some kind of incident with magic. She said that it took place three months ago, I think. Apparently, it's "the only incident that has remained unsolved".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An unsolved incident...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Oh! Now that you mention it, I remember hearing rumours about such a case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The only magic incident in Labyrinthia to remain unsolved, huh...</thought> Espella, about that incident... Could you tell us about it in more detail?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No way! We just got to the good part!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright, Maya! I really don't know much about that incident. But perhaps you could try asking an inquisitor about it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, Espella. Thanks for the help.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All right...we'll see you again real soon. Keep your spirits up, Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Thank you. Take care, both of you!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Wright... Maya... They're both doing so much for me. ............ I wonder...if there's anything I could do for both of them in return... The Great Witch Bezella... Until now, I hadn't given it much thought... ...!... ...The Great Witch... ...The Legendary Fire... ...Flames... Inferno... Oh my... Wh-what is this...? ...My...head...hurts...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">No! What...what was that? That...inferno...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This town's one and only unsolved incident of magic...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm sure she said something about an alchemist who lost their life to a witch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An alchemist was attacked? <thought>Hm, that sounds like a serious case.</thought> You got that from High Inquisitor Darklaw, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's right. When I was searching for Eve last night. I meant to tell you about it, but it totally slipped my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm...the only unsolved incident, huh? That's suspicious, all right. This might just be the lead that will take us to the Great Witch.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, let's get to investigating! We can do this thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. So, uh... I guess first we should check out the Inquisitors' Hall, right? We might just learn something there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sure! Let's get going!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>On the other hand...we may just learn how unwelcome we are there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! C'mon, Nick! Enough with that wishy-washy attitude!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I didn't even say anything!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Aren't we going to the Inquisitors' Hall?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So...the Inquisitors' Hall is upstairs, right? I hope someone's in.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">These old benches can wait. Let's go to the Inquisitors' Hall!</line>
<line speaker="???">Woof, woof, woof! Ruff, ruff, woof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-wait a minute... That aggressive bark... Please tell me that isn't...</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Woof, woof!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aha! It's Constantine! He looks happy to see us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wish I could say the feeling was mutual. Once bitten, twice shy... That pretty much sums me up right now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? I dunno... I think he's looking much friendlier today if you ask me. See? Come on, Nick, pet him just once...</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Grrrrr...grrrrr...woof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaargh! <thought>This mutt really, REALLY hates me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Well, well... If it isn't Sir Blue Knight... Exactly what are you doing over there on all fours?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...Inquisitor Barnham! Um, glad to see you again. Actually, there's something we'd like to ask you about. Come on, Nick...stand up already!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oooh...I'd like to meet that mutt's owner face-to-face.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Pfft... How foolish... Constantine happens to be mine. And a true knight's companion he is. He needn't waste time sinking his teeth into the likes of you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh...I had a hunch. So Constantine really is your dog, huh? <thought>Gotta admire the nerve of this guy... He just sits back and lets his dog bite people, err...I mean, me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Never mind that. What is it that you want to talk about? Just make it quick...Sir Blue Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So...you inquisitors are the ones who investigate incidents of magic in this town, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Yes, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If you don't mind, we'd like to ask you about that unsolved incident with magic.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ There's one thing you must never forget: the Knights of the Inquisition excel at their work.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Uh, right.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">All incidents of magic perpetrated by the witches are dealt with by the inquisitors. Without exception.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Spoken with that usual calm and collected air of confidence...</thought> That's interesting... You see, we heard different. Apparently, there's one particular incident that still remains unsolved.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Something about an alchemist being murdered... Ring any bells?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">What?! Who did you get that information from?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We...erm... Well...High Inquisitor Darklaw.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ Well, why the blazes didn't you say so?! You could have saved us some time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? How is it my fault...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">The High Inquisitor has put me on the spot by leaking such information to the likes of you. Well, I suppose that leaves nothing for it... I shall tell you the whole story, since I do not believe in doing things by halves...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please, go ahead. We're all ears.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It was three months ago that an alchemist living near the town square was murdered.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sorry, Inquisitor Barnham, but I'm kinda lost already... Is there a difference between alchemy and magic?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ When it comes to something that difficult, it will do no good asking me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">It seems that while the townspeople respected him, they also treated him with caution.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They respected him?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">He used his skills to make medical concoctions and acted much like a physician. The efficacy of his cures was almost like magic. He was famous within his neighbourhood. In fact, he was sometimes referred to as "Dr Belduke" by the townspeople. ...At any rate, it's safe to say that Sir Belduke was no witch.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">How can you say for sure?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">That's simple... Sir Belduke was a man.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>Well, can't really argue with that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Sir Belduke came to a mysterious end three months ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A mysterious end...?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">There were two things about his death that cannot be explained rationally. Firstly, the murder scene. His body was discovered in his residence, in the study. His room was locked. There was no conceivable way the crime could have been committed, except by witchcraft.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Isn't that what people call a "locked room mystery"?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Hmm...? A what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh...ah...it's nothing...really. So what was the other mysterious thing?</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ Secondly, until then, all incidents involving witches had been foretold in the story.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Foretold in the story? <thought>In other words, predicted by the Storyteller...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">However... The murder of Sir Belduke did not appear in the story. Such a thing had never occurred before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So not only was this the only unsolved incident in Labyrinthia's history... but it was also the only incident not to be predicted by the Storyteller.</thought> Hmm...this definitely sounds worth investigating.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ You certainly are an interesting one, Sir Blue Knight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You really think you can solve this incident alone, when the Knights of the Inquisition have been working on it for three months? I must say, that is some confidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...We won't know unless we try.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">You may risk becoming the target of some terrifying witch's vengeance...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>I'm hoping that was a joke...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Well... I suppose you may as well take a look... Who knows, you may even find something. Sir Belduke's residence is just beyond the town square. Ask anyone around there, they'll soon point you in the right direction.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Inquisitor Barnham.</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">............ Sir Blue Knight. I believe our courtroom battles are far from over. Until we meet again in court...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'll see you then, Inquisitor.</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Grrrrr...woof, woof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya...can you PLEASE get this mutt away from me? I can't feel my leg...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww...so soon? I was hoping he'd use you as a blue chew toy just one more time!</line>
<line speaker="Barnham">Sir Belduke's residence has already been scoured by the Knights of the Inquisition. I believe you will only be wasting your time if you go there now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Next time we pass through this door, we'll have the decisive evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, it's time for the Great Witch hunt! Let's go, go, go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If we're gonna take a short break and sit down for a while, let's find a more comfy spot.</line>
<line speaker="Old Rootie">Hee, hee, hee... Would you two folks be interested in a rumour?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? A rumour? What kind of rumour?</line>
<line speaker="Old Rootie">Hee, hee... That, young lady, is a silly question! It's not for me to choose the rumour... You two folks have to guess what it is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We have to guess it? You mean if we roll off a few yes or no questions, you'll answer them for us? Do you think you could tell us about the alchemist?</line>
<line speaker="Old Rootie">All right... But no need to rush. First, let's see what vegetable you folks get.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">See what...vegetable we get? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Old Rootie">Take a look at this! One, two... One, two... What's today's vegetable, I wonder... Hee, hee! That would be... a wee little pumpkin! This little fella is small, even for a pint-sized pumpkin.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... Right...</line>
<line speaker="Old Rootie">Now, as for that alchemist... He was an outstandingly handsome man. And that smile of his...why, it worked wonders on all the women folk, all right! Better than any medicine, or so they say. Worked a treat for me, too! That smile would always ease my nerve pains...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Oh...that's it?</line>
<line speaker="Old Rootie">Well, it was a very small pumpkin! That's all for today, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So you're saying...that the alchemist's remedies weren't so effective?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think that's quite what she meant...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, we've reached the square. But I wonder where the alchemist's residence is...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick, look over there! There's a street leading away from the square...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, you're right! Let's go take a look.</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Hey, I thought you two were working at the bakery... Are you goofing off?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well...not exactly...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Actually, we thought we'd give up baking and try our hands at something else.</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Is that so? Sounds like a good idea... Your bread did taste...a little unusual, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaaaaat?! You mean our bread wasn't delicious?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's strange... I mean, we used so much butter...and kneaded that dough so hard...</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Just my opinion, mind. I prefer my bread a little more fluffy and light.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, really? So, uh...just how fluffy and light are we talking here?</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Well...maybe about as fluffy and light as in this puzzle...</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">50</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Wow, impressive work! I really didn't expect you to solve that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, I thought the same thing too...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, I knew I could do it!</line>
<line speaker="Petter">So what were you out-of-work bakers doing hanging around here, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We're investigating an incident involving the alchemist.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know anything about it?</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Surely the Knights of the Inquisition are the ones you should ask... They could tell you a lot more than I can.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You might be right about that.</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Even so, it's a right shame someone like him could get murdered... I often went to him myself to get medicine. He was always friendly and understanding.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Seems like Sir Belduke was a good man... At least, from what we've heard so far.</line>
<line speaker="Petter">I just hope they manage to solve this case soon.</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Personally, I prefer my bread soft as a cloud, not hard as a rock. I seem to remember the bread being fluffier and lighter before...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this is Sir Belduke's residence...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It definitely looks like an alchemist's house. I've never seen plants like these before...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So...what do we do now? Just because the owner's deceased, we can't exactly go barging in...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... But have you noticed just how well kept his yard is? It looks like someone is still living here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Someone has definitely been doing the upkeep around here, that's for sure...</thought> ...Hey! Who's that over there?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's a strange place to put a vase!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seems to serve the same purpose as a mailbox. There are letters sticking out of it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'd normally call that weird, but since it's an alchemist's house, it's sort of fitting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Some plant is growing in that vase, too. I wonder if it's intentional.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What fruit is that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They look so juicy! I'm going to try one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is an alchemist's garden, Maya. I'd advise against eating anything that grows here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The bell tower's visible over the treetops.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So the town square is in that direction.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The bell tower is really tall. How come we've never heard the bell?</line>
<line speaker="???">My sincere apologies. I'm afraid medicaments are no longer being provided here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="???">Did you not come here for medicaments of some kind?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...no, we...didn't come here for that. We're here to investigate the incident... The one involving Sir Belduke.</line>
<line speaker="???">Forgive me if I'm mistaken, but... you do not look like members of the Knights of the Inquisition.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm Phoenix Wright, attorney at law. And you...? I'm guessing you live here?</line>
<line speaker="???">Indeed. My name is Jean Greyerl. I was butler to the late Master Belduke.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, a butler! This must be my first time meeting a real one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Mr Greyerl, if you don't mind... I've been told that the incident involving your master was shrouded in mystery. Has it got something to do with the Great Witch Bezella? We're trying to investigate that at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">The Great Witch...Bezella? Am I right in supposing that you are... defending Espella Cantabella?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, actually... Yes, yes we are. So you know Espella, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That goes without saying... Everyone around here knows her.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you think you can help us? We're here looking for leads.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ While he was alive, the master taught me the value of investigating the truth that governs the natural world. If you, too, are investigating the truth, then it would be against his teachings for me not to cooperate with you. Would you both like to come in? We can discuss the matter further, inside.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That would be great. Thank you, Mr Greyerl.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa. Spoken like a true butler! He's a pretty cool guy, isn't he, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is this room?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">This is the room that Master Belduke kindly provided as my accommodation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, uh... Is this the room where the incident took place?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That would be the master's study. It is the room right next door. However... the state of the room has been carefully preserved since the incident three months ago. As such, entry into the room is not currently permitted.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? Bummer...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that by order of the Knights of the Inquisition, by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes. And as I have lived with Master since an early age... they also decided it would be only fitting for me to stay on and keep the place in order.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So you've been looking after the place ever since Sir Belduke passed away?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes...that's correct. Now then, is there anything further you wish to discuss?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The town is over there. It's the opposite direction from the bell tower.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A pretty view like this makes you forget all about witches and murders.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Books and documents are all neatly placed on the shelves. Greyerl is a very tidy person.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe Jean could teach me some alchemy and you how to keep your desk tidy, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is that a minibar? What's inside all those bottles?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, don't drink it! Who knows what strange mixtures the alchemist kept in those bottles!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The floor's been singed. The Legendary Fire didn't spare even the alchemist's house!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why would the Legendary Fire manifest itself just in this room? Greyerl probably dropped a candle.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">As I mentioned a moment ago, I know very little about this matter. As a matter of fact, it might be better to ask the inquisitors. I can tell you about one thing, though... Namely, what occurred before the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Before the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes. It was three months ago, around the time that Master Belduke was murdered. We were on our way back from collecting specimens for research, and it was already into the small hours of the morning. There was a thunderstorm on the way, and as the storm drew nearer, we quickly made our way home.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Anyone would have been surprised at what we saw, but Master Belduke... well, how can I put this... he reacted in a most peculiar way. Unlike others who saw it, he seemed unsettled, as if he was truly afraid of something. After that bell tower appeared, he changed completely. Master Belduke became a different man.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-wait a second! Did you just say...a bell tower appeared?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, that explains it! That must be... what High Inquisitor Darklaw meant when she mentioned an incident involving the bell tower.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">To this day I do not know what the master was so afraid of...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you think...it was connected in some way to his death?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I think it must have been magic. I mean, for a bell tower to just appear like that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Mr Greyerl, do you mind if we have a look around? I know that the inquisitors have already carried out a full investigation, but... There just might be a clue or two with some kind of connection to the Great Witch.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............ Well I suppose... Providing I am allowed to accompany you, of course. There is sensitive equipment everywhere. And it is my responsibility to take care of it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I understand. We'll be careful.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder how the professor and Luke are doing with their visit to the Storyteller...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I've been wondering about that too. A chance to meet Labyrinthia's "creator"... Let's just hope they don't upset the guy and have some terrible plot twist written about them...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That'd only happen if it was YOU that visited the Storyteller, Nick. The professor would never let anything like that happen. I've got a feeling they'll come back with some pretty useful leads. We have to do our best too, Nick! Let's keep up our side of this investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You got it, Maya. We're all in this together. C'mon, let's see what we can find!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's the spirit!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">The Great Witch Bezella...will be tried in the court?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">That will be Labyrinthia's final chapter. A fitting end, for a town ruled by witches and their magic.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Am I to believe that this final chapter has already begun?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">That is correct... And there is no way you can possibly change its final outcome.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Hmm... I wonder about that. You see, I gave my word to a young lady. I promised...that without fail, I would be able to rescue her. If I'm not mistaken, the Great Witch trial will begin in two weeks' time. The same day on which you will hold your next parade. I believe that should give us sufficient time to show you what we can do.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Such a smug countenance... I find it...intolerable.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I beg your pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Two weeks from now, you say? I'm afraid that information is out of date, Hershel Layton.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Out of date? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">My parade will be held the day after tomorrow, according to the amended story.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Whaaaat?! The day after tomorrow? Th-that's not fair!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Now that's the kind of countenance I want from the characters in my story!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wh-what?!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">That's what I do, didn't you know? I decide the fate of characters who have no knowledge of their future. It would appear that you are not yet fully aware of the gravity of the situation. Let me see now... Just for fun, I'll write you a little story. A story full of surprises and a few tears... I shall enjoy seeing the emotions of the characters as they play their parts...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">A story...for us?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Stories are a fixture of this town... You would be wise to embrace them. Let's see...I think we need a stimulating incident... We shall have a witch, some witchcraft...and perhaps a little death.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Death... You can't!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Oh, but I can... Let me see... This is a golden opportunity to use the alchemist's residence. How about this...? Your comrade meets with death by golden curse in the alchemist's residence. Hmm...this could be a truly interesting story.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">No way...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Feel free to act as you wish, when playing your role in the story.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">H-how can you?!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">"A man from afar falls to a golden curse, and a woman from afar cries out in grief." Th-this must be referring to Maya and Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...! If we don't do something, Mr Wright and Miss Fey will be in danger! There's no time to lose, Luke! Let's go and find them.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Hm...the story has already been written. And no matter what you do, you will not change the result.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I do not agree. What we do next can change the future in any number of ways...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I'm sure that's what you want to believe. In fact, a naive outburst like that could be a poignant plot point... Please, be my guest. Your words may help to raise the tension and bring a little excitement to my story!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You...you monster!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Luke! Now is not the time... We need to help Mr Wright and Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Okay... Let's go, Professor! Better hurry!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hm? Professor, do you hear a... a flapping sound coming this way?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The sound of a large bird, perhaps...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Ah! That's the owl that we saw in the Audience Room!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's holding a letter in its mouth... Not to mention watching us intently.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Perhaps he wants to tell us something. I'll try talking to him to see what he wants.</line>
<line speaker="Hoot">Hoo-hooo!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">What can we do for you?</line>
<line speaker="Hoot">Hoo-hoo-hooo.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I've got it, Professor! Hoot - that's the owl - says the letter was delivered to the Storyteller three months ago.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">To the Storyteller? If that's so, then we can't very well keep it. After all, it's wrong to read letters addressed to someone else.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's what the owl said... But he also said there's absolutely nothing written on the sheets of parchment inside the envelope. Look, Professor! See...they're totally blank.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A letter with nothing written on it... That is, indeed, most curious.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">And another thing, Professor... The owl says this letter was sent by the alchemist...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What's that, my boy? Written by the alchemist? Do you remember what the Storyteller wrote in that story he penned a moment ago? A victim of a golden curse lies in the dwelling of a user of false alchemy. Which probably means the place at which this incident will occur...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">is [sic] the home of the one who sent this letter. In other words, at the alchemist's house, right, Professor?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It appears the address of the sender, Sir Belduke, is written on the envelope. Which means...we had better make our way there immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Hoot">Hoo-hoo.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Thanks, Mr Hoot!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The address on the envelope is somewhere near the town square.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">That's a little far from here, Professor. We might not make it in time... I think we'd better run!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Luke, my boy, we have the need... to rent a steed!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I think you're right, Professor! That would be far quicker than running!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Quickly, Luke! There's no time to lose!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hey, easy, boy! This horse is certainly spirited!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Say, Nick...have you noticed how the colour of that wall is different from all the other walls in the room?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I think I've investigated enough crime scenes by now to notice something as obvious as that, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I'm embarrassed to admit it, but actually there was a small fire here a while ago. It was my fault. The wall ended up a little bit singed in the process...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now that you mention it, there are some signs of a fire on the floor there, too.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes, that's correct. Anyway, I decided to paint the wall myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like Mr Greyerl is way handier with his herbs than with a paintbrush...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I let a candle set fire to some dry straw... In all my time as a butler, I've never made such a major blunder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nah, it's not that bad! You're being a little hard on yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's right, it's not so bad... You think that's bad? You should see Nick try and do the laundry. Now that's a major blunder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, that was one time... A-anyways...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's go check out Mr Belduke's study!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">While we're here, could you show us around your room a little, Mr Greyerl?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Of course. If it will bring you any closer to finding the truth, be my guest. However, as the Knights of the Inquisition have ordered that the crime scene be left undisturbed... I must ask that you refrain from touching anything while you are in the study.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, we'll be careful.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr Greyerl, there's something I was hoping to ask you.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Certainly, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This murder is the only unsolved case involving magic, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes, that is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is it really true that this crime would have been impossible without the use of witchcraft?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That is the conclusion to which the Knights, and the High Inquisitor herself, came. The crime took place behind a locked door, for one thing, which already leads to suspicions of witchcraft. Besides...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Besides?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">The Master was loved by many people, and wasn't at all the type to make enemies. He was kind to everyone, not to mention sincere... It has always been an honour to serve him.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick. How do you think the culprit got into a sealed room, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it was a witch, right? So I guess she used magic to get inside.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I think we should stop calling the culprit a witch... How about "magician"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure we need to be sweating over semantics...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Master Belduke was loved by many people, and wasn't at all the type to have enemies. He was kind to everyone, not to mention sincere... It has always been an honour to serve him. I cannot believe that anyone, other than a witch, would want to harm him.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I got a little careless and failed to properly extinguish a fire. I painted the wall green, so as to cover the discolouration caused by the fire.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The box covers slight burn marks from a small fire.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They could've painted that over with the same green paint as the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, look, Nick! There on the floor... It's one of those...whatchamacallits... You know...a crop circle, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's an alchemist's circle, Maya. We're not in a wheat field...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I'm sorry to repeat myself, but please be sure not to touch anything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You heard him, Maya. That means keep your hands to yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No problem! I'll just do the touching with my eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>With your...eyes?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's the matter, Mr Greyerl?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Oh... It's ah...actually, it's that pendant. I must say, I find it fascinating.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, you mean this old thing? It's called a Magatama.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Maga...tama?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup! You could say it's kind of like my "source of power", I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I understand... Stones are often charged with energy, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The pendant you're wearing is pretty neat too! It's such a mysterious colour...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Oh, this? It's an amethyst. Master Belduke asked me to wear it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An amethyst?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">The amethyst brings about good vibrations, in an alchemy sense. ............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr Greyerl...?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Oh, I'm sorry. I was just remembering Master Belduke. He gave me this stone, and accepted me as his assistant alchemist... But now, Master... Such is the order of the natural world. ............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Seems like Greyerl really misses him... He must have really respected Sir Belduke.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The cabinet might have contained the alchemist's research materials but it's been emptied.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Only some junk's been left behind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like a load of white powder has been scattered around the desk. Um...about this white powder... Has it been here since the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That's right. It was just like this when I entered the room on the morning following the incident. I have left it this way ever since.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess someone must have dropped a container full of some medicine...</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Please try not to walk in it. You may leave footprints...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now that you said it, all I wanna do is leave little ol' footprints all over the place... It'll be like... "Maya wuz here"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like a load of white powder has been scattered around the desk. Maya, try not to step in any of that. The last thing we want to do is leave footprints all over the place.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oooo... Urge to leave footprints everywhere rising...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, that's a pretty little picture over there. We could use a picture like this back at the office, don't you think? We could hang it right next to Charley!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm? What is it, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The wall behind this picture frame...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The wall? Oh...that! It seems like there's...some kind of green mark on the wall just by the painting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if there's something hidden behind this painting...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick, look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The wall behind the painting... <thought>It's painted green!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Is there a problem?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh...no... No problem. <thought>Hmm...this could be some kind of clue.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The wall behind the little painting has been painted green... <thought>Hmm...this could be some kind of clue.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a globe of the night sky.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The alchemist was also an astronomer! Or maybe he was into astrology?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, that's a magic circle! It's neatly drawn and it sure looks magical.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess that's the kind of stuff you're into, being a spirit medium.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A curiously shaped implement. No idea what it was used for.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This could be a device for turning bread into gold!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But we didn't find any leads on the Great Witch...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, uh...Mr Greyerl?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is there anywhere else you can think of where we might find more clues?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Let me see... Well, there is a cellar under this study... That's where the master kept his research materials.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A cellar under this room?</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Yes... There's a trap door in the floor, leading down to the cellar.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A room containing Belduke's research materials...</thought> If you don't mind, I'd like to have a quick look at that room.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">I see. Very well. If you'll please just wait a moment... That ladder leads down into the cellar. But be careful, it's rather dark down there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like it might be a little cramped down there too.</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">That's true... Perhaps it is a little bit small for the both of you at once.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, Nick, this seems more like your kind of thing, anyway!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I dunno...I guess you're just more suited to small, dark, damp places.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not a rat, you know...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">C'mon, you know that's not what I mean! I'll just stay up here and snoop around for some clues.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not snooping, Maya, it's investigating. ...Anyway, you do that. I'll be right back.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yay! Way to go, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Greyerl">Well, I should return to my room. Please give me a call as soon as you have both finished.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, got it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Brrr...it's a little chilly down here. Doesn't look like it's been used much... The air is so musty and stale. ...Anyway. Better hurry up and take a look around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Plenty of sketches and drawings. Nothing useful for us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like Sir Belduke studied alchemy here, too. I don't see anything medicine-like, but there sure is a lot of equipment... This desk is pretty messy. Not a speck of dust, though. I guess Greyerl must be keeping it clean... There's a wooden box by the desk, filled with all kinds of junk. A doll is peeping out of the box. I wonder if it was left by a little girl who was one of the doctor's patients.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like Sir Belduke carried out research here as well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was Belduke's research about? Will all his work be lost now that he's gone?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like...a sculpture of a goat, I think. Something about it gives me the creeps... Wait a second... Is this...?! This thing is completely made of gold! Could this be the result of alchemy? I guess in this town anything's possible... <thought>If Maya were here, she'd break her back trying to take that goat away with her...</thought> That's strange... Almost everything in this room is covered in a layer of dust... Everything except for that goat, that is. Seems to have been kept in pristine condition.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A finely crafted golden goat... and well taken care of, to boot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this? A map?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, well, well...if this isn't a well. Looks like it's still in use, too. I'm guessing you need quite a bit of clean water for alchemy. <thought>Come to think of it...I haven't noticed any plumbing here in Labyrinthia.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This well must have been built here specifically to provide water for alchemical research.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The poor potted plants are starting to wither. I'm going to get some water for them...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This is the alchemist's house! We have to hurry!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Pro-professor! Wait...wait for me!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Miss Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hi, Professor! What's up? You look flushed.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Where's Mr Wright? Have you seen him?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, Nick? He's just down in the basement, doing some investigating. He should be back up soon. So how did it go? Did you get to see the Storyteller?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Please, get Mr Wright, immediately! It's safer if we're all together in one place. I'll explain later...just hurry!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">As things stand, Mr Wright is in serious danger!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick's in danger?! What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I have reason to believe that a witch will appear here soon!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...!</line>
<line speaker="???">All is as written in the Story.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Do you happen to be the Great Witch Bezella?</line>
<line speaker="???">Concern yourselves not with who I am... but rather...with what you will now become!</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Oh dearie, dearie me! Whatever is the matter, child? You look positively flustered. Sir Belduke is no longer resident here. You'll need to go elsewhere for your medicaments.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I know that! Let me through... It's a matter of life and death!</line>
<line speaker="Birdly">Life and death, you say?! If so, then I may foresee a hit ballad. Raise up your hearts, and sing with Birdly! My bird is Cracker! First, second and thirdly!</line>
<line speaker="Luke"><thought>Ah! This must be that rival Mr Bardly was talking about.</thought> Anyway, I'm in a hurry!</line>
<line speaker="Ms Primstone">Oh dearie, dearie me!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ahhh!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It...it wasn't me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What the...?!</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">...It just won't do! I need that faiwy fwower bouquet badwy!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Don't worry, I'll definitely solve it later!</line>
<line speaker="Muffet">If I give him a faiwy fwower bouquet, will he fall head over heels for me?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Are there any other puzzles you wish to take a look at?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">That was splendid. You certainly know how to handle puzzles.</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Any time you feel like solving puzzles, just drop by and let me know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">At this rate, we're never going to find out where Eve is...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This is just a short break, Maya. Don't worry, I'll definitely solve this soon.</line>
<line speaker="Mailer">I'm not sure... About where to take the next letter, I mean. As soon as I am, I'll tell you about the cat. Until then, I can't continue my deliveries. That simply won't do!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">This is...actually quite difficult.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Grrrr... Let's give it one more try!</line>
<line speaker="Price">If you can solve this, I have a feeling I'll be able to remember about that cat.</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">Like I said, c'est la vie...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">C-calm down, Mr Bardly! You mustn't give up so easily!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Solve the puzzle and he'll feel better. Give it another try, Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Bardly">If you could only create such colour, I could surely find the heart to sing.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">We haven't seen, nor heard, nor do we know anything about your cat.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">There's no way you don't know!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's try to persuade them, Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">About your cat, we three knights... know nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Saw nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Heard nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">That was splendid! You certainly know how to handle puzzles.</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Grrr...ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Eve">...Meeow.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh-oh, looks like Constantine's getting a little stressed.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Okay, Maya, let's give this another try!</line>
<line speaker="Constantine">Ruff, ruff, ruff...woof!</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meeow!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Constantine is still acting kinda weird, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I'm certain that if we can all solve this puzzle together, he'll calm down.</line>
<line speaker="Mary">You mean to say you didn't appreciate the cute chorus of my adorable goats? Unbelievable! Drink more of the goat's milk, and it might put some sense into you! Don't you agree, my little Snowy-wowy?</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaa...</line>
<line speaker="Mary">Did you want to hear the cute bleating of my sweet Snowy and the other goats once more before you leave?</line>
<line speaker="Snowy">Baaa...</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Would you like to try another puzzle?</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">That was marvellous!</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">I'll be here any time, if you feel the need to solve a puzzle or two.</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">Was it so loud that you couldn't even solve the puzzle?</line>
<line speaker="Dewey">My neighbour is always stomping around his place. I'll show you just how loud it is.</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">I knew it... I knew I shouldn't trust a stranger like you... You're a friend of the witch...and you tried to take me away with you... Waaaaah! Help me, sis!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, brother... Somehow I had a feeling it would end up like this.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Stop complaining and solve the puzzle!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If only the professor and Luke were here...</line>
<line speaker="Cecil">If you can solve this puzzle, I'll go with you, I promise!</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">That was exceptional puzzle solving!</line>
<line speaker="Ridelle">Feel free to drop in any time you'd like to solve a puzzle or two.</line>
<line speaker="Old Rootie">Hee, hee! The puzznip is rare, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Old Rootie">Today's vegetable is a puzznip!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Oh, no! There's nothing I can do. I'm simply unable to let you in...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">And to think we came this far... What shall we do, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm certain we can solve this puzzle. Let's give it another try.</line>
<line speaker="Knight">I really want to let you through the gate, but I just can't open it! Surely the Hatter can solve this!</line>
<line speaker="Knight">Well, I thought you seemed confident, but maybe I was mistaken...</line>
<line speaker="Knight">As a knight of honour, I must find a way! Do you think you could show me how to defeat the black knight?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Hmm... This might take a little more time...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Why not leave it for the time being? We'll make sure to try again later.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This puzzle might prove to be a little tricky. Take a deep breath and do your best! If you think it's too much for you right now, you can always select "Quit" and come back to it later.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Right you are, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Like I said, it's obvious that the suspicious figure was this guy!</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">You got it all wrong, pal! C'mon, ol' Cutter has a face you can trust!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">At this rate, it's only a matter of time before they take him away to jail.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">But, even though his face looks scary, I don't think he did it... I think he's being falsely accused, just like we were yesterday. If we solve this puzzle, I'm sure we can prove his innocence!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, indeed. Let's give it another try.</line>
<line speaker="Cutter">I'm innocent, I swear! Please, you gotta prove it to 'em!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Even though we didn't solve it, it was still a pleasant diversion. Let's give it another try later.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">In a situation like this, perhaps solving a puzzle might help to relieve stress.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I think you're right, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...This puzzle is quite a tough one.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Come on, Professor! At this rate, we'll never get in!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We've come this far... We can't just give up now. Let's keep trying.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If we don't solve this puzzle, we won't be able to go in.</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Hey...didn't you like my fluffy little puzzle?</line>
<line speaker="Petter">Well? Are you going to solve this fluffy little puzzle then?</line>
</xml>