
<xml>
<title>The Lost Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wha...!? What have I done wrong!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...? B-But I'm just a simple defense attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What a nightmare... And I bet it was this ringtone that caused it... I really shouldn't be dozing off right before a trial starts anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, good. I finally found it. Talk about a close call. I hate to do this to you, but... It's nothing personal... Mr. Attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Ouch... My head... It's throbbing... And why does it feel... so foggy in there...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is this girl babbling about...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Is this how a defense attorney treats his clients, sir!? I can't believe this!!  </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, it's just... ...Well, I think you have the wrong person. I'm... </line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yes...!? "I'm..."!?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">The trial will begin shortly. Will the defendant and her lawyer please proceed to the courtroom immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Maggey Byrde.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The prosecution is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I should say, "Yes" for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... What if I said, "No"? Would that be alright?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Of course it wouldn't!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Then why bother asking to begin with??</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, you see, Your Honor... My memory is kind of...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will not hear the defense's excuses. Because the defendant is a member of the police, this case is under great scrutiny. Therefore, we must make this trial fair but swift. I believe I have told you this before. I hope you're not telling me you've forgotten!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Actually, I did...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Payne, your opening statement, please.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes, Your Honor. As I'm sure you're well aware, the defendant is accused of killing her lover. What's worse, her lover was a fellow police officer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A policeman? You did WHAT to a policeman!?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">It wasn't me! And besides, Dustin and I... We weren't "lovers" like that!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">In any case... The prosecution will prove that the guilty party is none other than the defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Mr. Payne, please call your first witness.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hee, hee, hee. It's been a while, Mr. Wright. Let's see what you've learned since last time. I won't show you any mercy this time, rookie!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okaaay... <thought>And who are you again!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Please bring Detective Dick Gumshoe to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Here we go! Don't let me down, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nowhere to hide... I'm sooo dead...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Witness, please state your name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">My name is Dick Gumshoe, sir.  I'm the detective in charge of homicides down at the precinct, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't look very well, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, sir, the defendant... She works under me, so, you know...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You work under that detective?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yes, sir! And while I was a trainee, he was always watching out for me, sir! He's such a wonderful guy, sir! I'll never forget what he's done for me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>OK, calm down, I believe you.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Detective Gumshoe. Please describe for us the details of this murder.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir. It happened at the park near headquarters, "Exposé Park". The victim was one of the local cops, Dustin Prince. He was pushed down from the benches on the upper path, sir. The landing beat his body up bad and snapped his neck.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The details are listed in the report that was distributed yesterday...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, yes. This autopsy report, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I not remember getting a copy...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see everything is in order here. Even the estimated time of death is unusually well documented!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The victim's watch stopped from the impact of the landing, sir. The results of the autopsy confirmed the time of death.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">If I may, Your Honor, the prosecution would like to submit this photograph.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court accepts it into evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, I recall at yesterday's preliminary hearing, a very important piece of evidence was brought to our attention.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... I guess?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Is your head on right today!? There was a very crucial piece of evidence found under the victim's body!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, was there?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Have you lost your mind!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, actually... Um, it's just nerves. Give me a second.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Whaaaat!? How can you talk like such an amateur!? I thought you were a pro, sir! ... Alright, sir. I'll help you through this! At a time like this, maybe you ought to take a glance at the Court Record!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Court Record?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yup! Info about evidence and people involved with this case are all listed there, sir! You can look at the Court Record by touching the Court Record Button!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Court Record Button...? You really know what you're talking about, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">It's too bad I'm a cop, right? Just think! I could totally be a legal aide instead!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is in session. Save your chit-chat for later!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry, Your Honor... <thought>Well, I guess I'd better check the Court Record, and see what I can find... What was it again? The Court Record Button...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Alright, Mr. Wright. Let's see if your notes are in order. What was the piece of evidence found underneath the victim's body?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... I'm pretty sure it was a wallet...</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">This is a court of law! You can't just make wild guesses!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Agreed.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">They're right, Mr. Wright! You have to check the Court Record before you answer! If you don't, your client might end up with a guilty verdict!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Your client"? You do realize that's you, right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I will ask you one more time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If he's a cop, then I guess maybe a badge or something...</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Mr. Wright! Please stick to the facts of this case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He is a policeman, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I don't think you understand the problem here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I will not have an uninformed lawyer in my court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. <thought>Guess there's no fooling those two.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Please, for my sake, look at the Court Record, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh, it's the Court Record Button, right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I will ask you one more time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's simple, Your Honor. A broken pair of glasses.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The victim grabbed the criminal's glasses as he was being shoved, sir, and held onto them as he fell.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Hey! Why are you giving me the evil eye!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Those glasses you're wearing...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Nnnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yes, this is my spare pair. But these glasses they found at the scene of the crime are not mine! I swear, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Look, it was a coincidence that on that same day, I accidentally stepped on mine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A "coincidence" she says... Urk...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Eh hee hee hee hee hee hee! Your Honor. I have further evidence to present.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh? You have more?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">And this evidence is very decisive.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well! Let's hear from our witness about this "evidence".</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's something even more incriminating than the glasses under the victim's body, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">This is a picture of the writing, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, this is...! Yes, I can see the name is clearly written here.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The prosecution would like to submit this picture.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Understood. The court accepts it into evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As if the glasses alone didn't make you look suspicious, the victim even wrote your name clear as day on the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">But, but, but, I already told you! Those glasses aren't mine!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And how do you explain his dying message?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">... It's a conspiracy! I'm not guilty, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, you may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Cross-examine?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">This is it! I'm counting on you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure... But what am I supposed to do?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">WHAT!? This isn't like you at all! Normally, this is the part where you get in the witnesses' faces!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Get in their faces and do what?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I guess there's no way around it! OK, I'm going to lend you a hand! The prosecution's witnesses all hide things from the court, which means they lie from time to time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lie? But... isn't that detective your superior?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Well, even if they don't mean to lie, sometimes people just remember things wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, like that detective. He does sort of look like a scatterbrain...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">It doesn't matter! Either way, it's bad for us, sir! That's why when you question witnesses, you have to find and expose their lies!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Your cross-examination, please.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor. <thought>Talk about trial by fire. Here goes nothing. As long as I can "expose the lies", we should be alright.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's something even more incriminating than the glasses under the victim's body, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, about those glasses... Do you have any proof that those belong to my client?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The lenses are for near-sightedness, and are almost the same strength as hers. Even the frames look kinda like the ones she's wearing in her ID, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... <thought>What should I do now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Almost" and "kinda" are not good enough in a case like this!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Er, um...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you have more definitive proof? Is there something that clearly links the defendant with those glasses!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Er, um, uh... The dirt and sand rubbed out any traces of fingerprints or anything else.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what you are saying, detective, is that you have nothing that proves those glasses are my client's.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, something like that...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... Hmm... So there is no proof...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Wow, that was amazing! I could totally feel it, down in my gut!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We're in real trouble if those glasses really are hers... It's probably better to back out while we can.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Argh... Why don't you believe me...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">During his date, the victim was pushed from the bench area.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, you're sure he was pushed and that's how he fell?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, pal. If you look at the wounds on the victim's body, there's no way it was anything else.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please continue with your testimony, detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Anyway, the victim fell pretty far...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But he managed to write the culprit's name on the ground where he landed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The culprit's name?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. I was surprised, too. I didn't want to believe it, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was the name that of my client?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't like saying it, but it was clearly the defendant's name, "Maggie", sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you absolutely certain!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry, pal, but that's what it said. This is a picture of it. No matter which way you look, it still says "Maggie".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... He's got a point...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Hey, hold on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Don't "huh" me! I know the picture says "Maggie", but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that she mentions it, something does feel kind of off about this picture...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">That's how you know you found a contradiction! Now hurry up and present some evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So THAT'S what spotting a contradiction feels like... I'd better check the Court Record again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">With this piece of evidence and the glasses, it's hard to say she's not the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And you are certain that it was the victim who wrote the name on the ground?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There were scratches on his fingers from the rough sand, and there were grains of sand stuck under his pointer finger nail.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It certainly seems that the name was written by the victim himself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That didn't go well. If it really was him, then we're in a lot of trouble...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Don't give up! Keep that fighting spirit going!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm glad you're all pumped up, but...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I really want to see your "special move", sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My what??</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">You always look so cool when you present evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Present... evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yes! The great Phoenix Wright is back! Oh, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I heard that lately, you can present not only evidence, but people's profiles as well!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">It sure makes things a bit more complicated, so be careful, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>People's profiles, huh? Alright, let's give this another try.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, about this "presenting evidence"...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">OK. When you're listening to testimony, you can compare, it with the Court Record. If you do that, you're sure to find contradictions in the witness's statements!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">C-Contradictions?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Well, there are many reasons why a testimony might contradict the evidence. The witness might be lying, or maybe they're just mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh huh. And?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">You still have no idea what I'm talking about?? When you find a contradiction, open the Court Record to the item you need...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And then I present that evidence, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">You got it! You can also present people's profiles as evidence! With so many items, make sure you present the right thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Sounds complicated, but I'll give it a try. You're pretty good at this.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Wow, being praised by a pro! I don't know what to say!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... ... ...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>What... What's come over me...? Without thinking, I just blurted out, "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>"... And I yelled it at the top of my lungs, finger outstretched, ready to take on my opponent! What a rush!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-You talking to me, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please state the defendant's name for me!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">What are you trying to prove with this futile exercise, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You'll see. This is a very crucial line of questioning! Actually, Mr. Payne, you can answer. The defendant's name, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-Where is this ridiculous question coming from? The defendant's, uh, name is, uh... "Maggie Byrde".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think someone needs to check the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">What...? It says right here that it's "Maggey Byrde". Aaaah!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like the bird caught the cat napping!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's going on here!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I have no idea either, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As you can see, the victim did indeed leave a name, "Maggie". However, the defendant's name is actually spelled, "Maggey"! This is a blatant contradiction of facts!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ohh!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">How about that? I hadn't even noticed!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">But, but, but...! But maybe the victim didn't know how to spell her name correctly...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">May I remind you that it was you who said, "The defendant is accused of killing her lover." If they were truly lovers, it would be impossible for him to have not known her name!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Noooo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is very true. Mr. Payne.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Y-Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you absolutely certain that the defendant and the victim, Dustin Prince, were, in fact, lovers?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Y-Yes, I am quite certain, Your Honor. They were a well-known couple in the police force.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Detective Gumshoe. Please testify for the court the relationship between the victim and the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Officer Prince and Officer Byrde had been going out for half a year.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh... Those two sound like they were close...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Nevertheless, tragedy struck.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, yes, I see... You may cross-examine the witness, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Officer Prince and Officer Byrde had been going out for about half a year.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How do you know about this?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Every year in March, we have a training camp for us cops. Officer Byrde was a rookie at the time, and she and Officer Prince seemed to hit it off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>They got close, I take it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Actually, I was supposed to go, too, but... I couldn't pay the deposit for the trip, so I didn't. If only I had gone on that trip...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, uh, nothing, sir! Really! Anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It sounded like they were even talking about marriage.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Marriage? But wasn't the victim 8 years older than her?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What!? You saying a guy's gotta marry someone the same age as himself, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, that's not what I meant at all...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Detective Gumshoe and Dustin were only a year apart, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... I think this fella has a ways to go before marriage...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mind your own business, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The day of the incident just happened to be the victim's birthday, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The day of the incident... You mean September 6th?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. The victim, Officer Prince, had just gotten off duty at 5:30 PM that day, and since Maggey's night shift hadn't started yet, they went to the park for a bit...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, I remember when I was young and in love. Oh, it was a jolly time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's great, Your Honor... I'm glad you're such a cheerful old man...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Maggey... I mean, Officer Byrde, had gotten Officer Prince a present.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... You seem to know a lot about the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, that's because, uh, I'm her boss. And I've gotta watch out for my subordinates!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But even what she was going to give as a present? Isn't that going a bit too far...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal! Watch what you say! I know everything that happens under me! If someone so much as scratches their...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I REALLY don't need to know that much...</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Mr. Wright! Please refrain from badgering the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I agree. Even if this witness has a crush on the defendant, that should not be the point of discussion at this time.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whoa! Wait a second! Why are we talking about this!? It's all YOUR fault, pal! You're guilty, guilty, guilty! I should have you arrested!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think the good Detective is about done here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It was something she had gotten over 2 months ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Over 2 months ago?"</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup. She's a very considerate woman, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... What was this birthday present?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She got him a glove.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A single glove? Why would she only give him one?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Um, actually, Your Honor, the glove in question is a baseball glove.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, I see. A baseball glove.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Officer Prince was a huge baseball fan.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A baseball glove. Hmm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just now, I believe you said that the present was something she had "gotten over 2 months ago".</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you saying she went out and bought the glove over 2 months ago?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nah, nothing like that, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then, what is it like?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She ordered it. It was custom-made!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Custom-made? The glove was custom-made?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup, that's what I said!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So the glove was custom-made.</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Honor, I really don't see how this glove is related to this case.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, it would seem that there is little relevance. What do you think, Mr. Wright? Do you think this glove is really relevant to this case?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, I suppose it isn't really relevant.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-Then...  Then why were you wasting this court's time with irrelevant questions!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, I was curious and got, uh, carried away, Your Honor...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, please ignore this airheaded lawyer and continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Detective Gumshoe, please tell the court why you knew about the baseball glove.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, it's just a birthday present...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">If there are no further questions, Your Honor... </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Witness, why do you know about this glove?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I should know, 'cause she came to me to ask what she should get for him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You discussed what the defendant was going to give to her boyfriend?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I'm, er... *ahem* She, uh... trusts me, so...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Boy does he look proud of himself right now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Wh-What is it this time?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That testimony didn't sound like it had any contradictions in it to me. There just wasn't anything that really stuck out as odd.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yeah... I wonder what would happen if you tried to get more information from him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Get more information?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yeah! You know! Like how they "press" people on those old cop shows, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So I should try "pressing" him, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't know where this will lead me, but...</thought> Of course it is relevant! That glove is the key to this whole case!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yes! Bluffing to the max! Now, THIS is the Mr. Wright I know! I'm so happy you're back, sir! I was wondering how long it'd take! This is great!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, pressing people... It feels like I've done this before. As if I used to do this to squeeze information from even the most tight-lipped people.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. If you are that convinced, then let's hear some more about this matter.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Actually, I brought the glove with me today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why didn't you say so earlier? Hurry and show the glove to this court!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I didn't think it had anything to do with this case... Anyway, this is it, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's, uh... rather yellow, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Officer Prince really liked the color yellow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's why you had to special order it?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yup, that's right! That, and one other reason...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think this court has heard enough. It is clear that the victim and the defendant were involved with each other.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes, that's correct, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, if that is true, it brings up an important question. Was the name "Maggie" really written by the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I see your point, Your Honor. Detective Gumshoe, please tell the court a little more about the name on the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We first looked into the handwriting, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes, a perfectly logical conclusion. Now then, Mr. Wright, you may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We first looked into the handwriting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But can you really determine handwriting based on a sample written in sand? </line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Heh, this is why amateurs are amateurs. We're not a buncha simpletons, pal! Scientific investigation in this country's actually pretty good. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, I believe it's time to get back to the real point. </line>
<line speaker="Payne">Agreed, Your Honor. So, what was the result of the investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Unfortunately, we couldn't confirm that it was the victim's handwriting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So in the end, you couldn't confirm it? </line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, don't you look down on us! I told you! We're not a bunch of simpletons, pal! Everyone knows you can't find out everything you want with scientific investigation! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">I've never heard that before. </line>
<line speaker="Payne">Me, either. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nor I. </line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I never heard anything like that at the police academy, sir... </line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OK, so I made it up. Anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Next, we checked the victim's pointer finger.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His pointer finger? </line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You know, the one you're always POINTING and waving around in people's faces. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aha, ha, ha. Don't tell me it bothers you... </line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Every time you do it, I have a mini-heart attack. It's like you're trying to kill me, pal. </line>
<line speaker="Payne">In any case, you examined the victim's index finger, correct? </line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. We figured there should be something on his finger if he had been writing in sand. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... And the results?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We found that there was sand trapped under the victim's fingernail.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what does that prove?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, it proves that he did write that name with his own finger.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes, which explains why there was sand stuck under his nail.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess he's right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And there's more...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There were also scratches on the skin that were caused by him writing on the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Scratches on his skin?"</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup. You can't see them with your naked eye, but they're there. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is incredible! </line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure is! That's the power of scientific investigation! They're so small that we had to use a magnifying glass... like a really strong one. It's got that really scientific-sounding name... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean a microscope? </line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, that's it! We used one of those and that's how we found them! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't believe this guy doesn't know what a microscope is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">From this, we could confirm that the victim wrote this name with his right hand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you absolutely sure?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I believe in the power of science.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, I wonder if my evidence is solid enough to counter with?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Listening to this, you would think there was only one conclusion... that the name was definitely written by the victim...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">But don't you think that would be really strange, sir!? If Dustin really wrote that message with his right hand, do you think I would have gone through that much trouble to get him his present?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The present...? What about it...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe. Take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's the glove, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell the court what is special about this glove?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What's special? Um, never really thought about it, but uh... It's REALLY yellow... ... And that's about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, it's REALLY yellow, but that is only one of its qualities.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's another reason why it's special.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's very simple.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This glove is made for a left-handed person!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Left-handed...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, you're absolutely right! This glove is made to be worn on the right hand!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That is why it had to be custom-made. I have never seen a bright yellow left-hander's glove for sale. Have you?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, um... no.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, Detective. Which hand did the victim use to write the name with, again...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's easy! Look, it's obvious from this picture that it was his... W-W-Wait a sec...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't forget that the victim was left-handed!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aaaaah!!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">This is... This is... I mean... I... Objec--</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Overruled. Mr. Wright, I would like to know what your line of reasoning proves.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is only one conclusion that can be drawn! A left-handed person could not have written a message with his right hand! Therefore! The person who wrote the name "Maggie" could not have been the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! When you think about it that way, then yes, it is not possible that this name was written by the victim himself.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Then that means Maggey is...!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">No... IT'S NOT POSSIBLE!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Payne.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Y-Y-Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The evidence the prosecution has presented has failed to prove the defendant's guilt. In fact, I believe you have proven her to be innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">NOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Alright! You did it, Mr. Wright! Whew! I feel like I can breathe again!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems that we have reached the conclusion. You did a fine job once again, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me, Your Honor? Ah, well, thank you, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">See, you got complimented by the judge again! You're really good! And that's why you can't give up being a lawyer, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Are you joking!? I'm more than ready to retire!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I will now announce my verdict. This court finds the defendant, Maggey Byrde...</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">No!! Not yet! I mean, please give me a few more minutes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What is the meaning of this, Mr. Payne!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The prosecution is not finished yet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">We would like to call our next witness to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what did this witness... witness?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The moment the victim was pushed to his death! What's more, he saw the very face of the culprit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What the heck!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court! I believe a recess is in order. Afterward, we will hear from this new witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I had a feeling that was a bit too easy... Hmm, I need more information. I'll have to see what I can find out during this recess. I can't let my guard down! It's only going to get tougher from here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is adjourned for recess!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">A-Amnesia!? I can't believe my lawyer's trying to defend me in such a state...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I... Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Why didn't you tell me, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry I didn't mention it to you.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Oh! I know what to do! I heard you can fix something like this with a really strong shock to your system! Come on, lower your head a little! A Maggey Kick should be all you need!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, no, no, no. I think I'll pass on this one.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Come on!... Ah, I'm sorry. Whenever I see someone in trouble, I have a hard time leaving them alone... I tend to stick my nose where it doesn't belong and try to tackle everyone's problems.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, my head's one problem you won't be tackling today...</thought> Well, we're here to solve your problem first. We can deal with mine later. For now, do you think you can fill me in on a few things?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Of course! I'd be honored to! Ah, well, I guess we'll start with my name and then I can tell you about me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, that's ok. Really. I think I know you and your name pretty well by now. I was wondering if you could help me figure out a few things about myself. So, my name is "Phoenix Wright"? What a weird name.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Hmmmm... This is serious. You really don't remember. I'll tell you what, sir. You can have this back, and maybe it'll help!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...? This is... a business card?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I got this from you. It's my most prized possession! You can borrow it for now, but please give it back, OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK. <thought>There are some numbers written on the back...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Oh, that's your cell phone number!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess for now, we should stop talking about me, and start talking about this case.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">This case...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup. Can you think of anything that would be helpful for me to know?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Um, what can I tell you...? Ah, um... Hmm... I can't think of anything other than the incident with that cell phone, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Cell phone?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yeah! Your eyes lit up when we talked about it at the Detention Center, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hurry up then and tell me! This might be very important!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">OK! Roger!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">It was on the day of the crime, just before 6 PM... I picked up a lost cell phone while on a walk with Dustin.</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...............</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">All of a sudden, the phone began to ring...</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">"Um, hello?"</line>
<line speaker="???">"Oh, thank you! I've been searching for my phone."</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">"Is this yours? Oh, I'm glad you called! We can meet up and I can give this back!"</line>
<line speaker="???">"I'll be right there, um... I'm sorry, I didn't catch your name..."</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">"You can call me Maggey!"</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">We agreed to meet up at 6 PM. Dustin and I waited for the person to show up... but they never did.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmmmm... So where is the phone you found now?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I gave it to you yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? To me? <thought>Is it that phone in my pocket...?</thought> Y-You mean this?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Do you think it has anything to do with the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... don't really know... But if my eyes "lit up"...</line>
<line speaker="???">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHH!! YOU WERE HERE ALL ALONG!! You're so mean!! I called you a million times but you wouldn't pick up! And when I went to check in the courtroom, everyone had already left...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ack! Now who in the heck is this? Let me guess. I'm supposed to know this girl too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Hey, good morning, Maggey!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">And a good morning to you, too, Maya! </line>
<line speaker="Maya">So!? So!? How's it going!?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Is there a word for "worse than abysmal"...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh? And what if I said that everything will be fine? That's right! It's Maya to the rescue with the ultra-decisive super-important evidence! Here you are, Nick! The thing you wanted me to bring!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Oh, ah, thanks... <thought>What the heck is this? A list? It has about 20 people's names and phone numbers written on it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It was kind of tough, but I managed to find out some dirt! It looks like these guys are up to no good.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"No good"? As in?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's a group of con artists the police are currently investigating. I think these guys are members of that group.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why would a group of con artists pop up in a case like this?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't look at me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... And where did you get this list from in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaaaat!? Why are you asking that!? You're the one who asked me to look this up yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">These numbers were in the memory of that phone Maggey found.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, so that's where they're from.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're awfully forgetful these days, Nick. I hope I never get to be a forgetful old prune like you!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Um, Maya... Actually, Mr. Wright is...</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Mr. Wright! Recess is now over. Please bring the defendant and return to the courtroom immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, oops! Guess you have to get going! We can talk about you being old later, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">W-Wish us luck!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I have all the pieces now... More or less. All that's left is to put it all together. I'm not going to lose this. I can't!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, Nick. Better get a move on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will now reconvene. Please call your next witness to the stand, Mr. Payne.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes, Your Honor. But before I do, if I may say a few words...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, Mr. Payne? </line>
<line speaker="Payne">It's about the next witness. He has a tendency to say things that rub people the wrong way, you see, so I ask that the court might be a little lenient on...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There is no need to give a preface. Just hurry up and call your witness, please.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Y-Yes, Your Honor. ...The prosecution calls its next witness; a drifter who was taking a walk in the park on the day of the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Please state your name for the court, witness. </line>
<line speaker="???">Before I do, I'd like to clarify a little something.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Huh? Oh, alright, go ahead.</line>
<line speaker="???">Just now, you introduced my wonderful self to the court, correct? Perhaps as a "drifter who was taking a walk"? </line>
<line speaker="Payne">D-Did I?</line>
<line speaker="???">But I will not stand for that! Now you've tinted the court's eyes and colored me wrongly. Sure, I suppose calling me a university student would not be the absolute truth, but to give in and just settle would be as evil as death and I can't have that! Everything in my life is to be of the utmost, highest, top grade quality, you understand. I am merely looking for that perfect, top notch, unbeatable university, don't you see...? I have a rigorous selection process and I was in serious thought during my "walk" as...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes, yes, I understand. I'm very sorry. I will be more careful from now on.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-What is he? A human chatterbox?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh... I have to question HIM?</line>
<line speaker="???">Fashion! Cars! Women! Glasses! And of course, University! First-rates only need apply!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Glasses...? But you aren't wearing glasses...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! Your name, witness.</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh? Is that how you want to play this? Using your power and influence to keep the young people down. I see how you work now. You old people and your dirty tricks. You thought you had me, but you thought wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I'm sorry. It won't happen again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh man...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wellington">I forgive you. Alright, I suppose I can tell you my name. I am Richard Wellington, the "Drifting Virtuoso" with a Ph.D. in Drifting, as it were. If you wanted to, you could call me a "University Student in Transit".</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ahem, Mr. Wellington. On the day of the murder, you were taking a... er, strolling through the park, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">It would appear that you are attached to that word. If you must, then by all means. But I remind you that I am in no way a prepubescent boy, "out on a walk" with mommy. If you must know, I am--</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Anyway! Please testify to this court what you saw during your walk through the park!</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">See, you said it again! "Taking a walk"... You know, you--</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What you witnessed will do, Mr. Wellington!</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">I was at the park all afternoon, deep in thought about my life situation.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, that was certainly a decisive testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Decisive!? Nick, did you hear what he just said!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's all you have to say? How can you be so calm!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's strange... My mind is very calm and clear.</thought> Maybe it's because I... believe in my client.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You mean Maggey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. And if she really is innocent, then that can only mean one thing: That guy is lying!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You may now question the witness, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll find out the truth, no matter how well you craft your lies!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wellington">I was at the park all afternoon, deep in thought about my life situation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you were at the park all afternoon? You seem to have a lot of free time. </line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Hmph. That was very rude of you. But then again, what can I expect? That's what you get from a man who graduated from a no-name, trashy university. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No name? Trashy...? </line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Now, this might be hard for a mush-headed, feeble-minded baboon like you, but I have to think very carefully about the future of our great country. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I thought you said you were thinking about which college to go to just now... </line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Oh, puh-leaze. Which university I go to will directly affect the very future of this country! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That arrogant little snot...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wellington">I don't remember the time all that well, but I do believe it was past 6 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How did you know what time it was? I see you're not wearing a watch, so... </line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Is that the best you can do? Do you think you can discredit me like that? You're just a third-rate, biased fool. I guess I can't expect real smarts from you. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grr... His arrogance is really intolerable... So, what should I do now...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Answer the question! How did you know what time it was!?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Tsk, tsk. I can't believe I have to deal with a worm like you. You're just a shallow man who can only slam on desks and point at people for fun. Hmph, I guess I don't have a choice. I'll try to explain it so that even a third-rate simpleton like you can understand. There was this little thing they call a "clock" at the park. Did you get that? Do you know what a clock is? It's a thing that tells you the time.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">As you can see, Mr. Wright, it's even in this picture of the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh... So it is... Urk.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wellington">I looked at that clock, and that's how I knew the time. But if you ask me, this whole concept of breaking time apart into fragments... It's total and utter nonsense that no man should follow. A real first-class person doesn't live by, nor is he chained by, time. And to wear a watch? Hah! What a ridiculous notion! People should live freely without constraints. That's how life should be!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And yet again, another flood of meaningless words... Talk about a first-class waste of time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wellington">In any case...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I guess there's no point in pressing him further. After all, there was a clock right there at the crime scene...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wellington">All of a sudden, a police officer falls from above, right in front of my eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And how did you know he was a police officer?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">You obviously have no idea how powerful my deductive reasoning skills are. With one glance, I could tell just what kind of occupation he held. That shoddy, do-it-yourself hairstyle practically screamed "I'm a police officer". It was also the way he tied his tie and those cheap, low-quality shoes. Ugh. Oh, and I suppose it was also because he was wearing an officer's uniform.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Shouldn't that statement have come first!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, that's pretty impressive. Hey, Nick! Do you think he's figured out what I do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even I haven't figured that out yet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Without a thought, I looked up, and there I met the eyes of a charming, young lady.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure you got a good look at her face?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Animals have this thing called an "eye", Mr. Wright. They use this "eye" to see things. In the case of humans, we have two of them. Yes, even you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't care if I have them or not! Did you or did you not get a clear look at her face!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">That's what the witness was just about to get to. I would like to request that Mr. Wright not use such a loud voice during questioning.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Sustained. Mr. Wright, please refrain from raising your voice in this court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Then please don't make me have to raise my voice.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Are you finished? I'd like to continue, if that's alright with you.</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Of course I remember her sweet face. It was that of the pretty defendant there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you're SURE you are not mistaken?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Please. Don't confuse your pitiful, train-wreck of a life with mine. I'm what you call a famous brand-name product, while you are only a cheap imitation. There is no way someone as magnificent as myself could have made a mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Of course, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh ho ho ho. Of course.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Did you notice anything else of interest, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">The only other thing I saw was the banana that fell with the police officer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The banana...?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Well, it was actually more than just one. More like a bunch of bananas.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now what would a bunch of bananas be doing there...?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">And why would I know such a thing? I'm only telling you what I saw.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's really strange. Maggey never mentioned anything about a bunch of bananas. That's it, Nick! He's gotta be lying about the bananas!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... He could be, but... there's no reason for him to lie about there being bananas at the crime scene.</thought> And what if it's not a lie?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, maybe he thought he was seeing one thing, and it was something else...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If he mistook something else for a bunch of bananas, then that would be an inaccuracy. Think Phoenix, think!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If my client is innocent, there is no way he could've seen what he says he did.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Which means if we can somehow show he's lying...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, that's exactly what we need do. <thought>She's right. She's got a sharp mind, but I just wish I could remember who she is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is everything OK, Nick...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Wellington. I believe I have the bananas you saw... right here!</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Ah, so you knew about the bananas, too. Why didn't you say so earlier? But don't think you can use this as a way to pull more information out of me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And that's where you'd be wrong.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Wright. What is the meaning of this?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Isn't that the baseball glove?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Huh!? Wh-Wh-What!? A baseball glove??</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Doesn't it look delicious? Care for a bite?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Th-That's... That's not... It's a... Noooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! I think this proves one very important fact! This witness...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Wellington loves large bananas!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">... </line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh, Nick... I hope you've noticed the icy glares we're getting from everyone in here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What in the world do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">I'll have you know I like strawberries much better than bananas.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoops...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Think it over one more time and try again, Mr. Wright. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Wellington has never played baseball! That would explain why he didn't even know what a glove is!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh, Nick... I hope you've noticed the icy glares we're getting from everyone in here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What in the world do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">When I was in junior high, I was a star pitcher... Well, 4th in line, actually, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoops...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Think it over one more time and try again, Mr. Wright. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By the way, just how bad are your eyes?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Huh? How... What... You... Why are you asking me about this all of a sudden!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Honor, it is very simple to mistake a glove for a bunch of bananas...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, I don't think so. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Y-Y-You... You're one of those people. Yes, you know what I mean. You're like those people who refused to accept Galileo for his Copernican Theory! You're too used to your world view to realize that there are other, new possibilities! Sure, in the end, we find out that it is in fact, a glove, not bananas. However... when viewed from afar, I do think there is room enough for doubt, don't you...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that is why I asked you how bad your eyesight is!</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">They're both 20/200. I suppose you're going to tell me that's terrible, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why are you not wearing your glasses today then?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">... Ummm... That's because I lost them recently, you see... Of course, I was planning on getting a new pair made right away! But you know, my glasses are no ordinary glasses, so to replace them--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How about when you witnessed the crime? Were you wearing your glasses then?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How about it, witness!?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Y-You are an unrelenting, evil man. You're like those people who rejected Joan of Arc and put her to death! She was brave and courageous, only to be caught by horrible, unrighteous people. And while she didn't do anything wrong, she was still gruesomely burned at the--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which boils down to you were not wearing your glasses at that time! Therefore! The identity of the "woman" at the scene of the crime and that of the defendant can not be proven to be the same by this witness!</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">...!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">But the height difference was only 9 feet! It was very possible for him to see the face of the culprit standing on the upper path!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Witness. Please be more accurate in your testimony. Remember, a person's life is at stake.</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Y-Yes, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Please tell the court what happened next, in the moments after you witnessed the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">The girl on the upper path ran away as soon as she realized I was there.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So the person who was on the upper path saw you and then ran away.</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Yes, that is correct. Which is why, even someone without a superior brain like mine can understand that... that girl is the murderer!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You may question the witness now, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">The girl on the upper path ran away as soon as she realized I was there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She ran away, just like that?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Yes, she did. She saw me and flew the nest like the guilty bird she is. Oh, I'm sorry. Was that pun too hard for someone who only got a third-rate education?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Actually, that did take me a few seconds to get...</thought> Anyway, if she ran away the instant she saw you, how could you tell it was my client?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">The witness has already answered that question. He has stated that the defendant is the culprit!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is true. Mr. Wright, I'm striking your question from the record.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, how can I get more information out of him?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wellington">After that, I immediately called the police station to report the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Immediately? As in?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">As in immediately! I mean, sure, a minute might have elapsed before I did, but... That's the duty of every good citizen, or did they not teach that at your pitiful school?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You think people learn about how to call the police in COLLEGE!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick. I think you should take a look at the Court Record for a sec.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Wellington">It must've been 6:45 PM when I made the call.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How do you know what time it was...?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">That detective told me. You know which one I mean. The one with the jacket that makes him look like a dropout from a no-name high school.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal! I graduated from a pretty good, I mean, top-ranked college!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't believe this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wellington">It doesn't matter. I don't believe I was mistaken on what time I called. And if I am wrong, then that detective obviously doesn't know how to tell time.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What!? Why you!!! You're just some lousy kid who...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I think the court can see your point. Anyway, how did the police respond?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Wellington">They must have a lot of free time on their hands since they showed up within 10 minutes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you're saying that there were police on the scene by 7:00 PM?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">They got there before that, I think. There usually aren't many people in that area at that time of day. But suddenly, before I knew it, there were people crawling all over gawking. It certainly says something about the morals of the people in this country.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't find anything out of the ordinary in his testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why don't you take one more look at the Court Record?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I guess I should.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Wellington, would you please take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You mean the victim's autopsy report?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to this, the murder occurred at 6:28 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">So what of it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You said that you called the police immediately after the murder took place. However, by the time you had called the police, it was already 6:45 PM. There is clearly a 15 minute gap here! Do you deny it!?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Aaaack!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think this court would like to hear what you were doing during this 15 minute gap!</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Grrrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">The witness was in shock at the time after witnessing a terrible murder! It's only to be expected that he would be a little dazed...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Fifteen minutes is hardly what I would call "a little dazed"!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Aaaaah! </line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Explain yourself. What were you doing during those 15 minutes?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Answer the question!</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">... I... Uhh... Telephone... Err... I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Spit it out! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A phone booth?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You mean, you don't have a cell phone?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">...! You and your questions! As if you're trying to open all the layers of a Matryoshka doll. You must think you're really something special!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Witness!</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">I-I lost my cell phone! There! Are you happy!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You lost it...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Unbelievable! You lose your glasses, and your cell phone! You must be very scatterbrained when it comes to your belongings.</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">What!? Are you saying that first-rate people are never allowed to lose things!? Haven't you ever heard that all geniuses have a strange quirk or two? So by that rationale, since I have my own quirk, it would mean that I am a genius I don't think simple, plain people like you can underst--</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Enough!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh man, oh man... Wait! Hold on a second. He lost... his cell phone?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! That cell phone! Could it be...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean this phone Maggey found? There's no way...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Boy, I didn't see this coming. What should I do now...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's probably just a coincidence. I mean, what are the chances that this phone is that snob's anyway?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick!? What do you think you're doing!? You really should check out this lead!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is there a problem, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, Your Honor. <thought>I should give this some more thought...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Wellington! Where is your cell phone right now?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Heh, what are you getting all excited about? You seem to be a little confused. I found my phone, I'll have you know. See. Here is it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... I see... </line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm, looks like he's got his phone. And I thought that just maybe this was his.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, I think we've cleared this issue up. At the time of the murder, the witness did not have his cell phone because he had lost it. Therefore, the delay in his call was caused by his search for a phone booth.</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Well, that's the gist of it. I guess you could put it that way and leave it at that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you have any further questions, Mr. Wright? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... No, I think I'm done here, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait, wait, wait! What is with you today, Nick!? Take a good look at the Court Record!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What are you talking...? ... Ah... Aaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, Mr. Wright? By your screaming, I assume you have a question after all?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! The witness' testimony does not make sense! I don't believe that there was ever a need for the witness to search for a phone!</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">H-How dare you!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">You can't just make outrageous claims like that! You do have some sort of proof, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, yeah... O-Of course! <thought>This evidence should be good enough, I think...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Alright. Let's have this proof, then. Please present proof that the witness had no need to search for a public phone booth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's very simple! This is the evidence that backs up my claim!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And yet again you have presented this court with an obscure, meaningless item.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? This evidence? It's meaningless?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't get it at all! Why do you think he wouldn't need to look for a phone in the first place!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, that's... because... I was looking at the evidence and it just hit me. I thought, "Hey, he really didn't have to look for a phone."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then why don't you hurry up and present that piece of evidence!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, now what was that piece of evidence again...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's quite simple, actually. Please take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">At the crime scene photo?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Is there a problem with it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, there's nothing wrong with the picture. But if you don't understand my logic after looking at it, something is wrong with you!</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Noooo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's... It's... A phone booth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That is correct! All the defendant had to do was walk three steps! Mr. Wellington! Why did you not use the phone that was right in front of you!?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Ooooooougn!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-What does reporting the crime a little late prove for you!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness can't explain what he was doing for those 15 minutes! That is reason enough to throw suspicion on his testimony! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, this is very true. What do you have to say for yourself, witness!? </line>
<line speaker="Wellington">... </line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then I bet this phone really is his, Nick! He must've killed Dustin to get his phone back! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But Maggey said that she was going to return it to him. So there was no reason for him to kill for it. And on top of that, we still have the phone she found anyway. </line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... But if he wasn't looking for his cell phone, was he looking for something else...? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Was he...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor? </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you have any thoughts you would like to share with the court? Can you offer an explanation as to what the witness was doing during those 15 minutes? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is only one possible explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm afraid it's too early to say anything for sure at this time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... Mr. Payne? Will we be hearing further testimony from the prosecution?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">No, Your Honor. That is all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh crud...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This witness has said that he saw the defendant commit the crime at the crime scene. While it is true that the witness was not wearing his glasses at the time, the court feels that since he was near the culprit, positive identification is possible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which means...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The guilt of the defendant, Maggey Byrde, has been sufficiently substantiated.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAAAAAAAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! You have to do something before it's too late!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hereby close the cross-exa</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait! As to the actions of Mr. Wellington during the 15 minute gap, the defense would like to propose an explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">I thought the defense had just finished proving that this couldn't be explained!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, there is one possibility! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Alright. Let's hear your explanation. However, be forewarned that if your explanation is not persuasive, you will be penalized. Think carefully before you present, Mr. Wright. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor! <thought>Urk. I probably shouldn't have said there was only one possibility...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please present to the court the one piece of evidence that will answer the following: "Why didn't the witness call the police right away?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Perhaps this is the evidence you need to be convinced!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aha ha ha. That was just an idea I thought I'd throw out.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suggest that "perhaps" you should find a better piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, of course, Your Honor! Well then...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But before you do, you will be penalized.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ouch.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Wellington! </line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Wh-What!? Don't do that! You almost made me have a heart attack! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These are your glasses, aren't they? </line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Ah! Where... Where did you find--!? Ghaaaa! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe the court all heard what you just confessed to: That these glasses are in fact yours! I'll tell you where they were found, Mr. Wellington. These glasses were found under the victim's body. </line>
<line speaker="Wellington">U-Under the v-victim's body!? </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! </line>
<line speaker="Wellington">N-Now, w-wait a second! Hold on! I-I didn't confess or confirm a-any-anything! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! I think the answer is quite clear here! As he fell, Dustin Prince grabbed the culprit's glasses. The culprit knew that he had to find his glasses, and searched frantically for them. What he didn't realize was that they were under the victim's body! And that is why it took him 15 minutes to make that call! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Wright! Are you...? Are you indicting the witness as the real murderer!? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course! That is precisely what I am doing! </line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Oooo...OOOOWAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I know I'm right!He is the real murderer!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Did you figure it out, Nick!? </line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So basically, you are saying that in order to make the defendant look guilty, the real criminal used the victim's right hand to write her name on the ground? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ah, I forgot! Hmm, was there any way this creep could've known Maggey's name beforehand?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No matter how I look at it, it's no good! There is no way he could have known Maggey or her name!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! You can't let this slimebag get away! Think harder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You're right... <thought>OK, let's go over this from the beginning one more time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It would be best if I could prove that the witness had a chance to learn... that the defendant's name was "Maggey".</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is how!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Am I supposed to take this as evidence that the defense doesn't know what's going on?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?... Oh... Ah ha ha ha.</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Aren't you a little old to be laughing like a 5-year old? Take some responsibility!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>As if I need a lecture about responsibility from you, of all people...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense will receive a penalty. Please think carefully before presenting your case again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phone">............... ...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">"Um, hello?"</line>
<line speaker="???">"Oh, thank you! I've been searching for my phone."</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">"Is this yours? Oh, I'm glad you called! We can meet up and I can give this back!"</line>
<line speaker="???">"I'll be right there, um... I'm sorry, I didn't catch your name..."</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">"You can call me Maggey!"</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">It's very simple, Your Honor. A person usually would not kill someone without a reason. Mr. Wellington had no reason to kill anyone!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Wellington's motive is right here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The cell phone?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In the memory of the phone the defendant found was a list of certain phone numbers! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Wellington's motive is right here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is this? ...A list?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These phone numbers were pulled from the memory of the phone the defendant found. And we have determined that the people on this list are members of a "certain group".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The murderer killed the victim because of this!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">The defense is obviously haphazardly throwing out evidence in desperation!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It certainly seems that way. Don't let all your hard work up to this point go to waste on a random guess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... What was I thinking...? </line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's investigating that group! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What in the world are you saying, Nick!? If he was just looking into the group, then he has no reason to kill anyone!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can not accept the defense's answer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, I should have seen that coming...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'll ask you again:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He was victimized by this group of con artists!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-Is that right!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And to take his revenge, he's looking for the names and numbers of the con artists...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hold on, Nick! What are you talking about!? If that's true, then he doesn't have a motive to kill Dustin Prince!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>I guess so...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it? You became quiet all of a sudden.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, I'm sorry, Your Honor. I'd like to try one more time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*sigh* Alright. One more time, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">"Um, hello?"</line>
<line speaker="???">"Oh, thank you! I've been searching for my phone."</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">"Is this yours? Oh, I'm glad you called! We can meet up and I can give this back!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness saw this!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wellington. I-Is he correct?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">By the expression on his face, I would say that wasn't it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looks like I was wrong...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wright, Wright, Wright. Try to think before you present again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So, he went to get his cell phone back, but when he got there, he lost control of himself. It was probably because he saw something that was really bad for him there... And that "really bad thing" was...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What Mr. Wellington saw was... the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">T-The... The victim!? You mean Dustin Prince!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Dustin Prince had gone on his date right after his shift was over. With no time to change, he went to the park still wearing his police uniform!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He couldn't have known they were going out so he began to worry. He was afraid the policeman would ask a few questions before returning the phone. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In his mind, it was possible they had already run a check on the phone!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And he went into a panic, is what you're saying?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. Officer Prince was murdered simply because he was in uniform!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Payne. Do you have any comments?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I, um... I'm thinking...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, it seems the truth has come out at last. The witness... Mr. Wellington, you are--</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Ha... Ah ha ha... AhahahahahahaaahahaahahaahahahahahaHahahaAhahahahahaHahahaHahhaahaAAAHAHAhhahahahahAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAWAHAHAHAHAHAWAHAHAHAHAWAHAAHAHAHWAHAHAHAHAAAAAA Ha ha ha ha... Impressive... Not bad for a person with a third-rate education...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's that supposed to mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">The evidence... Evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uuugh! That guy is really creeping me out--</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">All you've been waving around and talking about is that "suspicious" cell phone. Suspicious phone number this, suspicious con group that! They're all on that phone! But who's to say that phone is really mine!? Where's your proof!? Your evidence!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You want proof that this phone is yours?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Ahahahaha! Ahehehehehe! I already told you earlier! That phone I lost -- I've already found it! You don't have even the slightest idea who the phone in your hand belongs to! You can be sure it isn't mine, you simpleton!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Hehehehe... Heh... Hehehehe... It feels good to see you squirm.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... We do seem to have a problem on our hands with this phone. Whose phone is it? Without knowing that, it's meaningless as evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! <thought>This is bad... I can't let him turn the tables on me like this!! Hmm... This cell phone... There has to be something I've overlooked. There's got to be! Hmm... Maybe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This phone has the names and numbers of those in the con group in its memory. I can show them to you, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">I don't believe this. What are you talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... </line>
<line speaker="Wellington">What we are trying to determine is who that phone belongs to! Who cares about what phone numbers are stored on it!? Besides, who knows. Maybe you went and added some of those numbers in yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness is quite right. I'm afraid I have to reject the defense's proposal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grr... That jerk is back to his arrogant, annoying self again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I got it! We should check for fingerprints!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Finger...prints...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. Mr. Wellington must have left some prints on this phone! </line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Don't you remember!? When you got that from Maggey, you wiped it off!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I what!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You said there was sand all over it, so... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wiped it? I wiped it...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pretty thoroughly, too...</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">WahahaHahaHAHahaha! It's oh-so-much fun watching third-rate trash babble like morons amongst themselves!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Aaargh! He's made a complete recovery...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wellington">How many times do I have to say this: my phone is right here! You see? Oh, and incidentally, you can't check the numbers stored on this phone. It must have glitched because all the numbers just magically disappeared!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You've got to be joking! He erased all the numbers I was going to use as evidence!</thought> ... Mr. Wellington...</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">What's this? From the way you talk to me, it sounds like you still have some fight left in you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Where did you finally find your cell phone!?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">... ...Heh heh heh... Ah ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Oh, you are too much! And of course you have no idea what I'm talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...? ... I... I... Oh my g-- NOW I REMEMBER!!</line>
<line speaker="Phone">............ ...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh, looks like they hung up.</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, good. I finally found it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's when...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wellington">What's wrong, Mr. Attorney? Why the harsh glare in your eyes...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! We've worked so hard to get this far, but if you don't do something quick, he's going to get off scot-free!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know. <thought>I know this phone has to be his... But how am I supposed to prove something like that!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. If you cannot prove who the owner of that cell phone is, your indictment has no basis, and therefore, no power. It looks like you came up a penny short.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Where...? Where did I go wrong...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Don't blame yourself, you're merely a third-rate lawyer. You only made one big mistake. Who are you? What are you? That's something you haven't figured out for yourself yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who... I am?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court hereby concludes the cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Heh heh heh... If that will be all, I'll have to bid you gentlemen and ladies goodbye. I have a reservation at that ultra-fancy restaurant on the upper side of town.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Thank you for your assistance. You've had a stressful day, so please, bon appetite!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What am I supposed to do!? Am I supposed to just let it go at that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's no use. I can't do any more. There's nothing left. Nothing left but to go back to my hometown... But where in the world is that, anyway?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you mumbling about!? You're... Well, you're YOU, Nick! And because you're you, you can't give up now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"If I were me"...?</thought> Alright. If I were me, then what would I do?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's easy! For starters, you'd raise your voice and object!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So for now, I should at least say something!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please wait, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Alright, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think I may be able to prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Prove it...?" Prove what, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Everything!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Y-Your Honor! The cross-examination has already ended! If he questions the witness with any more of his badgering...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You will not harass the witness. Is that clear, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Did you hear that? No harassment allowed, Mr. Attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Very well. But this is your last chance, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You may present one piece of evidence to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I only get one shot at this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you cannot "prove" everything... It's over. For your client, and for you. Do you fully understand?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Hon-</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">I'm sure you are well aware, Your Honor, but the cross-examination period has ended!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Were you paying attention, Mr. Payne? I said that Mr. Wright could present only one more piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Wright. This is your last chance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It all comes down to this! It's Go time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please present the one piece of evidence that will explain everything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Is this your final answer? It's a bit disappointing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nonono! That was just a friendly gesture!</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Ha ha ha. You sure know how to send a friendly gesture to me, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is your absolute last chance, Mr. Wright. So no more of these "friendly gestures"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor... Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, thank you. How nice. Here, please have one of mine.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wait, what am I doing!? This isn't the time to be exchanging business cards!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor. There is something very important about that card. And that is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The name on that card tells people who I am! It even told ME that I'm "Phoenix Wright"!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Did you not know that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nope!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-Wh-What's the meaning of this nonsense!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Get a hold of yourself and start behaving like a proper lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ouch... Talk about a tongue-lashing, Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Urk. I should probably try this from a different angle...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This card is important because of what is on the back!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm? You wrote your cell phone number on the back, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that's exactly it. Can you please call this number from your cell phone?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Right now!? But court is still in session!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's OK. You'll see.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">OK, if you say so.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is the defense preparing something, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We are going to call my cell phone now. And then the court will see everything for what it is!</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">O-Of all the idiotic, stupid things to...</line>
<line speaker="Phone">................</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Aaagh! Wh-What!? Why is my phone...? And what is with this stupid-sounding ringtone!?</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Wellington.</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... How strange... I could almost swear that you're holding MY phone!</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Y-Your... AAAAAAAAAAAH! No, no, no, no, no! It can't...!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By the way, before I forget, thank you very much for the lump on my head this morning.</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">Nnnnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think I need to explain any further, except to say: When you went to retrieve your cell phone, you mistakenly took the wrong one!</line>
<line speaker="Wellington">...Mmgh... AaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAaaaaaaaagggggggghhhnn!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So that is what happened. You were knocked out by Mr. Wellington...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He is a man who lives on his pride and self-image alone. And in order to hide his involvement with the con artists' group, he has become paranoid, and has lost all ability to make rational judgments.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Then... Then, Mr. Wright... The phone you're holding...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Speaking of that man, how is he, Mr. Payne?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ah, he was arrested and has been taken away, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Now then, this court finds the defendant, Maggey Byrde...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is all. This court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I knew that the real you would shine through eventually! I am so moved by what you've done for me, sir! Thank you so much, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I feel really bad for Dustin. He didn't do anything to deserve this...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">... It's probably because of me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">My whole life has been nothing but a whirlwind of bad luck and failures.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Your whole life? It couldn't have been that bad, could it?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Since I was 6 months old, when I fell from the 9th floor of my apartment building, I've been hit by all sorts of vehicles, gotten sick from all sorts of foods, failed at almost every test I've ever taken, experienced almost every kind of disaster, and never won or even tied at a game of tic-tac-toe! My life has really been nothing but a string of disasters.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That is, uh... pretty bad...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Up until I went to college, I was known as the "Goddess of Misfortune". And then, at the academy, everyone called me "Lady Luckless".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Lady Luckless"...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">What's worse is that my misfortune always seems to latch onto those around me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">When I see someone in trouble, I always try to help...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, that's right. You were talking about this earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">It happened again recently, too, sir. There was an old lady pacing back and forth by the pedestrian crosswalk. I gave her my hand and... before I knew it, we were having dinner at my house.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I'm sure that Dustin's gone because of me...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's not true!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">That glove didn't even have any sort of special meaning. It was just a present to say thanks for covering one of my night shifts.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Everything is all my fault! Dustin's death, your head being all messed up...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, well, I don't think my head is that messed up yet...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I'm going to find a new life for myself starting now. The next time we meet, I'm sure I'll... I'm sure I'll have found a whole ocean's worth of good luck by then, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. After all, the "Goddess of Misfortune" is only a name!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">You bet! I'm gonna make it! I promise! Next time we meet, I'll only be an "Unlucky Person", instead of a goddess!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah! That's the spirit!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Well, Mr. Wright, Maya, I should get going.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">OK! Good luck to you!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Thanks! You take care of yourselves, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*sigh* What a horrible day... I've gotten my memory back, but things are still a little fuzzy...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But you're OK, and that's what counts. You really had me worried! Come on, let's go back to the office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I'm afraid to ask, but here goes...</thought> So, this might sound bad, but... uh... Who are you...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? I thought you said you got your memory back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>At that moment, everything really did come back to me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And this girl...</thought> ...Maya...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You... You finally remembered!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is Maya Fey, my assistant. That's right... I have so many unforgettable memories about her. For example...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Earth to Nick! What's wrong? You keep staring at me! Don't tell me you've missed me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, well, yeah I suppose I have. I feel like I haven't seen you in ages.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh? Well, I'm back now. So it's time for us to create new memories together!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright. Sounds good. <thought>All the phone numbers on my phone were erased by Mr. Wellington. I guess I have to start over from the very beginning...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, Nick! Let's go to our usual burger joint!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK, OK. <thought>Actually, it hasn't even been two months since she came back into my life.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't sound very sure, Mr. Wright. Objection denied.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection denied. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This evidence clearly reveals the contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are the evidence and the statement just now related?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They aren't, are they...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Wright, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness's statement is clearly faulty, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry, but I can see nothing faulty. Unfortunately, I will have to penalize you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh, I must be on the wrong track...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! This court sees no reason to further prolong the trial. Nor is there any need for more time to decide the case against the defendant. This case is extremely clear. I see no room for misinterpretation of the facts. This court finds the defendant, Maggey Byrde...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accused will surrender to the court immediately, to be held pending trial at a higher court within a month from today's date. That is all. This court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>