<xml>
<title>The Memoirs of the Clouded Kokoro</title>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What is it, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This bar of soap... When we first found it, I could have sworn... ...there was some sort of round disk in this depression just here. A reddish one.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, you're right. I remember it, too. But now the depression is completely empty.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Where could the disk have gone...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What is it, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This bar of soap... When we first found it, I could have sworn... ...there was some sort of round disk in this depression just here. A reddish one.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, you're right. I remember it, too. But now the depression is completely empty.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Where could the disk have gone...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The Old Bailey... This place always makes me feel strange. I seem to get chills down my spine and break out in a nervous sweat all at the same time...</thought> Well...I didn't think I'd be back here so soon.</line>
<line speaker="???">That's my line!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">GOOD MORNING!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Good morning, Mr Natsume.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">It was only two days ago that I was declared not guilty here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, we somehow managed to prove he didn't stab Miss Green in the back...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">BUT NOW THIS! ANOTHER MORNING, ANOTHER MURDER! AND HERE I AM AGAIN IN THIS HELLHOLE!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'm beginning to think he's right. It really does seem as though he's cursed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! I'm afraid I have bad news! .........Oh! Mr Natsume... Good morning.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">...Yes, morning.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So...here we are again!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">...Yes, again.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... JUDICIAL ASSISTANT MISS MIKOTOBA ESQUIRESS! WHAT'S THE BAD NEWS?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... You heard, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">If you come in shouting at the top of your voice...PEOPLE CAN'T HELP HEARING WHAT YOU SAY!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh... I am sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You've done nothing wrong, Miss Susato. Now, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Well...it seems that the prosecution in today's trial... ...will be led by Lord Barok van Zieks.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Van, van Zieks...?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">GAAAAARGH! Oh no... Oh no no...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The so-called 'Reaper of the Bailey'... The most legendary prosecutor in the land... In the trial two days ago, he pursued Soseki-san and I relentlessly. Of course, by the skin of our teeth, we managed to pull through, but still...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps Mr Natsume's acquittal in the last trial wasn't the end of the matter. After all...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I know what you're thinking. The legend of the Reaper that says... ...nothing can save a person in the dock when Lord van Zieks is the prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh no...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That even if that person is found not guilty...the accused will meet a mysterious end one way or another...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And we've experienced it firsthand. A man we successfully defended met the most terrifying end after his acquittal...right here in the Old Bailey...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">AGH! DO I HAVE TO PUT UP WITH THOSE ICE-COLD EYES BORING INTO MY SOUL AGAIN?! CURSED BY EVIL SPIRITS AND NOW BY THE REAPER!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, if it's 'potentially'...at least you appear to have hope, Mr Natsume.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Locum Student Mr Naruhodo Esquire!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! ...Yes?!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I'm...I'M INNOCENT! YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE ME! You, more than anyone now...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Don't worry. I'll be your steadfast ally every step of the way in this battle. ...I promise! <thought>...And this promises to be a hard battle, I fear...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well... ...the trial is scheduled to begin shortly. We should move into the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes, I forgot to say... I'm afraid he won't be able to make it. Mr Sholmes, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... That's probably for the best.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If he were here, I might be tempted to rely on his help. And that could be seen as a weakness. If Lord van Zieks were to notice, he'd prey on it mercilessly. At least, that's my gut feeling.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">You're right... Yes, you're so right. Oh, well said, Locum Student Mr Naruhodo Esquire! Well said!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I swear on this sword at my side, and on the spirit of Kazuma that it harbours... ...I'll show him what a Japanese lawyer can do! I'll set you free...with honour!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In the name of Her Majesty the Queen, I hereby declare this court to be in session. I now call upon the counsels for the prosecution and defence to declare their willingness to proceed.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The prosecution is ready.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The defence is ready, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Readiness for the trial, my learned Nipponese friend, is not what the defence needs. What you need...is readiness for your inevitable defeat.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>It's not just in my imagination; it's really there... Lord van Zieks has such an animosity towards us Japanese for some reason...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was some time ago now that he first became known as the Reaper of the Bailey, I believe. These past few years, he hasn't appeared in court at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yet now he's back in the courtroom. Though for some reason... ...only when I'm defending. <thought>This 'Reaper', with his curious disdain for us Japanese, is a prosecutor shrouded in mystery. Still...this isn't the time to be pondering that. I have to concentrate on Soseki-san's trial.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Furthermore, I now call upon the six ladies and gentlemen of the jury. You have been chosen at random to represent the will of the people in this trial. Are you ready to fulfil your duty?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Absolutely! I had a feeling this larrikin wasn't innocent before!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">I must say that I feel especially ruthless on days when my hat refuses to sit right!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Oh...well I rather like how you're wearing your hat. I think the ruthless look is very fetching, actually...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">I need to be somewhere at ten o'clock. I have a very important meeting. Let's make this quick.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">I couldn't agree more. I need to take home five bob tonight, or the missus will go through the roof!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Oh, may the Lord show us all the light here, and lead His flock to a righteous verdict...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The British jury system is so very different to our own, isn't it? It's quite extraordinary to think that the power of judgement is in the hands of six members of the public. And that the judge can only pass sentence when all jurors are in agreement about the defendant's guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Six citizens of London, chosen at random... Or at least, that's the idea.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The prosecution would draw attention to the fact that the accused was on trial here but two days ago. Accordingly, where possible, the same jurors have been asked to return for duty today.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, let us commence the trial. Lord van Zieks...your opening statement, please.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, it is not the intent of the prosecution to cast doubt over your past decision... However, the innocent verdict afforded to this eccentric Nipponese before...has had dire consequences. Did the accused repent for his wrongdoing in that affair? Far from it. Instead, he used his freedom to perpetrate a most blood-curdling crime! Namely, that of the attempted murder of his neighbouring lodger, an innocent Englishman.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">To explain the circumstances of the crime, the prosecution calls its first witnesses to the stand... ...the detective responsible for investigating the scene, and the accused himself!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Witnesses, your names and occupations, please.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yes, sir! Tobias Gregson, Detective Inspector at Scotland Yard's homicide division.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... Ah! Soseki Natsume from the Empire of Japan! My government ordered me to come here as a student to study your language and culture.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr Natsume...</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Yes! My Lord, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm quite sure I'm not mistaken... ...that you swore on oath...never to set foot in my courtroom again. I remember it as if it were yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The day before, in fact, My Lord. But close enough.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Ugh...believe me, this is the last place I want to be...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Inspector, let's hear from you first. Explain the case for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Right you are, sir! The incident occurred at the Garrideb household where the defendant has lodgings... ...in the ground floor room of the victim, Mr William Shamspeare. The defendant has already admitted to visitin' the victim on the night in question. Mr Shamspeare collapsed in his room as a result of poisonin' by strychnine. He was found the followin' mornin' when the landlord, suspectin' somethin' was wrong, broke down the door.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This means, I presume, that the door to the victim's room was locked at the time of the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Correct, My Lord. It was locked from the inside, making entry to or exit from the room impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Although the victim, Mr Shamspeare, lives to tell tale... ...he very nearly didn't. The man was halfway to Heaven when we first found him.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I was the first officer on the scene, My Lord... ...and I have a photographic print here that I took at the time to show how it looked.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, a chilling scene indeed. The man looks very much deceased.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">That's right. Everyone present believed that's exactly what he was.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, I shall accept this photographic print as evidence for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr Natsume...</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Ah! Y-Yes...yes...YES?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As the defendant, do you have anything to say at this juncture?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... They're, they're haunted... Haunted by evil sp-spirits...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious! What's haunted?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">MY LODGINGS! THERE'S BEEN A WHOLE SERIES OF STRANGE HAPPENINGS IN MY LODGINGS! The tenant before me died in mysterious circumstances! A woman was stabbed by no one on the street outside! My neighbour was poisoned! And ME! WHAT ABOUT ME?! I've nearly been killed countless times!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Killed, Mr Natsume? How?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Even on that fateful night, it happened. When I returned from Mr Shamspeare's room... ...I lit my gas stove and climbed into bed, but before long... ...the stove went out, AND SOMEBODY TRIED TO KILL ME!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You must always extinguish all fires before retiring for the night, Mr Natsume.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">BUT IT'S SO COLD! My, my runny nose would freeze! The point is, I, I didn't poison my neighbour. Oh...why am I being accused of this? Why is my existence so cursed...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, witnesses. I believe I have a reasonably clear picture of events.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">If I could raise one more point, My Lord. One more...conclusive point.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Conclusive? Go on...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Fortunately, the victim, Mr Shamspeare, has regained consciousness after his ordeal. And he has named the true culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The poison consumed by the victim was administered in a cup of tea that he drank on the night in question. Tea, My Lord, that was brought to the victim's room by the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accused...? Good grief! Ordaaar! Ordaaar!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes...that's the crux of this whole case. If Soseki-san is innocent, then why...? Why has the victim accused him?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr Natsume? What have you to say to this accusation?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">That evening, yes...I did take some freshly brewed tea with me when I visited Mr Shamspeare's room, as a gift. The public water pump outside always freezes at night, so I bought bottled water especially to make it. And this is the result! Never will I touch tea again! Never!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The public pump was frozen, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's not information we've heard before.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That will do, thank you. Now, according to our laws, the defence must have the opportunity to cross-examine witnesses at least once. Therefore, I call upon these witnesses now for a formal testimony. ...I presume the prosecution has no objection?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">None whatsoever, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good. Then you will give your account of events on the night in question to the court now.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Ye-Ye-Ye...YEEEEEESSS, MY LORD!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">It was around nine o'clock that evening when I visited my neighbour, and I took some tea with me as a gift.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Strychnine takes some time to have an effect on the body. People don't keel over immediately after takin' it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm, yes, I see... It all seems relatively straightforward.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Excuse me, but...that testimony does raise one rather crucial point, I think. Mr Natsume claims his tea to have been harmless. Presumably, though... ...the teacups have been examined for traces of the poison...haven't they?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Why didn't I think of that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Well, as it happens, no. We haven't been able to.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Did I hear you correctly, Inspector? Scotland Yard has failed to examine the suspect substance?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How could you have overlooked something so important?! Isn't that the first thing you should have done?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...My learned Nipponese friend is falsely incensed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The inspector said Scotland Yard was unable to examine the tea. Not that it was overlooked.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Unable? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">It's simple enough. There was none left. Not a drop. Someone must have been very thirsty indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">With current scientific techniques, it's not possible to test for poison under such circumstances.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">We only need a drop, but that one drop does actually have to exist, funnily enough.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The lack of examination notwithstanding... ...it appears nothing other than the tea passed the victim's lips on the night in question.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Thank you. The matter is clear.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Cast your eyes over the jury, my learned friend.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">You can see it in their faces, I'm sure. The recognition of the accused's guilt. Your client's fate is all but sealed. In mere moments from now...you will lose, and your compatriot will be damned for all eternity!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He's right. I can feel all six of the jurors looking daggers at me. But I can't let them beat me down... I won't...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel for the Defence...proceed with your cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">It was around nine o'clock that evening when I visited my neighbour, and I took some tea with me as a gift.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Were you and your neighbour good friends, then?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Argh! NO! We weren't friends! Not at all! NOT AT ALL! Never...ever!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>A simple 'no' would have sufficed...</thought> Then, um...why did you decide to pay him a visit?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Mr Shamspeare fancies himself as having great literary knowledge. As a fellow scholar of English literature, we find much to talk about together.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...Come now, no Nipponese could understand the finer points of English literature.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And on the night in question, that was the topic of conversation as well, I presume.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">It was the day of my last trial, when I was acquitted. I'd just arrived back at my lodgings... ...when I ran into Mr Shamspeare outside on the street. That was at around six o'clock. We exchanged one or two pleasantries, but it soon turned into a heated discussion. He was on his way out at the time, though. So I promised to visit his room that evening at nine to continue our debate. ...But did I have ill intentions? No! Not one! Not two! Not any! Not at all! Never...ever!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">A simple 'no' would have sufficed, I feel...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Then tell the court what did happen when you visited the victim's room.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">We had a heated literary debate over a nice, hot drink. After which I went back to my room, at around eleven.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A literary debate...about Shakespeare's works, I think you said, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Shakespeare? Ah, a very worthy topic of conversation, I must say.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh yes, My Lord! Romeo! And Juliet! Who was stronger?! ...It was a profoundly pleasurable parley.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Romeo and Juliet?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...'Who was stronger'?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I know I'm going to regret asking this, but...how did the debate go?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Well...we both agreed that we would reach a conclusion more quickly with a reenactment. So we battled it out! In a Greco-Roman style, naturally.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Mr Shamspeare had all sorts of costumes in his room for just such a contest.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So, when you say a 'reenactment', you mean...you were actually in costume?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">He as Romeo, I as Juliet. And after a vigorous, wild tussle... ...I, as Juliet, came out on top! A VICTORY I'LL CHERISH FOREVER!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I dare not imagine the terrible scene of carnage...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The fact remains that it was you who prepared the tea and took it to the victim. ...Correct?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I boiled the water in my room and made a pot to take with me. I'd heard that he was too poor to have tea himself, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It's true...there was no sign of any tea leaves in the man's room.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I wanted to do something nice. To be friendly. So why is everyone looking at me with such suspicion?! MY TEA WAS HARMLESS! OF COURSE IT WAS!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And do you have any basis for that statement, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Argh! My tea was completely harmless! He couldn't have locked the door behind me otherwise, could he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, there was not a drop of tea left in the victim's room anywhere, was there?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">That's correct. Anyone would think the fellow had never had a pot of tea before. He must have licked it dry. Which is a pity, because one drop is all we would've needed to analyse it for poison.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And you say that you returned home to your room at eleven o'clock, Mr Natsume?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Yes! Definitely! By heaven and earth, I swear it!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">The landlord was able to verify that, as it happens. He confirmed that the defendant went back to his room at eleven that night.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And how is the landlord able to attest to this?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">He, um...said it was the lamps, I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The lamps, Inspector?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>When tenants return to their rooms and start using gas, the lamps in other parts of the house flicker.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, Mr Garrideb seems to pay a lot of attention to the comings and goings of his tenants...</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">There's only one key to Mr Shamspeare's room! I know that for certain! So he must have locked the door himself! From inside his room!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">The victim has confirmed that to be the case, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">SO I'M RIGHT! MY TEA WAS HARMLESS! COMPLETELY HARMLESS! IF YOU TAKE POISON, YOU DIE! EVERYONE KNOWS THAT!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">It's not that simple, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Uh! Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Strychnine takes some time to have an effect on the body. People don't keel over immediately after takin' it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How long does it take for symptoms to appear, then?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">According to the coroner I was speakin' to at the Yard, about thirty minutes after the poison's consumed. Then the victim suffers violent convulsions, crampin' and stiffness, and eventually dies from asphyxiation.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So there's a thirty-minute interval between when the poison is ingested and the onset of symptoms. There seems to be a lot of different types of poison in the world, that's for sure...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... Death by poisoning again. It's always so awful...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Thirty minutes is a long time. Certainly long enough for the victim to have locked the door behind the accused after he left.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>You can't deny that. And it further degrades Soseki-san's alibi.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I have the medical report from the doctor who examined the victim here, My Lord. It spells it out, really. The accused is the only person who could have done it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, the court will add this report to the Court Record as evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes...I see it here. 'Delayed onset of symptoms'...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Great...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How long does it take for symptoms to appear, then?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">According to the coroner I was speakin' to at the Yard, about thirty minutes after the poison's consumed. Then the victim suffers violent convulsions, crampin' and stiffness, and eventually dies from asphyxiation.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So there's a thirty-minute interval between when the poison is ingested and the onset of symptoms. There seems to be a lot of different types of poison in the world, that's for sure...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... Death by poisoning again. It's always so awful...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Thirty minutes is a long time. Certainly long enough for the victim to have locked the door behind the accused after he left.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>You can't deny that. And it further degrades Soseki-san's alibi.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I have the medical report from the doctor who examined the victim here, My Lord. It spells it out, really. The accused is the only person who could have done it.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">The victim would have been perfectly able to lock the door after his guest left. The argument still stands.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The argument still stands, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">This is what Mr Natsume has been sayin', isn't it? The pair of them drank tea together that night, so if there was poison in it... ...the victim wouldn't have been able to lock the door after the accused left later on.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">EXACTLY! ARGH! Me and my tea are INNOCENT! SWEET and INNOCENT, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I'm afraid, sir, that doesn't follow. You see, strychnine is a slow-actin' poison. In other words, it takes time for symptoms to appear. So you could have left the room up to thirty minutes after the victim drank the tea. And as long as you did that, Mr Shamspeare could've locked the door after you'd gone.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">But, but NO! We drank the tea straight away! The battle over whether Romeo or Juliet was stronger...! That came after the tea.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Do you have any evidence to support that statement?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... In my great homeland - the Empire of Japan - we have a saying: 'Drink tea while it's hot!'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Sure, a proverb will satisfy the prosecution...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid there's no conclusive proof to support the defendant's assertion. On the contrary, there are sufficient grounds to infer his guilt in this matter!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">N-N-No...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's the extent of their testimony, is it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">If I could voice a personal opinion, Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of course. Go ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Natsume is arguing for his innocence so adamantly and so persistently... ...yet Inspector Gregson just brushes what he says aside. It's really quite infuriating!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I agree. So we need to find an inconsistency in what the inspector is saying, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm afraid so. As things stand, the jurors are sure to find Mr Natsume guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>As I see it, what we need to focus on is the poison and the tea...</thought> Let's listen carefully to this testimony again.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The argument still stands, you say? I think not, Inspector!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">...Come again?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think you'll find...that you've overlooked a very significant chronological inconsistency here!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">A chrono-what? What are you on about?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">According to this report... ...the victim must have consumed the poison at around... one thirty in the morning. And yet... ...the defendant, Mr Natsume, left the victim's room at eleven.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's right... There's more than two hours of missing time there!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">...Nnf...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In other words... ...if there was poison in the tea that Mr Natsume brought to the victim's room... ...how could the victim have fallen ill to it...two and a half full hours after the defendant left?!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">UWAAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence's argument is entirely reasonable. How do you respond, Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...Pray forgive the discourtesy if my mind has wandered. I was considering what cuisine would best complement the contents of my hallowed chalice this luncheon.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">How could it have happened, you ask? I do hate to shatter illusions, but my Nipponese friend appears to be chasing a phantom idea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A phantom...?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Is it so hard to imagine that the victim drank his tea after the accused had left? For example, at the time stated in the medical report. Yes...at around half past one.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Natsume brought the tea with him to drink together with his neighbour! And in Japan, there is a well known saying: 'Drink tea while it's hot!'</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The, the point is...if there was such a long gap... ...there may be other ways to explain how the victim came to be poisoned! Other possibilities!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What sort of possibilities, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Well...for example... The man could have had another visitor!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Another visitor? That's a very bold assertion, my learned friend...from someone who has nothing to substantiate it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Or...or...the victim could have taken the poison of his own volition!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You suggest this may have been a suicide, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but he could be lying!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is something wrong, Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I was listening to the sound of the carriage pulling up outside the courtroom. Pray, forgive the discourtesy.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Carriage? What carriage?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It would seem...that the key player in this case has just arrived.</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="???">'Out, out, brief candle! Life's but a walking shadow...'</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'...a poor player, that struts and frets his hour upon the stage, and then is heard no more. It is a tale, told by an idiot, full of sound and fury, Signifying nothing.'</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who, sir, are you...?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">William Shamspeare, My Lord. Alas 'twas I, undone by these bitter events. I...am the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha... What's he doing here?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The prosecution seeks to call this gentleman to the stand. With his testimony, my learned friend's futile resistance will be utterly crushed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're calling him as a witness?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Counsel. I grant your request with interest. I'm curious to discover what the court shall hear from the victim himself!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Happy am I, Shamspeare, to regale thee with my tale of woe, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">B-But...! I still have my own tale to tell! My own tale of worse woe! I CAN REGALE THE COURT WITH THE TALE OF MY PERFECT INNOCENCE IN PERFECT ENGLISH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That will do, Mr Natsume. Let the court now hear from the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Alright, so that's Mr Shamspeare... But who's that other man beside him?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I think... I feel sure that we've caught a glimpse of that man before.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">State your names and occupations for the court, please, witnesses.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">A writer of words so sweet, they do scent the breeze. An inventor of ideas so profound, they compose the earth. The unrivall'd poet, the unmatched scribe, William Shakespeare... Were the great bard to be recall'd to life anew, lo, what a magnificent man! Good fellows, I am he who ponders such a miracle... William Shamspeare.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Oh, um...the name's Metermann. Adron B. Metermann. I work for the Altamont Gas Company, East End branch office.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah! I remember now! It was yesterday, on Briar Road...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes! <thought>She's right. It's him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Oh...what's this? What's that man doing over there? He looks like he's trying to see into Soseki-san's lodgings...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Is something wrong, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, excuse me! Could we have a word?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, we spotted him outside Mr Garrideb's house that morning. And he's a gas company employee? What does he have to do with this case?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, Mr William Shamspeare...you are the victim in this miserable affair, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'O Heaven! O Hell! Do you command me to remember?' That sweet poison that didst cross me and cross mine innocent lips.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I subpoenaed him for the trial. With his doctor's permission, naturally. Hearing the testimony of the aggrieved will remove any room for doubt from the jurors' minds, I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Behold, you have only to rearrange the letters of my name to see that 'me's a seraph'! An angel, indeed! Thus be I noble of mind, sweet of nature and verily, honest of heart. As all heavenly angels be.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Because there isn't a less contrived meaning in your name. No, not at all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">The jurors seem to be very moved by this man, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>They're actually taking this 'seraph' anagram idea seriously...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, witnesses, for your illuminating introductions.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But My Lord...what's the man next to Mr Shamspeare doing here? The gasman, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Uh? What? Me? Well now...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Allow me to enlighten my learned friend. You recall, I presume, your earlier impertinence? When you suggested that the victim had another visitor to his room on the night in question. And, moreover, that the victim is a compulsive liar.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! No, no I didn't quite say that...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">This young chin-stroker is here to controvert your wild claims. Conclusively. Is that not so...Mr Metermann?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Eh? Hang on, no... I'm just here...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hereby call for your formal testimonies. You will tell the court as lucidly as possible what happened on the night in question!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'One may smile, and smile, and be a villain...' Yes, it doth pain me, but let the truth be spoken! The truth of that wintry night of my discontent.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Hmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">The snow lay about. My neighbour did cometh in the evening, bearing a gift of tea.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">I was outside this bloke's window in the freezin' cold all night, keepin' an eye on his room.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait, what did you say?! You were 'keeping an eye' on Mr Shamspeare's room all night?!</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">That's right. 'Course, the bloke's window is all but blocked up, isn't it? But there's a little gap in the bricks where you can see into the room. So I spent the night tryin' to keep my teeth from chatterin' as I peered in through that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The question is, sir...why?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Ah! Well now, that's because he's on my list!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'What a piece of work is a man!' ...Wherefore wouldst thou not stare in wonderment?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">This buzzing busybody hath not part in this play. I pray thee...pay him no heed. Make no more ado about his tedious words...</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">What'd you say about me?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Calm yourself. This court is concerned with what happened on the night in question. Nothing more.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed, that is so.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And, as the testimony we have just heard clearly reveals... ...there was no one other than the accused present at the time who could have carried out this crime.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well...I believe this may be the final testimony of the trial. Now, Counsel...the defence may proceed with the cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">The snow lay about. My neighbour did cometh in the evening, bearing a gift of tea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">To be clear, by neighbour, you are referring to the defendant, Mr Natsume?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">O, indeed, sire! Perchance thou wouldst that I call him 'the man from upstairs'?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And at what time did the moustachioed Nipponese visit you in your room?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Our meeting was promis'd for the hour of nine. And lo, did he come, to tender a gift of fragrant tea.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Details which are in accordance with the defendant's own testimony, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">And we were broil'd in such a literary debate as history hath nought seen before.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">By which I presume he means...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Their discussion about who was the stronger, Romeo or Juliet?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">I, Shamspeare, did play the part of young Romeo. Whilst my neighbour play'd the fair Juliet. Each of us dress'd as would our characters be, to bring weight upon our merry experiment.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I dare not imagine the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'Frailty, thy name is woman!' Canst thou imagine how dismay'd I was? Yes, I had heard of the Eastern art of ju-jitsu, but... ...ne'er did I dream 'twould be a skill practis'd by the comely maiden!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Juliet beat Romeo up? This is not helping our case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...I believe the court has heard enough about your... earth-shattering literary debate. Perhaps you could reiterate your statement about the tea that the accused brought to your room?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">My liege, I am thy servant. Glady, [sic] I would do thy bidding...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">But marry! Bitter was his drink! And when he left, I did fall prostrate on my table!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Let me stop you there! Mr Natsume left your room at eleven o'clock. But it wasn't until after two that the poison made you collapse. That amounts to more than three hours of 'missing time'.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If the defendant had really put the poison into your tea... ...that three-hour window of time...is something you're going to have to explain!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Gladly. 'Tis an easy task.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">I did drink of the tea not while my guest didst tarry, but after he took leave of me. Faith, 'twas stone cold, but...at one hour post midnight, verily were my lips parched.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That...doesn't sound normal!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Nay, 'tis quite ordinary, sire. After all... ...thou wouldst recall our fiery debate. Amidst such argument, there'd be no time for fiery tea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Romeo and Juliet again... And who was stronger...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Mr Shamspeare, in summary, allow me to confirm. Did you not come here with the intention of naming your attacker?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">But of course...my liege. 'Twas the stoop'd lover of words did attempt to shuffle me off this mortal coil.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh...we all know what that means...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'Twas the tea alone did pass my lips that late hour. Nought else.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you didn't have any kind of evening meal? Dinner? Supper?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Hah! Fie on luxury! Fie on gluttony! To eat thrice daily is but a waste of time!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">I would that my belly were full...no more oft than the sun doth rise!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... Most heroic eating habits, I must say.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Night and day do I fill my hours with learn'd study of the great bard and playwright. Hence is it that there doth nought in my chamber be than the costumes of mine art.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">That would appear to be the case...as even a rodent was found starved to death in your room.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Now I think of it, it's not just food that was conspicuously missing from that room, is it? I don't recall seeing a single play or script anywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">For I...have devour'd them all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You've...eaten them?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Ev'ry word be within my skull. ...Didst thou imagine otherwise?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Right. That wasn't misleading at all. Now, could you turn around, do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Which brings us to the conclusion...that the only way the poison could have passed the victim's lips...is in the tea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">I was outside this bloke's window in the freezin' cold all night, keepin' an eye on his room.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But the windows of that house have all been filled in.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">A historical artefact of the now defunct window tax!</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Yeah, you're right there. All bricked up horribly. But, as it happens, there's a little part of the brickwork at the bottom corner that's been opened up. I was lookin' in through that gap.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, there were a few bricks loose, weren't there?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And for some strange reason, a couple of bars of soap lined up on the ledge outside as well...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Metermann">I don't like goin' around pokin' my chin in other people's business. Especially on freezin' cold nights. But them's my orders! So that's what I'll keep doin'! ...As long as there's breath in my body!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What's with all the theatricals today?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Out of interest, Mr Metermann, after the accused had left and returned to his own lodgings... ...did you see the victim leave the room at all?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">No! He never left! He was in that room the whole time as far as I'm concerned!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And we can therefore discount the possibility of suicide.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! How can you be sure of that?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The police carried out a thorough investigation of the scene and found no receptacle for the poison. And since we know the victim didn't leave his room, and hence didn't dispose of the poison's container himself... ...it's clear that this was no attempted suicide. Only the culprit could have removed the receptacle.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, yes... Lucidly explained, Counsel. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It really was. You can't argue with the logic...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Metermann">No one else visited his room but that short little round-backed Eastern fella.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You say a 'short little round-backed Eastern fella'... So you can't be sure it was the defendant, then?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Well, of course...it's only a narrow gap and it was quite dark, so I didn't notice the moustache. But he showed up at around nine, so I'm pretty sure of myself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And when the person you saw arrived, did he and Mr Shamspeare drink tea together?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">......... Nah, sorry, I couldn't say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Because. I couldn't see into the room all that well, could I? But what I did see was the silhouette of that little round-backed fella wearin' a pretty dress. Then the pair of them started some kind of wrestlin' match. I tell you, I didn't know what to make of it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I suppose... ...that was the Romeo and Juliet championship battle getting underway...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Mr Metermann... ...allow me to confirm one final time: Apart from the accused, can you state with certainty, that no one else visited the victim on the night in question?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">No question! Gasman's honour!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So that's the entire testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">What do you think, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...erm... ...I can't see any obvious holes at all, to be honest.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No... Oh dear... If nobody else visited Mr Shamspeare's room that night apart from Mr Natsume... ...I imagine the members of the jury will all conclude the same thing.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Right. That he's guilty...</thought> Well, all we can do is press these witnesses for more information and hope for a breakthrough.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">My Looord!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Goodness me! Yes, Mr Foreman?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">I've kept my mouth shut and listened up to now, but this has gone on long enough. Are you all with me?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Are we to understand...that you ladies and gentlemen of the jury are in agreement with one another? That you've reached a unanimous decision?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Too right, we have!  Are you all with me?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait! No! The defence is in the middle of a cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">To be honest, I was holding out a bit of hope for you, young man. Especially after you identified those few hours that followed the accused leaving the victim's room.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Yes, the three 'missing hours' as you put it.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">But in the end, what difference do they make? None, as far as I can see.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">And since that's now apparent, there's really no reason to delay our decision any longer.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Like I was saying before: if I don't take five bob home with me tonight, the missus will blow her top!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Hm? What's that? Sorry, I didn't quite catch what you said...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, let the court be apprised of your decisions. Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, you will state your leanings as to the defendant's culpability!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A-All of you...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, it would appear that the jury is indeed unanimous.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">So...this time at least, it seems justice will be done. All's well that ends well, as they say. This calls for a toast, I feel... To the guilty being punished!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... UWAAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Get up, Mr Naruhodo! Please! The trial isn't over yet!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wh-What do you mean, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What about the information I found in this Encyclopaedia of British Law that I have? That obscure right that belongs to the defence in these situations...remember?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... ...A summation examination... ...Yes, that's right... We don't have a jury in Japanese courts, of course. But here in a British court of law, if we can reverse the decisions of a majority of the jurors... ...we can force the trial to continue. <thought>This trial can't end now. Whatever it takes, I just can't let that happen!</thought> The defence moves to invoke its right to a summation examination, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Why am I not surprised...at my learned Nipponese friend's inability to admit defeat? You choose to cling desperately to some archaic rule you barely comprehend instead of accepting the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Certainly no other defence counsellor in recent times has exercised the right to a summation examination.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Because they all know that once the jury's mind is set, it cannot be altered.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Nevertheless, the right remains and must be upheld. The defence counsel's request is granted. This court will proceed with a summation examination, as outlined in the Encyclopaedia of British Law! </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you and your fellows prepared, Mr Foreman?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Believe me, My Lord, we know all about this young lad's tenacity. And we're ready for it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. In that case, ladies and gentlemen of the jury, I hereby call upon each of you... ...to state the grounds upon which you find the defendant guilty of the crime for which he stands accused!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">The victim may not be well off, but he's a noble man and straight up! There's no reason to doubt the man.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Well, I do declare the good gentleman has no reason to lie. In fact...I think he's rather splendid.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Just look at the accused by comparison! He's Japanese, stoops all the while, and has a moustache! Very fishy...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">There's no evidence to suggest the gangling actor is a fraudsman. ...For now, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Agh! I really don't care, like! I just need this trial to end quickly!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Three hours of 'missing time' is nothing when you reach my age, you know. Nothing at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I knew it... Every single one of them seems completely convinced...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It would seem that all the jurors... ...have come to the conclusion that Mr Shamspeare is a fine, upstanding and honest citizen.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you ask me, they've all been bewitched by his strange theatrical movements.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And sadly, nothing Mr Natsume has said appears to have registered at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...here goes! <thought>Let's not forget... ...I've pleaded with the jury on Soseki-san's behalf before and it worked. So you never know!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Before we begin... ...it might be an idea for me to remind you exactly how a summation examination works, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, you're still very new to British law, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's true, I suppose. And Soseki-san's fate is entirely in my hands now, too. There's always a chance I might have forgotten some crucial detail. Perhaps I should hear Susato-san out. I wonder...should I let her talk me through it again or not bother?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Alright! So, if you remember... ...the key to changing the jurors' minds is the things that they say themselves.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes, it's coming back to me. First, it's important to listen very carefully to each juror's statement. Then, if it sounds as though one of those statements might contradict another... ...I have to pit the corresponding two jurors against each other to prove one or the other of them wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's right. In many ways, it's very similar to a normal cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Alright then. All that remains now...is to do it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you for the kind offer, Miss Susato... ...but I've been through plenty of these summation examinations already now. I think it's important that we don't delay the start any longer than necessary.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Of course, I understand. And I'm quite sure you're right. If you're confused by anything at any point, you can turn to me for advice whenever you like. I'll be here for you!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The key to this is really listening carefully to each juror's statement... ...finding two that are contradictory, and pitting the corresponding jurors against each other!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Without further ado, please, Counsel. Proceed with the summation examination!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">The victim may not be well off, but he's a noble man and straight up! There's no reason to doubt the man.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, there are plenty of people in London who seem noble but poor. Couldn't some of them also be liars?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">I've no doubt about it. Like that shaky client of yours, for example.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Absolutely not! Mr Natsume is no liar!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Look, the point is, the only thing that passed the victim's lips that night was that Japanese man's tea. When you take the gasman's testimony into account as well, the truth couldn't be any clearer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...well... <thought>...that's alarmingly logical.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">But let me be frank here. I'm a gentleman, with a gentleman's values. If it turns out that the old Shakespearean chum is a rotten liar after all... ...I'd gladly change my decision about the defendant. And I'm sure my fellow gentlemen on the jury would do the same. ...Isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Well, um...yes, perhaps. Though I don't see it happening.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Eh? What's that? Elderly gent on the end here, you know. You'll have to speak up!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Look, I really don't care about all this nonsense. I just need this trial to be over!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>How many 'gentlemen' do we actually have on the jury, then...?</thought> Alright, sir, I may hold you to that. Don't forget what you said.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Alright, if you can show me that the victim's a liar, I'll reconsider my position!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Will you stand by that statement?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">What do you take me for? I'm a gentleman, sir. A man of my word. So let me be perfectly clear about this. If it turns out that the old Shakespearean chum is a rotten liar after all... ...I'd gladly change my decision about the defendant. And I'm sure my fellow gentlemen on the jury would do the same. ...Isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Well, um...yes, perhaps. Though I don't see it happening.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Eh? What's that? Elderly gent on the end here, you know. You'll have to speak up!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Look, I really don't care about all this nonsense. I just need this trial to be over!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>How many 'gentlemen' do we actually have on the jury, then...?</thought> Alright, sir, I may hold you to that. Don't forget what you said.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Well, I do declare the good gentleman has no reason to lie. In fact...I think he's rather splendid.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Are you saying you believe the man to be trustworthy because he's 'rather splendid'?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">No, that's not what I said. The point is, the man is the victim here. What reason would he have to lie? And yes...he is rather splendid.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you say...yet again.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Meanwhile the man who stands accused behaves so suspiciously, it's exhausting to look at him! I'm afraid...he's not splendid at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Splendid logic there, madam. Thank you so much.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Just look at the accused by comparison! He's Japanese, stoops all the while, and has a moustache! Very fishy...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no no! Not one of those things is a reason to find the man guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">But he is fishy. There's no point dancing around the fact. He's Japanese, he has a moustache and he stoops. You see, you arrive at the conclusion in just three steps. Three steps...like a waltz, in fact! You know, the more I think about it, the more this trial seems like a dance!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>You seem to be several steps ahead of yourself, though... and you're on the wrong foot!</thought> No! There's nothing but circumstantial evidence here! There's no actual proof of the defendant's guilt!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">But the victim's version of events is backed up by what the big-chinned man next to him says, isn't it? One, he saw the Japanese man there. Two, he saw no one else. And three, he saw the Japanese man there. ...Oh! That's another three steps! All this really does seem more and more like a waltz, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Right...and the prosecution will waltz its way to victory if I let you speak much more...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">There's no evidence to suggest the gangling actor is a fraudsman. ...For now, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A fraudsman? What do you mean by that, madam?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">......... It really is a most tiresome problem for the company. Most irritating. We can be absolutely certain that a customer is stealing from us, but without hard evidence... ...we can't even threaten to take action for fear of being sued.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I'm sorry, you've lost me a little there. ...Who are you?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">I'm the wife of Augustus Altamont, owner of the Altamont Gas Company.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious! Altamont Gas, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Gas is the future of energy in this country and around the globe. But proper handling is essential. ...As I'm sure our employee from the East End branch office would be the first to agree.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Absolutely, Lady Quinby! Gotta be used properly! Altamont Gas is the best in the world, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Ah, I think we may have solved the mystery of the bow from earlier, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Right... He bowed in deference to his employer's wife, did he?</thought> Ah! So...would I be right in assuming... ...that the reason Mr Metermann was watching what Mr Shamspeare was up to in his room...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">I'm afraid that there's no end to the lengths the population of the East End will go to in order to steal our gas. So I really have no choice when the company identifies somebody as a possible fraudsman... ...but to dispatch a worker to watch the suspect day and night. We're very thorough in our investigations.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you mean, Mr Shamspeare is...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">I wouldn't come out and say it in public...but you can finish that sentence with 'a grubby little gas thief'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You have noticed the public gallery in here, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'The eye of man hath not heard, the ear of man hath not seen...' Faith, wouldst thou wound me with thy words...were I to let them penetrate the skin. But seraphs hear not insults, only choirs of angels in song!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">We may not have evidence yet. But my workers won't stop buzzing around you until they find it! And when they do...you'll find yourself blasted back to your angelic heights in an Altamont Gas explosion!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So Mr Shamspeare has been stealing gas...</thought> I wonder, juror number four, if you wouldn't mind adding that information to your statement?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">My pleasure. Was it the bit about ripping that thief apart you enjoyed?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...A little before the part about abject violence, if it's not too much trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Yes, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This could be it! This could shift the balance...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">The 'victim' puts on a fine performance, but in reality, he's a common thief...of my company's gas!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's a bold claim. How can you be so sure?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">It's really very simple.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Noble lady of gas, I pray thee! Hold thy tongue!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">I beg your pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Hath that rank-odoured air that doth our darkness illuminate any place in this assembly? Nay! 'Tis of sole import here that someone wouldst extinguish the light of mine own life!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">...!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Verily, I ne'er recall stealing thy gas. But pray, let the matter rest till anon!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Why, you little...</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Beggin' your pardon, my lady, but might I suggest you don't say any more at this stage? We need hard evidence first. If I keep secretly watchin' this bloke, I'll get him in the end. He'll slip up!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Do you think maybe that secret's out of the bag?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Hmph! Oh, this is so frustrating!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Agh! I really don't care, like! I just need this trial to end quickly!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You keep talking about needing to take home some money. What's that all about, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">...Finnish Lass, that's what it's about.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's that?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">I'm talking about the derby at Hyde Park, aren't I? It was the Queen's Cup last week, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A...derby?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">It was a dead cert, that's the thing! I couldn't lose! So I took my wife's secret savings, like... But then that hopeless old mare went and did the unthinkable! Argh, that stupid Finnish Lass!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Oh dear. I think it's clear what happened, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">This is the day the missus uses her savings for a trip down the pub! So, come on! Let this business lie now! Just give it up!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No! That's...not going to happen!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Three hours of 'missing time' is nothing when you reach my age, you know. Nothing at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you really mean by that, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Well, I'm not one to boast, but I get up at five every morning, I do.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">At five?! You're a really early riser then, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Hm? What's that now?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I said, you're an early riser!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Oh well, I wouldn't say that. I mean, I like to while away the hours in the evening reading books as well. But by about two in the morning, I'm usually too tired to go on.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">He sleeps at two in the morning and gets up at five...? Oh my! That means he only has three hours of sleep each night!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Hm? What's that, dear?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">ONLY THREE HOURS OF SLEEP EACH NIGHT!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">That's right, you see. Three hours of missing time, like I said. It's not much, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...This really isn't helping.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">The key to summation examinations is identifying contradictions between jurors' statements, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right, and once I've found two jurors whose statements can't coexist, I need to pit those jurors against each other. Then hopefully, when they see that what they're saying doesn't make sense, they'll change their leaning.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes. And if you're able to change the minds of a majority of the jurors, the trial will continue. But conversely, if you're unable to do that, the judge will declare the trial over and move to adjudication.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And I can't let that happen. Somehow or other, I have to turn this trial around!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Those two statements clearly contradict each other!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious! To whose statements do you refer, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Juror number one!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Eh? What are you yelling about, lad?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I presume you've heard juror number four's statement? Made by the wife of the owner of Altamont Gas.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Well, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The victim, who you claim to be a noble, 'straight up' man... ...in fact turns out to be a 'common thief'.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">So the good lady says. But there's no evidence, is there? You and I both heard them say as much!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">It's true, we don't have evidence as such...just yet. But the claims aren't baseless, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">What?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">You heard me. Seeing as his operation has already been compromised... ...I would suggest that the court hears testimony from our East End branch office employee over there.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">I'll do whatever you say, my lady! Gasman's honour!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Juror number one! You say you're a man of your word!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If I could show that Mr Shamspeare was a liar, you assured me... ...that you would reconsider your decision about the defendant's guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">......... Hm, yes, I did say that. And as a man of honour, I'll hold to it. ...As I'm sure the other gentlemen of the jury will!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Me?! Oh, well, yes... Now that we've found out the man's a liar, perhaps we ought to consider the matter further.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Well...if I'm perfectly honest, I haven't heard half of what you've all been saying. So if this means you'll recap a few points, that would suit me down to the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Oh no, I'm not having any part of this! I want this trial over and done with!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">In that case, I shall change my leaning.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">So, Mr William Shamspeare...if that is your real name... ...we of the jury demand to know exactly what kind of a man you really are!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's...four jurors! Four for 'not guilty'!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, Mr Naruhodo! Victory!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Well...this is quite extraordinary, I must say. As a result of the defence's summation examination, the jury's leaning has changed. Now only two jurors say 'guilty', whilst four say 'not guilty'. I therefore declare this court to be in a state of disaccord... ...and order the trial to continue!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">You have spoilt the bouquet...Mr Shamspeare.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The ladies and gentlemen of the jury now find they are unable to trust you, the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">......... 'But you gods will give us, Some faults to make us men.' So God mend me, I do swear... This gasman speaketh that which concerns him most: nought but gas! Nought but thin air! Ay, it burneth bright a while, but it hath no substance. And it doth reek foul!</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Oi, what did you say?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do I take it, Mr Shamspeare, that you deny the allegations of gas thievery?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Most heartily, My Lord! Hast thou forgot? I am as a seraph! An angel! Noble of mind, sweet of nature and verily, honest of heart.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Argh, you flowery-mouthed, pompous beanpole! Just cos I haven't got the evidence yet...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Shamspeare! If, in fact, you are NOT noble of mind, sweet of nature or honest of heart... If you are a liar... ...then your testimony should have no sway in this courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is my considered opinion... ...that at the present time, no other possible culprit of this crime has been identified. All testimony heard by the court thus far heavily implicates the defendant. In short, it would not be unreasonable at this stage for me to rule on the case.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">However...in light of the fact that the jury has expressed concern about the fidelity of this witness... ...I believe it would be inappropriate for this court not to pursue the point further.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Juror number four!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Didn't you say before that although you had no hard evidence to prove this man has been stealing gas... ...you have strong grounds for suspecting him?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">That's right, we do. ...Don't we, hm, worker?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Absolutely, Lady Quinby! Gasman's honour!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, then. We will hear your testimony now. You will tell the court precisely why you believe the victim, Mr William Shamspeare, has been stealing gas.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Yes, My Lord, it'll be my pleasure! On the Altamont Gas name, I swear-</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">If I may, My Lord...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Go ahead, madam.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">This worker's testimony may have a significant bearing on the good name of my husband's company. Therefore, I should like to take the stand alongside him, in a supervisory role. If you wouldn't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Wahoo! Oh, yeah! Sweet as honey! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. As an exception, I shall honour your request.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Thank you, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">You wait till the boss gives you an earful! Ooh, it's gonna sting, you mark my words!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, you will both testify before the court... ...on the subject of the illegal consumption of the Altamont Gas Company's fuel!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Yes... ...Is that clear, my good man?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Clear as Altamont gas, my lady! ...Which is the clearest in the world!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you think the gas has gone to his head, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think the man is just a very dedicated employee, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">I'm proud to be the company's East End branch investigator and meter money collection agent.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">And yet, the meter in Mr Shamspeare's room didn't have a single coin in it!</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Somehow, he's usin' all the flamin' gas he wants without payin' a penny! If that's not thievin', what is?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...Pray forgive the discourtesy. The irrelevance of this testimony caused me to turn to my hallowed chalice.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean by that remark, Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Did the moustachioed Nipponese poison the gangling excuse for an actor or didn't he? That is all that should concern this court. And yet now we must listen to this...abhorrence. Clearly what separates the vast British Empire and your Eastern island nation is more than geographical distance.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...but this could turn out to be crucial testimony! The cross-examination must go ahead!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...Do what you will.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Lord van Zieks appears to be in a violent mood.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...he does. <thought>An attempted poisoning...and an incidence of gas theft with no supporting evidence... It's true that they would appear completely unrelated at first glance. But I wonder... The truth tends to be buried in the most unusual places. And the first step in uncovering it...will be to establish just who and what this man really is!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Metermann">I'm proud to be the company's East End branch investigator and meter money collection agent.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So does that mean you enter people's houses in order to empty their gas meters?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">That I do. Have to try to catch people when they're in. Then I ask permission to come inside and do my business.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Does that mean you've been into Mr Natsume's room before, as well as that of Mr Shamspeare?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Well now...interestin' you should bring that up. Cos I couldn't believe how little money was in his meter. I mean how the pair of them survive the winter is beyond me, it really is.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Knowing Mr Natsume, he probably spends all his gas money on books.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And then when he's finished reading them, he probably burns them for warmth.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You will kindly reiterate your statement about the gas meters themselves, Mr Metermann.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Not much to say really, but as you wish...</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Altamont gas meters accept thruppenny bits, each coin givin' customers about two hours of gorgeous gas!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So all London houses that have a gas supply are filled with these gas meters, are they?</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">They're the latest model. The height of technology. Developed by our own company, Altamont Gas. And anyone who uses our gas will have one of these meters in their property, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So if a threepence coin gives two hours of gas, most people would use about three coins in a night?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">A bit more than that, usually. If they have both gas lights and a gas stove, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Thinking about it, Soseki-san doesn't have a fireplace in that room of his, does he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Some people still choose to use candles of course, and only have gas for heating.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah yes, I do remember seeing candles in Mr Natsume's room, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And how does the money in the meter get back to you at the gas company?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Every three days, gasmen like me visit properties on the gas supply and empty the meters of coins.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">I must say, the design and manufacture of the new meter cost the company an awful lot of money. But happily, it did put a stop to people not paying their dues...for the most part.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, because they have to pay in advance, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Yes. Exactly right.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">And yet, the meter in Mr Shamspeare's room didn't have a single coin in it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Out of interest, how long has this been going on?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Weeks and weeks! He's been pinchin' gas off us for ages!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And you've examined the meter in Mr Shamspeare's room, I take it?</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Naturally. We took it off the wall and went over it with a fine-tooth comb.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And found nothing suspicious at all, I presume.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">No, I'm afraid we didn't. Which is exactly why I demanded a new type of meter to be produced. One with an indestructible lock. The 'Shamspeare Special'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That sounds like it would have cost an awful lot of threepenny pieces...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Altamont">But even after all that...the rascal's meter was still empty!</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">I'll never forget the humiliation! When I opened up the money box and found it bare... 'You what?!' I said! 'You WHAT?!' And the look on his face! That smarmy smile of his!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">I pulled the meter straight off the wall and took it back to the office. But you know what? Nothin'! Not a trace of it bein' jemmied open anywhere! Not a single sign! And what's happenin' to my salary as a result? Down by three shillings a day, that's what!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A life-threatening situation...in a number of ways. Incidentally, what became of that meter?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Nothin' became of it. I've still got it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Right here!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No wonder they call you Metermann...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... I think it would be prudent for the court to sequester this item while the trial is ongoing.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Definitely... Although at first glance, there doesn't appear to be anything unusual about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Let's move this along, shall we? Continue with your testimony. Though I would say it has as much value as the contents of that meter.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Oof...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Out of interest, how long has this been going on?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Weeks and weeks! He's been pinchin' gas off us for ages!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And you've examined the meter in Mr Shamspeare's room, I take it?</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Naturally. We took it off the wall and went over it with a fine-tooth comb.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And found nothing suspicious at all, I presume.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">No, I'm afraid we didn't. Which is exactly why I demanded a new type of meter to be produced. One with an indestructible lock. The 'Shamspeare Special'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That sounds like it would have cost an awful lot of threepenny pieces...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Altamont">But even after all that...the rascal's meter was still empty!</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">I'll never forget the humiliation! When I opened up the money box and found it bare... 'You what?!' I said! 'You WHAT?!' And the look on his face! That smarmy smile of his!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">I pulled the meter straight off the wall and took it back to the office. But you know what? Nothin'! Not a trace of it bein' jemmied open anywhere! Not a single sign! And what's happenin' to my salary as a result? Down by three shillings a day, that's what!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A life-threatening situation...in a number of ways.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's a very sturdy-looking padlock, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And the money box is sealed with beeswax, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So if Mr Sholmes were to get up to any mischief, he'd be found out immediately.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! Mischief of that kind is not the sort of thing that Mr Sholmes would...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...You know you didn't finish that sentence, don't you?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well...anyway... It's understandable that the gas company would want to safeguard the money that's rightfully theirs...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But it does feel a little over the top perhaps, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, what's...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Have you spotted something, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just here...there's a little hole. Do you see?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Goodness, you're right! I wouldn't have noticed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's not a very neat hole, is it? Not professionally made, I'd say.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So...you think it might have been opened up by Mr Shamspeare?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Possibly. It seems the people at Altamont Gas must have missed it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, it certainly seems to go all the way through to the inside.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, but there's no way a coin could fit through there.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's true, but even so...it seems more than a little suspicious!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, what's...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Have you spotted something, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just here...there's a little hole. Do you see?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Goodness, you're right! I wouldn't have noticed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's not a very neat hole, is it? Not professionally made, I'd say.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So...you think it might have been opened up by Mr Shamspeare?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Possibly. It seems the people at Altamont Gas must have missed it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, it certainly seems to go all the way through to the inside.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, but there's no way a coin could fit through there.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's true, but even so...it seems more than a little suspicious!</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">The meter doesn't appear to have been tampered with, though, and the collection agent has the only key.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's only one key for all of your meters?</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Well, in truth, there's another key in the company vault at our main office. But even if someone had somehow managed to get hold of a key, we'd know if the coin box had been opened.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh? How?</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">I came up with a rather clever way to expose any little shenanigans, as it happens.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Would you care to explain?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Well now...in order to empty a meter, you have to unlock the padlock and remove the cover. But when I close the cover again, I stick a little beeswax seal on it, you see!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A seal? Like the sort of thing you'd put on an envelope, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Somethin' like that, yes. Basically, you can't remove the cover again without breakin' the seal.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Now, in the case of Mr Shamspeare's meter, there were no coins inside at all, as I said.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">But the seal hadn't been broken, either.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So that would mean Mr Shamspeare somehow managed to steal coins from inside the meter without opening it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It would seem so, but...that would be impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lady Altamont...I'm afraid to say... ...that this meter clearly does show signs of having been tampered with.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">What?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Get away! I've been over and over that thing! I'm tellin' you, there's nothin' wrong with it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In that case... ...what do you have to say about the small hole that's been made at the base of the coin box?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Hole? What?</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">You're right! You're quite right! There is a little hole there! The meters aren't supposed to have that! None of the others did!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In other words, we can assume that Mr Shamspeare secretly opened up this hole himself.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Yes...I wouldn't be at all surprised. ...But why?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Yeah, why? I mean, it's tiny! You couldn't get a farthin' through that!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Lady Altamont... ...I wonder if you could give the court some more details about your meter design.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">What sort of details?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, what I'd specifically like to know is...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How can the meter be dismantled?</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Dismantled?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. Given that there are no signs of it having been forced... ...I'm wondering if perhaps rather than being broken open, it might have been taken apart.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Well, yes, that does make some sense. The padlocks are made by a first-class locksmith from the finest quality steel. And the meter box itself is made from plate steel as well, welded shut to ensure it can't be opened again. I can assure you, it's quite impossible to dismantle it.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Wahoo! Yeah! Nothin' leaks from an Altamont meter! No coins, no gas, no nothin'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness will amend her formal testimony with that information in case it is pertinent.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">As you wish, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How does the meter tell the difference between different coins?</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, for example, if someone were to put in a one penny coin, that wouldn't work presumably, would it?</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">No, of course not.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...well, how does the meter know that the coin it's been fed is a thruppenny bit?</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Ah, I see what you're getting at now. The meter tells coins apart by their shape and size, which includes their thickness. A thruppenny bit is about three-quarters of an inch in diameter, you see. Other coins just won't fit.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, I see... It's clearly been very well thought out.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness will amend her formal testimony with that information in case it is pertinent.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">As you wish, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">All joints on the meter are welded shut, and the lock is made from solid steel. There's no way to dismantle it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Has anyone ever tried?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Oh yeah, they've tried. But they've all given up before long.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">After all, if they actually broke the meter, the company would be able to take legal action.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that makes sense.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What do you think, Mr Naruhodo? Is its welded steel construction significant... ...or perhaps there's some other aspect of the meter's construction that we should be focusing on?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...you may be right. <thought>Perhaps I should try a different tack here. Like asking about how the meter differentiates coins, for example...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How does the meter tell the difference between different coins?</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, for example, if someone were to put in a one penny coin, that wouldn't work presumably, would it?</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">No, of course not.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...well, how does the meter know that the coin it's been fed is a thruppenny bit?</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Ah, I see what you're getting at now. The meter tells coins apart by their shape and size, which includes their thickness. A thruppenny bit is about three-quarters of an inch in diameter, you see. Other coins just won't fit.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, I see... It's clearly been very well thought out.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness will amend her formal testimony with that information in case it is pertinent.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">As you wish, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">The meter is designed for coins the exact diameter and thickness of a thruppenny bit. Nothing else will fit.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But conversely then... ...it would seem that anything matching a threepence coin exactly in terms of diameter and thickness... ...could equally well be used. Would, um, that be true?</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Well...yes, in a way. The weight comes into it a certain extent as well.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">We've thought of that though, anyway! If I find any fake coins inside the coin box when I empty the meter... ...the contract says the customer has to pay one hundred times the amount they diddled as a fine! We live for moments like that, us gasmen do! Live for them! Ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm... It would seem the gas company has thought of everything.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Wahoo! Hurrah for gas! Hurrah for cash! Altamont all the way!</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">That's quite enough of that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Remind me, how big are thruppenny bits?</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">About three-quarters of an inch across.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What do you think, Mr Naruhodo? Is this two centimetres measurement significant... ...or perhaps there's some other aspect of the meter's construction that we should be focusing on?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...you may be right. <thought>Perhaps I should try a different tack here. Like asking about whether the meter can be dismantled, for example...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How can the meter be dismantled?</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Dismantled?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. Given that there are no signs of it having been forced... ...I'm wondering if perhaps rather than being broken open, it might have been taken apart.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Well, yes, that does make some sense. The padlocks are made by a first-class locksmith from the finest quality steel. And the meter box itself is made from plate steel as well, welded shut to ensure it can't be opened again. I can assure you, it's quite impossible to dismantle it.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Wahoo! Yeah! Nothin' leaks from an Altamont meter! No coins, no gas, no nothin'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness will amend her formal testimony with that information in case it is pertinent.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">As you wish, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let us return to the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Of course, My Lord. As I was saying, Altamont meters are unsurpassed. They can't be manipulated.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...? Look at this bar of soap. There's a circular depression on this side. About two centimetres across.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Or...three-quarters of an inch- Ah! Do you think...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We did find this soap at the scene, didn't we?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes... Yes, there were two bars, on that little ledge just outside the window. So we took this one. But I'm sure that when we first found it... ...there was some sort of reddish medallion in the middle there. I remember it clearly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, but there's no sign of it now... <thought>Where could it have gone?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...? Look at this bar of soap. There's a circular depression on this side. About two centimetres across.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Or...three-quarters of an inch- Ah! Do you think...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We did find this soap at the scene, didn't we?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes... Yes, there were two bars, on that little ledge just outside the window. So we took this one. But I'm sure that when we first found it... ...there was some sort of reddish medallion in the middle there. I remember it clearly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, but there's no sign of it now... <thought>Where could it have gone?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Somehow, he's usin' all the flamin' gas he wants without payin' a penny! If that's not thievin', what is?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How do you know that he's been using gas, though?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Well now... Since I started investigatin' this bloke, I've been to his room more than a few times. And on every single occasion, his lamps have been blazin' and his stove poundin'! It's the middle of winter, and he still turns to me, sweat drippin' down his cheeks, and says...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'Get thee to a nunnery!'</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hamlet, indeed!</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Argh! I could wring the bloke's neck! I get all hot under the collar, but still... ...every time I open up that flamin' meter, it's empty! He's robbin' me of my salary, too! What's wrong with the world?! Where's the justice?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But how can Mr Shamspeare possibly be stealing the money? I don't understand...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The simple explanation is right before your eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">A toast...to you eventually realising that the gasman could be an accomplice.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">YOU WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good Lord! Eminently plausible indeed...</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">......... Well, what do you have to say for yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Oh, please! Lady Quinby! I'm a faithful worker. And besides...if the money us gasmen collect doesn't tally with how much gas has been used... ...YOU DOCK OUR PAY BY THE SAME AMOUNT!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you'd be stealing money only to have the same amount taken from your wages... Clearly that makes no sense.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps it's a case of losing the battle to win the war?</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">No no no! I'm not gonna stir up that hornets' nest! If I went stealin' from the company, I'd be finished!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It would seem there is no evidence to support the claims of thievery made against the victim. Because Mr William Shamspeare...is innocent. Pray, forgive me if that shatters some illusion my learned Nipponese friend was clearly under.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I certainly didn't expect to uncover another crime that looks like it's been taking place in the very same room...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">According to the testimony, it's only the meter in Mr Shamspeare's room that's under suspicion. It does seem as though perhaps it has nothing to do with the incident involving Mr Natsume...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know. It does seem that way. But the fact is... ...since I've been practising law in England, I feel like I've encountered this at least once already. Cases that are interlinked.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It might seem that two cases have nothing to do with one another at first. But in fact, they're intimately connected.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, we have experienced that before, haven't we? I wonder if this is another instance...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Perhaps... But we can't be sure of that yet. <thought>If the Altamont Gas Company has been investigating Mr Shamspeare so earnestly... ...there must be something to it. But then how has he been managing to steal their gas?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Let me just confirm something here... If the diameter and thickness were to be correct... ...the meter would accept any object as if it were a thruppenny bit. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Yes, that is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, by something of a coincidence, while we were investigating in Mr Shamspeare's room... ...we found a particular item that matches the dimensions perfectly.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Something the same size as a thruppenny bit?! What was it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The item in question...is this!</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Wha...? Have you been inhalin' gas? That's a bar of soap!</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">It certainly looks nothing like a thruppenny bit, I must say...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It looks like I'm going to have to point out exactly what I mean here.</thought> What's so important about the soap...is this part here!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It doesn't look as though this soap has been used much, does it? If at all.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, I agree. I'd say it's never been used. And yet it doesn't quite look new, either. It's lost its colour slightly, as soap does when it ages.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I wonder why Mr Shamspeare has apparently had it for so long, but not used it then... <thought>That could point to the answer here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's that funny little round depression in the middle of the soap...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, it's a perfect circle. And I would say almost three-quarters of an inch in diameter.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Rather like something else we've been talking about recently, in fact.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo, it's this part of the soap you need to show to the court!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">I'm lookin' closely...and it's still soap!</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">I'm not sure why you think it bears any resemblance to a coin at all. It's not the right size or shape, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! I think your finger must have slipped!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes! Let's say that! It, it is soap after all... My Lord, I believe I may have inadvertently misled the court. I request permission to try again!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, and wash your hands of that rather sorry answer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You have to turn over the soap to see what I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Ah! Are you referring to that round depression in the middle of the soap there?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right. A depression that's approximately three-quarters of an inch in diameter. Or in other words, almost exactly the same size as a thruppenny bit.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">GET AWAY!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Does anyone here present have in their possession a thruppenny bit? Quickly now! Hand over your coins, ladies and gentlemen!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It sounds rather like a highway robbery, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thanks to a kind member of the public in the gallery, I have here a thruppenny bit. Now, to see if it fits... ......... My word! It couldn't be more snug!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, as I suspected... This, without a doubt, is a vital clue to explain how the Altamont Gas Company is being defrauded!</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Well! I don't believe it!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">So...your assertion amounts to what? That some inferior bar of soap has a tentative connection to the theft of gas?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes! The depression in the soap was clearly made by a thruppenny bit.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I must concur at least, that pushing a coin with some force into a poor-quality bar of soap such as this... ...is a remarkably simple way of replicating the coin's shape.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">And then you could use...well, some melted wax or somethin' to pour into the mould... You could make fake coins in no time!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This brings all the pieces of the puzzle together. It's the method Mr Shamspeare has been using to steal the gas... That's the missing link! And now if I follow the chain of thought... ...it's going to bring me to a new explanation for what happened that nobody's considered yet!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Altamont">But...this is all nonsense! If the man had been making fake coins, my worker here would have found them when he emptied the meter!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Quite true, Lady Altamont. In the absence of some black magic that could make them disappear...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... I see. That's what we're dealing with, is it? There is one form of 'black magic' that could cause the fake coins to disappear into thin air, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Exactly. And the meter here gives it away.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">What on earth...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There are remnants of the 'magical' method used visible on the gas meter taken from the victim's room!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that is your assertion, Counsel, the defence will identify these remnants for the court at once! Where on the meter can the remnants of the method used to make the fake coins disappear be seen?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This...is quite...a tough...padlock...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Um...what are you doing, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh. I was just seeing if it was possible to force it open.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...If you break it, I'm afraid you'll be forced to pay a fine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh no! Whew, that was close then! Perhaps tell me a little sooner next time...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's this little hole in the bottom of the meter here, isn't there? And it looks as though it was made by somebody who didn't really have the right tools...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It does actually go all the way through to the inside. Though it's hard to see that unless you look closely. In fact...it goes right into the part of the meter where the money ends up!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm... I suppose it's nothing, then.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well you couldn't possibly extract a coin through such a small hole, could you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...No, I suppose not.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>But then the question remains: why would somebody go to the effort of making a hole here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It sounds like the gasman didn't find a single coin inside this meter.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But no one could survive a London winter without gas lamps...and certainly not without a gas stove.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How does it go? 'Out, out, brief candle...' or something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps it's the same kind of spell that Mr Shamspeare has been using to make the coins come 'out'?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Magic or not, there must be some trace of the method he used on this meter somewhere... <thought>We need to look over it very, very carefully...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...A rather vague answer, wouldn't you say, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What is highly suspicious, I would posit, is my learned Nipponese friend's panic-stricken expression.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I don't claim to know much of the backwater from whence you hail... ...but I hear that the Nipponese are wont to cut open their stomachs when they recognise their failings. Please...don't hold back on our account.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">UWAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I assume the Japanese, like the British, have but one stomach? Might I suggest no more failings, Counsel? Consider your response carefully before trying again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We found this bar of soap at the scene of the crime, just outside the victim's window.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Outside...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, outside, where you yourself, Mr Metermann, were loitering...in the freezing winter air. That's where we found this soap.</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">Ah! I get it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right. The answer, of course...is ice.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Did you say...ice?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Shamspeare has been leaving soaps like this outside his window each evening, filled with water. After a night outside in the bitter cold, the water is completely frozen solid the next morning.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Then he takes his fake coins of ice and feeds them into the gas meter, giving him light and warmth in spades. As his room becomes very comfortably warm, the ice now inside the meter's coin box...melts...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Turning back into water... ...and draining harmlessly away through the small hole made in the underside of the meter. That is how, without leaving any evidence of his wrongdoing, this man has been stealing Altamont gas!</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Just like that... So simply... Is, is he trying to make us look like idiots? He's been fooling us all with some bars of soap and some water?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right, madam.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">I don't believe it! It can't be true! Do you have any idea how much money we spent to develop that new meter? And now you have the audacity to suggest...that a bit of soap and some water can render it totally useless?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm fairly sure I didn't design it...</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">...Evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">I want evidence! If you're going to stand here and tell me our meters are rubbish, I want to see proof!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...She's very good at enforcing accountability, isn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Very well, Lady Altamont. If you'd like evidence, I'll provide it.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">What?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! Are, are you saying...you do actually have evidence to support this theory?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I did notice a trace of something that bothered me a little at the time. And I have a feeling that this theory we've come up with now could explain it.</thought> The piece of evidence that substantiates the theory about how Mr Shamspeare has been stealing gas is...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...yes... That was my plan, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! Your eyes are darting around like little fish!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Little fish, otherwise known as small fry. And small fry, I find, are quickly polished off!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Have I just been devoured by the prosecution...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">If Mr Shamspeare made coins out of ice... ...wouldn't there perhaps be some trace of that at the scene? In his room, I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>At the scene... Yes, that's true. Let me have another look through the Court Record...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is a photograph of the scene at the point when the victim was discovered, taken by Inspector Gregson. And it clearly shows the remnants of the crime carried out by Mr Shamspeare!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What remnants?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Here you can see the gas meter on the wall in Mr Shamspeare's room. Now...look closely at the floorboards directly underneath the meter.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">What, what is that? Some kind of grubby stain...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Almost certainly...it's a water stain resulting from the liquid that drained out of the hole made in the meter.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If one coin gives around two hours of gas usage, and the occupant was heating his room in all his waking hours... ...we can imagine he would have used around ten of his fake coins each day. The melting ice inside the meter's coin box would have been dripping out almost constantly... ...leaving a stain on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">This, this is awful...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And there's further evidence, too. Mr Shamspeare is slumped over the table, apparently having consumed strychnine. And right there next to him...is a bar of soap, broken in half.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">You're right...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would appear to me then, Counsel... ...that the man was eating the soap, was he?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Pardon me for disagreeing with Your Lordship, but... ...certainly not.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">He didn't beat about the bush there, did he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In truth... ...Mr Shamspeare was found with a fork in his hand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A meal of soap is sounding increasingly likely, Lord van Zieks...</line>
<line speaker="Metermann">D'you mean to say...? He was using the fork to...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. To extract a frozen coin from the bar of soap.</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But the bar broke in half... ...so perhaps it didn't go very well.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">L-Lord van Zieks!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I was throwing my hand up in despair... ...and happened to catch my hallowed bottle on the way. Pray, forgive my maladroit mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is the meaning of this, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Allow me to pose my learned friend a question: What exactly did you establish with your most recent cross-examination?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...well...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That Mr William Shamspeare is a liar and a thief. In other words...that his testimony is unreliable!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's it! That's exactly it!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Very well, let us assume the man is a liar. Now allow me to pose another question: What possible difference does that make?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">We know that suicide can be discounted. Scotland Yard's investigation revealed no sign of another vessel that contained poison.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And on the night in question, there were no visitors to the room except the accused. The young gasman's testimony, which we have no reason to doubt, has confirmed that.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">...!</line>
<line speaker="Altamont">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Furthermore...the only possible way the poison could have entered the victim's body is via the tea. The court has seen no evidence whatsoever that suggests otherwise.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Even if William Shamspeare is the liar you claim him to be... ...these facts have been objectively established. There's no escaping it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Therefore, in light of these facts... ...the prosecution calls for immediate adjudication!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Y-You......... WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Well, Counsel? How does the defence respond?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">M-Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What was the point of that last cross-examination? Did it actually get us anywhere? Or did it make no difference at all, like Lord van Zieks is saying?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Everything is up in the air at the moment. Perhaps I should just wait and see what happens next.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! This no time [sic] to sit back and watch how the trial unfolds! We have to make our own way forward!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">A fledgling idea will never flourish into a mature argument that's able to win over the jury... ...unless it's nurtured with some carefully chosen rhetoric.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Susato-san... I feel like your rhetoric is more carefully chosen than anyone's sometimes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...It seems your argument has run its course...to nowhere.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No! This isn't over! The defence will not rest!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But, Counsel, you've successfully explained everything! You've identified and substantiated the unscrupulous method employed by Mr Shamspeare to consume gas. What more is there to discuss?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord van Zieks just highlighted three 'facts' in order to make his point. But contrary to what he would have the court believe, not all of them have been objectively established at all!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What are you trying to say, my Nipponese friend?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">At least one of those so-called facts is an assumption, made due to a lack of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But the situation has changed now following the cross-examination of the latest witnesses to take the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Don't be absurd! What is this nonsense?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, when you bring everything we've learnt so far together and consider it as a whole, it's clear... There's a question that we now need to consider. Namely...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What if it was somebody else entirely who poisoned the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">If that's your assertion, by all means, tell us who it was.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, yes, um... Well...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well? Who was this mysterious third party, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I think it's a little too soon to be naming names, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">On the contrary... ...it's a little too late. Much like your defence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">GAAAAAAAAAH! <thought>But we've shown so much... The situation has changed, I'm sure of it. Mr Shamspeare was trying to make more ice coins on the night in question. I really feel like that's a clue here. That it's pointing us towards something else.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What if the victim did in fact have another visitor besides Mr Natsume?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">If that's your assertion, by all means, tell us who it was.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, yes, um... Well...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well? Who was this mysterious third party, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I think it's a little too soon to be naming names, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">On the contrary... ...it's a little too late. Much like your defence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">GAAAAAAAAAH! <thought>But we've shown so much... The situation has changed, I'm sure of it. Mr Shamspeare was trying to make more ice coins on the night in question. I really feel like that's a clue here. That it's pointing us towards something else.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We've all been led to believe that the strychnine poison that afflicted Mr Shamspeare... ...was in the tea brought to him by Mr Natsume. But that's conjecture at best.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As I said, the situation has changed. Because in fact...some of Mr Natsume's tea WAS left at the scene! And a particular piece of evidence proves it!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence has made a bold claim indeed. Very well, Counsel... Present your proof! What evidence from the scene of the crime can tell us about the nature of the defendant's tea?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...I suspect it may, possibly, be related to the tea in some small way...if we dig deep enough!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Then you will be digging for a very long time indeed, my learned friend.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Even at the bottom of the deepest chasm...you will find no sense in that absurd assertion!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">UWAAAAAAAAAGH! <thought>Ugh...sometimes I wish I could disappear down a deep chasm to escape his deep sarcasm.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then I advise you to think more deeply before you answer again this time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious! The soap again? The same bar the victim used to fashion his coins of ice?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's right, My Lord. It's just come back to me. Something about when we first found this bar of soap at the scene yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's...more bars of soap!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Soap? What are bars of soap doing lined up on a ledge outside the window?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm quite certain that when we originally stumbled upon the bars of soap... ...there was actually a frozen coin in each bar.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">So you discovered the gas thief's coin factory. Fascinating...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The soap is looking at me with one hollow, two-centimetre-wide eye...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">How poetic, Mr Naruhodo! All the literary references we've been hearing are starting to rub off, I think!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really, whoever would have thought of using this depression to make coins of ice?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was clearly one of those ice coins that was in the soap when we first found it, wasn't it? Although...it was a sort of reddish colour, I seem to remember...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In a way, yes. But there's more. The coins we found in the soap at the time weren't normal ice.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There, there was something strange about them, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Exactly. Something very obviously strange. They were red.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The ice...was red? No... You mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right. It's obvious to me now. The fake coins in the soap...were made from frozen tea!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I would remind the court of a statement made by Mr Natsume earlier in this trial...</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">That evening, yes...I did take some freshly brewed tea with me when I visited Mr Shamspeare's room, as a gift. The public water pump outside always freezes at night, so I bought bottled water especially to make it. And this is the result! Never will I touch tea again! Never!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah yes. I believe there had been a snowfall that day. It was particularly cold. Sadly on such occasions, the poorly constructed water mains in the East End are prone to freezing.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So on the night in question, Mr Shamspeare, having no running water to use... ...was forced to use the tea brought by Mr Natsume in order to make his fake coins!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">My word!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There were two bars of soap on the window ledge when my judicial assistant and I investigated the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's right. And we only borrowed one of them.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Which means...that even as we speak, some of the defendant's tea is still present at the scene of the crime... ...frozen solid in a bar of soap outside Mr Shamspeare's window!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Extraordinary!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Earlier today, Inspector Gregson informed the court... ...that if even one drop of the tea remained, Scotland Yard would be able to analyse it for poison. As such, we are now in a position to prove or disprove what has until now been mere conjecture... ...by finding out for sure whether or not Mr Natsume's tea actually contained strychnine at all!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Argh! You...smug Nipponese...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My Lord, we cannot do the defendant the injustice of passing judgement now! The police should be dispatched to recover the remaining bar of soap from the scene at once! And the defence requests a thorough analysis of the frozen tea embedded in it... ...to determine whether or not it contains any poison!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Bailiff! Instruct the police to attend the scene at once!</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Yes, My Lord! Understood!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would seem we have no choice but to suspend these proceedings for the time being. I trust you have no objection, Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">None, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Scotland Yard will recover the tea from the scene and carry out the requisite tests immediately. The trial will resume at the same hour tomorrow. The prosecution and defence may conduct further investigations as appropriate in the interim.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well... ...we managed to scrape through there somehow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, Counsels. Court is adjourned until tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't find anything out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That last statement was contradictory in a number of ways, I think you'll find!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In a number of ways, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right, My Lord. In a number of ways!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps it would serve you well to concentrate your efforts on one contradiction at a time, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... I made a bit of a mess of that. In a number of ways, actually.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The witness's last statement is clearly contradictory when you consider this piece of evidence here! Yes! Undeniably!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You say it's undeniable, Counsel, but I fail to see any contradiction here at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I think perhaps that itself is the contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... Time for a rethink...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My Lord! There are clearly grounds for being suspicious of that last statement!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sorry, Counsel, but I fail to see why.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, you know...I was just playing devil's advocate!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Yes. You do appear to have something of the devil in you, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Says the man merrily dishing out penalties...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Those two statements are fundamentally at odds with one another.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">My Lord! As foreman of the jury, I must object!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Being their leader, it's my duty to stand up for all jurors here present. And stand up for them I will!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I concur with the foreman. Counsel, I warn you, I shan't abide any pettifoggery!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Until you've got your facts straight...keep your pointy fingers to yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I thought I did...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We're trying to find inconsistencies in these jurors' statements, Mr Naruhodo. The key to it is comparing the different things they say before attempting to pit them against one another.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Alright. I'll have another go!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, Counsel, that will do! I've seen enough. According to the powers vested in me by Her Majesty the Queen, I declare no further examination necessary. I believe the court has been presented with more than enough evidence to pass judgement. As such, I shall be requesting the final decisions of the members of the jury. Are you all ready, Mr Foreman?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">We're all ready, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very good. Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, you will announce your findings to the court in turn, please.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr Soseki Natsume, in accordance with the findings of this court, I pronounce you...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I applaud the jurors for doing their civic duty and for finding a swift resolution to this matter. That is all. Court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>