<xml>
<title>The Return of the Great Departed Soul</title>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! So you have scale balances in Japan too, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well yes, but nothing like the Old Bailey's huge example.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">The thing about those scales is, they're only ever in balance right at the start of a trial, aren't they? Otherwise they always seem to be hanging one way or another...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'd noticed that exact same thing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ooh, is this Japanese kanji script embroidered here?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right. The name of the armband's owner.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah! So that's how you write 'Naruhodo' is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Actually, no. It's my best friend's name, not mine. It's pronounced 'Kazuma Asogi'. I actually believe this armband in some way embodies his spirit, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hm... So you have to write all those lines just for one person's name? Kanji is funny, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's right. Never mind my feelings about my best friend. It's lines I really want to talk about...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...Runo! Runo, are you listening?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Sorry, um...what was that, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hmph. What's the matter with you? You've been miles away all morning. Didn't you like what I cooked for breakfast?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no, that's not it at all. Um...what were we talking about again?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Today's paper! It's full of news about the Great Exhibition again!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah yes...the Great Exhibition... I'd like to go sometime. .........</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You're really not your usual self today. You seem very down. Don't you agree, Hurley?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm...? Did you say something? Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh gosh! You're even more down!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... UWAAAAAAAAAGH!!! Wh-When did you arrive, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I've...been here for about half an hour already. We had breakfast together.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What?! Why didn't you mention it before?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, um...thought you might have known I was here. You know, because...breakfast?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm, Iris is quite right. You're clearly lacking in vim. So much so that I didn't notice your presence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Thanks.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Of course, I could deduce the reason perfectly well with some simple observations.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Let's see... Yes, for example, your tussled hair this morning, with all its unruly spikes. Clearly it can be deduced therefore, that-</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, let me stop you there, Mr Sholmes, because I think I can see where this is going. My hair always looks like this. It always has. Ever since we first met, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Oh really? How interesting. It just doesn't look like a haircut as such, I suppose. Ah ha ha ha ha hah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Thanks again.</thought> ......... It crossed my mind recently...that it's been six months now.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Six months?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Since I was forbidden from working in court. So I've been wondering how much longer I'm going to be banned.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh... Well, that would explain why you seem rather glum. Don't you agree, Hurley?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm...? Did you say something? Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ah...back to moping...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's the matter with Mr Sholmes today? He seems even more down in the dumps than me.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I know! And the Great Exhibition has opened! You'd think he'd be excited. Oh, why don't we all go to see it together?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I want to! Of course I do! But I can't! ...Not for the time being.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Why not? Why not?! Because! I'm a great detective, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So you're embroiled in some tricky case that you can't be distracted from? Is that it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">I don't remember hearing that you're working on a case, Hurley.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I suppose I should try to find out what's going on.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Every time I look at that machine, I can't help thinking what a monstrosity it is. What's it called again?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">The Great Analytiscope! It can analyse absolutely anything, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It does seem incredible. ...And at the same time, incredibly useless.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah, but it looks impressive, doesn't it? So that makes it very useful.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How does that make it useful?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Because! It means you can pawn it for lots of money! The pawnbrokers always make idle remarks like 'What an incredible-looking machine...'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">So Hurley often takes it to the pawn shop when he's a little short.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It sounds like this thing pulls its weight around here more than I realized...by having its weight pulled around.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Books, papers, scientific implements... These shelves are stuffed to the gunnels. Miss Susato wouldn't be able to help herself if she were here. She can't stand mess.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Susie might not be able to stand mess, but she wouldn't dare touch those shelves.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh? Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Everything's in intricate balance. Hurley spends ages on it. If you were to touch even one thing, the whole lot would come tumbling down.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Susie noticed it was a very delicate arrangement right from the outset.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You make it sound like a meeting of great minds. But the truth is, Mr Sholmes just needs to tidy up.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah yes, Mr Sholmes's faithful musical companion. Wasn't this violin made by somebody famous?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, it's a Stradivarius. I'm afraid you'd have to save up for a hundred years before you could afford one, Runo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If I were to save up for a hundred years, I wouldn't choose to buy a violin, personally.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh? What would you buy then?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I really have no idea. I think I'll have to do it so I can find out...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I do love a good fire in the colder months. Watching the flames flickering and dancing about is just so very relaxing.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Cleaning out the chimney isn't so relaxing, though.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No. Getting covered in soot isn't my idea of fun.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You know, Hurley decided he was going to clean it out himself last year. But you can guess what happened, can't you? He got himself stuck inside the flue.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He's a very slim man, I admit, but there are limits to where a fully grown man can fit.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah yes, the huge metal chest with the lace cloth laid on it, being used as a table for tea and coffee. It's very sturdy, that's for sure. And firmly locked shut.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That chest contains my father's detailed records of Hurley's many cases!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, so I've been led to believe. Though personally, I've never actually seen inside.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And that's the way it will stay! Those papers are a secret between Daddy and me. If you go opening it uninvited, you might find yourself being bitten!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What, is there a beast inside there, or something?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, all these different pieces of evidence from cases that Mr Sholmes has solved are very interesting...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">The trouble is, Hurley forgets things so quickly. He never remembers why these things are relevant. The other day, for example, he saw the orange pips that were there and decided to plant them in the garden.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Pips?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes. They've all sprouted now. We have five new little plants.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, well I don't know what case they were from, but... ...if Mr Sholmes can get oranges to grow outside in England, he should change his profession!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I look forward to finding out what aroma your tea will have, Iris. Every single day.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah, well, I infuse a different concoction of herbs from the garden every time, so it's never the same twice.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When you call it a 'concoction' it sounds more like a science experiment than something for teatime.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh yes! That's because different blends can have very different properties! Some calm you down, some make you feel jolly, some give you energy... Today's particular blend is something quite special, so you're really in for a treat!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That sounds...ominous...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah yes, this is where you note down ideas, isn't it, Iris? What's in the melting pot today? Hm, 'The Blue Carbuncle'...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, it's from a case of theft that Hurley solved ages ago. The theft of a precious stone. A carbuncle is another name for a garnet, you see. Especially if it's cut with a rounded top.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, really? And this garnet was blue, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, that's the thing... They're usually red. No blue garnets have ever been discovered.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">So who knows what the stolen gemstone actually was. That's the real mystery of the case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...A proper Herlock Sholmes conundrum, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>There are so many different bottles up there on that charming little set of white shelves.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! Do be careful, Runo! You mustn't try the contents of any of those bottles, even if you're hungry!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I wouldn't do something stupid like that! I'm not a child, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, I wish I could say the same for Hurley. The other day, he polished off a full bottle of one of my alkaloids.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He what?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">He said he was hungry.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'll...be extra careful.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I can type with my eyes shut, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can believe it. When a deadline's approaching, you sound like a Gatling gun!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That reminds me of a dream I had the other day. It was such a funny one! It woke me, actually. I was typing for a whole hour in the pitch-black, but I didn't make a single mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's incredible!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But then, when it got light...I found that there wasn't any paper in the machine. Now I wonder if I'd actually been typing at all...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I think you might just have fallen asleep on the job.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Half a year ago now... ...I took on the defence of a young girl in a trial heard at the Old Bailey. What at first seemed like a simple case of murder that took place at a London pawnbrokery... ...turned out to be one part of a much more far-reaching plot that involved the British government. During the course of the trial... ...it was found that I made an unavoidable, yet at the same time, unforgivable mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Words fail me. This situation is...utterly deplorable. Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I will decide upon your fate following the conclusion of this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of course, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In the end, I had my right to represent people in court revoked. I was told I had to spend my time in research and study, so that's what I've been doing.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You have, haven't you, Runo? Reading all those big, fat tomes about British law up in your room. And the notes about Sholmes's old cases.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Brewing Iris's special blends of tea... Fetching my daily bread for me... You've become something of a manservant around here. Start on the silverware next, Master Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...I'm thinking of going to ask the powers that be to reconsider. Specifically Lord Stronghart, at the British Supreme Court on Whitehall.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Lord Stronghart?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, the delightful Lord Chief Justice? ...Not my favourite fellow.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He's not mine, either. But he's the man I have to talk to. He's the only one who can grant permission for me to start working in the courts again. <thought>I came to Britain to become the best lawyer I could. And I can't do that just sitting around here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The whole of London has been swept up in this Great Exhibition, hasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The most advanced science, the most modern technology, the finest works of art and feats of engineering... For the next six months, our capital will be showcasing these things, and the world will be watching!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, do you know what I'd like to do? I'd like to look down on London from one of those lovely balloons!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">L-Look down on...? Do, do you mean those things... ...fly?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, of course! They fly high in the sky and don't even need wings to do it! All you need is hot air!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But how?! How does hot air have anything to do with flying?! It makes no sense! I can't understand it at all...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's true of a lot of new scientific discoveries. Most people can't understand them at first. But in a hundred years' time, all these things will just be common knowledge.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I...suppose they might be.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Mind you, some of the science being demonstrated seems very questionable. Something went wrong on the open experimentation stage yesterday, apparently. There was a huge explosion. Still, I wish I'd seen it, though! I'd love to see how bad some of these scam experiments really are!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Says the innocent ten-year-old girl...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">See here. Every page of this paper carries some article or other about the Great Exhibition. But the brighter things shine, the darker the shadows that are cast behind them. Personally, I find myself drawn to the darkness. To the impenetrable. That is my proper atmosphere.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>'Shadows cast behind'...? Is that a metaphorical way of referring to the back page of the paper?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The whole of London has been swept up in this Great Exhibition, hasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The most advanced science, the most modern technology, the finest works of art and feats of engineering... For the next six months, our capital will be showcasing these things, and the world will be watching!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, do you know what I'd like to do? I'd like to look down on London from one of those lovely balloons!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">L-Look down on...? Do, do you mean those things... ...fly?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, of course! They fly high in the sky and don't even need wings to do it! All you need is hot air!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But how?! How does hot air have anything to do with flying?! It makes no sense! I can't understand it at all...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's true of a lot of new scientific discoveries. Most people can't understand them at first. But in a hundred years' time, all these things will just be common knowledge.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I...suppose they might be.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Mind you, some of the science being demonstrated seems very questionable. Something went wrong on the open experimentation stage yesterday, apparently. There was a huge explosion. Still, I wish I'd seen it, though! I'd love to see how bad some of these scam experiments really are!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Says the innocent ten-year-old girl...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">See here. Every page of this paper carries some article or other about the Great Exhibition. But the brighter things shine, the darker the shadows that are cast behind them. Personally, I find myself drawn to the darkness. To the impenetrable. That is my proper atmosphere.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>'Shadows cast behind'...? Is that a metaphorical way of referring to the back page of the paper?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Are you investigating a particularly tricky case at the moment, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm, you could say that, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Nothing more to add? That's not like you...</thought> What sort of case is it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Shh! Quiet, Mr Naruhodo! We must not discuss it here. You never know who might be listening.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You're acting very strangely, Hurley.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well usually... ...the more mysterious and complicated a case is, the better Hurley's mood.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Is it really a case that's bothering you?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Iris, please! You mustn't exercise your astute powers of observation and deduction on me without invitation! Remember what I always say: put yourself in the shoes of the individual about whom you're making deductions!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You say that, do you? You...Mr Sholmes...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Never mind. Once I've had a cup of tea, I must make my way at once to the crime scene. Haaaaaah...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That was a deep sigh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It says in the paper that Lord van Zieks was attacked! That's terrible!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You know the legend of the Reaper of the Bailey of course, don't you? Only too well, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. <thought>Prosecutor Barok van Zieks...</thought> They say that if the Reaper is the prosecutor in a case, there's no salvation for whoever's in the dock... ...even if the defendant is found not guilty. Once the Reaper has someone in his sights...one way or another, that person's time left on this earth will be short.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">London's finest rogues always find ways around the law. They'll stop at nothing to secure an acquittal at trial. Falsifying evidence, paying sham witnesses, threatening jurors, bribing judges. But even such devious tactics as these cannot save them from the hand of the Reaper. As you've experienced yourself, haven't you, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes. I've seen the Reaper's 'retribution' at work.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Many of these criminal rogues are reckless and quite unafraid to die. If a leader among their fraternity is seen to have been 'taken' by the Reaper, retaliation like this does occur. Really, the capital has a never-ending supply of such scoundrels.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So... Do you mean... ...Lord van Zieks has been attacked like this before? This isn't the first time?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">He's quite an accomplished combatant, you know. He doesn't take these attacks lying down. Although...it seems that his assailants were armed with guns this time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh my goodness! Is, is he alright, then? Is Lord van Zieks hurt?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow...how on earth would I know?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, in the article here it says: 'As to what of Lord van Zieks and his condition? All will be revealed in tomorrow's morning edition!'</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, I see. Well, we shall have to be patient then.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no no! I can't wait until tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In that case, you shall have to enquire with somebody in the know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...who? <thought>Lord Stronghart...perhaps?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, um, Mr Sholmes, about this...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Shh! Not another word! ...Ah, yes, I see... This would be a collar...for a breed of miniature canine with a particularly long neck. And for winter use!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Actually...it's the armband I always wear that symbolises my role as a defence lawyer...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Precisely! Which leads us to but one conclusion: Your arm is in fact the particularly long neck of a miniature canine!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'm starting to wish I'd never shown him this now. The man's barking mad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Mr Sholmes, about this...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow, without wishing to sound rude... ...I'm currently in the middle of a very important blink. Perhaps some other, more convenient time, hm?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Is there a set time for your 'important' blinks, or are they an all-day affair? Just so I know...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Every article on the front page is news about the Great Exhibition. Public experiments to demonstrate brand-new scientific ideas, cultural exhibits from around the globe... It's all so positive and hopeful about the coming century. We must all go to see it properly before too long.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So many glowing reports about the Great Exhibition and everything that's going on there. Other than this rather gloomy-looking one, that is.</thought> ......... Wait, what...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">What's the matter, Runo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'The Reaper Attacked'... That's, that's Lord van Zieks! This must be what Mr Sholmes was talking about. <thought>Does he know any more, I wonder...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'The Reaper Attacked'... It's the kingpins of the criminal underworld generally managing to escape conviction in the Reaper's trials. And this isn't the first time their henchmen have tried to attack Lord van Zieks as a result, by the sound of it. ...It makes you think. If that's how the justice system works in London... ...then there must be dark forces at work.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, understood. See you later, Mr Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hah! You really are a shameless liar sometimes, my dear fellow!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You seek to put me off my guard and follow me, don't you? Well, you would be wasting your time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The thought hadn't crossed my mind! <thought>But now I'm wondering where you're going...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah ha ha ha hah! Well then, 'see you later' indeed!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Listen to him. He's still laughing on his way out of the door...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Alright then, Runo! Let's get going!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Um, Iris... What are you wearing?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I've got changed to go to the Great Exhibition. You're going to take me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? But, but I was just about to go to the Supreme Court...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! Well that sounds fun, too! You're going to take me there, then!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright, fine. Just...lower that weapon, would you?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Of course! And after the Supreme Court, then we'll go to see the Great Exhibition!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The office spade... Now that Susato-san's gone, the shovellers aren't represented to correct me. ......... Maybe I'll have to do it myself. 'That's not a spade, Mr Naruhodo; it's a shovel!'</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah, so you're a spader, are you, Runo? What, you want to battle it out?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Alright, I'm not going to argue with a native English speaker...who has some kind of gun...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Susato's tea set that she left here with me. I still think green tea is just too bitter, though. Thank goodness for sugar and milk! Mr Sholmes certainly wasn't expecting the acrid taste that one time. I've never heard anyone let out a scream like that before. Or seen anyone fall down the stairs quite like that either. ...It always bring a smile to my lips when I'm feeling a little down.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah well, do you know what that reminds me of? The day I gave you some black coffee when you weren't expecting it. You fell all the way down the stairs as well, didn't you, Runo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes, do you think we could try to forget that, please, Iris? That doesn't bring a smile to my lips at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The kettle's gently simmering away there on top of the stove as usual. It was kind of Miss Susato to send that Japanese tea. You really like it, don't you, Iris? But for me, it's the sound of the stove and burbling kettle I like the most. On biting winter mornings.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">'And it feels even cosier in here when the delightful Iris pours the tea for me. I really couldn't manage without that wonderful young girl.' Oh, Runo! It's so sweet of you to say so!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Stop putting words in my mouth, please, Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Now at first glance, my desk here might look as though it's in a mess. However... ...it's not in a mess at all. Everything is exactly where I want it to be. But whenever Miss Susato looked at it, she'd put her hands on her hips and say, 'Oh dear.' Her way of saying that I should make it a more orderly and neat mess. ...I miss that.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You sound just like Hurley, you know. He says the same about his mess.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It's the kind of logic that transcends international borders, obviously...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah yes, the daruma doll I brought with me from Japan. I always intended to colour in the other eye once I'd become a fully-fledged lawyer. But it's still winking at me. Like it's trying to say, 'I can wait. Take as long as you need.' ...Or maybe not. I'll just have to keep on doing the best I can, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I could colour it in for you, Runo! Just that one eye, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no! It needs to be done with a bit of ceremony, Iris! It's not just a toy for colouring in, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The photograph of us all together that day... It makes me a little sad to look at it now, which is why I'd taken to lying it flat. But Mr Sholmes righted it every single time. And I've grown accustomed to it. ...I hope we'll all be together again like that one day soon.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I never did see what Miss Susato's room looks like. I could go in now, of course. But I don't dare. They say a young maiden's private chamber is a place of bitter-sweet secrets. Although from the laughter I used to hear when you would visit, I imagine it's mainly sweet.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, we used to have such fun in Susie's room! She told me all sorts of interesting things about your country, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at the prawns and the anemones gently swaying around in the tank. Regular cleaning, some food and fresh seawater is all they need. And some conversation, of course. It seemed like a lot of effort at first, but it was worth it. I'm starting to be able to tell what they're thinking. Funny to think that so many people in London had aquariums like this once. When they were in vogue. You'd never expect to find sea anemones in the middle of the capital! I think I'll have to name them soon...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh no! Runo's disappeared!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah...I expect he's been eaten by Hurley...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I think I'd prefer it if you used your imagination more when naming the sea life...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's...Miss Susato's desk... I suppose it won't get used now that she's gone back to Japan. It'll just have to wait here patiently for its old friend to return...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Even now, I sometimes find myself pouring a cup of tea for Susie by mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, that explains why I sometimes find a steaming cup on her desk here. It shocks me every time. But it's just one of your pranks, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It's no prank! I miss her!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I'm so excited about the prospect of Naruhodo's Anything Consultancy opening for business again!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's not what it's called. It's Naruhodo's Legal Consultancy. <thought>I've done a lot of studying in these past six months. Reading law texts and judicial precedents... I'm sure I'm a better lawyer now... I can't wait to start practising again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Nothing's changed in here at all though, has it? It's as though time has stood still in here since Susie went back to Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I wanted to keep it ready for Miss Susato, in case she was able to return to Britain at any point. So I've just left everything the way it was.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, I see. Right... And there was me thinking it's because of the way you are, Runo. You know, never bothering to tidy up, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Iris... ...this isn't the time or the place to bring up my tidiness... or lack of it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Iris, have a quick look at this...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Your lawyer's armband? How many times have you shown me that, Runo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh. Sorry. It's very important to me, that's all. I don't feel complete somehow if I'm not wearing it.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well personally, I think you should try wrapping some different things around your arm from time to time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh really? Like what?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">......... Perhaps a pretzel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Pret-zel'...? I've never heard that word before.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Um...well I think it's a kind of German defence lawyer's symbol.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Interesting... I'll have to try wearing one sometime...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Iris, about this paper...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh yes! It's all about the Great Exhibition! I'm so excited about it! Once you've done what you need to do, we should all go together and explore!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't know... It sounds like it could be quite dangerous. We wouldn't want to get caught in an explosion as we were walking around in the showground.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh...is that what you think's going to happen, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's been about six months now since I was last here. But some things never change. Like the sense of foreboding I always seem to feel in this place. <thought>It doesn't seem to be bothering Iris at all, though. She's happily reading over there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, I love this place! I always find so many interesting books here!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of course. I was forgetting that you've been here before. <thought>The time we came here six months ago... ...when Susato-san was given the news that she was to return to Japan.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Ah. I understand you wish to speak with me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! L-Lord Stronghart! I trust you've been k-keeping well?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Let's see... Since you've arrived and requested an audience, it's been four hours, thirty-two minutes and... ...twenty-six seconds. I've kept you waiting a while. My apologies.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh no, not at all! I like nothing more than standing around, staring into space.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...Good to know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Good to know that doesn't appear to bother him at all.</thought> Mael Stronghart, Lord Chief Justice of London. He's the man who allowed me to start practising as a defence lawyer when I arrived in Britain as a student. You need only savour the air for a moment in this grand office to understand his pre-eminent status.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">As you will be aware, the Great Exhibition of London is now underway at last. We're extremely busy as a result. Policing the grounds, guarding the new technologies, dealing with petty crime... And furthermore, as of next month, we shall open the International Forensic Science Symposium.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...I've not heard about that.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Investigating authorities from forty countries around the globe will be taking part. Including from your own land. Forensic science is the future! The world must embrace it! As we're the hosting nation, I have much to do. And it is my highest priority. If others must wait for my attention as a result, so be it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Well, it's nice to know where I stand.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">So...you wish to consult with me? Of course, I can very well imagine what this is about.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...well, um... Thank you for agreeing to this meeting, My Lord! <thought>I want to be allowed to start working as a defence lawyer again in court. That's what brought me here today. But actually, there's something else playing on my mind, as it happens...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Runo, just take a deep breath and come out with it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You couldn't read all these books even if you were reincarnated three times over! As a bookworm!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, I know! So much reading material! I'm very envious. I've really been running out of things to read recently.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's because you read so fast!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Perhaps little by little I could swap some of the books here with some of mine from home.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't see why not. No one would notice. Or at least, I wouldn't. Even if I was reincarnated three times over as a librarian.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! I've just had a great idea!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">We could hide inside these suits of armour and spy on the fob watch master to find out what he's really like!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't have much interest in what Lord Stronghart is 'really like', though.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, please! It would be fun! You could be inside the left one, and I'll go in the right!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You really want to have a go in a suit of armour, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hmph! Now you're making fun of me because I'm a child, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I wasn't making fun of you at all. I'd like to have a go, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The cogs of the giant clock are keeping time as usual with their steady, rhythmical motion... It's really quite disturbing how little sound they make considering their massive size.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Someone very brilliant must have designed it. And whoever maintains it must be very talented, too. But I'm not entirely convinced it's even a clock.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! But what about the huge clockface that forms the window over there?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Some people just make machines that move for the fun of it. Because they enjoy watching them. Rather like how Hurley makes his rambling deductions just for the fun of it. Even if the outcome isn't quite right.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Never mind all the trouble it gets others into along the way...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The Lord Chief Justice's desk. When you look at that, there's no mistaking Lord Stronghart's authority, is there?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But the light from that window behind is far too bright. It would be very bad for the eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I hadn't thought of that. There are no curtains, that's for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">What's more important, having a desk with an air of authority, or having eyes that work?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I can't say I'd ever considered it. <thought>After all, my little office barely has any light to speak of... and I haven't really seen my desk in a while.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I actually came here today to ask for your permission.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...Go on.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Six months ago, my right to work in court as a lawyer was revoked and I was told to spend my time studying. Obviously, I'm very sorry for what happened. But the thing is... ...it made me understand what it really means to defend somebody under the rules of a foreign justice system. And I desperately want to have another go. Please! Permit me to enter the courtroom again!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">......... Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Y-Yes? <thought>Ugh...here it comes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I'm sure you haven't forgotten your position here, have you? At best, you are a substitute for your compatriot. This was never your intended role.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>Well, that's true. The Japanese government actually sent my best friend on this study tour, not me. It should have been Kazuma. He was so determined to bring change to our own justice system at home. That was his calling. If that tragic accident hadn't happened... ...I wouldn't be here in this office now.</thought> Mr Asogi was my best friend, you see. That's why I can't leave it unfinished. I have to fulfil his calling for him.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Hm, his 'calling', you say... Has it never occurred to you... ...that perhaps you know nothing of his true calling?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">The mission with which that young law student was charged. What do you suppose it really was?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wh-What do you mean? <thought>'Mission'? He's not making any sense.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">......... Never mind. I've read all the reports you've submitted over the past six months. It's clear to me that you regret your actions, and have been studiously obeying your revised instructions.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do, do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">As of this moment, I reinstate your licence to practise law here in Great Britain!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you! Thank you so much!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's wonderful news, Runo!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">In fact, I believe I have the perfect case to mark your comeback. A curious affair. You'll consider it, I hope?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! Of course! Please, tell me more!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You described it as 'a curious affair'...?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Yes, that's right. I believe it was reported in the press. Are you aware that there was a serious accident at the Great Exhibition yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh. No.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes! I read about it. A professor from Germany tried to carry out a crazy experiment. Let me see...how was it described...? 'Super-high-voltage instantaneous kinesis' I think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Instantaneous kinesis? As in...moving things with a click of the fingers?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's right... It's just what my herbal blends need: a dash of devil-may-care!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Whatever this serious accident was exactly, it's clearly captured Iris's imagination.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">It's an unfortunate business. A large explosion engulfed the public experimentation stage and a man lost his life. A certain Mr Odie Asman. An investor and a well known figure in society.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A large explosion...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">A, a man died?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">The man responsible for the experiment was Professor Albert Harebrayne. He was detained immediately after the incident, and is due to appear in court tomorrow. On the charge of murder.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! Murder?!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">If you intend to take on his defence, you should hurry to meet with him at the prison. There is very little time left for you to carry out any kind of investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The Great Exhibition... A scientific experiment gone wrong... And...murder...? I feel out of my depth before I've even started. Still...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">We should go to the prison straight away then, and try to meet with this German professor...don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Definitely!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Ah yes...one more thing about the case... There's a connection with our mutual acquaintance...the Reaper.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! <thought>With Lord van Zieks? How?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">All sorts of conferences have been taking place around the world to coincide with the Great Exhibition. And next month, the largest and most important of them all will take place at last: The International Forensic Science Symposium.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It does seem as though criminal investigation needs to embrace scientific methods, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Exactly!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">London - the global epicentre of culture, science and wealth - now has a population exceeding six million. Sadly, crime in the capital is growing at a similarly startling rate. So it's imperative that we use the latest scientific methods to investigate and resolve cases as efficiently as possible.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Which is what's known as 'forensic science', isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Exactly! The future of policing!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Regrettably however... ...Britain is currently dragging its feet when it comes to the adoption of forensic methods.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh dear. That's alarming.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Exactly! It's extremely alarming!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">If I were Her Majesty's Attorney General, you can be sure... ...the numbers of crimes committed and resolved in London would be very different to the current figures. And I can cite twelve solid arguments and two hundred and twenty-three individual reasons to support my claim!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">By way of apology for keeping you waiting earlier, I shall detail every one now!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, how fascinating!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">It all began fifteen years ago. I was..........................................................................................</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">............................................................</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Um, right...yes... That's...wonderful!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...Exactly. Wonderful is precisely what it will be.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Iris isn't paying attention at all. She's got her nose in another book now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, is it over? Did you learn anything useful?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I actually drifted off for the most part. <thought>He's surprisingly ardent about forensic science...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Fortunately, Lord van Zieks emerged from the attack unscathed. Street ruffians are no match for that man. He's a very capable fighter.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but that's incredible! They were armed with guns! Why was he attacked, though? Do we know?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">......... It's related to events that occurred a month ago. A leader of one of the capital's criminal organisations was indicted and prosecuted...by van Zieks. But the man was acquitted. I've no doubt large sums of money were involved behind the scenes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Large sums of money?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">A deplorable situation. Members of the jury were bribed, it seems. However...despite winning his freedom... ...the man in question met a dramatic end yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but you're not suggesting that was the work of the Reaper, surely?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">The victim's henchmen certainly seem to think so. He was a man by the name of Asman. Mr Odie Asman.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Did...did you say Asman?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's the man who died in the big explosion at the Great Exhibition!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Yes. Known publicly as an investor, but in reality...the head of a significant criminal organisation.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Unbelievable...</thought> ...I wonder, could I ask you something, Lord Stronghart?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Try me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why do you use Lord van Zieks as a prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">All the criminals who manage to get off in court then meet with mysterious ends outside the courtroom. And fearful of that fate, they seek to strike at Lord van Zieks first. I know there's no evidence that he actually is the Reaper in that sense, but still... Something's clearly going on here!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I have van Zieks work for the prosecution service for two reasons: Firstly, the man is the best prosecutor in the capital, bar none. And secondly... ...any deaths of criminals that have occurred outside the courtroom following his trials...are nothing to do with him.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But that doesn't make sense! How can you explain the way so many have died if not by someone's hand?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Van Zieks may have earnt himself the moniker of the Reaper, but he is no killer. So he will continue to prosecute on behalf of the Crown. ...Unless he wishes otherwise, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">By the way, Lord Stronghart, about this...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">The symbol of a defence lawyer in the Japanese judiciary.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! I, I didn't expect you'd know that.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">We never accept foreign students before first researching the legal systems of their home countries. ...But such trinkets are merely for show. The only true measure of your worth is your performance in court.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. Right...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! That reminds me! Have you seen this?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">The reports of the overwhelming success of the Great Exhibition? Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no, not that. The story on the back page.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">What story...? 'The Reaper Attacked'... Ah, that. You've enjoyed some victories in court against my number one prosecutor, have you not?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Poor Mr Reaper... What happened to him? He, he wasn't killed, was he?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">There's no need for concern. Lord van Zieks would not be so easily dispatched, I assure you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Can you tell us what happened? I'd really love to know!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...Very well. If it interests you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It does...strangely.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">E-Eleven hours late? That's...quite something.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">That meeting had already started when I arrived back here for this engagement with you. So lateness was inevitable. Time stops for no man.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'm sure it stopped for me during those twelve solid arguments and two hundred and twenty-three reasons...</thought> Oh, yes! Where would I find Lord van Zieks now?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I would assume he's at his office.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Right, I'll go and ask him about the attack in person. I want to get this straight from the horse's mouth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Away with you now. I'm leaving Professor Harebrayne's defence entirely in your hands.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of, of course, yes! Thank you very much, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ooh! So this is the legendary Reaper's office?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, it appears so.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Brrr, it sends a chill down your spine, doesn't it? What an amazingly deathly atmosphere!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Oh, is that...? <thought>That hooded figure was so still, I hadn't noticed his or her presence. I wonder who it is...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He's as unwelcoming as I thought he'd be. Actually, maybe even more so...</thought> Oh, I, um... I'm glad to see you're well.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...I am.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... So...who's the person over by the wall being...punished for something or other?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">No punishment is taking place here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">That's my apprentice. And he's sitting there of his own free will.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I didn't know you had an apprentice. <thought>It must be the same person who was pictured in the newspaper...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">He's very able in combat. ...A requisite skill for anyone under my tutelage.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Are you referring to the attack on the Reaper that was reported in the papers?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The Reaper? I'd be interested to know the Reaper's true identity myself. Assuming, that is, such a fabled fiend genuinely inhabits our great courtrooms...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at that fine collection of hallowed chalices and bottles neatly lined up there...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">My hallowed bottles are filled with the essence of the finest grapes from the finest vineyards I visit. And I personally oversee these chalices being made by the finest crystal craftsmen in the world.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And yet you throw them around in court like they were worthless.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yes...because this imbecile is so unimaginably and repeatedly wide of the mark sometimes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Before you open your mouth next time, you should consider the poor artisans whose work you defile.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...it's my fault? ...Silly me. How could I ever have thought otherwise?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord van Zieks's desk, look. It's so stylish.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And that's a marble chess set beside it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Chess... That's the Western version of our Japanese 'shogi' game, isn't it? You know, I'm actually quite good at shogi problems.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, really? You'd probably like chess problems, in that case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'd love to challenge Lord van Zieks sometime. To a bout of shogi problems.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">If you only really want to challenge yourself, you can always do that on your own at home.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That portrait really dominates the room, doesn't it? It's a very majestic outfit and pose. But sadly... ...whoever painted it didn't do a very good job of capturing Lord van Zieks's facial features.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, you're right. I mean, it's not far off, but the artist has exaggerated his subject's handsomeness, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! That reminds me... I heard Emperor Napoleon of France ordered artists to make him look more attractive when they painted him.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">How vain. That's really not an attractive quality in a person, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">That portrait does not depict me. Surely that's immediately obvious!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Then...who is it?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ooh, look! It's a scale model of the Great Exhibition showground!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's amazing. I wonder why it's here...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Perhaps he made it to take his mind off the sadness of being too busy to attend in person?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Or perhaps he's too embarrassed to queue up for a ticket.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Surely it's obvious that I'm using it as an investigative aid!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">You Nipponese have no business painting others as overly reserved.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... I really didn't think he'd overhear that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wah! They were bats!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes. The Reaper's familiars, I expect.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But what about the mute man in the dark cloak? I thought he was the familiar. Just not the flying kind.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">He must be a dear friend of Mr Reaper, then.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I think the familiar idea is more likely. <thought>Scary though, either way.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It really looks like a punishment to me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">I've never seen someone sitting like that before!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He hasn't moved a muscle since we arrived. Do you think perhaps he's dead?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">If he was dead, Runo, he wouldn't be sitting up, would he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well anyway, dead or alive, he's not overly approachable, is he? I don't think he's going to talk to us.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">He's not dead!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at all those ancient casks lining the wall there.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Casks in the Reaper's chamber... ...Or are they caskets?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You, you don't think... ...all those p-people who escaped c-c-conviction in court are lying inside them...d-dead, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What ridiculous notions are going through your head, man? This is my collection of fine vintages!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes, of course. Thank you for clearing that up...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Runo and I were just musing to ourselves. Don't mind us, Mr Reaper.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I wouldn't, if you hadn't invited yourselves to my office to talk nonsense within my earshot.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord Stronghart said that the assault last night was some sort of revenge attack?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">True. Carried out by henchmen of Odie Asman's criminal organisation. The investigation meant their arrests were imminent. Presumably some hoped to kill me before that happened.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Odie Asman...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">He's always masqueraded as one of London's most powerful financiers. A global investor. But his enormous wealth came to him by underhand means, via his criminal activities.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And he used that money to buy himself a verdict of not guilty when he found himself in court, didn't he? Being prosecuted by you, Mr Reaper.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">But the man got his comeuppance in the end. Yesterday in fact, in extraordinary circumstances. It was a most unusual cause of death.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I know about that! It was super-high-voltage instantaneous kinesis gone wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Asman died when the demonstration on the public experimentation stage ended in an enormous explosion.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...Correct. And you think I have some kind of divine ability to cause an accident like that to happen, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...no, that does seem a little far-fetched. <thought>If this man really is the fabled Reaper, then he has to be innocent of this particular death, at least.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">It's strange how this has worked out, isn't it, Runo? I mean, what with you taking on the professor's defence for the trial tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What?! You're going to be defending him?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, yes, that's right. Though I barely know the man's name yet, to be honest.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Albert. Albert Harebrayne.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right. ...Do you know him, by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Of course. He's a contemporary of mine. We were at university together.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'd understood that Professor Harebrayne was from Germany, though.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Harebrayne's from a respectable British family. After graduating from the University of London, he moved to Germany to carry out research, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you were students together...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I was in the faculty of law, of course. And he in science. So our paths rarely crossed. But curiously, we got along. Though I've not met him since my university days. I certainly didn't expect our next encounter to take this form. And with you of all people representing him.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... Only if I make it out of this office alive...</thought> He's actually been charged with murder, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yes, I know. Because the prosecution... ...will be handled by me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">By you?! But...but you made it sound as if you and the professor had been friends.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">We are friends, it's true.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Then why would you do this?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">If the Reaper is the prosecutor, there's nothing anyone can do to save him! He's doomed!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>What's Lord van Zieks thinking...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean by what you said before? If you'd like to know the Reaper's true identity, does that mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I'm a Crown prosecutor and a mortal like any other. I'm no demigod.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But they've all died, haven't they? The people you've prosecuted, I mean. ...Whether or not the trial ended in a conviction or an acquittal...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Those I prosecute are the vilest wretches of our society. People who without question deserve to be found guilty. ...The world is a better place without them.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But... ...that's not true of Mr Natsume, for example. He wasn't a vile wretch at all.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Nor was Ginny! In fact, she's ever so hard-working now.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... I can't deny that since I encountered you, things have taken a turn. But the point is this: If any of those vile wretches that escaped justice subsequently died in mysterious circumstances... ...it was at the hand of their own kind. It's not my work.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord Stronghart said the same. He believes you're not involved in any way.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But you were attacked by those ruffians because they believe it's true!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... The fact is, since people started to call me the Reaper of the Bailey... ...the number of serious crimes in the capital has dropped substantially.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It would appear that even the most hardened criminals can be made fearful for their lives.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Do you mean to say...?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I mean to say that if my pseudonym serves a useful purpose... ...I adopt it gladly, and with honour.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But it's putting you in danger! You could be killed!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">If that is my fate, let God decide.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord van Zieks...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">He's in my tutelage to become a prosecutor. So you could say he's my apprentice, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah, like you are to Hurley then, Runo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I don't remember taking an apprenticeship with a great detective...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">He's currently compiling a report about last night's attack.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It looks like he's wearing some kind of mask...?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">On Lord Stronghart's orders. Nobody knows the man's face. ...Or indeed his identity.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But why would you agree to take on such a clearly suspicious individual?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Lord Stronghart's orders again. He's not one for meaningless follies. There will be a good reason for his actions.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I hope you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Apprentice">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The task is complete? Good. In that case, you can collate all the briefs.</line>
<line speaker="Apprentice">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... N-Nice to meet you...?</line>
<line speaker="Apprentice">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Back to work again... That was really strange, though. I've never met the man before. I didn't even know he existed. And yet... ...somehow it didn't feel like our first encounter.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Don't bother trying to converse with him. He says nothing to anybody from outside this office. Lord Stronghart has strictly forbidden it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh. I see...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Why are you so interested in my apprentice anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm? Oh, no! I mean... Sorry, I didn't mean to... <thought>The way he stood there so casually, yet with that flawless posture... ......... It, it couldn't be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, I know you've seen this around my arm before, but...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What is it, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's the mark of a defence lawyer. ...In Japan at least.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And what's your reason for showing it to a British prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...well... I don't know, really.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... I can understand, at least... ...there's merit in reminding yourself of who helped you become what you are today.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">But that's a personal matter. Something you may want to keep close at all times, not something to flaunt.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No...I suppose not. Thank you for understanding, though.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord van Zieks, about the article in this paper...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Ah, yes... It seems there was a reporter nearby when that little skirmish took place. I had no idea I'd been photographed. It was careless of me.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It looks as though it was taken after the people who attacked you had run away, though.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Rest assured, the police have already apprehended every last one of them.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But there's someone else fighting alongside you, it seems. And I think it's the same man who's sitting over there as we speak, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... As I mentioned already... ...he's my apprentice.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Perhaps you could tell us a little more about him?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Having read what happened to you, it's lucky you weren't injured...or worse.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">My highly skilled apprentice was with me. Our attackers are the lucky ones...for escaping with their lives.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What I really can't believe is that the incident was captured on film. If the journalist had been spotted, it would have ended very badly for him indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>It sounds like the luckiest person there... ...was whoever wrote the article for the paper.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">That Nipponese man. Is he faring well?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The one arrested twice in succession six months ago. With the stoop. And the moustache. And the jitters.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Mr Natsume, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...I'm not sure he'd be very pleased to find out you identified him from that list, Runo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He's fine, thank you. In fact, I received a letter from him by international post only the other day.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I see. ......... Well, I think we can end our discussion there, don't you? There's little time left before tomorrow's trial. I advise you to spend it investigating the case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, thank you for the advice. And for the conversation. <thought>I can't believe he's asking after Soseki-san. After a 'Nipponese'! I'm not sure whether to feel happy about that or worried.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">I never imagined that Mr Reaper would be friends with a mad scientist, did you? That's a turn-up for the books!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A mad scientist? Ah, you mean Professor Harebrayne? <thought>Yes, it might be worth quizzing the professor about his relationship with Lord van Zieks, I think.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The warden said cell eleven. That's this one...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! There's someone curled up in a ball in the back corner, look!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's his name again? Professor Albert Harebrayne, wasn't it? ...Um, excuse me! Professor Harebrayne!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">...! Who are you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm Ryunosuke Naruhodo. I'm a defence lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">A LAWYER!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh! <thought>Was it something I said?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">A, a lawyer, you say? W-W-W-Would you be here... a-a-a-about the experiment? ARE YOU GOING TO DEFEND MY HYPOTHESIS?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your...hypothesis? Sorry, I don't-</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yesterday's demonstration! That demonstration was... That magnificent demonstration was... It was an out-and-out success! By anyone's calculations! B-B-B-But despite that... ...no one listens! No lawyer believes in the science! When it's explained, they all leave...at high velocity! Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>Now's probably not a good time to mention that your zeal made my concentration leave for a while, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, you mentioned the demonstration yesterday...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">The papers have called it a spectacular failure. After all, a man died in the explosion, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAARGH! Yes, you could interpret the results that way if you really wanted to! Well, I, I suppose in the strictest sense... ...the experiment was a failure. But at the same time, it was a great success!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You've lost me.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I saw it with my own eyes! Right there in front of me! Mr Asman was spontaneously disassembled! Until then, everything was going exactly as my calculations had predicted! At that point, he should have been beamed to the Crystal Tower by instantaneous kinesis! However...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...The machine exploded and Mr Asman in fact perished?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yes. I can't deny that part of the experiment was a failure.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So what you're really saying is, the large explosion that killed Mr Asman was an accident, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But the bigwigs had you arrested on suspicion of murder.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... I was responsible for a man's death. That is the immutable truth here. And for that, I wish to be punished. At once! B-But... ...murder?! Never in a million years! It, it was an accident! Simply an accident!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I see.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hurley and I were talking this morning, you know. He said the situation would change completely depending on whether it was treated as an accident or murder.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, if it really was an accident, then the professor's machine would be kept in protective custody.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">On what grounds?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ah, yes, it's newly established here in Britain. The Special Dispensation for Scientific Equipment Act.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That one passed me by...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">But if the case is treated as murder...</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">...Then they'll say my machine was the murder weapon, and they'll be able to pore over it as much as they like! If they examine it in detail, they'll find out how it's made, and then... They'll be able to copy my idea! My precious hypothesis will be stolen! The machine must be protected from that at all costs! That's why it's imperative this whole incident is shown to have been an accident in tomorrow's trial!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, I see now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So in short...there was a terrible accident at the Great Exhibition showground yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yes! Or rather no. The devil is in the details! Strictly speaking, there was a terrible explosion.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Sounds the same to me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">You were demonstrating super-high-voltage instantaneous kinesis, weren't you? How fascinating!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Humans, like all matter, are made up of particles that are held together by electrical bonds. So it must be possible, using a sufficiently high voltage, to break those bonds and beam the particles through space! That's, that's it in a nutshell! That's my idea, you see? That's my amazing hypothesis!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gosh... That's unimaginably high-level science.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Oh, but dare to imagine it! Dare to dream of such incredible technology! Just think! One moment I could be here in this cell, and the next...I could be at the Great Exhibition again!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, yes! That would be incredible.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">And the next, in the mere blink of an eye, I could be at a great Parisian theatre, say! The possibilities are endless! The whole of our vast planet would be within reach!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...So no more hiding in wardrobes on rocky seas for fifty days?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hm, I don't really see it like that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, if you could travel anywhere in the world instantly... ...the planet wouldn't really seem vast any more, would it? I think it would feel like it had shrunk.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">My word! That's, that's exactly right! Wh-What are the implications...? What does this mean? .........</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oops, that's got Professor Bunnybrain really worried by the look of it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Clearly this is yet another case of 'just because you can, doesn't mean you should', I suppose...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">The point is, my calculations are flawless! The science works! But without a practical demonstration, it means nothing! And that's always the fly in the ointment.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Because practical demonstrations cost a lot of money. Money that young scientists like you don't have.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">That's...that's exactly it, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hurley's always complaining about it. He says the government should invest more in science.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Well anyway, I bumped into him at the right time. I met the well known investor, Mr Asman!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The victim who died in yesterday's terrible incident, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I understand Lord van Zieks is a friend of yours from your university days?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yes, that's right. He was studying law whilst I was studying science.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What was he like back then?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Hm, a good question... Unassuming...gentlemanly... An all-around nice fellow, really.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Sorry, I, I think you misheard me. I'm talking about the cold-hearted, merciless prosecutor Barok van Zieks... What was he like when he was at university?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...Talk about a leading question, Runo.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">As I said: an unassuming and extremely pleasant gentleman. After all, he is the little darling of the van Zieks family, with all its great aristocratic origins.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I, I didn't realise he had quite such noble blood!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Little darling?!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... It was a bit of a shock when I came back to Britain and learnt what he'd become. The Reaper of the Bailey no less!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I did hear, though... ...that there was a very big event in his life that completely changed him after graduation.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? What sort of event?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAARGH! I'm, I'm sorry, but I don't know any more. I wasn't in the country at the time. I was in Germany already.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh. ...Yes, of course. <thought>If he's heard all about the Reaper... ...I really don't have the heart to tell him that Lord van Zieks will be the prosecutor in court tomorrow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The full name of the man who died in yesterday's accident was Mr Odie Asman, wasn't it? What exactly was your relationship with the man?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">He first visited me in my laboratory in Germany a year ago now. He said he wanted to invest in my immaculate hypothesis. I thanked my lucky stars!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I see... So you hadn't really known each other until then.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Money for scientific research... I'm so envious!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">As far as I was concerned, the man was an angel!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...really?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">An archangel, even! He was prepared to fund a practical demonstration of my hypothesis for presentation at the Great Exhibition! And if that went well, I could expect additional financial support for my research from the British government! Mr Asman provided me with money and an exceptional engineer. He produced a machine to my precise specifications.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But then your dreams were blown to dust in one enormous explosion.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">As you can see, I owed everything to Mr Asman. I would never, ever have thought of taking the man's life!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well, he seems genuine enough. I don't think he's lying.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ah, fascinating, yes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In Japan, where I come from, it's the symbol of a defence lawyer. Wearing it is very bracing, I find.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Hm, your words make some sense to me, but they are entirely illogical.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Well, for example, I find this white laboratory coat that I wear for my work very bracing, too. However, in my case, there is a perfectly logical reason for that feeling.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Really? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I, I purchased the wrong size by mistake. This one is too small for me. The sleeves, especially, are extremely bracing. I can barely move my wrists.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... That's what you call logical, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Of course! It's entirely logical! That's science, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ugh...how could this have happened?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You must feel awful. As well as a man losing his life, the Crystal Tower was greatly damaged, too.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I, I know what happened! It must have been that!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'That'?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">The day before the demonstration, I had my usual meal of frankfurters at the hotel restaurant. When I paid the bill, they gave me three shillings too much in change. But...instead of saying anything, I just slipped the coins into my pocket! They're still there now! It's divine retribution for my wrongdoing, that's what this is!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>For a scientist, he has some very illogical anecdotes. Long and illogical.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">As correct as two squared is four! I swear it! Yes, it's true that the man perished in a machine of my invention. So I know that I'm far from blameless in all this. But still! I would never use my discoveries, my inventions, to take a person's life! Not in a centillion years! I'm a man of science! It's all I know! You have to believe me! Please! Do you believe me? Do you believe in my hypothesis? Science is the pursuit of truth, you know. I've always believed that. All my life!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I'm afraid I don't know much about science. Or your theories. But I do believe you. And I will fight to prove your innocence with all my might. I'm a man of the law! It's all I know! You have to believe me! Please!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... When I went to live in Germany after I graduated, I learnt something very important. Nationality, class, lineage...none of that matters. As long as you try your hardest, you can achieve anything.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you for that, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">And thank you in advance for defending me tomorrow in court!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Alright, Runo, it's time! Time to visit the Great Exhibition!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, that's where the incident happened, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I suppose that's true. <thought>Time to investigate at last!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... The showgrounds are a little too big for my liking... We've been walking around in dense crowds for two hours now, and I've felt myself swooning three times.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">There are a lot of people, aren't there? I've almost been trodden on three times, too!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Be careful, won't you, Iris? Don't let go of my hand. <thought>We've finally made it through the throngs though, by the look of it. Here we are underneath the public experimentation stage where the explosion happened yesterday.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">.........!</line>
<line speaker="???">.........!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What's that...? I can hear voices from up on the stage. It sounds like an argument...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Right, I've had it with you this time! I'm warnin' you, I'll arrest you in a minute!</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh yeah? Go on then, 'Spector, give it a shot! You ain't got no evidence, an' you know it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Wait... I know those voices.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">You've got a cheeky little mouth on you, young lady! But a night in the cells will teach you some manners!</line>
<line speaker="???">Just try it, I dare ya! If ya want that bag o' chips rammed down yer throat!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yoo-hoo! Gregsy! What are you doing up there?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">......... Ah! AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH! It's you! Here! You're here! Here you are! You! Here! Your Ladyshiiip! How are you, Your Ladyship? I do hope you're well, Your Ladyship?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Does that make her three times a lady?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">I'm not well at all. It's far too busy everywhere. I wanted to ride in a balloon, but there was a three-hour queue.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Unbelievable! I'll go an' have a word for you at once, Your Ladyship! You'll be flyin' as high as a kite in no time once I pull some strings for you!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Tobias Gregson, an inspector at Scotland Yard. Until recently, he was suspended from duty, but it would appear he's back in action now. He's actually quite well known, appearing as he does in 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes'. And for that reason, he can't say a word wrong to the stories' author, Iris. <thought>But there are limits, surely... Or there should be!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Watch it, sunshine!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">S-Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">What gives, then? Don't tell me you're on this case?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I'm acting for the defence.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">So we're here to investigate!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Hmmm... Dear me, that's the situation, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Is it really that troubling?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Tsk. A measly five bob? Is that all ya got? Yer a lawyer, ain't ya? Ya could stand to carry a bit more copper around in yer pockets, Mr Narra-'Oddo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...? Hey! That's my last bit of spending money, that is!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ya can 'ave it back, but I'll 'ave to charge ya for all the bother. Three bob.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is Gina Lestrade, a pickpocket, or 'diver', born and bred in the East End of London. In the case that led to my own suspension six months ago... ...this is the young girl I was defending in court.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Wot's yer problem, eh, 'Oddo?! 'Diver'? Pickpocket? Wot's wiv all the name-callin'? You wanna bag o' chips rammed down yer throat an' all, do ya?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I thought you were proud to be a diver, Gina? You were just arguing with Inspector Gregson about it, weren't you? I assumed you'd been up to your usual tricks here at the showground.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">That ain't no way to talk to a lady, 'Oddo. 'Alf a year's a long time. People can change. I'm an apprentice now. Learnin' to be a Scotland Yard detective. So you'll 'ave to call me wot everyone else does: It's Inspector Lestrade now!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In... Inspector?! <thought>That badge is homemade, surely...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">The 'inspector' part isn't entirely accurate. No one calls her that. For what it's worth, anyway. Investigatin' is off the cards for all of us.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Right, well, I'll be back up top. You hold the fort down here, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Right...sir.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This... This raises a LOT of questions!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">These stairs obviously lead to the stage above. We should go up there and investigate the exact spot where the experiment was being conducted...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This platform must have been set up for the experiment, I suppose. It's very high up.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">About thirty feet above the ground, apparently. That's what a policeman I just spoke to said.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't really understand 'feet' very well. We don't use them in Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh yes, sorry. It's about nine metres. But soon you'll have been in London a year, Runo. It's time you got used to our measurements.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, well... This thing is so tall, the spectators at the front would just have seen a wall and nothing else!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">They probably thought they'd secured the best spot to watch from, only to be disappointed...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's a saying in Japan: the darkest spot is right under the lighthouse. ...I feel like it probably applies here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The Crystal Tower... It's certainly an apt name. It was built to be the focal point of the exhibition. And it definitely is, being so tall and with all that glass... I can't imagine a building like this ever being erected in Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">There are lots of exhibits inside the tower as well, apparently. Of course there's an observation deck, but there's also an art gallery, a zoo and a museum! But I heard you have to queue for three hours just to get through the doors!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, at the moment, the shattered glass from the failed experiment may well be the biggest draw.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And thanks to that accident, the whole tower is shut.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Suddenly it's not the Crystal Tower any more, but the Crystal Glass Shower...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Apparently everyone's taking to the skies now to look down on the disaster area from above instead. But there's a three-hour queue to go up in a balloon now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Londoners must be very patient people.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">That's where the cove ended up after 'is 'instant kinesis' or wotever they call it. Dead, o' course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And yet they're calling the experiment a success?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">What's the wooden scaffold there for?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">The coppers - our lads - set that up after the incident 'appened. To get the body down, I think. Dunno, really...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Didn't you help to erect the scaffold, then?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Nah, lookout duty's more my thing. Wanderin' round the exhibition an' keepin' a 'lookout' for the fun stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Mind Gregson doesn't hear you saying that, or he'll give you the boot. <thought>It's incredible though, isn't it? I mean...could the victim really have bridged that gap by some sort of invisible kinesis...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I've been meaning to ask you for a while now, but what are those funny round blobs floating in the sky?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, they're the flying balloons I've been talking about. I want to go up in one sooo much!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I've, I've read about situations like this in a magazine about strange phenomena. C-Creatures from outer space c-coming in round, flying objects...t-t-to attack Earth!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I suppose inhabitants of o-other planets are b-bound to be interested in the G-Great Exhibition... This is it, Iris! It's happening!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...It's not, don't worry. I'll explain it all to you later over a nice cup of tea, Runo.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh look, what's this? A ripped piece of cloth...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm, it's not like any fabric I've ever seen before. <thought>It's very thick and stiff. It looks extremely durable...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">It's canvas, I think. With some sort of rubber backing. And the edges appear to be a bit charred as well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Maybe that means it had something to do with the explosion...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Let's make a note of it while Ginny's mid-yawn!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh look, what's this? A ripped piece of cloth...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm, it's not like any fabric I've ever seen before. <thought>It's very thick and stiff. It looks extremely durable...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">It's canvas, I think. With some sort of rubber backing. And the edges appear to be a bit charred as well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Maybe that means it had something to do with the explosion...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">For some reason the ground is damaged in this spot, look. ...Almost as if there was a fire here or something.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, if you look closely, there's some scattered ash and burnt embers, too...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I suppose there was a big explosion just above here. People probably wouldn't bat an eyelid at a small fire like this would have been.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...I'm not sure we English are quite that laid-back, Runo.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...Ah, it looks as though somebody dropped something behind the tree just here...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Dropped...or hid? What is this? Some part of the machine that exploded?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Maybe. It could have fallen from the platform above in the blast, perhaps.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Wot's goin' on 'ere?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Nothing. <thought>I think I'll hang on to this, just in case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It was eight months ago now that I first encountered Gina, in connection with a case I was working on. At the time, she was living in the East End with a group of other orphans. She helped all of them survive by pickpocketing, but then she got embroiled in a murder.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I 'ad a lot of time to think in prison. I realised I couldn't go on like I was. The divin' weren't workin' out.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, I'm so pleased to hear it, Ginny! Well done!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you went from being a pickpocket...to a detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">You got it! Good, innit? Inspector Lestrade! Sounds like somefin' out of a book, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Talk about a sea change...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">And then there's Iris's old man to think about.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Iris's father, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah. I promised 'er, didn't I? I said I'd get all the police forces 'round the world to pull out all the stops lookin' for 'im.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Just a small promise, then. Nothing serious.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, Ginny, you're so sweet...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">So anyway, that's 'ow come I 'ad a go at the test for Scotland Yard. Only trouble is, I don't read so well, do I?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Just a small problem. Nothing serious.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And that's when Hurley approached Gregsy and asked for help. So the inspector said he'd take full responsibility for Ginny and made her a sort of apprentice.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That was very magnanimous of Inspector Gregson. And brave.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, you know Hurley. He enjoys finding ways to make people do what he wants.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The great detective likes digging for dirt, in other words...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">So, the long and the short of it is, if you've got questions about the case, ya can ask Inspector Lestrade!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right then...'Inspector'... <thought>Actually, there's still a big mystery surrounding Gina, isn't there?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ooh, what, Runo, what?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, six months ago, Gina was the defendant in a trial prosecuted by the Reaper. A trial in which she was found not guilty. And yet here she is still...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Come on! Yer not still on about that, are ya? The legend o' the Reaper or wotever it's called. Cor, ya don't 'alf worry, 'Oddo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>If I didn't 'half' worry, there probably wouldn't be a 'whole' lot of you left!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">It's like I told ya before, innit? The Reaper's kind o' like 'Im upstairs. So 'e knows wot I'm like on the inside. That I ain't really done nuffin' wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>'Nothing wrong' might be stretching a point...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">What about Mr Natsume in Japan? He's perfectly fine, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...that's true. Perhaps the Reaper is more discerning than I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Exactly! So I ain't worried. I'm totally fine!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Cor, it was out o' this world, it was! The brainy bloke pulled a bunch o' levers on 'is machine, and suddenly it started billowin' smoke. Then it just went pop. I ain't seen a better experiment 'ere yet.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You mean...you saw it, Ginny? With your own eyes?!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, 'course. The boss is in charge 'ere, ain't 'e? Of keepin' everyfin' runnin' smooth, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The 'boss' being Inspector Gregson, I suppose. That's going to take some getting used to...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">So all I 'ave to say is that I'm on duty, an' I can do wotever I want to! Get this! I was up in one o' them flyin' balloons when it 'appened! Watchin' it from above!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">No! You're so lucky, Ginny! Maybe I should join Scotland Yard, too...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, do it! You know 'ow to put the boss in 'is place already, right, Iris? You'd 'ave no trouble at all.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Then it's settled! When do I start?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no no! You can't join Scotland Yard, Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">We'll see... Anyway, what I don't understand is this: if the machine exploded so spectacularly... ...how can Professor Bunnybrain still be claiming that his experiment was a success?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Oh, right. Well, it was a success...in a way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It was? <thought>How can it have been?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Surely after the whole machine blew up, no one could call the experiment a success.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">It's like I said, it did sort of work. I mean, yeah, there was a load o' smoke an' that whoppin' great bang... ...but where d'ya think they found the victim's body, eh? In the Crystal Tower over there!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? <thought>In the tower?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">You can see for yerself, can't ya? Up there above the scaffold...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! Where all the glass is broken, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah. The cage wot the victim got in to start wiv... ...really did get beamed through the air or wotever and landed all the way over there. So, ya see? It did kind o' work...didn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">WHAAAAAAAAAT?! <thought>I, I don't believe it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">I mean, I don't get the ins an' outs of it, but anyfin's possible, right? Wiv science. Oh, I tell ya wot. You can 'ave this. It's a plan o' the experiment they drew up at the Yard.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Are, are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, go on. I 'ad three bob off ya before, so fair's fair.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, I didn't actually give that to you...did I?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Surely after the whole machine blew up, no one could call the experiment a success.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">It's like I said, it did sort of work. I mean, yeah, there was a load o' smoke an' that whoppin' great bang... ...but where d'ya think they found the victim's body, eh? In the Crystal Tower over there!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? <thought>In the tower?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">You can see for yerself, can't ya? Up there above the scaffold...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! Where all the glass is broken, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah. The cage wot the victim got in to start wiv... ...really did get beamed through the air or wotever and landed all the way over there. So, ya see? It did kind o' work...didn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">WHAAAAAAAAAT?! <thought>I, I don't believe it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">I mean, I don't get the ins an' outs of it, but anyfin's possible, right? Wiv science.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Something Inspector Gregson said before seemed a little strange.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">For what it's worth, anyway. Investigatin' is off the cards for all of us.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, naughty old Gregsy ran off after that without explaining himself.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Oh right, that. The boss said no one's allowed to investigate that weird machine wot blew up yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well that's not fair! We're representing the defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In that case, could you at least tell us what you've learnt from your investigations?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Nah, yer not gettin' it. We ain't allowed to investigate, neither.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why?!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Wot did the boss call 'em again? The Forensic Investigation Team, I think. Anyway, apart from them lot, no one's allowed to lay a finger on the scene. Bit funny, innit?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So even Scotland Yard's own detectives can't investigate... Yes, I've never heard something like that before.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I thought I could 'ave a gander on the quiet, though, but the boss caught me at it. You prob'ly 'eard 'im givin' me an earful about it before from down 'ere, didn't ya? It's not bleedin' fair!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I think you were giving him as much of an earful back, as I remember it.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, well, sometimes I think it's all them chips wot make 'im so stubborn. You say somefin' to 'im, 'Oddo. Go on! See if you can get through to 'im!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He's up on the platform above us, is he? Where the machine that exploded is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">We can try, can't we, Runo? Gregsy will listen to us!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This armband is proof - in Japan at least - that I'm a defence lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">And this badge is proof that I'm a detective! So yer all gonna 'ave to start callin' me Inspector Lestrade!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In that case, you'll have to start calling me... Well, anything but ''Oddo'.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I could call ya 'Defender Narra-'Oddo' if ya like. ...But it don't really trip off the tongue.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No...it doesn't have a great ring to it, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gina, would you take a look at- Oh! Where did it go?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Hehe! Lookin' for this, 'Oddo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>When did she do that?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">I wonder if you've got anyfin' else to show me, eh? Wot d'ya reckon?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Give that back first, please.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It looks like layers of thick canvas with a thick rubber lining of sorts. I've never seen anything like it before. But applying Mr Sholmes's methods... ...you might deduce it was part of a raincoat worn by someone who really, really didn't want to get wet. And the charring...must have occurred when the person was struck by lightning! ......... Or maybe not.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, there's some sort of lever here... What the- What is this?! It, it looks like a cross between a bow and a gun! ......... <thought>I think it's probably used for the same thing, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, there's some sort of lever here... What the- What is this?! It, it looks like a cross between a bow and a gun! ......... <thought>I think it's probably used for the same thing, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It looks like you wind this around in order to draw the bowstring back and create tension. You must be able to fire arrows with a huge amount of force using this device, then. In fact, I would imagine it's far more accurate and powerful than a Japanese longbow. Ugh... I really had no idea what I was picking up when I spotted this at the exhibition grounds.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This groove here...must be where the arrows are loaded, I suppose. So I was right, it's a sort of bow with an automatic firing mechanism. This would be perfect for someone like me who catches his ear with the bowstring two times out of three. ......... <thought>In fact, if I'd had one of these, maybe I could have beaten Kazuma in kyudo archery training.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I've been thinking... Hurley might know something, mightn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">About what?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">About Mr Reaper!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! About what happened to Lord van Zieks, you mean? <thought>Because it sounds like something very significant occurred after he graduated from university. Something that completely changed his life.</thought> Maybe, but I have no idea where to find Mr Sholmes at the moment. He's in the middle of some big case, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Here, this is what you need!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's this? <thought>Some kind of entrance ticket?</thought> 'Madame Tusspells'? Is this supposed to mean something to me?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You don't know it?! It's the most popular attraction in London at the moment! It's very close to Baker Street, actually. We could go now, if you like?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no, we don't have time for visiting attractions today, Iris. We have a big trial tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But that's where Hurley is.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? At, at this popular London attraction?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How is it that you know where he is?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hurley told me. But he told me to keep it a secret from you, Runo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Madame Tusspells...? <thought>I don't see how it could be related to the case we're investigating here, but then... ...stranger things have happened. And when they happen, Mr Sholmes is usually at the heart of them.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So that's it, is it? The machine that blew up.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ooh, it must have been a magnificent explosion! And I've seen my fair share.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You've seen things like this before, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Of course! Hurley's always doing experiments that end in a bang. In fact, in his own words, 'Explosions are the very essence of chemistry!'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...that might explain the smell of burning that frequently comes wafting up the stairs.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">One time, he made something that exploded with such force, it took the roof off the building! I wish you'd been there to see it, Runo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...It's hard to get too excited about that...given that I now live in the roof.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well anyway, that's enough about that. It's time to investigate!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah look, Inspector Gregson is over there. He seems to be deep in thought about something... whilst eyeing up the machine carefully.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Really? He just looks confused to me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There are all sorts of strange buildings here in the Great Exhibition grounds, aren't there? I...seem to remember something similar being exhibited in Japan one time...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! In your country, Runo? I do wish I could go and see it! I'd present a particularly steely samurai with a present of one of Hurley's stories I'd written especially... ...and see if I couldn't get Hurley into a jam against some bartitsu-master ninjas!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm...you might not find as many of those sorts of people around as you think.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh... Well that's dull...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ooh! But I do know a prosecutor with a chonmage topknot I could introduce you to!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">A chonmage! Really?! Do you think I could have my picture taken with him? Do you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Assuming he's recovered from the 'trim' Kazuma gave him a year ago, yes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wh-What is that gigantic thing over there? It looks like an enormous waterwheel...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, that's a Ferris wheel. There'll be people riding inside those little cabins you can see.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Why?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well...they rotate nice and slowly, so it's a wonderful way to see the surrounding scenery.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait...it's turning? But it looks completely still.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes. That's because it's turning so slowly. One complete revolution takes about half an hour.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you were mad enough to go in one, it would be more fun to whizz around fast, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...I feel as though you might have just invented a new sort of ride there, Runo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So those are people-carrying balloons, dangling silently in the skies over London... I always thought the day would come when humans would discover how to fly. But I never imagined it would involve them being suspended from colourful, floating temari handballs...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I'm sure it must feel amazing, being up there among the clouds! Let's take a ride together, Runo! Please!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If I'm being perfectly honest, I would like to try it. But without a cast-iron guarantee that the thing won't plummet to the ground...I'm too scared.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh well, in that case, I should tell you what Hurley said. 'It's physically impossible for a flying balloon to plummet to the ground...as long as it doesn't explode.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...call me crazy, but I think that exploding part might play on my mind a little...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It ripped itself apart magnificently, didn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Magnificently...and mercilessly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So someone stands in the middle of the machine to be disassembled and then 'beamed' through the air...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, 'beamed' not 'blasted'. That's the point.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, that part's crucial, really.</thought> Is something like that even possible, though, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, Runo. I'm just a child. How should I know?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>A child when it suits you, you mean...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">From what I can tell, I think if you were to pull this lever here-</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">STOOOOOOOOOOOOP! Don't touch that!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah ha ha! That was practically instantaneous kinesis the way you flew over just now, Gregsy!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Please, Your Ladyship... I didn't mean to startle you, but I can't let you touch anything up here.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">So sorry. You can have some of my latest special blend to make up for it.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">*Glug* *Glug glug glug* Aaah! Wonderful! This stuff really is wonderful!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It's just like old times, this is...</thought> We're representing Professor Harebrayne in court tomorrow, Inspector. So we should be allowed to examine the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Hah! Listen, sunshine, even I'm not allowed to touch anythin' up here! It's that blasted Special Dispensation for Scientific Equipment Act to blame. It's drivin' me potty!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes, that special dispensation... <thought>The professor mentioned that, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">More red tape's all we need. I dunno what the government thinks it's playin' at sometimes.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But...we're allowed to just look, aren't we?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Surely that's alright...isn't it, Gregsy?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">......... 'Course, Your Ladyship! Anythin' you say, Your Ladyship! But please don't get your dainty hands dirty, will you?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Don't worry. We wouldn't dream of touching anything, would we, Runo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>She really knows how to get what she wants...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Considering how badly damaged everything is, Professor Harebrayne was lucky to escape unscathed, I'd say. <thought>We should have a good look around the machine while we can, I think...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Touch anythin' and I'll make sure I kill you before I get strung up myself, you hear?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I won't touch a thing, I promise. So please...spare a thought for your digestion! Anyway...do you really think this machine could actually disassemble people like the professor claims?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">He asks, lookin' totally incredulous. Give it a rest, sunshine. If we were allowed to examine all this bleedin' scrap metal, maybe we could answer that question. But we can't, can we?!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Because of the annoying rules, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Exactly! The annoyin', obstructive flamin' rules!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Oh. Look at the base of the machine there...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh yes! There's a tool of some kind poking through the wire mesh.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's...a screwdriver, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, isn't it a lovely one! The handle is in the shape of a capital letter 'A'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It is? ...Oh yes, you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?! Don't touch anythin', I said! Touch anythin' and I'll make sure I kill you before I get strung up myself, I said!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes yes! I understand! Sorry! <thought>I only touched it a teeny weeny bit...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">But Gregsy! I'm very curious about this screwdriver. Really very, very curious.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">......... 'Course, Your Ladyship! You're so clever, Your Ladyship! Fancy spottin' somethin' like this! But I'm afraid, I can't let you have it.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But Runo found it first!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I assure you, I'll investigate it thoroughly!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He's gone off with it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hmph! That was very mean! I'm afraid... 'Inspector Gregson' is going to make a very clumsy and embarrassing mistake in next month's instalment now!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Poor 'Gregsy'...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Considering how badly damaged everything is, Professor Harebrayne was lucky to escape unscathed, I'd say. <thought>We should have a good look around the machine while we can, I think...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Touch anythin' and I'll make sure I kill you before I get strung up myself, you hear?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I won't touch a thing, I promise. So please...spare a thought for your digestion! Anyway...do you really think this machine could actually disassemble people like the professor claims?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">He asks, lookin' totally incredulous. Give it a rest, sunshine. If we were allowed to examine all this bleedin' scrap metal, maybe we could answer that question. But we can't, can we?!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Because of the annoying rules, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Exactly! The annoyin', obstructive flamin' rules!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That amazing horn-shaped device is pointing towards the Crystal Tower. I suppose once people are disassembled by the machine, they're shot out of that thing to wherever they're going.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I don't think it was supposed to shoot anything, Runo. It was set up to 'beam' people to the Crystal Tower where they'd be reconstructed in their original form.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...I don't like the look of it. If it was as amazing as it looks, the accident wouldn't have happened in the first place, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I suppose that's true, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But nothing ever goes according to plan, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Using high-voltage electricity to somehow 'disassemble' a man's body... ...and then beam him across to the Crystal Tower... It's an extraordinary thing to attempt...especially in public.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">True. It was by far the most unusual of the experiments planned for the exhibition, mind.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">To be honest...I'm a bit surprised it was allowed. Carrying out something so dangerous with so many spectators present, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">The government's doin' everythin' it can to promote new science and technology at the moment. They're more worried about bein' ahead of the game than the odd spot of public safety infringements. If they can be the first to develop some new technology, it makes Britain more powerful in the future, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I suppose that's true, in a way.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">So the powers that be are placin' a heavy emphasis on scientists' rights at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">What sort of rights?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">They're makin' it so that any theories the brains have remain their legal 'property', as it were... ...right through developin' it into a practical idea and even goin' into production. Which is the infuriatin' reason us coppers aren't allowed to touch the crime scene! Because the new highfalutin Special Dispensation for Scientific Equipment Act forbids it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, I see now...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">The only people with permission to investigate here are from some brand new department at the Yard. The 'Forensic Investigation Team' it's called. We've been relegated to keepin' guard.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The Forensic Investigation Team...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Any old fool can see that this heap of scrap metal was a sham to begin with! But just because it says 'scientific equipment' on the paperwork, we can't do a flamin' thing with it!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Poor Gregsy... He's very het up, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Remind me again, what's this new legal act that means we're not allowed to touch the scene here?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Are you havin' me at it, sunshine? It's the Special Dispensation for Scientific Equipment Act.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hm, yes... I think Hurley mentioned that recently. With a real twinkle in his eye as I remember.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I'm sure he did, Your Ladyship, I'm sure he did. Passed especially for this Great Exhibition, it was. All scientists have to do is present their ideas or inventions to some suits in the civil service... ...and if it gets rubber-stamped, that's a guarantee of rights to maintain the invention's confidentiality.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What does that really mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Think about it. Think of all the world-changin' new inventions on display every day at this exhibition. ...Although a good half of them are a load of cobblers if you ask me. Put forward by shammers like yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Thanks for that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, I love how absurd some of the inventions here are! It's all so fun!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">It might be fun to you, but a member of the force has to be present at every single demonstration. Can you imagine, eh? Hang science, that's what I say!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, I don't think so. That sounds like my dream job.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">You'd soon think otherwise after spendin' a day guardin' all these shammers' bogus contraptions.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But if they're all bogus, how can anyone hope to demonstrate them? There'd be no point.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yeah, well...there is a point, sadly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Thanks to another of our government's bright ideas. If any theory or invention is deemed to show 'potential', the government hands out a research grant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The scientists get funding?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Exactly. And that's what they're all after. All these shammers comin' from far and wide to clog up Hyde Park. And who has to keep 'em all safe, eh? Who has to smile politely and welcome them? Us coppers, that's who! So you can see why I say it now, can't ya? Hang science! Hang it!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh...maybe I can see your point...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Apparently Professor Harebrayne lives and works in Germany now conducting his research.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">That's right. Came back to Britain especially for the Great Exhibition, as I understand it. Probably after one of the government's research grants. Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Actually, we learnt something else about the professor earlier today. About his time in further education. It turns out he was at university with someone we both know: Lord van Zieks.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Eh? What's that? That's news to me! But, but if van Zieks mans the prosecution, then as the accused, the professor's fate is...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Sealed? Because the Reaper will get him one way or another...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Blimey. That man's beyond me. I dunno what goes on in that head of his. Talkin' of van Zieks, this mornin's paper ran the story of him bein' attacked. Read that?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh yes! But Mr Reaper is completely fine. Nothing to worry about!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yes, right... Glad to hear it. Still, the Reaper, huh... How long's that business gonna keep up, I wonder?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The victim of this case, the investor, Mr Asman... He was another of the Reaper's victims...or so I heard.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">......... Lord Barok van Zieks is a top-class prosecutor. But even he can't always push the right verdict through. Sometimes justice can't win.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I've heard about jurors being bribed and evidence being falsified. And...that's how the notion of the Reaper of the Bailey came about, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Obviously, Scotland Yard suspected van Zieks initially. We all assumed he was takin' matters into his own hands if he failed to seal the deal in court.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Although the man himself denies that charge.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Well, we've done a very thorough investigation. And the conclusion we reached... ...is that Lord van Zieks is in no way related to the deaths of those people outside the courtroom. There's no question in my mind. I'd stake my reputation on it, I would.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But if that's true, then how do you explain it? All those defendants couldn't just have coincidentally died if nobody killed them!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I know that! But...I can't explain it. It's a mystery, after all, isn't it? That's the whole point of the Reaper.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Professor Harebrayne mentioned something else. He said that at university, Lord van Zieks was a totally different person. Easygoing and kind.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">You what?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He said that it was after they both graduated that something happened to change the man. ...Do you have any idea what it was?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">......... No clue.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Look, I've got my hands full watchin' over this frustratin' crime scene. Why don't you go and make a nuisance of yourself elsewhere, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is the symbol of a defence lawyer where I come from, Inspector.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Well, it doesn't pass muster here in London. You might as well chuck it in the deep fat fryer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...No one's ever said that to me before. Mr Sholmes suggested I feed it to a dog, though.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">If you fry it first, you can feed it to me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Does he think it's made of potato?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Inspector, have you read this paper?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yeah, two unwelcome blasts back to back. This one at the exhibition, and the Reaper gettin' attacked.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know. Terrible news to wake up to, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I tried to pretend I hadn't read it and turned over for another forty winks. Thanks to that, I was late up and got a roastin' from the super.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Some mornings are like that, aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As a detective, what do you make of this?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Personally speakin', nine times out of ten I find clues turn out to be red herrings. So there's every chance that's totally irrelevant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's actually a fairly persuasive argument...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Isn't it about time you were leavin'? Or rather...it IS about time you were leavin'! That lot are here now.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That lot?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">The Forensic Investigation Team. They'll be givin' me the heave-ho in a minute, too.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh dear. Poor Gregsy. Here! Have another cup of my special blend to cheer you up!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">*Glug* *Glug glug glug* Aaah! That hit the spot! Yup, hits it every time!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well, at least I've seen the scene with my own eyes. It looks like this is as far as we're going to get with our investigations here at least...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">I've been thinking... Hurley might know something, mightn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">About what?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">About Mr Reaper!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! About what happened to Lord van Zieks, you mean? <thought>Because it sounds like something very significant occurred after he graduated from university. Something that completely changed his life.</thought> Maybe, but I have no idea where to find Mr Sholmes at the moment. He's in the middle of some big case, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Here, this is what you need!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's this? <thought>Some kind of entrance ticket?</thought> 'Madame Tusspells'? Is this supposed to mean something to me?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You don't know it?! It's the most popular attraction in London at the moment! It's very close to Baker Street, actually. We could go now, if you like?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no, we don't have time for visiting attractions today, Iris. We have a big trial tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But that's where Hurley is.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? At, at this popular London attraction?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How is it that you know where he is?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hurley told me. But he told me to keep it a secret from you, Runo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Madame Tusspells...? <thought>I don't see how it could be related to the case we're investigating here, but then... ...stranger things have happened. And when they happen, Mr Sholmes is usually at the heart of them.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Lord van Zieks...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I think he's ignoring you, Runo.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The prosecution and defence should avoid speaking outside of the courtroom as a rule. So if anyone is being rude here, it's most certainly the man in black there standing before us.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, I see! Well, thank you for setting the record straight! Hehe! Did you see that? He spoke to me, Runo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So, Lord van Zieks, have you managed to visit the Great Exhibition yet?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Iris">He's definitely ignoring you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Right. No niceties either, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Iris, have a look at this...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's not right. I thought you were supposed to say '<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>' or the like when you present evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no. That's only in court.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's not fair! If you won't say it, then I won't look! Hmph!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yay! That was great! Right...next!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Alright, I get the message. Someone's not in the mood for looking at things...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wh-What is this place? L-Look at all these t-terrifying scenes! But why are all the p-people so still? <thought>Guillotines... Ruthless murderers... I know what I'll be dreaming about tonight.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">They're all wax models. They're amazingly realistic, aren't they? What do you think, Runo? Shocked?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">W-W-WAX MODELS?! .........AAAAAAAAAGH! I, I read about d-dead bodies and wax once...in a m-magazine about strange phenomena. Depending on how c-c-corpses are kept after death, p-parts of them can turn to wax, apparently. It's c-called a...adi...adip... Adipocere!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...Stop talking about creepy things like that, Runo. You're scaring me. Anyway, adipocere doesn't form readily, you know. It's only in very specif-</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">AAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">What now?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I've, I've just remembered something else I read, in another m-magazine about strange phenomena. There was an old lady - maybe a w-witch - who used to pour molten wax over c-corpses and put them on display.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">None of the exhibits in here are real. They're all entirely man-made replicas.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">They can't be! Do you really expect me to believe that? Just look at them!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's no way anybody could make models of people that are this realistic! And...they're all such gruesome scenes... .........Wait.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...no... <thought>I must be seeing things...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is, is this s-some infamous m-m-murderer?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes. Called 'Jane the Ripper'. All her victims were young women.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I knew it! You can t-t-tell by the way she's h-holding that knife. Sure sign of a m-m-murderer!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...Well yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">AAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">What's the matter, Runo?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I've worked it out! I know what she's doing! She's trying to fill that bathtub with blood so she can have a soak in her victims' gore!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Um...not according to the information about the exhibit on the little board here. It doesn't mention anything about the bathtub.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Sorry. I don't think it's significant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>I still think it has to be there for a reason...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That big, heavy curtain is in a very prominent position, isn't it? I've a nasty feeling there's going to be something truly terrifying behind it.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh yes! That's the famous Tusspells Special Exhibit! It depicts one of England's most notorious killers. Do you want to pay the extra fee and have a look?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Pay more money? To be even more terrified? Ooh, let me think about that for a moment...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...It was only a suggestion.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">These models are so well made, I can't tell what's a waxwork and what's a real human.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Or maybe...ALL the exhibits are real people! And when it's closing time and all the visitors have gone home, they suddenly start moving about.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh...just thinking about it makes me wish it was closing time already and I was on my way home...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! That's a funny place for a little ladder.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Iris">What is it? Is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, it's just that in Japanese, we have a totally different word for a ladder that folds in half like that.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">We do in English, too, you know. It's a stepladder, or just 'steps'. So be careful of making assumptions about other cultures, Runo. That's how wars are started.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...I didn't realise stepladders were an international point of contention. But the writer makes an astute point.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... Is, is this an example of Western tsujigiri?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">......... I don't know what that is.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You know, when an unscrupulous samurai randomly attacks a passer-by to test his sword?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...I still don't know, no. But actually, a waxwork samurai would probably be hugely popular. Could you model it, do you think, Runo? Doing that tsujigiri thing you mentioned.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I do have a sword...but I've no intention of testing how sharp it is on a human subject. For now at least.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's...it's... ...the great detective, Mr Herlock Sholmes! <thought>Mr Sholmes has his own wax statue in here? Really?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well he is world-famous, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's an uncanny resemblance, isn't it? It makes my skin crawl to look at it...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I know! But look, Runo. You can kick this Hurley, and he doesn't move a muscle!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You can't go around kicking the exhibits, Iris! .........Wait. It, it just moved, I'm sure. And not just a little bit, either!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hm? Really? Did it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And look closely... ...there are beads of sweat on the face...of this waxwork... model...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Sh-Shall we move on, Iris? ...Over there, look! There's a great murder scene to enjoy! Much more appealing.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow! I take exception to your recoiling in such a manner, as if you've seen something truly abhorrent!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr...Mr Sholmes! <thought>I knew it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Iris, what possessed you?! I strictly forbade you from divulging my temporary waxwork secret to Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Temporary waxwork? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And that kick! Could you not have exercised a little more restraint? You winded me!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But Runo has something he needs to ask you.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah...a question?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And I thought you'd probably be getting bored, too. So here we are!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm... Well, I can't deny that your timing was impeccable. A mere two minutes more being stationary like that... ...and my great brain, upon which all my success has been built, would have turned to wax!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Thank goodness we arrived in time.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed. In many ways, the pair of you just saved the world from an unimaginable loss!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, Hurley! You do like to talk nonsense, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He could know something, it's true. About Lord van Zieks, and what happened in the past to change him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Now that you're here, let's take our time. How can I be of assistance? For you're in luck. I'm suddenly quite taken with the idea of conversing!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...well, actually, I'm in quite a hurry.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And if my eyes don't deceive me... ...I believe something is afoot within the walls of this very museum. A most fascinating case, if I'm not mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Moreover... ...I have a strong suspicion that it is related to the matter about which you've come to me now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>But...how could it be?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">We shall speak again presently, my dear fellow. But for now, I must return to my work.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What, back to being a temporary waxwork exhibit?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">These models are so well made, I can't tell what's a waxwork and what's a real human.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's how Hurley gets away with making himself a temporary exhibit for the day.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Maybe there are other people posing as exhibits in here then...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Or maybe...ALL the exhibits are real people! And when it's closing time and all the visitors have gone home, they suddenly start moving about.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh...just thinking about it makes me wish it was closing time already and I was on my way home...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What is this place?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Madame Tusspells came to London from France three years ago, I understand. Since she opened this little waxwork museum last year, it's enjoyed great popularity in London.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There are museums like this in Japan, too. But these displays are something else! I mean...they aren't made from actual real people, are they?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The extreme realism of these waxwork models is a particular secret of the Tusspells family, they say. They earned renown during the French Revolution for waxworks of victims of the guillotine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... That sounds grim.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The gruesome scenes were portrayed with such realism in the expressions of the faces of the condemned.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Apparently, the sculptors would make the models directly from the corpses, right there at the site of the executions.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">At the...? <thought>That really turns my stomach...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">That's just one of several legends about the Tusspells family. Whether there's any truth in it, I couldn't say. But anyway... ...this museum houses models of famous people from all over the globe. Nevertheless, the most popular area of the museum by quite some margin is this House of Horrors.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">H-House...of H-H-Horrors...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Of course, visitor numbers are dwindling now as a result of the Great Exhibition. But people usually flock here to see the exhibits of some of London's most vile criminals at their gruesome work. Naturally, most of the miscreants portrayed here were sent to the gallows. So they're even stiffer now than the models of them! Ah ha ha ha hah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Have you heard of poor taste?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow, the public live for poor taste! They yearn to be shocked.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...the hideous exhibits in here are...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">They're all portrayals of real events that actually took place!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Is it just me, or did the temperature in here just seem to drop?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Anyway, I advise you not to think too deeply about what you see here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Oh. He's back to being a waxwork, is he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean by a 'temporary waxwork', Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Exactly what you see. I'm part of the exhibits here! Catching these criminals in the act!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Catching them...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Every half an hour, I home in on a different killer in one of the displays and adopt a new pose to ensnare him. When members of the public come for a closer look, I offer them my hand to shake. For a shilling, I'll happily allow them to take a photograph with us!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>'Us'? Does he mean him and the waxwork murderers in here?</thought> But...why, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow, isn't it obvious? For the money!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...He really roared at me there. Very fitting for the House of Horrors.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As it stands, I may struggle to pay this month's rent. And I have the ravenous Iris to consider.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, Hurley...I'm sooo hungry...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">If push comes to shove, I shall have to ask you to do your bit, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">(What's he threatening to rope me into now?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So...with that in mind, how about a photograph? As a special treat, you may have your pick of the murderers and scoundrels in here. The choice is yours!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Maybe some other time.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hmph. ...Remember, Mr Naruhodo: ignore me at your peril!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Back to being a waxwork again. Is it just me, or did his final remark there sound a lot like a curse?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes, would you have a look at this newspaper?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You've been into my room and helped yourself, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Let's not turn this into a scandal, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, considering I've already read it, one thing immediately strikes me: this paper is old news!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What would possess you to show me this? What's done is done! You must distinguish, my dear fellow! Distinguish the old from the new!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>There are some conversations you wish you'd never started...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes, about this...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As you will see, I'm rather busy at the moment. If it's advice you seek, come to my office tomorrow and I shall be happy to help you. Shall we say thruppence per item as a consultation fee?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's two hours of gas, that is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Well? What is it you'd like to ask me, then?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um. Actually, it's... It's about Lord van Zieks.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, our friend Mr Reaper. How did you find him? Well, I trust?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So I'm wondering what it was that happened to make Lord van Zieks such a different person.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I was sure that you'd know, Hurley.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You said there was something going on here in this exhibit hall before. That something was afoot. And that you believed it was related to what I wanted to ask you about.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Mr Sholmes...? <thought>He's suddenly clammed up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, it seems we've reached the unavoida-</line>
<line speaker="???">Greetings...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Ah...hello. <thought>Where did she appear from? And what's she wearing? Could she look any more mysterious?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">I hope...you are appreciating my museum?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry? Have we...? Mr Sholmes, do you know this- <thought>Not again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">My apologies. I am Esmeralda Tusspells. This is my museum of waxwork.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha... You... You're THE Madame Tusspells?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Bien sr. Though only twenty-six years young, I might add.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Is that significant somehow?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">I'm a 'madame' in name only. It adds a certain...je ne sais quoi.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right...</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Firstly, I must apologise for my waxworks. Or rather, one waxwork in particular.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That'll be Mr Sholmes, then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">I was led to believe he was a great detective, but he seems...unable to settle. Next time you move from your designated exhibit...there WILL be toil and trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">She sounds deadly serious.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's a problem. How am I supposed to ask Mr Sholmes about Lord van Zieks now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Let's not forget what Hurley said before. About something being afoot right here in the museum, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I know, but...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I'm so curious! I want to know what's happening here!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Haven't we got enough on our plate already?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He's not even blinking now! He really is a perfect model of a waxwork model!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">I know it doesn't always seem like it, but Hurley's quite a perfectionist in fact. He practises at night sometimes instead of sleeping. Not blinking, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Well, practice makes perfect, I suppose?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I've just realised, though, seeing him standing over there now... He looks like he's that murderer's accomplice, doesn't he? Or henchman, even.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's news to someone, by the look of it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Did you make all these waxworks, Madame Tusspells?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">I did. I am the third generation of waxwork artisans, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Gosh!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">It was my grandmother who began the tradition in my family. Her fortunes were chequered, living through the turbulent times of the French Revolution as she did. Though that is when she acquired the savoir-faire that leads to the astonishing lifelikeness.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">All these waxworks really do look as though they're alive! In fact, they look more alive than Hurley.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Hehe... What you see exhibited here represents the most atrocious of London's criminal past. All the waxworks were created in the presence of the real people on which they are modelled... ...in the hours immediately following their executions. That...is the secret to the extraordinary lifelikeness.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That sounds...terrifying.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">All walks of life have similar challenges, I'm sure. To carry out one's trade par excellence, one must go to extraordinary lengths. My exhibits are a reflection of society. I create only that which the public wishes to see.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... Why couldn't the public have wished for something less horrifying?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Do not fear...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">This room is the only one in the museum with such a macabre theme. I do hope you'll explore. There are models of famous singers, actors, politicians... Something for every taste, I hope.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It was Iris who dragged me straight in here, come to think of it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Sorry. Perhaps I should have eased you into things.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, what's the situation with...that?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Ah, my temporary waxwork model? He approached me some days ago, you see. With a business proposal.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh. What sort of proposal?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear madame, what these sparse exhibits need is the addition of a world-famous great detective!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">...Or words to that effect.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Naturally, I am well aware that Mr Sholmes is widely known in London as a talented detective.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's 'great detective' actually. He's very specific about it.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Yes, the crme de la crme. So I was keen to come to some arrangement with him, of course. But sadly, we were unable to agree terms.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Let me guess: someone wanted to charge an exorbitant price for his services?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">For a mere five hundred pounds, I will dive into your cauldron of wax this very moment!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">...Or words to that effect.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Mr Sholmes might have overdone it slightly with the sales pitch...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Regrettably...the museum has a shortage of funds at the moment, due to...unforeseen circumstances. So we came to the current arrangement instead.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Surely he doesn't really need to do what he's doing though, does he?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">I would think not, but...he was very insistent.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I have a fifty-shilling problem that must be resolved by the morning!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">...Or words to that effect.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It's the pawnbroker, that's what it is. He must have something to redeem.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Is the consulting detective work not going so well...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Madame, there's something I'd like to show you...</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Yes, what is that? I remarked on it to myself immediately and I've been very curious since.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, well, it's actually the mark of a defence lawyer...in the Empire of Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Oh. Quel dommage. Not quite as interesting as I'd hoped.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What exactly were you expecting from an armband?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Could I show you this?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Oh, how fascinating! Is this made of wax?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...No. Sorry. It's a piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Why would you want to show me this?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>She can only wax lyrical about wax, is that it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, I wonder...could I ask you something?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Bien sr...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm just curious. Is anything going on in the museum at the moment. [sic] Some kind of incident, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">......... Whoever suggested such a thing to you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, well, it was... ...your temporary waxwork over there who mentioned it to me a little- Oh! <thought>He's disappeared!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...A wax model is a work of art. Not some tawdry object for trade.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Th-There you are!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Leaving the exhibit again when you should be working? ...Do you wish to be melted down?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear Madame Tusspells, save your reprimands. There are more pressing concerns. The wax can wait. It's our ideas about your current problem we must throw into the melting pot instead!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Personally, I would advise you not to involve the police.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Why ever not?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>She's turned as white as a sheet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Because you have at your disposal a great detective, whose services you may employ for a mere fifty shillings. Though please be aware that I prefer- No, I insist upon payment in advance!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">......... ...Very well. Let us see if the great detective is able to live up to his name, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Before I engage my analytical processes, I must ask you to clarify something. What, pray, is behind the curtain?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">That is the Tusspells Special Exhibit. There is an extra charge to see it.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, the 'special' exhibit in the House of Horrors... It must depict a special killer then, I presume. Would you be so kind as to draw back the curtain, I wonder?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Ah! Absolument non! There is nothing amiss behind there!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Nothing amiss, madame? What about the arm protruding ominously from under the curtain?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I strongly encourage you to allow me to see what lies beyond, before the situation worsens.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">......... Yes, very well. I will draw back the curtains. ...But only a soupon.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I must confess, I peeked behind the curtain earlier. The Tusspells Special Exhibit is a very bleak graveyard scene indeed. And yet somewhat surprisingly... ...the waxwork killer one would expect is nowhere to be seen. What does strike one, however... ...is the portly gentleman lying peacefully on his back on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, well then perhaps, Mr Sholmes... ...that man on the floor is the ruthless killer himself!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm afraid not, my dear fellow. He's a perfectly ordinary London gentleman. Not even a waxwork, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As skilfully made as these waxworks are, they are always distinguishable from real humans. So, allow me to present my two conclusions. The first... ...is that a sizeable business transaction has been taking place in this special exhibit.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Why...? Why would you say that?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And the second... ...is that the aforementioned transaction is linked to a serious crime!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">AAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>She looks as pale as candle wax...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">I, I don't understand...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So, Madame Tusspells, as you've agreed to my fee... ...you shall now have the pleasure of seeing this famously great detective - and temporary exhibit - at work.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">To begin with, we must ask ourselves what exactly is afoot here in this museum? The answer is revealed by the bundle of banknotes protruding so helpfully from your bag. In my estimation, some...two hundred pounds.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">That, that is all my own money!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So what does this large sum of money reveal? Ah, not as much as the involuntary glance you cast, it would seem, Madame Tusspells. Yes, the answer lies where your eyes now fall. The significance of the two hundred pounds is revealed by that public notice! 'Waxwork for sale'? Your business has hit hard times, it would seem. In short... ...you sold the infamous killer - the centrepiece of your special exhibit - for the sum of two hundred pounds!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Nooooooooon!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Now...let us explore the next curiosity with which we are presented. Who is the portly gentleman stretched out so peacefully on the floor?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It would appear the man has suffered a severe shock. The cause of which...is clearly known to you.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Unfortunately, madame, keeping secrets does not appear to be your forte. What dealt the man such a shocking blow was of course... the two hundred pounds! It would appear that you twisted this gentleman around your little finger most effectively.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">What are you suggesting?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">He rashly agreed to purchase the waxwork for the sum of two hundred pounds. Only when he came to hand the money over, did it occur to him what an extortionate amount he was paying. But the money was no longer in his hands. And the result? The scene we see before us. He collapsed in shock. Yes, the killer in this special exhibit fetched a killer price! We can only pray that the gentleman's dreams are not plagued with regret...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The question that arises then, is what has become of the waxwork that changed hands? Let us consider that problem for a moment.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">You, you cannot possibly...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What immediately strikes me about this conundrum, is the young man standing over there. Who is this fellow? To find the answer, we need only observe...his neckerchief. Such as is worn by policemen as a secret sign to fellow members of the force that a crime is being perpetrated. Yes, this young man is an undercover policeman, currently investigating this museum. I know him well, in fact. It's Sergeant John Clay.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The man's quite a celebrity. He received triple accolades at last year's policing awards.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">But...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Next we turn our attention to the old man sat before him with the particularly unsightly visage. I've been watching closely and he hasn't moved a muscle. Almost, in fact...as if he were a waxwork.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Ah! But, but you...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Your reaction only confirms my suspicions, madame. I noticed it at once, of course... Observe! The telltale sign that instantly proves whether or not this old man is a waxwork is the obvious price tag! 'Thruppence'...? A tragically low price, you might say. Though perhaps the going rate for ageing waxworks riddled with cracks. And yet you sold it to the portly gentleman for an exorbitant two hundred pounds! The sort of plucky behaviour that's sure to attract the attention of Scotland Yard... Isn't that so, madame?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">I, I do not...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, the waxwork you sold has already been seized by the police and remains in their custody as we speak! The old man must be reunited with his grave in the special exhibit, and not a moment too soon!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Thus concludes Herlock Sholmes's great deduction...of this horrifying puzzle!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I see I've stunned you all into silence.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You have, Hurley, you have. And you've obviously upset this young lady in the process. Her cauldron looks awfully hot...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...if I could just bring up one point, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah! The notorious Naruhodo 'one point'! I'm all ears, my dear fellow!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">According to your deduction, then, the special exhibit featured this old policeman. So...that would mean that he's the particularly ruthless murderer, wouldn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... The killer policeman, Ottermole.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It was a mysterious series of murders that rattled the capital only last year. The police rushed to the scene every time, only to find the culprit had disappeared into the aether.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And it turned out the culprit was a policeman himself! A senior officer by the name of Ottermole!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you mean that's who the sinister-looking old man there is supposed to be?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed. It is a particularly grim face, is it not? Unforgettable, in fact. Yes, I remember that odious countenance only too well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But is two hundred pounds a lot of money for a wax model?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It would be enough to afford one of the latest steam carriages, if that puts things in perspective?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">S-So...it is quite a lot then.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">......... Is there anything else you wish to add? Before I melt you down.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That bubbling wax is looking more and more ominous...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ugh...the smell of all that molten wax is starting to worry me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes did more or less just accuse her to her face, so... I think I might have to call on your assistance here, Iris, if that's alright? To make some minor corrections to the great detective's great deductions...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Of course it's alright! We'll soon set things straight!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...let's get started then, shall we? Before Madame Tusspells vents her anger!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Just what I was waiting to hear, my dear fellow! So, Madame Tusspells, in accordance with our agreement... ...you shall now have the pleasure of seeing this famously great detective - and temporary exhibit - at work.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">To begin with, we must ask ourselves what exactly is afoot here in this museum? The answer is revealed by the bundle of banknotes protruding so helpfully from your bag. In my estimation, some...two hundred pounds.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">That, that is all my own money!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So what does this large sum of money reveal? Ah, not as much as the involuntary glance you cast, it would seem, Madame Tusspells. Yes, the answer lies where your eyes now fall. The significance of the two hundred pounds is revealed by that public notice!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">She definitely looked in this direction, it's true.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But I'm not sure she'd sell any of her waxworks, even for two hundred pounds.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">She must pour her heart and soul into making them, don't you think? Over and above the wax. If it were me, I wouldn't sell them for anything.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>For that much money, I would! ...But it sounds like that makes me a bad person.</thought> W-Well anyway... ...I wonder if the two hundred pounds could have some other significance.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Let's follow that furtive glance again and see if there's anything else that could explain it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Waxwork for sale'? Would anyone really buy models of mass murderers?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I think I'd rather have two hundred pounds in my pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Exactly. You could buy one of those brand new types of steam carriage! That's what I'd spend it on if I had it, no question.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ooh, I'd buy all the herbs in the world!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>There must be another explanation for the money... We need to keep looking.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It seems this well-dressed gentleman is alive after all. Just not alive and kicking. And he's not a waxwork or a model of a mass murderer.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I'm not sure I'd pay two hundred pounds for him...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't think the man's up for sale!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well anyway, it was a silly place to put him. Other museum visitors could easily trip.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't think the man was put there on purpose, either!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">What's that note doing pinned on the wall there?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes. Let's see... 'Dear Madame Tusspells, We've taken the prisoner from this room. The price for his safe return is two hundred pounds. Have the money ready by noon on 23rd October.'</line>
<line speaker="Iris">WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This, this is... It's just like the sort of thing that's left behind when someone is kidnapped!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes! It's a ransom note!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Exactly!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Dear Madame Tusspells, We've taken the prisoner from this room. The price for his safe return is two hundred pounds. Have the money ready by noon on 23rd October.'</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You can't deny, that's a very well-written ransom note. Clear and concise.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And the ransom amount is two hundred pounds...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo, with that answer you haven't righted my reasoning in any way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As a logician, you will never surpass me. The science of deduction and analysis requires long and patient study. I'm several steps ahead of you. And your attempts to correct me serve only to highlight your deficiencies.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...this is what you get for agreeing with someone? <thought>(I need to reconsider my answer, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Shirking of that nature will hasten the end of the world, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The end of the world?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And there is a distinct possibility that the man has no knowledge of the money, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So, do you cause the destruction of our planet...or continue with the deduction process? The choice is yours.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Looks like I'd better get back to saving the world, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Shirking of that nature will hasten the end of the universe, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The end of the universe?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">At the very least, you could examine the note before jumping to conclusions. You owe the universe that much, my dear fellow!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well, if it's for the survival of the universe, I suppose I could...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Judging by appearances... ...this man and the two hundred pounds are in no way related at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The poor man was just in the wrong place at the wrong time, it seems...</thought> But there's no doubt that Madame Tusspells did react to what Mr Sholmes said. The way she automatically looked over this way must tell us something, I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...Then let's have more of a look around!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The significance of the two hundred pounds is revealed by that ransom note!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Quite so. And we must congratulate these criminals on their inventiveness, abducting a waxwork.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Two hundred pounds is no small ransom fee. Yet you clearly intend to pay it.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">The model in question has...special importance. So I put together all the money I have...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In summary, then! The two hundred pounds you have in your handbag...is ransom money! Now...let us explore the next curiosity with which we are presented. Who is the portly gentleman stretched out so peacefully on the floor?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It would appear the man has suffered a severe shock. The cause of which...is clearly known to you.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Unfortunately, madame, keeping secrets does not appear to be your forte. What dealt the man such a shocking blow was of course... the two hundred pounds!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So if the waxwork was kidnapped, where does that leave us in terms of who this man is?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">We could just ask him when he comes around.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I think the point of this exercise is to understand the beauty of the deduction process, Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, you're right. Hurley's trying so hard, we mustn't let him down.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, there's little doubt that he suffered a shock. That much seems clear. But in that case, what's Madame Tusspells trying to hide? Let's have a closer look around...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">So she was prepared to pay all that money to get her waxwork back again? It really must have been a very special model.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Of a mass murderer. Just how special can a model of a ruthless killer be?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well anyway, we can be fairly sure the man lying on the floor didn't take it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I suppose we should leave him in peace...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Madame Tusspells has very long hair, doesn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, but you couldn't tell looking at her from the front.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You know...it looks rather like a whip, don't you think? The sort of whip that could have floored the gentleman with a single crack!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That seems a little far-fetched, even for you, Runo.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">This is just Madame Tusspells's right hand, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, it must be. I can clearly see her left hand, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, but wait a minute... This is a left hand as well, look.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... D-Don't say such c-creepy things, Iris, please!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And...it seems very stiff, too. In fact...it's really hard.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You, you mean...? <thought>...it's made of wax?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">This is just Madame Tusspells's right hand, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, it must be. I can clearly see her left hand, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, but wait a minute... This is a left hand as well, look.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... D-Don't say such c-creepy things, Iris, please!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And...it seems very stiff, too. In fact...it's really hard.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You, you mean...? <thought>...it's made of wax?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo, with that answer you haven't righted my reasoning in any way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As a logician, you will never surpass me. The science of deduction and analysis requires long and patient study. I'm several steps ahead of you. And your attempts to correct me serve only to highlight your deficiencies.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...this is what you get for agreeing with someone? <thought>I need to reconsider my answer, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm afraid your imagination is overactive.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well yes, perhaps I was clutching at straws a little...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I, on the other hand, can picture the scene of your spiked hair running the man through quite clearly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And you say my imagination is overactive...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In that case, perhaps I should ask that she knocks some sense into you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You've missed a crucial clue right before your eyes! The art of deduction relies not just on observational skills, but on GOOD observational skills!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It must have been a considerable blow to have knocked the man unconscious.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, he looks like a very sturdy man, doesn't he? Ooh! Perhaps he was struck on the back of the head with something hard?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Don't sound so excited about it, Iris. <thought>Whatever did leave the man out cold like that, it must have been quite something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What dealt the man such a shocking blow was of course... the waxwork hand!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed. With a solid waxwork limb, one could deliver a very substantial blow.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">How, how could you...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The hand protruding from the bottom of your cape... It ought to be a right hand, but closer inspection reveals that in fact, it's a left hand.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And somewhat masculine as well. In other words, it does not belong to you, madame. It is the hand of a waxwork model!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">KYAAAAAAH! Some of the visitors to my museum can be...troublesome. They meddle with the exhibits and cause damage.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you mean, that arm...?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Yes. This gentleman saw fit to try to remove it as a souvenir.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm, no small keepsake.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Like taking a whole branch of a cherry tree when you go to view the blossoms...</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">I am afraid I had to teach the man a lesson.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You confronted the man and tried to take the arm back.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And the result? The scene we see before us. He was knocked unconscious. A point we may need to revisit later. But for the time being, we have our conclusion: Yes, the killer in this special exhibit has been kidnapped!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The question that arises then, is what has become of the waxwork that changed hands? Let us consider that problem for a moment.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">You, you cannot possibly...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What immediately strikes me about this conundrum, is the young man standing over there. Who is this fellow? To find the answer, we need only observe...his neckerchief.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">According to Mr Sholmes... ...the yellow neckerchief is a sign to other policemen that some crime is underway.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">A way of communicating with his colleagues without revealing his identity, yes. It's a secret that's closely guarded by Scotland Yard.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That Mr Sholmes didn't hesitate to give away.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, uncovering secrets is in any true detective's nature, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right... Anyway, judging from Madame Tusspells's reaction to Mr Sholmes's deduction... ...I think perhaps we might not have identified the man quite correctly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A secret scarf sign to warn other agents of an ongoing crime...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I know! It sounds so thrilling, doesn't it? Maybe I'll try to work it into next month's instalment.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But then the police's secret will be revealed to all of London's six million inhabitants.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, they'll just have to come up with a new sign, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>How does this ten-year-old manage to have such terrifying influence?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I've seen hats like this in Japan as well. They're called flat caps, aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, or hunting caps. Hurley's hat is called a deerstalker, by the way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Hunting...stalking... The British certainly seem keen on catching game...</thought> Every time I see a deerstalker, I automatically think of Mr Sholmes... ...but a flat cap makes me think of a Japanese country gentleman, somehow. <thought>In other words people from all walks of life wear all different types of hat... So that doesn't really help us.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What the...? The man has a stub sticking out of his shoulder where his arm should be!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah. Well that settles that, then.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right. This isn't a real person at all.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">His entire arm's been ripped off, from the shoulder down.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">His arm's been...? <thought>Of course. That ties in with what we just found out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo, with that answer you haven't righted my reasoning in any way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As a logician, you will never surpass me. The science of deduction and analysis requires long and patient study. I'm several steps ahead of you. And your attempts to correct me serve only to highlight your deficiencies.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...this is what you get for agreeing with someone? <thought>I need to reconsider my answer, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo, your powers of deduction are improving. But in your own words, there's just 'one thing'... Are you and I not both run-of-the-mill Londoners, too?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">On second thoughts, you yourself may not quite satisfy that description.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'm not sure that you do, either.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">According to Mr Sholmes, this young gentleman is actually a policeman in plain clothes. And the secret scarf sign appears to back that idea up. It does seem plausible.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But Madame Tusspells's reaction was strange. Which must mean...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That we haven't got to the bottom of who or what this man really is yet.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Who is this fellow? To find the answer, we need only observe...his shoulder stub.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">No such boneless human walks this earth. Of that, I can assure you. In other words, the man standing here - the young Sergeant John Clay... ...is in fact, defying all odds, a waxwork model!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I seem to remember it was you who concluded he was a real person in the first place, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">He has become quite a celebrity in London, being the winner of no less than three policing awards last year. I simply had to make a model of the man.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Naturally! What other explanation could there be?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And it was this detective's arm that was pulled off by the man on the floor in the special exhibit, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Next we turn our attention to the old man sat before him with the particularly unsightly visage. I've been watching closely and he hasn't moved a muscle. Almost, in fact...as if he were a waxwork.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Ah! But, but you...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Your reaction only confirms my suspicions, madame. I noticed it at once, of course... Observe! The telltale sign that instantly proves whether or not this old man is a waxwork is the obvious price tag!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A killer policeman...called Ottermole, was it? Was he well known?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It was all over the papers last year. But I can't say I know what he looks like. It's a very low price, though. Thruppence isn't much money.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Only enough for a few measly hours of gas in Mr Garrideb's delightful lodgings, in fact...</thought> So this is the special killer taken from the special exhibit...is it? The waxwork that somebody stole from the museum and tried to ransom for two hundred pounds... ...is this crusty old killer policeman Ottermole? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Perhaps we should have a good look around again and see if another idea crops up!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Three pence? It's a far cry from two hundred pounds, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">For thruppence, you could buy it and put it on display in your room, Runo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I think I'd rather not go to sleep being watched by an old man, if it's all the same to you.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">This price tag does stand out, doesn't it? I mean, you couldn't even buy the helmet on his head for that much money, I don't think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I wonder what the price tag's really for, then...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I don't believe it!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It's the secret sign that lets other detectives know some criminal activity is underway!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...it's a slightly strange choice of outfit if he was trying to go unnoticed...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah! He must be a detective disguised as a policeman!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Or a detective disguised as a waxwork model of a policeman!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">He doesn't look like he's clever enough to think of something like that, though...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Perhaps you should try to be a little more polite about him, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">L-Look at this! The old man's tapping his foot like crazy!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">He seems to be fast asleep, though.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He's, he's not tapping his foot consciously, then? So you mean...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...It must be a twitch!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Never mind that! The point is, waxworks don't tap their feet!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Or twitch!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And look at his arm, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo, with that answer you haven't righted my reasoning in any way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As a logician, you will never surpass me. The science of deduction and analysis requires long and patient study. I'm several steps ahead of you. And your attempts to correct me serve only to highlight your deficiencies.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...this is what you get for agreeing with someone? <thought>I need to reconsider my answer, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo, pray...what part of this man's outfit would you call 'plain clothes'?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And I believe I described the man as young, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It was only last year that I saw him being awarded his triple accolades at the policing awards. They say detective work can age a man, but this would be extreme, I'm sure you'll agree.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well, I know I suddenly feel ten years older after that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">If we just poured a little bit of molten wax on him, we'd soon find out if he was real or not.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...you never know, there may be another way. We've already come this far, so maybe we should stick to logical deductions, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Alright, if that's the way you want to do it, then we should examine him in more detail.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>If anyone saw, they'd think we were obsessed with the elderly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The telltale sign that instantly proves whether or not this old man is a waxwork is the obvious twitch!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Even the most realistic waxworks do not exhibit a twitch. In other words, this splendid old man is in fact a genuine member of Scotland Yard!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Slight shift in your choice of adjectives, then...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And there you have it! Well, Madame Tusspells?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Well what? It was me who contacted the police and demanded that someone come in the first place. He is clearly fatigued. He is sound asleep.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But then, what's this tag about showing a price of three pence?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">No doubt the price tag of the muffler, which the old bobby purchased recently at a local market. And I presume you've observed the scarf tied around his arm? Does that not strike you, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes! The secret sign used by detectives to show that some criminal activity is currently underway.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Of course. Because, as you know, there has been just such criminal activity happening here. As you deduced from the very beginning, detective.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So, it would seem that we finally arrive at the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The waxwork of the especially ruthless killer from the special exhibit has been kidnapped.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And Scotland Yard are already investigating. But the model's whereabouts remain a mystery. Thus concludes Herlock Sholmes's great deduction...of this horrifying puzzle!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">All sorts of people visit my museum here. Men and women, young and old. Sometimes they drop in just for a short time on their way back from the pub. I welcome them all. But if anyone tries to damage my exhibits... I do not take it lightly. Anyway... ...your great deduction was even more enchanting than I had been led to believe.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It was a pleasure, my dear madame. I'm gratified that you enjoyed the spectacle. And as for your 'rough customer', I've no doubt he'll regain consciousness shortly and return home. What concerns me more... ...is the waxwork from the special display...if it was indeed genuinely abducted?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">......... Yes. Tragically, it was...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Then I would ask you to recount to us the events surrounding the stolen waxwork. In as much detail as possible, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">...Very well. But after I have told you what I know, I must insist that you return to your work.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... The talents of a great detective could be put to better use, I feel, but as you wish...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... It's just a collapsed man.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">At least it turned out he's not one of the mass murderers' victims.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">True. But he is one of the waxworks' victims in a way, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...He's not showing any signs of life.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Because he really is dead...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Come on, you're always pointing that finger of yours in court. Poke that arm now and see how it feels.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Tell us more about the stolen waxwork, please.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">It was some days ago now, when I came in here one morning. I immediately noticed that a waxwork was missing from the special exhibit here!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It is your most prominent display. So...that's why the curtains were closed.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">And I found the ransom note in its place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The culprit must have broken in during the night and taken it, then?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">So this waxwork that was stolen... It was a model of some horrible criminal, I suppose?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">......... Of a particularly horrible criminal, in fact. The killer who left a more profound scar on society than any other, I would say: the Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Not a name I've heard of.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So, Mr Naruhodo...it seems the circle is complete.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">The Professor case happened at around the time I was born, didn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed it did, Iris. Ten years ago. A series of murders that rocked the capital.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ten years ago?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes. At exactly the time... ...that Barok van Zieks graduated from university, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? <thought>S-Surely he's not saying...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">So the big event that changed Mr Reaper's life...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... As you've surmised. It was the Professor case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Who was this Professor then?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">It was a series of gruesome murders that had all of London gripped in terror a decade ago. After five victims were killed, the man was arrested, and put to death.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And now he's immortalised here in wax for all Londoners to admire and enjoy! Though of course, he happens to be absent at present, on account of the abduction.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But I don't understand. How is all this related to Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... You must first understand, my dear fellow, why it is that the Professor earnt such infamy. It was due to the victims he chose. Some of Whitehall's finest.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">What do you mean, Hurley?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Those murdered by the Professor were some of the highest members of the British aristocracy. Members of the nobility. Even royalty. It sent shockwaves through the country's administration.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Members of the... Ah! Wait! Of course! What Professor Harebrayne said! Lord van Zieks is from a family with noble blood!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh gosh!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It was the fifth victim that led to the Professor's arrest. The last of the killer's prey was a young noble by the name of... ...Klint van Zieks.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No! I don't believe it! Van Zieks?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm sure you can piece together the rest for yourself. In the wake of his older brother's murder, the young Barok pursued a career as a prosecutor. And eventually...became the Reaper we know today.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I had no idea Lord van Zieks had such a tragic past...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, I'm afraid that's all I can say on the matter. For the time being at least. After all, I have work to do... ...as a waxwork exhibit.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">I am afraid I shall have to excuse myself as well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, yes, of course. It's, it's been a pleasure. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="???">...Well, none of the predicted scenarios I've been analysing involved you coming to visit me here.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">It's been too long, it really has. I'm delighted to see you, Barok.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It's been ten years. And here we are, meeting in a prison of all places.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I can't forgive myself for what happened to Mr Asman! I just can't! I, I still can't believe it could happen...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Tomorrow the court will decide.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yes! I have a young Eastern man acting for my defence. He seems reliable enough, though. It, it was an accident. A terrible accident. He, he, he assures me he can prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I must warn you...</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Oh, I know, I know! I've heard already. You're going to be prosecuting, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... Since I returned to England, I've heard lots of stories. Barok, are you really...?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... Never mind. I know that you have my best interests at heart.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">My friend is on trial. ...I wouldn't entrust it to anybody else.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Of course. I fully understand. Thank you, Barok.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Until tomorrow, then. I'll see you in court.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't find anything out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Nothing particular of note...</thought></line>
</xml>