<xml>
<title>The First Story</title>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't quite know what to say... I am truly shocked... ...to see the Storyteller again! Alive and well!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">This was unexpected by me too, as I did not plan to appear before you all again. I was convinced that you would all see the last of me at the parade.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But...this is the trial for your murder! And you are alive...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! See? No one was killed! So let's call this whole thing off and never have witch trials again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-whoa, Maya...take it easy. We're still in court, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But what's the point of this? The Storyteller wasn't killed! Espella would never do anything to harm her dad!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But...Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Search your memory and you will know the reason why. The crime Miss Cantabella is accused of is not just murder. The purpose of the Witches' Court is to sentence the witches for what they are. Isn't that right, Mr Storyteller?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I fully intend to expose the true identity of Bezella. And this would not be possible... ...without you, Mr Storyteller, on the witness stand.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I see... And so, you assumed the role of an inquisitor just to lure me here?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Be that as it may, the inquisition still maintains that... Espella Cantabella is the Great Witch Bezella!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ Dad...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">It's been a long time, Espella. Four years, in fact. You must have experienced many hardships, living among the townsfolk. This daughter of mine...never fits in with the others, no matter how hard she tries.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">No, it wasn't quite like that. There were people who supported me. Aunt Patty was very kind, and the customers who came to our bakery were nice to me.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I'm happy to hear that. I wanted to watch over you, ever since you left for the town. But in the end...I failed to do so. I had no idea of what was happening to you. I am...very sorry, Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh, Dad, you don't need to apologise to me for anything. It's me that owes you an apology. I was...I was...trying to hurt you...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">It was all my fault, not yours. There's no reason for you to blame yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Dad...I'm happy we got to talk.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">You were so busy writing everyone's stories that we stopped talking to each other... Before...it was different. You used to have time for me.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Please forgive me. Why did it have to come to this...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Storyteller. It's time to put everything in order now.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">...!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The townsfolk and your daughter deserve to know the truth. The truth about yourself and the Story.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............ Yes, I suppose it is time I told you the truth. ...Your Honour!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-yes, Mr Storyteller?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Let us begin. In this trial...I shall be judged.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ Understood. The witness shall testify!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">People of Labyrinthia who have gathered in this court! I will now tell you the true story. Many of you will certainly find it hard to believe and difficult to accept. Nevertheless, I ask you to please lend me an ear and listen with open minds. Espella, my dear daughter... I ask you to do the same, too.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Although you know me as the Storyteller, I have one more identity. I am the president of Labrelum Inc.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ I...I don't understand. What does it all mean? I don't quite understand what I've just heard.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I do not blame you. I suppose all the townsfolk are just as confused. Labyrinthia is an artificial town, created entirely by me. But, of course...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I...I am lost for words. It feels as if the whole world has been turned on its head.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Your Honour, it is certainly not an easy matter to grasp this new situation at once. Regardless, I suggest we hear more of what the witness has to say.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I agree, let's continue. The defence may begin the interrogation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Although you know me as the Storyteller, I have one more identity. I am the president of Labrelum Inc.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Labrelum Inc.? That's a name I have heard before. It is a global pharmaceutical company with headquarters in England. If my memory serves me right, it was founded by Arthur Cantabella.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Indeed. That is my true name.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Were you familiar with that, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-sure! Yeah! I've, uhh...heard of Labrelum Inc., of course.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Labrelum Inc. is known for developing a completely harmless anaesthetic about 20 years ago. It is now widely used in hospitals all around the world. The company is also working on various other plant-derived sedatives, revolutionising medicine.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I suppose I shouldn't be surprised by your vast knowledge, Mr Layton.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The real world, Mr Wright? Then what would you call the world we are in now? Do you think this is a fantasy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, that's not quite what I meant...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright, I do not mean to be so rude as to presume I know what thoughts are running through your head... However, Labyrinthia is certainly not a place within a book or in the past. Labyrinthia is a part of the world we know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh... WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But, but! How could a town like this exist in the real world?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Do you think it's impossible? Why would that be? Are you saying that everyone would know about an unusual town like this, if it existed?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's...something like that. Anyway, it would be on a map, at least!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">No. I'm afraid that cannot be so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">This town is not marked on any map. It doesn't officially exist.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">The answer is quite simple.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">This whole town...is one of Labrelum's research facilities. It may be hard for you to comprehend...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Yes. This whole area is a private property of Labrelum Inc.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So...they own all this land, then.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">That is why Labyrinthia is not marked on any map and people from the outside cannot enter. We have taken measures to ensure that this town is not noticed by local residents.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What measures are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Consider the fact that magic is supposed to exist in this town. Perhaps special mechanisms that were used to create "magic" also serve to conceal Labyrinthia. There are limits to what "magic" the Shades are capable of producing on their own, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">That is the case indeed. The "magic" in this town has been made feasible owing to the latest technology.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Tech...technology? Tricks? I cannot believe this...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">However, there is one question... There is no industry in Labyrinthia. How do you obtain necessary commodities?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Very observant, aren't you? All commodities are regularly shipped in by sea. A young man once made his way here on a freighter and took Espella out of the town.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That was Carmine Accidenti, a friend of mine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, I see... But, is something on this scale really possible?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">As you might suspect, it would be beyond the power of Labrelum Inc. to keep a facility this size a secret for so long. Labyrinthia is a project co-funded by the British government.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? It's a government project? But what would be their stake in this?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............ It's all because of my beliefs.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>His beliefs?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ Ah, by the way...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Yes? Your Honour?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is a research facility? I've never heard of anything like that before.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Ah yes, that was careless of me. Naturally, you wouldn't know what it means. How should I explain... This whole town is my creation.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, that's what it was about! In other words, it's all your Story. That makes it all clear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Swing and a miss, Your Honour...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Getting back to the topic... There is an important reason why we have chosen to build such a facility here.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">This land is rich in a very special substance, which affects everyone who lives here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">This area has been isolated since ancient times, developing its own unique culture.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There are underground ruins on the verge of the town. We've found writings there, presumably left by the natives of this land. A bell that was supposed to be there was missing.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............ So you have seen the ruins. I suspected that you would find them. Then perhaps you have also noticed... that everyone who lives here has a very peculiar condition.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A peculiar condition, you say! [sic] I can't just sit here quietly like a patient old man when you're saying such things! Just what kind of condition is it?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">You have every right to know. This condition makes people fall unconscious upon the sound of a certain metal being struck.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-metal? What kind of metal?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Pure silver. And so there is not a single object made of silver in Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that I think of it, that's true. Just imagine what a disaster a fancy dinner would be, if everyone fainted whenever they used silver cutlery...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">This condition is an integral part of "magic".</line>
<line speaker="Layton">How so?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">All inhabitants of Eldwitch Woods carry small silver bells.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I see now. The Shades ring the bells when they need to create the illusion of magic. Everyone present falls unconscious, and the Shades set to their work.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, look at where that Shade's hand was! So that's the secret of the time-stealing magic Darklaw told us about!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that they mention it... Kira had a small bell with her when we saw her back at the marketplace...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">We have been researching this condition at Labrelum Inc. And finally, we discovered its cause. It was the groundwater.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Water causes it?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">The groundwater contains a certain unique substance found in the soil in this area.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So if you drink that water, you get this... silver allergy thing?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-but...of course we've been drinking it. It's impossible to live without water.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Of course. That's why everyone who lives here has that condition.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh...oh dear...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">You needn't worry. This condition is harmless. Especially as silver is unknown to the townsfolk.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hm, something's still not quite right though. If the sound of silver bells makes people pass out, why don't the Shades pass out, too?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Although the effect of the substance in the groundwater is powerful, it doesn't last long. The condition will vanish after a day or so without drinking that water.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh...that's convenient...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">That substance's effects aren't limited to humans. It can also affect plants to a great extent.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Plants...are affected by it?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Our research was focused on the plants rather than humans.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">This substance enables the manipulation of people's minds. And that is what Labrelum is researching.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">The substance enters the groundwater, affecting organisms that consume it.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">People who drink it daily acquire that odd condition. They fall unconscious upon hearing the sound of silver metal.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Yes. Although, the substance in the groundwater also has a tremendous effect on plants. Wild flowers in this area contain a certain poison.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Upon my beard! Poison?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">This poison doesn't harm the body. It has the effect of manipulating the mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So it brainwashes people...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I've been writing the Story for ten years...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The title of the Story is... Historia Labyrinthia?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">The ink I used to write it...was made from those plants.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, Nick! Do you remember how funny the ink smelled?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">That was the gas released when the ink evaporates. And that's where the trick is.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaat?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Those that inhale the gas become extremely susceptible to suggestion.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You mean, brainwashing?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">They will believe anything they are told, or anything they read, however strange or unrealistic. It will be imprinted into their minds as the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">So that was the true purpose of the parades. Pages of the Story, written in that special ink, were regularly distributed among the townspeople. It was done so that everyone would be in a state of hypnosis.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Indeed. "The Creation of a Fully Controlled Town with the Inhabitants Subject to Long-Term Hypnosis" That was one of the topics of our research.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then...the story that is written in the Historia Labyrinthia...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You could call it a self-fulfilling prophecy, realised through the Shades' work and the hypnotic effect of the ink vapours.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is that...how it was all this time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Labrelum used hypnosis to control all these people... I can't believe that the government was supporting that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">This experiment began ten years ago. The townsfolk all became test subjects.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">No, we started with just a few people, gradually getting more and more.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I must say that I am afraid of what the answer to this question might be, but where did these people come from? You haven't resorted to abduction by any chance, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Of course not. Every test subject signed a contract with Labrelum.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A contract to have their memories erased and be used like pawns in a story?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">The current inhabitants of this town have one thing in common. They were all dissatisfied with their lives and wanted to start anew. Forgetting about their mistakes, forsaking unwanted identities. There are more people like that out there than you might think. They have all agreed to participate in our research.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But...that's insane...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">It's not as unreasonable as you suggest. We give them a new identity, a chance to start their life again. In return, they subject themselves to hypnosis and live in this town as our test subjects. In order for this project to be possible... we suppress their memories of the past, including the memory of signing the contract. So, ultimately, they are not aware of what is going on.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I couldn't agree more. I've got no idea what's going on.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Let me make this clear, Mr Wright. We do not erase their memories. We suppress them. They will regain their memories of life before Labyrinthia once their contract is over.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, this place was uninhabited before you started this research ten years ago?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And you've managed to keep everyone in a state of hypnosis for ten years straight?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Can you really hypnotise someone for that long? I mean, ten years is one heck of a long time.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">It was achieved through the distribution of the Story during parades. The ink vapours have a powerful effect, but it wouldn't last ten years, of course. With each parade, the effect was renewed. That's why the parades took place at regular intervals. That was the true purpose of that event.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All right...so that's it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">That was...sorta mind-blowing, wasn't it? The townspeople seem to be in shock. They've gone completely quiet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No kidding. They just heard that their town is really a research facility run by some company.</thought> At least Mr Cantabella seems prepared to tell us the whole, honest-to-goodness truth. So let's put our surprise to the side and get every last detail out of him.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! Let's press him on everything he says, from start to finish!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's a shocking revelation, even for us... I've got to stay focused and pay attention to everything he has to say.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I have been born and raised here. It was a poor, small town with no industry to speak of, that had fallen behind the times. Ever since I was a child, I had one friend that was especially close to me. He was a bright boy, curious about the world. His name was Newton Belduke.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Sir Newton Belduke...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So they were childhood friends... The plot thickens.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">He had always been interested in the unique natural features of this land. There was really nothing here, but to us this area was an exciting place worth exploring. And one day we made an astonishing discovery on the outskirts of the town. We stumbled upon the entrance to the underground caverns leading to the colossal ruins.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">That is all that we managed to decipher.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Bezella's curse...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It was sealed in the ruins, you say? Would that be the Bell of Ruin?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">The Bell...of Ruin...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, that's the bell from the bell tower. I wonder why it's got an ominous name like that.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Regrettably, we couldn't get any further information from the writings at the time. Needless to say, Newton and I were very excited by the discovery.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">And so Newton began studying the indigenous plants, and substances dissolved in the groundwater. On the other hand, I studied economics and management at a university in London. I dreamed of bringing prosperity to this poor, forgotten town. I wanted to change it for the better with my own hands. Meanwhile, Newton had succeeded at extracting a new anaesthetic from the local plants.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Was that the anaesthetic which led to the foundation of Labrelum?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Yes. It was a huge success for Labrelum Inc. And before we knew it, we were making a fortune. We wanted the whole world to hear about our home town. Alas, fate was not kind to us, as we never realised that dream. Everyone in our town...had died. All the townspeople perished.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Just what on earth happened to them?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............ That does not matter any more. We purchased the environs of our town - the mountains, the lake, the plains...everything. Then, ten years ago... having received financial support from the government, we started Project Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">More people were signing the contract with Labrelum, slowly increasing the number of inhabitants, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Yes. They would sign the contract, be hypnotised and assigned a role, and then be introduced to the world of the Story.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I have spoken at length. Thank you for patiently listening to my tale. "Bezella" is the name of a witch from an ancient legend that we read about in the ruins. It is a fictional character. She does not exist.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-but then...magic and witches...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Magic is just an illusion. And there are no witches.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All right, so it was all fake... That doesn't make it much better! Why did you write a story where people get killed with magic and witches are thrown into the fire? You could've made it a peaceful, pleasant world, where everyone would be happy!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">No, that was not possible.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But why?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">This is a research facility, after all. We're researching ways to completely control human beings. Test subjects need to be exposed to extreme situations, so we decided on a fantasy setting. We wouldn't have got funding from the government otherwise. In other words, we're running a business.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But just what instructions do you give to the people you hypnotise? You don't give each of them a full set of memories of their whole fictional life, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">No, it's much more simple than that. We only give them two pieces of information. The first one - that they were born in this town. And the second was their new occupation. Then they fill in the gaps themselves, without being aware of it. The human mind requires a consistent story of one's life. Which means, of course... that no Labyrinthian has memories from earlier than ten years ago. No one has any memories from before they came to Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What...what are you saying...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">As you can hear, no one can remember their real past. There are no exceptions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? Wait a second... No exceptions? I smell a contradiction here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah, it seems Mr Wright, too, has noticed it now.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">What are you talking about, Layton?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr Cantabella, you have just testified that... not a single citizen of this town remembers anything from more than ten years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Yes, as that is the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, that's a strange assertion, especially coming from you.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">What? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is one person in this town... who remembers what happened more than ten years ago!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">That cannot be! It is impossible. They must be merely imagining things now!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright, please enlighten us all. Who is this person that remembers their past?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, of course! You're Hershel Layton!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That's a weight off my mind. I was concerned for a moment that your memories had evaporated, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is to say, pull yourself together, defender!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arghhhhhhhh! <thought>Dang.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, you've been served some gentlemanly sarcasm, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, let's give the defence one more chance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Someone in this court said they remember things that happened a long time ago... Now, who was that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Precisely, Mr Wright... That person is none other than Espella Cantabella.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">What?! That's impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's true, Dad! I...remember it clearly, as if it happened yesterday. The Legendary Fire!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">N-no, that's impossible! That's just your imagination, Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">No, it's not! I couldn't remember it before, but it all came back to me! Because...I'm Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">No, no, no! Espella, there are no witches! That fire, it was just a bad dream!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The inquisition would like to call Espella Cantabella to testify!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Regardless of whether Miss Cantabella is Bezella or not... her memories may contain valuable clues!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Yes, that may be so.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">No, wait! I don't agree to this! This trial is over, Your Honour!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">...!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You are merely...one of the characters. And this is also why we will not cease seeking the truth until we find it.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Grrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defence, what is your opinion on this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Espella keeps insisting that she's the witch Bezella. As her attorney, I should refuse to let her speak to the court. But what's really important now... is finding the truth, just as Layton said.</thought> There's only one way to proceed with this trial. And that's...by questioning Ms Cantabella about her memories!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In that case...the court summons Espella Cantabella as a witness! Attendants! Bring the accused to the witness stand!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, witness. Testify about your memories of the Legendary Fire.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I was...just a little girl then. It happened during the annual fire festival.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, what you have told us... wasn't a bad dream or a fairy tale, but what you actually experienced?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, it was. Like I have already said. I remember it very clearly. The heat from the fire, the smell of smoke...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Espella, what are you talking about...!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence may cross-examine the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Your Honour. <thought>Was there really a huge fire that destroyed the town? And what about Bezella? Is she even real? The answers are in Espella's testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">I was...just a little girl then. It happened during the annual fire festival.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm not quite sure, but I think I was six or seven.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And how old are you now?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm 18 years old.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That means those events did take place more than ten years ago. It's very odd that you have memories that old. But perhaps you're mistaken about your age at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph... Yes... I suppose that makes sense.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">That doesn't make any sense at all! How many times do I need to tell you there are no witches, no magic! The Legendary Fire is just a story. This interrogation serves no purpose!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr Cantabella. The court asks you to be quiet during another witness' [sic] testimony unless you are asked to speak.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Grrrrr...!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Everyone was gathered in the town square for the fire festival, and I was watching them from the bell tower.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, it seems to be an ancient custom in this area. The townspeople make a fire offering to the Great Witch Bezella so that she will not bring misfortunes upon them. A great fire is lit in the middle of the town square. The festival lasts all night long.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's correct. The festival takes place once every year. It is quite magnificent with all the townsfolk assembled in the square. Unless...it is a counterfeit memory, imprinted in our minds by you.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">No, this festival has been held here since before I was born. It appears to be a very old custom indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By the way, why were you in the bell tower in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know, you said everyone was at the town square. Why weren't you there?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ I can't remember. I probably went there...because Bezella awoke within me.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Despite having vivid memories of the fire, you do not remember much of anything else that occurred at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Y-yes. I was at the top of the bell tower, looking down at people in the town square... Someone was with me there. Ah, that's right. It was Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Eve... Her black cat, huh.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I didn't think Eve was that old.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Well, then...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">The Great Witch Bezella awoke within me and brought calamity upon the town.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ I...cannot remember. But the town, perishing in the flames so fast, is engraved in my memory...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You look upset, Mr Cantabella.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............ Ah, pardon me. Did you want something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd like to know what you think about Espella's last statement.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............ My opinion about all this has not changed since last time. It's all just a dream.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Listen to me, Espella! You are not Bezella! There was no Legendary Fire!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Dad...you have no idea how much I want to believe you! But...I just can't. I remember what I saw! And how it felt - the heat, the smoke!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Magic doesn't exist; it belongs in fairy tales. There are no fire dragons either!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Espella seems certain that she saw a fire dragon at that time. However, as long as we do not have any evidence to support or disprove this claim, we can't make any progress.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, do I have any relevant evidence? Anything that could demonstrate that the "fire dragon" Espella saw as a child was real...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defence will...present evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Evidence? I suppose you mean evidence that will prove... that my daughter's memories of the dragon amount to nothing more than wild imagination?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the contrary... I'm pretty positive Espella did see the dragon.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">What? I thought you had more sense in you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, well, aren't we all curious about what the defence has got to show us? Present evidence that proves a dragon appeared in this town over ten years ago!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright... You just said aloud "How about this?!" Was that addressed to anyone here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, he seems to be confused.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps you were so lost in your thoughts that you didn't realise... that you vocally expressed something obviously meant for yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaack! <thought>I knew it - it was the wrong evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, maybe we don't have the right thing to present just yet?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe. I wasn't too sure about that piece of evidence. It was more of a gamble, to tell you the truth... <thought>I might need more information here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, continue your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think there's anything I could use.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ I can understand your choice to be cautious with your judgement, Mr Wright. However, I must remind you... that the only way to discover the whole truth... is to bring to light the true nature of the dragon witnessed by the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>Hm, I guess he has a point there. Maybe I overlooked some clues in the testimony?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's arm ourselves to the teeth with evidence and give it another shot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. But first, we need more info.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Time to do some pressing!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That must be a very harrowing memory...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I think that... whenever Bezella takes over my body, my consciousness drifts away. But, I'm sure of it! There's no mistake about me being Bezella!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What makes you so certain about it?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Because...because Eve has always been with me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean that black cat? How is that relevant?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">According to the legend of Bezella, she is always accompanied by a black cat. That small furry animal is actually her minion. In the stories, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Eve was there with me. I'm sure she was. And I saw the town, engulfed in flames!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>These memories are causing her a lot of pain...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Espella...hang in there...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ I...cannot remember. But the town, perishing in the flames so fast, is engraved in my memory...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You look upset, Mr Cantabella.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............ Ah, pardon me. Did you want something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd like to know what you think about Espella's last statement.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............ My opinion about all this has not changed since last time. It's all just a dream.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Listen to me, Espella! You are not Bezella! There was no Legendary Fire!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Dad...you have no idea how much I want to believe you! But...I just can't. I remember what I saw! And how it felt - the heat, the smoke!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Magic doesn't exist; it belongs in fairy tales. There are no fire dragons either!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Espella seems certain that she saw a fire dragon at that time. However, as long as we do not have any evidence to support or disprove this claim, we can't make any progress.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, do I have any relevant evidence? Anything that could demonstrate that the "fire dragon" Espella saw as a child was real...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, defender?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defence will...present evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Evidence? I suppose you mean evidence that will prove... that my daughter's memories of the dragon amount to nothing more than wild imagination?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the contrary... I'm pretty positive Espella did see the dragon.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">What? I thought you had more sense in you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, well, aren't we all curious about what the defence has got to show us? Present evidence that proves a dragon appeared in this town over ten years ago!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright... You just said aloud "How about this?!" Was that addressed to anyone here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, he seems to be confused.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps you were so lost in your thoughts that you didn't realise... that you vocally expressed something obviously meant for yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaack! <thought>I knew it - it was the wrong evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, maybe we don't have the right thing to present just yet?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe. I wasn't too sure about that piece of evidence. It was more of a gamble, to tell you the truth... <thought>I might need more information here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, continue your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think there's anything I could use.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ I can understand your choice to be cautious with your judgement, Mr Wright. However, I must remind you... that the only way to discover the whole truth... is to bring to light the true nature of the dragon witnessed by the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>Hm, I guess he has a point there. Maybe I overlooked some clues in the testimony?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's arm ourselves to the teeth with evidence and give it another shot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. But first, we need more info.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Time to do some pressing!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That must be a very harrowing memory...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I think that... whenever Bezella takes over my body, my consciousness drifts away. But, I'm sure of it! There's no mistake about me being Bezella! Because...because Eve has always been with me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean that black cat? How is that relevant?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">According to the legend of Bezella, she is always accompanied by a black cat. That small furry animal is actually her minion. In the stories, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Eve was there with me. I'm sure she was. And I saw the town, engulfed in flames!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>These memories are causing her a lot of pain...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Espella...hang in there...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">An enormous fire dragon appeared. I was trembling with fear, terrified by what I had summoned.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">That monstrous image is still so vivid... It looked just like the one that attacked Dad this evening! I have...I've done something terrible again!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Then you are sure that the fire dragon you saw more than ten years ago and the one summoned this evening... were exactly the same?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes. They were definitely the same.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is something wrong, Mr Cantabella?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............ It's impossible... There's no such thing as magic.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">You never believe me, Dad. I don't know why you have to be like this. There was a time when things were different.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Espella, what are you saying! [sic]</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look at them. It's like a common argument between a teenager and a parent.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mr Cantabella created this town. He knows better than anyone else that there's no magic here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Miss Cantabella.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Would you mind giving us more details of what you saw?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ Could I borrow a sheet of parchment and a pencil? I think it'll be better if I draw it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your request shall be granted. Bring parchment and a pencil for the witness immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">This is it. This is the fire dragon that I saw that night. I only caught a glimpse of it. But it was real.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I must say... it does closely resemble the supposedly magical creature we witnessed this evening.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It does indeed. This drawing shall be added to the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">This is a farce...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What happened over a decade ago? Was the town really destroyed by a fire dragon?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Discovering the truth about the dragon shall be our next objective.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, continue the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, Milord.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, Espella, magic isn't real! Therefore, the dragon summoned by the spell Granwyrm doesn't exist either!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">But I did see it! I'm not lying! I saw it just for a moment, I'm sure of it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's like talking to a wall! There's no convincing her!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">There may be another explanation. Espella might have seen something in the shape of a dragon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All right then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhm, Nick? Mr Cantabella wrote this town's Story, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So he's the author, and he's saying that Bezella doesn't exist.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If that's the case, then there's no point to this whole trial!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We know that, but that's not enough to end it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The professor has taken on the role of inquisitor in this trial in order to get Mr Cantabella to testify. He wants to get to the bottom of this mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And learn the whole truth...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Besides, I think this will be in Espella's best interest, too. I trust the professor's judgement on this. So I'll carry on with the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, I trust you, Nick! I'm sure you know what you're doing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It is, of course, Espella's drawing of the dragon. It's impossible to draw a dragon with so much detail unless you've actually seen it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed! And it looks very much like the fire dragon we saw this evening. It cannot be a mere coincidence.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">You can't possibly use that drawing as evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And...why not?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Because she could have just drawn the "dragon" from this evening!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Dad! Why don't you believe me! [sic] I saw that dragon when I was little...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">This town is my creation! I know everything about it. And I assure you there's no magic! If there's anyone who can tell you what's possible and what is not, it is me, the creator of Labyrinthia!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Your overconfidence... has clouded your judgement and is preventing you from seeing the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">...! Wh-what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">In order to see what is really there, you need to reject biased assumptions and keep an open mind. You are overlooking certain facts precisely because you are the creator of this town.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">It's nothing short of insanity!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Magic doesn't exist. And yet, Espella says she saw a fire dragon. It seems like a contradiction. But perhaps...it is not. Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The solution to this mystery is out there. We just need to find it. Do you suppose you know where it is? "Magic doesn't exist." "Espella saw a fire dragon." Where is the evidence that bridges the gap between the two?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If anywhere, it's got to be in the Court Record, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-what?! Nick, what's wrong with you? We're talking about evidence relating to what Espella saw from the bell tower over ten years ago. We don't have anything that would fit the bill in the Court Record!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It would serve you well to listen to Miss Fey. What Miss Cantabella saw then...is where she had been at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Where she had been?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You do remember her testimony, don't you? She was in the bell tower when she witnessed that monstrosity.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The bell tower, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's only one way to explain this contradiction. Espella somehow saw the dragon, but it wasn't a magical creature.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Then will you just tell us what it was! [sic]</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That event took place over ten years ago. What she saw then...should still be in the place where she was at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's still there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honour. And that place is...the belfry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella was watching the town burn at that time. She says she saw an enormous fire dragon. Now, if you put the two together... I think our best guess is that the dragon she saw was this town itself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This town?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">In other words... Espella saw a dragon's shape looming over the burning town.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">How absurd! That's mere speculation!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I will not dispute that. However, it is entirely possible to test our theory.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">What?! And how would you go about doing that?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is all quite simple, Mr Storyteller. We will now go to the belfry.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Over ten years ago... The witness was standing somewhere around here when she saw a "fire dragon". Am I correct?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, Mr Layton.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">However, what was it that you actually saw then? Let us see if we can find the answer to that question.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Why not? Go ahead and try! But, I have warned you that it's futile. You will find nothing here!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, it happened a long time ago. Whatever she saw might not be there any more... And if we wanna see exactly what she saw at the time...we'll need to set the whole town on fire. Want me to go get matches?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I may be an attorney, but even I couldn't clear you of the charges if you ACTUALLY committed such a crime, Maya!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">I will pretend I did not hear that. Shall we begin?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Let us look for the fire dragon. We can see the whole town from here. Look in every direction for something that would resemble Miss Cantabella's drawing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Uhm...I don't know... It doesn't look like the dragon I saw...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Hah! I was right, not Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It seems so, unfortunately.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, we're not done. I was just "testing the waters".</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright. A gentleman should admit his mistake rather than try to cover it up with an unconvincing excuse.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>An excuse? That's what I get for imitating the professor...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhm, Nick? What was that about biased assumptions that the professor said earlier?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They're what prevent us from seeing the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So let's approach this with our minds wide open!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And eyes wide open, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella, can you have a look at this? It looks like the dragon was hiding in here, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh! This...this is...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! That's identical to the one Espella drew!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">But...uhm... It's not...the fire dragon. The fire dragon was a creature made of flames. It was so big it could swallow this whole tower! This is just some tiny fretwork...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ I think we can consider this mystery solved. I suggest we all head back to the court. I will explain everything there. Is that all right with you, Mr Cantabella?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's gotten into Mr Cantabella? He looks paler than you do with a cold.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have no idea. Let's follow the others back to the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The inquisition's investigation seems to have yielded some unexpected results. But...can someone explain them to me?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Your Honour, the inquisition will interpret the results of its investigation. Witness... You said you were about 6 years old at the time of that incident?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Did you see the moment the dragon appeared above the town?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Huh? N-no... I...don't remember. I remember seeing it at some point. It was like a flash... The town was ablaze, and this fiery beast was hovering above it.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Then, when you noticed the dragon, the town was already engulfed by flames?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Uhm... Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That information completes the picture. Miss Cantabella's statement has offered me an insight into the true story of the fire dragon.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This is what I have deduced.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ It wasn't...a monster?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Miss Cantabella, the illustration you have drawn for us bears an uncanny resemblance... to the fretwork in the belfry. You saw the "dragon" when you were confused, possibly mildly asphyxiated from the smoke. There was no magic and no magical beast.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">You believe a stranger but not your father. That's so typical of teenagers. You should have listened to me! And now that all the mysteries have been unravelled, can we not end this trial and go home?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">What else do you want from us?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There is just one more problem I'd like to solve tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">One more? What on earth could it be?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Miss Cantabella, we've ascertained that you were in the belfry when you saw the "dragon". However, that creates a new question. How did you get there?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh...I haven't thought of that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, neither have I... Ohhhhhhhhhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">As expected of an ace attorney, Mr Wright seems to have noticed the problem, too, at last. In order to access the belfry, you need to use the bell tower mechanism.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The mechanism can only be set in motion with the pendants!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. Miss Cantabella, did you have your pendant with you at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I...yes. I think I did. I always had it with me. But why did I have that pendant? I can't remember it at all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This pendant is not just for show. It's the key to the belfry. Why was she carrying it around?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We must also not forget that one pendant does not suffice to operate the contraption. Two of them are required.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Two...pendants...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Miss Cantabella. Are you certain that you were alone in the belfry?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ No, I wasn't alone. I was there with a friend.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What friend?</line>
<line speaker="???">Meow...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Eve! Where did you go off to?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The friend you mentioned... Was it this cat?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes. She's my best friend.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That kitty's always appearing out of nowhere to keep Espella company.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Of course she does. After all, Bezella is always accompanied by a black cat.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What you saw from the bell tower when you were little was so terrifying that even an adult would have been scarred for life. The town burned in front of your eyes. You thought you saw a fire dragon... You see, your memories have been twisted by the horrors you saw.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Wh-what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The dragon you saw wasn't real. And I suspect... that the friend who was with you in the bell tower might not have been that cat.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">No, it was her! It was Eve, my only friend...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Miss Cantabella, the pendant needed to access the belfry is too large for a cat. Are you following? If Eve was with you, it would have been impossible for you to enter the belfry!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Aaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">W-wait! Inquisitor! Where is all this going?! You have no right to tamper with my daughter's memories!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You are right, of course. However, neither do you. Nor should you attempt to cover up the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Ugh.........!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">No...you're wrong! Eve was my only friend...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Think about that day again, Miss Cantabella. You went to the top of that bell tower with a friend who also had a pendant!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, why don't we have the defence present some evidence! Can you prove that someone was with Miss Cantabella in the belfry that day? If so, I'd very much like to see the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaaaaaaaaaat?! Why me? It was the professor's idea! I have nothing on the Legendary Fire! Why ask me for proof...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Right. I suppose you wouldn't have any proof. Not one of us remembers that incident.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I've had enough of this, Your Honour! You have no grounds to continue this trial!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, we appear to have reached a dead end. There is nothing else for us to do.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh... What is this, all of a sudden? Inquisitor Layton?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The defence does not have the necessary evidence, but someone else does.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This time the inquisition will present its evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The inquisition will present evidence, huh... Wait, SERIOUSLY?!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">You...you son of a witch! This is what you wanted from the very start, isn't it?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, in that case... The inquisition shall present evidence that somebody was with Miss Cantabella in the bell tower when she saw the fire dragon!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Have a look!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Have a look!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's with that satisfied look on your face, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've always wanted to do this. Everyone's always poking fun at me if I present the wrong evidence. It feels so good to do it to somebody else for a change!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Unfortunately, Inquisitor Layton, I fail to see a connection between the matter at hand and the evidence you presented.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Ekhm... Well, if you don't test the waters, you won't know if you're out of your depth. I'll present the correct evidence next time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're looking very happy again, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's music to my ears. Someone other than me making a silly mistake and coming up with lame excuses.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, maybe you could use some time off. So that you can release your pent-up frustration...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This is the proof. This photograph shows Miss Cantabella with a friend.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Golly! This is... this is the finest illustration I have ever seen!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's a photograph.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It looks as if...as if it were a reflection of the real world on paper! Tell me, who created this exquisite work of art?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well... Your Honour, I understand you are fascinated...but let us focus on what this picture shows. This picture was found in the Storyteller's Tower. Mr Cantabella, we have taken the liberty of borrowing it for this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">It's enough to look away for a second and you already cause trouble!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhm. Professor? Aren't photographs against the rules? I mean, this is supposed to be a medieval setting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Meh, who cares.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What's important now is helping Miss Cantabella to grasp the truth. And in this case the end justifies the means.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Grrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Please take a close look at the two girls in this picture. Each of them is wearing a pendant.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, that's so! These are the belfry contraption pendants!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We know that one of these girls is Miss Cantabella. But then... Who is the other girl?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Accused, do you have any idea?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella? Are you okay?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It doesn't look like she is...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It's...it's...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">E-Espella! Your Honour! Stop this trial! Stop it right now! Can't you see you're driving Espella into insanity?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">...!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If we turn away from the truth now... Espella will close herself to the world forever!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Grrrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You know who it is, don't you? You know the identity of the other girl in this picture.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is that so? If the defence knows that... Tell us all who this other girl is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I was expecting you'd name a woman about the same age as Miss Cantabella. I'm astonished anyone would make a mistake...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh... What can I say? I, err...like to surprise everyone with my answers...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If such was your intention, Mr Wright... you would have achieved a greater effect had you said it's Miss Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"That was very half-baked, man!" ...Is what the professor is trying to say, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gaaaaaaaah! I'm sorry... Mind if I try again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm thinking it's High Inquisitor Darklaw.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">High Inquisitor Darklaw?! I cannot say I didn't have slight suspicions about her, but...oh my.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Miss Cantabella, what do you say? Do you now remember the girl next to you in this picture?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I was with...Lady Darklaw...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">This is crazy! What are you basing this preposterous claim on! [sic]</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-but...Mr Cantabella. This girl closely resembles the High Inquisitor.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Resembles? That's just your personal opinion! It's meaningless in a court of law!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Wh-what?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The definitive proof that the girl in the picture is High Inquisitor Darklaw is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Honestly, Mr Wright... At this point I am beginning to wonder if you aren't giving the wrong answers on purpose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's as if you were hoping something funny would ensue. However, I'm not going to let you make light of this trial for your own amusement!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arghhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh! <thought>I really wasn't trying to do that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, you totally did that on purpose, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I swear I didn't... Although it'll help me save face if everyone thinks I did... <thought>Anyway...I'm gonna try again and get it right this time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And this is the proof it was the High Inquisitor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The pendant needed for that contraption in the bell tower...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have Ms Darklaw's testimony here. She said this pendant was hers. And so... the other girl in the picture is definitely Ms Darklaw!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Is it...is it really... Eve? Where are you going?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I was expecting you, Miss Darklaw.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I see that I was not mistaken about you. I trusted in your ability to get this far.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">H-High Inquisitor Darklaw! Where did you just appear from?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Does your memory not serve you well, Your Honour? You know what I am. I can disappear at will any time I wish to. So, Storyteller... Everything has worked out just as you had written, oh revered creator of Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Darklaw...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Lady Darklaw.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Miss Darklaw... Did you enter the belfry with Miss Cantabella when you were little?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ Yes, I did.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then you have memories of events from before ten years ago?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I certainly do.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order in the court!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">L-Lady Darklaw...you were with me?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Your memories have been suppressed. By that man.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">...!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">B-but! I was with Eve...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">"Eve", huh... Eve the black cat?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, she has always been my dear friend... She was by my side on that day, too.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What a bizarre coincidence. "Darklaw" isn't my real name.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what?! Then what is your real name?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ It's...Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What... Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">You...you are...Eve...? Ah... Ahhhhh...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">It...can't be... That flashback... was it real...?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Darklaw, why are you doing this? Are you trying to undo everything I have accomplished in the past ten years?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">No. You have already ruined everything yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">What is it that you want?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What I want? My aim is to make the truth known, so that everything returns to how it should be.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms Darklaw... Will you tell us what you remember about what happened back then, more than ten years ago?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">It would be my pleasure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, that's something I'd like to know as well. Even if we assume the celebratory fires got out of control... Surely the whole town wouldn't have perished like that!</line>
<line speaker="???">...Now it all makes sense.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That was the missing piece of this puzzle!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean, Professor?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I can imagine now what transpired that night. What happened in the belfry and what caused the Legendary Fire. We have all the clues we need!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If the inquisition has evidence to show us, I'd very much like to see it. What caused the Legendary Fire?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Have a look!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Have a look!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It is conceivable that it was this, for instance!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ I'm sorry, but I don't see how this could have caused that disaster.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Hmph. Is that the best you can do? I see I set my expectations far too high.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ugh... Well, haven't you been paying attention? I said "for instance", not that it was definitely the correct item!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Professor, I understand your pride has been wounded, but just get over it and show us the right piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Eve">...Meow.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Layton's face is so fiery red, it looks as if it could start a legendary fire of its own...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">The cause of the fire is in the belfry!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It was the bell...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That bell had been made by the natives and later sealed underground. It was called the Bell of Ruin.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">B-Bell of Ruin...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">By the way, why does this bell have such an ominous name?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Could it be because it's made of pure silver?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Pure silver...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Exactly. Mr Cantabella has told us earlier...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">...that everyone who lives here has a very peculiar condition.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">This condition makes people fall unconscious upon the sound of a certain metal being struck.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And that metal is pure silver.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes...and we've been told the condition is brought about by drinking the groundwater.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed. That bell was also the reason why the original inhabitants of this area decided to forsake it. It seems that the Bell of Ruin caused a devastating disaster.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can't help but wonder what disaster this bell had caused.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">An enormous bell made of pure silver... and the locals with their peculiar condition... It's not too hard to imagine what happened. It was probably the same calamity as the one that happened over ten years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that is...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, what disaster happened to this town before Labyrinthia was built?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The...Legendary Fire...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Now, let us contemplate the following scenario. What would happen if the Bell of Ruin were sounded during the fire festival?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Everyone who heard it would fall unconscious.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">As it was an annual festival, all the townspeople were assembled in the town square.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh dear...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Therefore, on the night of the fire festival over ten years ago... all the residents instantly lost consciousness when the bell was struck.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh no...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Had it been even just slightly windy that day... the fires lit for the Great Witch Bezella would have gone out of control. And they would spread throughout the town with no one left to stop them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because everyone was unconscious...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Exactly. That also includes the two girls who were in the belfry.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Espella and I.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You were the closest to the source of the sound, so it was inevitable. When you recovered consciousness, it was already too late. The town had been swallowed by flames, as if a fire dragon had come to burn it. That was a calamity caused by the bell.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Calamity...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You say here that the cause of calamity is the Great Witch Bezella. That night, in this very town...Bezella was more than a mythical persona!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">......Be...Bezella......</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She's losing it again!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ ......The Bell of Ruin...... ......Bezella......</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Cantabella. I would like to apologise for putting too much pressure on your daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">...!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Only your words can bring her back from the brink of madness. Let her hear the truth from her own father.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............ All according to your plan, Layton? You've driven Espella into a corner, in order to push me to the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I had no other choice.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Espella, please listen to me.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">You haven't done anything wrong. You didn't cause that...accident. You have suffered so much, thinking that you were Bezella... I must take the blame for that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You, Mr Cantabella?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I sacrificed everything to make up for what I've done... But all I managed to do was inflict more pain upon others. Is that not so, Darklaw?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Now that you are willing to talk, Mr Cantabella... Would you mind telling us your story? Yours...as well as Espella's and Miss Darklaw's?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">...Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">The two of us chose different paths in life. I studied management in London, while Newton devoted himself to the study of the natural sciences.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And then...you made a fortune following the invention of a new anaesthetic?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">We both got married around that time, and each of us had a daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean Espella was born shortly after your company gained funding?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Pardon the interruption, but at the time, were you aware of the meaning behind the bell's name?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Obviously, we were not. Thinking back to my ignorance at the time, a chill now runs down my spine.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Newton and I went to the bell tower the day before the festival.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">The bell weighed so much that ringing it was not easy. We tackled that problem by constructing a special mechanism, which we installed in the belfry.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Espella, who was there with us, was utterly enchanted by the bell. She wasn't a bad child, but she was very stubborn and would rarely listen to me when she wanted something. I told her a story to try and convince her to leave the bell alone.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">The legend of Bezella has been passed around these parts for centuries.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It probably originated from beliefs of the tribes that populated this area in the past.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">What I told Espella... was just a silly story that I invented for the occasion. It was only meant to stop her from ringing the bell. I could not have imagined that it would have such far-reaching consequences.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ ............ It's all coming back to me now... I remember that day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">On the day of the fire festival, just around the time when the preparations ended and everything was about to begin... I sneaked [sic] out of our house. I took mum's pendant with me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your mother's pendant? Do you mean this one?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes. It belonged to my mum.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">We needed to limit access to the bell, so we made the two keys. We decided to make them into pendants and each gave one to our respective wives. Both are needed in order to access the belfry.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I saw you and Mr Belduke use them... So I told Eve to meet me at the bell tower.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">So it is just as I thought. Miss Darklaw... you are Mr Belduke's daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Heh. Well done, Inquisitor. ...I was almost afraid you would fail to make that connection.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What in the... This is too much for one day! O-order! Order in the court! Lady Darklaw... you mean to say that you're Sir Belduke's daughter?!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Yes... My real name is Eve Belduke. I'm the "alchemist's" daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-this is unbelievable!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I also sneaked [sic] out of my house that evening, clutching my mother's pendant in my hand. I did just as you asked me to, did I not, Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I rang the bell, against my father's warning. And so, Bezella possessed me. Because of me...the town...and everyone in it... They're all gone.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">No! It's not your fault! Stop blaming yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Supposedly, the former inhabitants of this area also used to fall unconscious upon the sound of that bell. Perhaps they experienced a similar nightmare.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">It was I who brought the Bell of Ruin into this town. The one to blame for this calamity is not some witch...it's me!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...I brought destruction upon this town... ...I am...Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Espella! You're going to drive your dad crazy if you keep repeating that!</line>
<line speaker="???">...Heh heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Seeing you like this is giving me a strong feeling of dj vu.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Eve... How can you be so evil? Are you happy now?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'm afraid we're in the dark as regards [sic] Miss Darklaw's sense of "dj vu"...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............ Only four people survived the fire.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Only four...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Espella and Eve, who were in the belfry. And the only two residents who did not participate in the festival. Newton and I.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And where were you at the time, if you'll permit my asking?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">We were investigating those fateful ruins. That's why we didn't notice anything until it was too late. It was getting near the time at which we planned to ring the bell, so we headed towards the town... Then, we saw it...the town had been burnt to ashes, the air shimmering from the heat.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's...too awful for words...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">We searched for survivors, sick with anxiety. Eventually, we found our daughters in the bell tower.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What was it...? This suspense...it's too much for my ageing heart!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I believe...I may know what it was. It was the only way to get through to little Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Inquisition, what are you talking about? What was Mr Cantabella's idea for saving his daughter from insanity?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Have a look!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Have a look!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is...that it? I don't quite understand...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Unfortunately, you were wrong. Even the great Professor Layton can err, it would seem.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Hmm.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, let's not make such a big deal out of it, huh? Let the guy try again.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't think you're helping, Nick. If you're going to console him, you should probably wipe that stupid grin off your face first...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't know why, but...I can't help it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">We all learn from our mistakes. I believe I now know the right answer. It was the only way to get through to little Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He just sailed through that like nothing even happened...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">We discovered this in Espella's room.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uhm... And that is...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It's a handmade picture book. The illustrations and handwriting are truly exquisite.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">That's the first story I wrote. I made it for Espella after that dreadful fire.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! The Storyteller's first story...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">It was but a simple children's story. The plot was very straightforward - the townsfolk join forces to banish evil witches who serve Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Espella was mentally broken, and I couldn't get through to her any other way. I talked to her as if magic and witches were real, avoiding any mention of that fire.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Espella spoke to me for the first time in so many days... I was beyond myself with joy and replied without thinking...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I was desperate. I feared she would close herself off to me again. Now, in hindsight... I see what an utter fool I was. I made an irreversible mistake yet again.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">And so, I wrote another story for my daughter. A story about mischievous witches getting caught. This time I had the story acted out in front of Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You had it acted out?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Back then...I wasn't the only one tormenting myself over the mental state of my daughter. Newton was going through hell, too. His own daughter had been badly scarred by the event. Isn't that right, Eve?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ My father and I repaired a building that had survived the fire and continued to live in this town. Espella wasn't even able to leave her room. We couldn't leave her behind when she needed all the help she could get. Mr Cantabella showed us this book one day. Then...he made an unusual request of us.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">When I saw her smile, I felt as if something broke inside me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How much reconstruction?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">It wasn't anything on a big scale. I simply paid people to move in and act out their roles. But... I began to think that I would need more than that. The story had to be real.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">To make a lie seem true, you resorted to even more lies...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Yes. I was certain that was the only way. How did I do so? I remembered about Newton's research.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He was working on a certain medicine...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">It was a kind of tranquiliser, made from local plants, that he was testing at the time. But it was difficult to put into practical use. The substance had a danger of causing unconsciousness and hypnosis.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can see how that could be abused to cause much harm, supposing it fell into the wrong hands...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">At the same time, it was just what I needed for my ambitious project. I contacted the government... And that was the beginning of what came to be known as Project Labyrinthia. A town with human test subjects, all in a state of long-term hypnosis.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You devised that plan solely for the sake of your daughter?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Yes. We acquired the land which had been laid to waste by the fire. The new town was slowly becoming populated. Gradually, the rules of Labyrinthia were established. It was to be a town where magic and witches were a reality to the residents. All of this was possible thanks to the drug.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The test subjects were exposed to it through the ink used to pen the Story, right?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">That's right. It was the dangerous drug developed by Newton. About ten years have passed since then. Even now, the town...continues to change.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Project Labyrinthia. And all this was done...for one girl...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Espella was only able to be herself when she lived within my Story. Oh, the irony of it... Only within a world in which Bezella was real could Espella's tragic memories be sealed. All this while... Eve was assisting me.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ ...I was the first Shade.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">As soon as the Story began, I disappeared from the scene. If Espella was to see some magic... then someone had to don this robe.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's the robe of invisibility!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I gave Espella new memories so that she could live in this town with everyone else. I also sealed the memory of her friend, Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what?!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">My existence was too strongly connected to her memory of the fire. Afterwards, I returned as Darklaw, a stranger to Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-but! Even if you were doing this for Espella's sake, that's just going too far!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I made that choice... I do not regret the past ten years. Meanwhile, my father was supporting Labyrinthia from behind the scenes, in his own way.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you mean his contributions as an alchemist?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">My father's knowledge of medicine was indispensable for this town to function. The hallucinogenic ink was my father's work, as well.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">So it was. Newton and Eve sacrificed more than anyone else for the sake of Espella and this town. I will be forever indebted to them.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ We wanted to save Espella, just like you.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But then...there's still something I don't understand. Why were you trying to destroy this fake world? In the end...you chose to betray Espella and Mr Cantabella!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Oh, but I've told you already, have I not?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It was your revenge against Mr Cantabella for choosing to end the Story, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I wonder...whether that was the true reason.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Would Miss Belduke really betray them merely because she did not want the Story to end? I dare say there was another, considerably more important reason.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She had another reason?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">No need to frown in dismay, Mr Wright. Please leave this to me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, let's hear what the inquisition has to say. What other reason led the witness to betray Mr Cantabella?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Have a look!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Have a look!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Is this some kind of a puzzle, Inquisitor Layton?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It was intended as proof of your real motive for the betrayal...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I'd say you're a fine traitor yourself. You have betrayed the trust of the profusely sweating attorney over there.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ugh... Not to worry. I was merely warming up.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do not force me to turn up the heat on you, Inquisitor. Be sure to present the correct evidence quickly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoa... No love lost between the judge and Layton.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">This letter was Miss Belduke's real motive.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is this? I think I've seen it before...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's the letter written by Mr Belduke for Mr Cantabella. It's also Mr Belduke's suicide note.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Something was tormenting Mr Belduke. It became too much for him to bear and drove him to suicide.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ These past ten years... I thought Father was glad to be helping Cantabella. But...little did I know... he was suffering terrible anguish all that time.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">...!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Cantabella twisted the lives of so many people for the sake of his daughter... Was the Story not but a glorified lie, stripping so many of what little happiness they had?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">His agony culminated in the incident of three months ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr Belduke's death...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Before Labyrinthia was created...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I see... Had she seen it, it would have been certain to stir up those traumatic memories. ...Memories of the Legendary Fire.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The only way to prevent that was to erase the bell tower from Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But how could you do that?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Using the same method as with this robe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The robe of invisibility...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">In short, we covered up the tower with a huge "robe". Although it wasn't as easy as it sounds...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In other words, the bell tower had been there all this time... Only, the townspeople couldn't see it... Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I...I don't know what to say...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">At any rate, the situation changed due to that lightning strike three months ago, did it not?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">It was a most unfortunate accident. The lightning set the bell tower's cover on fire.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That tower emerging from the flames...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Having realised this, Father chose death.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">He was such a kind-hearted man... I didn't have an inkling of what he had been going through!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">To him, the participation of Labyrinthia's people within this project was not voluntary. Even though they had themselves signed the contract, I believe he felt those people were being deceived.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Father...took his life because of you, Cantabella!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...Now you know why I did what I did. I lost my father three months ago. That day, my revenge began.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your revenge...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The first step of my plan was to rewrite the Story.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Wh-what did you say?!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">As president of Labrelum Inc., you had to spend most of your time in London. Over the past few years, you were coming to Labyrinthia only for the parades. So naturally...I knew you would never notice if the Story were slightly changed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That explains it... I couldn't help thinking there was something strange going on. Mr Cantabella is Espella's father after all. He wouldn't have made Espella a witch in his Story.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Espella was... a witch?! When did that happen?!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Heh heh heh. How could you have known, after all? Let me fill you in on the details. Espella has already been tried once within the Witches' Court.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Impossible! Why?! How could you... You knew the risk that would carry!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Look at you... What a fine author of that grand Story you are. You left all the work in Labyrinthia to me. Meanwhile, you were making millions for yourself in London. What a pathetic excuse for a father. You didn't even notice that your precious little Espella was in such danger.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Grrrrrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Miss Belduke. Why did you do that to Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Do you even need to ask? I did it to unlock her memories.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">When the Legendary Fire took place... Espella was so traumatised that she closed herself off to the world. We were just little girls then. That tragic accident was too much for us to handle.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">This fictitious town was created as a facade, to keep the truth away from Espella. But the weight of all these lies led my father to his suicide. Despite that...the person responsible for all this carried on as if nothing had happened.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I couldn't forgive him. As Belduke's bereaved daughter... I had to have my revenge against both Cantabellas. Judge... This is the whole truth. Now you know the true identity of Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Professor...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What are you going on about now?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">We have been provided with a clear picture of what happened to Espella so long ago. Nevertheless... we haven't yet heard your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Don't be ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">This will be the last testimony in this trial. Tell us about the night of the Legendary Fire. I request that you tell us your story.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Who do you think you are, Inquisitor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I am merely one of the supporting characters within this tale. However, I am very much interested in the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This has been a very long trial...of which this shall be the last interrogation. The court demands that the single other witness of the Legendary Fire provide us with her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Very well. There is only one truth... Nothing can change that.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Espella wanted to ring the bell no matter what, so we went up to the belfry.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The bell could only be rung with a special mechanism?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">That's right. It was made in such a way that even a child could use it.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">It was probably constructed by my father. I suppose he wanted to make it possible for anyone to ring that bell. In light of the events that followed... that was clearly a very foolish decision.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A mechanism for ringing the bell...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh dear... Fate can certainly be cruel.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I have to agree.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Unfortunately, Mr Cantabella, the tragedy occurred. All that remains for us to do is to seek out the truth. Not for the sake of vengeance...but for the sake of the future.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhm, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You have been fighting fiercely to uncover the truth. This is the final interrogation. I trust you know what to do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leave it to me. <thought>To be honest, I have no idea what lies ahead... But whatever it is, there's no question we need to get to the bottom of it. There's got to be light at the end of this tunnel!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Espella wanted to ring the bell no matter what, so we went up to the belfry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Espella asked me to bring my mother's pendant, so I did.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">That wasn't the only requirement, however. You also needed to solve a puzzle in order to use the contraption.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I've always been a master puzzle-solver. For me, it was child's play...literally.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She solved it when she was a little girl... What's your excuse, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! I have...different talents.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Espella and Eve were best friends at the time. Eve is two years older than Espella. She used to be like a big sister to her.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">So, the two of you went to the belfry. What happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The festival celebrations had already started. The mechanism for ringing the bell was at a height even we could reach.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I intended to make it so that the bell would only be rung on special occasions. That's exactly why I put that puzzle in place, to restrict access.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You also divided the "key" to the belfry into two components, as an extra precaution.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I was careful...but the same cannot be said of Newton, who constructed the mechanism as a whole. He presumably wished to make it so that even our young daughters could use it, meaning strength was not a requirement.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...And that became his undoing.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">By the way, how old were the girls at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Espella was six. And Eve was eight.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I see.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">That mechanism was the last thing I saw before falling unconscious. And then...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The next thing I remember...is coming to, and running to Espella's side.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Yes, I believe so.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Our peculiar condition causes an instant reaction. The brain probably doesn't even have the time to register the sound before consciousness is lost.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">It was almost as if...a slice of time had been stolen from my life. When I opened my eyes, I was lying on the floor. I lifted my head and saw Espella lying nearby. I sprang to my feet and ran to her side.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what about the situation in the town at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I was preoccupied with Espella, so I didn't notice it to begin with.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">At that time, was Espella still unconscious?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Yes. I...panicked a little and took her in my arms, hoping she'd wake up...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I was shaking her until she finally opened her eyes. The next moment...we saw that nightmarish view.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Yes, it was me. She was out cold, curled up on the floor, until I shook her awake. As soon as she came to, she turned to look at the town - to that nightmarish view, stretching out before us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">When you say "nightmarish view"...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I can find no other words to describe it. We froze in terror at the sight. It took us a while to notice that smoke was creeping up the bell tower, too. Our eyes filled up with tears and we couldn't stop crying...perhaps because of the smoke. The town seemed like a fire dragon's playground. I was trembling with terror unlike anything I've known before.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Dear me... Merely imagining it now raises the hairs on my beard.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">All strength abandoned us, and we didn't know what to do. That was when we were found by my father and Mr Cantabella.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Of course not. We were paralysed with fear... It was an event so traumatising, it still haunts us. Espella fainted again when she saw the "fire dragon". I was crying and waiting until our fathers found us.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">We went to the bell tower, as it was a good vantage point. We weren't expecting to find our daughters there.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Of course, neither suspected at that point that the disaster had been caused by the Bell of Ruin...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Eve was in tears, sobbing violently. As for Espella...she was in a daze. Her face frozen in an expression of disbelief. She didn't know what was happening around her.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I cannot say this with certainty, as my memories are a little vague... but I think I was trying to protect her. Maybe not. Perhaps it's just my imagination. At any rate... the only thing I clearly remember is that I couldn't stop crying.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr Cantabella?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............ I remember that very well. As if it happened yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">C-Cantabella...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Would you mind telling us what you saw?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Eve said it with a most serious look on her face.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">When she said that...I grasped the situation. I realised what had transpired in the belfry. And I thought to myself: "I must protect these children."</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="???">...E... ...Eve...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm so sorry, Eve...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">E-Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Espella, sweetie...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Dad... Please forgive me... You've done all this for me...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Espella...you're with us again!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">All this for me... ............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well, well. At last...it would appear we are one step away from the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Professor! You seem to already know what that truth is...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Do I? That remains to be seen. Continue the interrogation, and we shall all know soon enough.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court agrees with Inquisitor Layton. Witness, continue your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">As you wish...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I feel sorry for Eve... She's seen some scary stuff too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">She may not be showing it, but I bet it's painful for her to talk about all this.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I cannot say I don't sympathise with Miss Belduke. However, the truth is our utmost priority. It must be exposed. Even if it may come as a surprise to the witness herself...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? You think Ms Belduke isn't aware of the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure what the professor has in mind, but let's trust him on this one. I'm sure we can unravel this mystery together.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All righty! Let's do our thing and grasp at straws...I mean, grasp the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Espella, are you okay?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Y-yes...everything's fine.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">My apologies for bringing back such troubling memories. Nevertheless...you must endeavour to face them and overcome the power they hold over you.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes... I...remember it now...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">No, Espella! It was just an illusion!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">No... You're wrong, Dad. It wasn't an illusion. It was a fact. If I hadn't rung the bell, none of this would have happened. Bezella is the bringer of disaster. And that's what I've done to our town!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Espella, be careful! It's dangerous up there!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Please, Espella, come down!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm sorry, everyone. I...have no right to be here any more.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Espella's going to do something crazy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I...I can see that... <thought>...But what the heck can I do?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Espella! Please, do not make any hasty decisions!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Mr Layton...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The truth is close now. Be brave for a little while longer...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">The truth? As if it wasn't [sic] clear already! If I hadn't rung that bell, everything would've been fine...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Layton:</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Isn't that so, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>I had the same feeling when I was listening to Eve's testimony... I felt...something was not right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? I thought that was pretty much it!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The pieces of the puzzle that don't yet fit are themselves the hints to the solution!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-no way... You mean...Espella didn't ring the bell?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What?! Nonsense! Of course she did!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As it stands, it's hard to say for sure that she didn't ring the bell... However! We've got evidence that will clear any doubts.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Show us this so-called evidence you claim to have then! What do you think proves Espella didn't ring the bell?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Darklaw:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Oh, I assure you it was just the wind, Miss Belduke. Isn't that so, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhm... Yeah. The wind.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Looks like they're turning a blind eye to your mistake, Nick... Don't waste their generosity, and get it right next time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What really happened in the belfry when Espella was little... can't be proven with the evidence in the Court Record alone. But that thing in the belfry, along with another piece of evidence, can explain everything!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Don't make me laugh! You're as delusional as Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella, can you hear me?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Y-yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Where you're standing now is the same spot from where you saw this fire dragon.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...! Yes...that's right. This fretwork here is the same as what I saw that day... When I look at it now... it's [sic] seems so small...even adorable.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Defence! What does this have to do with anything?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As you will no doubt recall, Mr Cantabella told us that people who drink the groundwater here suffer from a condition... A condition where they fall unconscious the moment they hear the sound of pure silver.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella, can you please check that for me? See if the contraption is located near the dragon fretwork!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Uhm...okay. Give me a minute! Mr Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella, did you find it?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I don't know if it's the right thing... but there's something on the other side of the belfry. A contraption with a handle...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Wh-what?! On the other side?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. I figured there was something weird when we went up the bell tower. But I couldn't quite put my finger on it.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">No...no way...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You see where I'm going with this, don't you, Ms Belduke? If it was Espella who rang the bell... there's no way she could have seen the "fire dragon" when she woke up!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Ack! No... No... This can't be right!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">An excellent deduction, Mr Wright. Miss Darklaw. It seems that everything is now clear as day.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What...what do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Why, of course... I mean the answer to the question of who rang the bell.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">It was her...it had to be...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What do you say, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ It looks like we've arrived at the same conclusion. We now know that only one person could have done it.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">W-wait! What good will saying it out loud do?!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Is there a problem, Mr Cantabella? It wasn't your daughter who rang that bell. Should that not lift some burden off your shoulders? Are you not curious to know the name of the true culprit, who has pinned the blame on your daughter all this while?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">How about you stop taunting us?! Just say the name already! Who is this true culprit?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's do it, Professor. Are you ready?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I am always ready, Mr Wright. It's time to set things straight. The person who rang the bell is...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Have a look!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Have a look!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ Of course it wasn't that person.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, what?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">There's no way it would have been them... I am well aware of that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, then...why did you say their name?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright, I was merely practising my enunciation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The professor is one cool customer. And he's never wrong, either!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why does it feel like I'm the one who made a mistake...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">In any case, I'd say we should announce the real culprit's name now!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">M-me? But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There were only the two of you in the belfry at the time. You know that better than anyone.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">And as it wasn't Espella who rang the bell... it had to be you.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">That's preposterous... It can't be true...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It was an extremely traumatising event for both you and Espella. Your friend's memories were altered from the shock without her even realising it.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">No... It wasn't me... Espella...she rang the bell... It was her, not me...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What's the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I don't want to do this now. We'll be taken over by Bezella!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Bezella is just a fairy tale, and you're the one who said she wanted to come and ring the bell.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I did, but I... changed my mind!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">After coming all this way... Espella...Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">...Bezella.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Then...if that's true... for the past ten years... I've been pinning the blame... for what I've done, on Espella. It can't be. It can't be true. It's impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Darklaw's just disappeared!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...She's donned the invisibility robe!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! Nick, look at the bell tower! Espella's gone!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No! She's on the roof!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I beg you! Don't blame Eve! It really doesn't matter any more who rang the accursed bell! This town was all created for me! It's my fault you've all been used, and suffered so much!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">E-Espella! What are you saying?! Please, come down right now! You haven't done anything wrong! It was all my fault!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Dad, I know that you did this for me. You've been so kind to me, and what did I do? I selfishly ran away from home...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I will finish your Story for you. The evil witch will be gone forever, and everyone will live happily ever after. Dad...thank you for everything you've done for me.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Wait! Don't do it, Espella!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">What are you...?</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Isn't that...D-Darklaw?!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">But...why, Eve? Why would you...? I finally remembered everything I've done...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">You're not the only one who remembered. You still have the pendant...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Yes, of course. That's because... somehow I always knew it was important to me.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">You kept your pendant as well, didn't you, Eve?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">For some reason... I just couldn't let it go.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella...Ms Darklaw!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Quick! They'll fall if we don't do something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's go! We have to save them!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">No, you won't make it there in time!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why...?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">The wooden handrail Eve's holding on to is rotted through! We'd need some sort of magic to save them!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No way!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Magic, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got an idea, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If a bit of magic is all that's needed to save these two young ladies... then perhaps that is something I can arrange.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! You can?!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Eve... You have to let go! Otherwise, you'll fall too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what's going on here? Anyone?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">P-Professor! You're a sorcerer!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">No, Miss Fey. We have already established that magic doesn't exist, even in this town.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But then, how did you just do that?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What you have just seen... was the last, and greatest, illusion within Labyrinthia!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? An illusion?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Magic is but an illusion. And this illusion has been produced through the power of suggestion and Labrelum's...medication. Everyone in Labyrinthia has been under this particular "magic spell". Now then, shall we break the spell?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Magic" is the last mystery to be solved...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">You've seen through all my tricks, Layton...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I wouldn't have done it without the vital hint you gave me when we spoke in your tower. "The final spell is concealed at the start."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay...so what does that mean?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">As you know, all the spells are listed within this book.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right...the Grand Grimoire!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Now, what did Mr Cantabella mean by the start?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The...front cover?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Precisely, Mr Wright. The final spell shall dispel the illusion. The correct incantation is hidden on the front cover itself. Well then, Mr Wright. This is the final puzzle. Soon a new day will begin for the townspeople. Let us put an end to this illusion, once and for all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Picarats">90</line>
<line speaker="Notes">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Additional dialogue">N/A</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The sun is rising, and when it does... its light will reveal the truth behind Labyrinthia's mysteries.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes. Shall we, Mr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix/Layton">Taelende!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this is...the real "magic" behind Labyrinthia...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Excellent work, my boy!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, it's Luke!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on a second! The town's full of machinery?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So much for magic. It was all done with these machines!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">That's right. With magic, witches can fly, buildings can disappear... Those are no easy feats to stage. To make all those incredible things real, we needed a great deal of machinery.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Couldn't he have just, I dunno, made the magic a bit simpler?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">A "witch" would say the incantation, and Shades would "stop time" with their silver bells.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And they'd go wild with these machines, making all sorts of crazy stuff happen! That's so cool. I'd love to try it!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I took a quick crash course before operating the machines! Not bad, hey?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes, Luke. What would we do without you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, when's my turn? I wanna pick something up off the ground and make it fly through the air!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I wish you'd stop looking at me when you say that, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Well... In any case, I think we should head back to the courthouse.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right you are, Professor! The judge might have fallen asleep waiting for us!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The sun has risen above Labyrinthia and has shown us our town's true form. Well, I really don't think there is any need for a verdict any more. The witches on trial weren't witches after all. I am deeply relieved that those I have sentenced are still alive and well. At last, I can step down from this seat with a clear conscience. And now... the final verdict in the last Witches' Court session ever to be held...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm very grateful for all the help, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">The feeling is mutual, Mr Wright. A gentleman always fights for the truth. I could not have done otherwise.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'd like to congratulate the two of you. You both did splendidly in the court.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! It's the judge!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You've brought to light the truth about this town... although I still find it astonishing that we could not see all of this. I cannot even begin to imagine how it was achieved...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">You were all given a very simple instruction when you were hypnotised. "You cannot see pure black." That was sufficient.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, now I see! These strange contraptions are made from some sort of black metal...</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Wait just a second! There are plenty of black objects all over Labyrinthia, aren't there?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, that's right! My hair's charcoal black, too!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">...Ah, but it is not pure black.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Whaaat...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">What we often perceive as the colour black is in fact far from being "pure black". Our brains interpret reflections of light as colours. Objects which reflect even the smallest amount of light are not pure black.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Pure black is only encountered within nature as darkness.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Darkness, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">The machines used in Labyrinthia are coated in a special material developed by Labrelum Inc. It absorbs light without reflecting any. It is the only material that can be said to be pure black.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! I bet this invisibility robe is also made of that same material, right?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">That's correct. And of course, the bell tower was concealed using the very same material as well.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">............ When you think about it... this town abounds in all things invisible.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Miss Darklaw...or should I say Miss Belduke...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Y-yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">For ten long years, your memories had been suppressed.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">The truth about what occurred in the belfry was invisible to me, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Cantabella and your father knew it all along. They knew who actually rang the bell.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What? Did they really... Is that true, Cantabella?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">As we have demonstrated, it was easy to deduce from the situation in the belfry.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">But if he knew that all along, why didn't he say something...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">It was, of course, for your own good.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">You were trying to pin the blame for that disaster on Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Yes, I was! But if you knew that, why did you keep quiet about it...? If you had only scolded me back then for lying... maybe Espella wouldn't have suffered such trauma!</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............ It was...your eyes, Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Your eyes weren't those of a liar. You believed in what you said. You truly thought it was Espella. What you saw was too much for you to bear. Your mind blocked out the real memory of what happened in order to maintain your own sanity.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">You would probably have suffered a mental breakdown.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Cantabella and your father created this town. You were mistaken in thinking it was purely for Espella's sake. It was also for you, Miss Belduke.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Argh...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Remember what your father wrote in his suicide note.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ I had an argument with my father once. He was always thinking only about the town and paid no attention to me...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">So you moved out and broke off contact with him... But you were wrong about your father. Not a single day passed without him thinking about you. He helped to make the Story I was weaving a reality, for your sake.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ I've been so ignorant. I was so convinced Father was driven to suicide by you...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Your father couldn't bear the sense of guilt he had accumulated over the past ten years. Even though he killed himself in the end, I believe you were always the most important person to him.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="???">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Eve...?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Espella! ............ Espella, what I did to you is unforgivable. I rewrote your Story, putting you through all this... I can't believe I went to such an extreme because of one wrong assumption!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">No, it's okay, Eve. I wasn't angry.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">You weren't?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">You've always been on my side. Protecting me. And even today...you saved my life.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Espella...</line>
<line speaker="Espella">I also owe you an apology. After all...I forgot about my dearest friend. I'm so sorry, Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">...Meow.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Ah, there you are, Eve! Where were you, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Ahh... Your cat's called Eve?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Eh hehe. You know what I've just noticed? You two are very much alike. You and Eve the cat.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Wh-what...? It's all in your head.</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meow.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">It looks like Eve has taken a liking to the other Eve!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You've got that right! And the similarity is really striking!</line>
<line speaker="Eve">...Meow.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Oh dear...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">My accidental guests, Professor Layton and Mr Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I must say, I am indebted to you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, don't mention it.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">You know, when I started planning my revenge three months ago... Mr Layton was a part of my plans. I needed to lure him to Labyrinthia.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Why me?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">You were famous in London, and word of your skills reached me even here. What's more, you specialise in mysteries... So I thought that if you came to this town, you'd feel compelled to solve ours.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ha, well...I am honoured.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's cool. And...what about me?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Ah...well. About you... Err, how should I put it... Your arrival here was purely accidental.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean it wasn't planned?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">As you know, Espella escaped and got involved in that incident on the freighter. As a consequence, I had no choice but to bring you here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see. <thought>I shouldn't have asked...  My fragile pride has suffered yet another blow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, you can't escape your fate. You're doomed to always find trouble, if it doesn't find you first!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How about some words of sympathy for a change?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">I am terribly sorry. The only thing on my mind the last three months was revenge.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Whatever your intentions were, the last witch trial has ended in the best possible way for this town. You were correct in your judgement. You always are.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">You're too kind to me...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I thank you from the bottom of my heart, Eve. For opening my eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sorry to break up this little happy ending, but... I've sorta got an important question. Why were you going to end the Story?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............ Only Newton knew the real reason... I am suffering from an incurable illness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what...?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">D-Dad! You're ill? I-is it serious?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">It is a rare disease with no known cure.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">Why didn't you tell me?! Had I known...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I wanted this to be my secret. I suppose that was a bad decision on my part. I thought I'd finish the Story before I died and lay the foundations for a new world. Honestly, I was desperate. I didn't much care about Labyrinthia any more.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Dad...why did it have to happen to you?! Especially now that we're finally back together...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Cheer up, Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">How can I?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Labrelum's new drug development centre contacted me a short while ago. They have succeeded in creating a new medicine, thanks to Belduke's research. It's a top secret wonder drug for my illness.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">A wonder drug?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Newton had been working on finding a cure for my illness until the very end. It would seem that the cure was his final gift to me.</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">...! My father...</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Newton was the truest friend I ever had. I'm going to undergo surgery. Do not fear, I shall return. So stop making that sad face, Espella.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ Dad...will everything be back to how it once was?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Of course it will.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">And, Eve...will you...will you still be my friend?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............ Of course.* <thought>voice-over only</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">Thank you!* <thought>voice-over only</thought></line>
<line speaker="Espella">I'm going to drop by Mrs Eclaire's bakery. I've got so much to tell her! Do you mind if I go, Dad? It won't take long.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">Of course not. Please do.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Looks like Eve wants to come too!</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">What? Oh... You meant the cat...</line>
<line speaker="Eve">Meow.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Espella, mind if we tag along?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Not at all! You're welcome to come!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Awesome! Maybe we'll get some tasty baked bread out of this!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Uhm...I thought we were going there for a different reason... Well anyway, I'll be off then, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Pass on my regards to Mrs Eclaire, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, uhm... What's going to happen to the town?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I've released everyone from hypnosis. They will soon recover the memories of their lives before Labyrinthia. As of today, Project Labyrinthia is over.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">They are free to leave, if they so wish. I imagine they will make a run for it... This place will turn into uninhabited ruins, just like it was ten years ago.</line>
<line speaker="???">I have some doubts about that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Your Honour!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I now understand that this town is an artificial creation of yours. Nonetheless... To us Labyrinthians, the past ten years were real.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............</line>
<line speaker="Layton">No one can yet tell how this town will change. However, it is possible... that some people will want to stay. Who knows, perhaps you will find yourself creating a new town along with them.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">A new town, you say...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I am no longer the judge. But, if possible... I would like to remain here.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............ You have my gratitude, Your Honour.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You need not address me as "Your Honour" any more, "Sir Storyteller".</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">...Heh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whew...and so... the last witch trial has drawn to a close.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What a beautiful sound.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Almost as if it's ringing in a new beginning for the town.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Thank you, Eve...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Okay, then... whenever you are ready, Mr Barnham.</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Thank you! Thank you all so much for everything!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Espella, you take care now!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You too, Mr Cantabella! Bye!</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Be sure to visit us again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can bet on it!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I wish all of you the very best!</line>
<line speaker="Townspeople">Goodbye!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Mr Wright... I knew I could count on you, to stand your ground and fight me to the very end.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me too... I always believed in you, Professor. And I know that's why we managed to get to the mysterious truth behind this town.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">When we get back to England, we'll drop by and see you, Luke.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Great! I'll show you around London!</line>
<line speaker="Luke">You know, Professor, I feel like I've just finished reading a really long story.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Indeed, Luke, I know what you mean. It certainly was an enthralling adventure.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I wonder how Espella and the others back in Labyrinthia are getting on... I'd love to go back and see them. Although I'd rather not have to be sucked into a book to get there...</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Perhaps we should ask Carmine to come along with us.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">Great! It's a real relief he recovered from all of his injuries! ...But he was a bit put out when he found out you'd already solved all the town's secrets, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ha ha ha... Well, we mustn't forget that we didn't solve them all by ourselves... We couldn't have done it without the help of our friends across the Atlantic.</line>
<line speaker="Luke">I wonder what they're doing right now... Battling away in a courtroom somewhere?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">I'd wager they may well be, Luke. At any rate, we must make our own preparations. There's a brand new case that requires our attention... And that means a brand new set of puzzles to be solved, my boy.</line>
<line speaker="???">If clearing for the first time</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's the matter, Wright? Has the cat got your tongue?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Or are you still in a holiday kind of mood? Perhaps your mind is as clouded as the English sky...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Any hints, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Not really. If only the professor were here... I think at this point you've gotta use that patented "spell" of yours, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Patented spell?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Helloooo, Earth to Nick?! Just when we think it's all over, you always use it to turn the tables!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ah, got it. I just have to close my eyes and say the "magic" word... Luckily, I don't need a witch's sceptre for this one... Heh.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Save the chit-chat for later, Wright. I've almost missed that utterly annoying "spell" of yours... Fine. Let's hear it then.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">Well, well, well! Thought you could get rid of me that easily, did you?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh...  Um... Any hints, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Not really. If only the professor were here... I think at this point you've gotta use that patented "spell" of yours, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Patented spell?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Helloooo, Earth to Nick?! Just when we think it's all over, you always use it to turn the tables!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ah, got it. I just have to close my eyes and say the "magic" word... Luckily, I don't need a witch's sceptre for this one... Heh.</line>
<line speaker="Flynch">What's this? A spell? What foolishness are you spouting?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Just take a deep breath and give it all you've got!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, here goes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Fin.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I have no idea how... And here's your penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arrghhhhhhhh! P-Professor...I could really use a hand!</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Regrettably, Mr Wright, I cannot oblige your request.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why not...?</line>
<line speaker="Layton">A gentleman must play the game fair and square, would you not agree?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ughhh... Apparently gentlemen make for pretty cold-hearted prosecutors.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">I am, after all, a gentleman.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's rather hopeless. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's...hopeless?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, defender. Hopeless. That which lacks hope. Much like the accused's fate. And here is the punishment to match such a performance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I could've done without the definition... or the insult, for that matter...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Unfortunately, you appear to be mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gaaaaah! <thought>Ugh... Yeah, it looks like I was wrong.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah, Mr Wright. Speaking of mistakes, that reminds me of a puzzle...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I understand that puzzle-solving is a wonderful pastime, but please indulge in it after this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">Ah, yes. My apologies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Are you trying to make me feel worse, Professor...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, hello? Espella?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">Oh! Yes? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Regarding the testimony we've just heard... Is there anything you'd like to say about it?</line>
<line speaker="Espella">............ I'm sorry, Mr Wright. I'm not sure about anything at all...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something's blocking out her memories... Maybe trying to force them back all at once isn't the best thing for her... I've got no choice now but to trust the professor and keep on going.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, let's carry on. Witness, continue testifying!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr Storyteller?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">............ I am no longer the Storyteller. I am...Arthur Cantabella.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The president of Labrelum Inc., a pharmaceutical company...yes, I know.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">That's my true identity.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay. So, Mr Cantabella, is there anything in the testimony we've just heard that you'd like to expand on?</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">No, there is nothing to add.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you really sure about that? The expression on your face indicated otherwise.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">I'm afraid you are mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ By the way, I wanted to tell you I'm a big fan of Labrelum's flu syrup. The slogan's kind of catchy, too.</line>
<line speaker="Storyteller">"Hey, you! You, with the flu! Labrelum that illness and feel good as new!" ...I wrote that one.</line>
<line speaker="Layton">If I may interrupt... This small talk is irrelevant to the trial and probably of little interest to Mr Cantabella, the company president.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's right. And now, witness, continue testifying!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Ms Darklaw...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you like to comment on the testimony we've just heard?</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seemed like something in it attracted your attention...</line>
<line speaker="Darklaw">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess whatever I say, she'll just stand there going "..." with her eyes closed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Darklaw doesn't make a great witness, does she?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't you "..." me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, witness, continue testifying!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There is no need to continue this trial. The accused's true identity has been proven beyond doubt. The court shall now issue the final verdict for Espella Cantabella!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is a crime to be a witch. We must do everything to erase magic from the world. Despicable witch! Into the flames with you!</line>
</xml>