<xml>
<title>The Forgotten Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Kay">Wh-Who are you...? Why are you wearing that raincoat...? Ah! AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHhhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This badge's design is said to reflect the relentlessness and discipline of law enforcement. It comes from the authority vested in us as strict protectors of the law... ...and executors of sentences, much like harsh winter frosts and blazing summer days. To wear it is to identify oneself as a prosecutor, but I have no interest in doing so.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Each Prosecutor's Badge is engraved with the number of its owner on the back. Hmph. Numbers. As if we're not human on the inside like everyone else!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Calm down. You're getting dust everywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I've already cleaned this room three times since this morning!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, now you'll need to do it a fourth time.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You're way too calm, sir! What if they actually take your badge!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A decision has not yet been made.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But it looks like it's pretty much decided! Don't you remember what Judge Courtney said!?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Prosecutor Edgeworth, the P.I.C. has you in its sights. They will receive a report on everything you did here today... ...and you will most likely be required to appear before them.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have been ordered to attend the meeting. ...That's all.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I hate this, sir! I won't be able to work with you anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As a detective, perhaps you should welcome this turn of events. You would no longer have to work with such a troublesome prosecutor as myself.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-Why would you say something like that, sir...? The problem is with the P.I.C. and their false accusations... Mr. Edgeworth... Don't tell me... you actually want to become a defense attorney?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">B-Because you can't do that! Being a prosecutor is exactly what makes you Prosecutor Edgeworth, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...A defense attorney, huh? I became a prosecutor because of the incident where I lost my father... However, the reason I became interested in the legal world... ...was because my father who passed away... had been a defense attorney.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">To fight crime as a prosecutor, or to save people as a defense attorney. I want you to think carefully, about how you want to live your life from now on.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Are you listening, sir!? I don't like this one bit!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is no need for you to be so pessimistic. Maybe my replacement will be more lenient during your salary assessments.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A-Ah, I see... That way, I can eat more than just instant noodles every day...! Wait, what am I saying!? That's not the point here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He was... actually imagining it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We're busy right now! Come back later, pal!</line>
<line speaker="???">Paging Mr. Edgeworth. Is there a Mr. Miles Edgeworth here?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth is busy now! I'll listen to whatever you have to say later, pal!</line>
<line speaker="???">Hrmm... This isn't good! Your face has become all red. Errrm... A red face, a red face...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm, like I said, we're kind of busy right now, so...</line>
<line speaker="???">I've got it! You have a tummy ache, right!? This calls for an injection, stat! Please roll up your sleeves!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aiiieeeee! Nonono, I'm perfectly healthy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Who might you be?</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Aaaah, I'm so sorry! I forgot to introduce myself! My name is Karin Jenson. I am a registered nurse at the Dye-Young Hospital.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sorry, but nobody here is sick. You must have the wrong room.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Are you Mr. Miles Edgeworth? You have such great wrinkles between your brow... Could it be lupus? This calls for an injection...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-It's not lupus! Just tell me what business you have with me!</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Ahh. Yes, yes. Actually, there's someone who would like to see you. Please wait a moment. I'll call them here right now!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She left, sir. I wonder who she's going to bring. Hmm, if she's bringing someone from the hospital... Could it be a patient, sir? Maybe it's someone who was traumatized by your harsh words...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">S-See? When you glare at me like that, it feels like I'm going to have a heart attack. You could send someone to the hospital with that...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I-Is it really that bad...? I'm just being my normal self, though.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karin">Sorry for the wait! Well, what do you think?</line>
<line speaker="???">........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do I think...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Umm... Do you not recognize me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Now that she mentions it, I feel like I've met her before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Umm... this card... Your name was written on it... Do you know who I am?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">M-Mr. Edgeworth... Maybe you really did send her to the hospital...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course not!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But this is your business card, sir. It clearly says... "Prosecutor Miles Edgeworth".</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Umm. Th-That's true...</line>
<line speaker="???">I-I am terribly sorry... I'm, umm, well...</line>
<line speaker="Karin">The truth is, this girl... suffers from memory loss.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">M... Memory loooosss?</line>
<line speaker="???">Yes... That seems to be the case.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Ahh... Her parents should be worried sick right now... They probably haven't been able to sleep. I doubt they've gotten more than 8 hours...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Isn't that plenty of sleep?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I see. It sure sounds horrible... but it's alright now! Since she has that business card, she must be an acquaintance of Mr. Edgeworth's. Just leave her to us, pal! Right, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed... We might be able to verify her identity, at least.</line>
<line speaker="???">Would you... really do that for me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">First, I'd like you to tell us everything that you know.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's our Mr. Edgeworth! You have nothing to worry about now, Miss!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Good grief...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...I am terribly sorry. Even if you give me that, I still don't remember anything about you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No... I wasn't planning on giving it to you...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>But still, where to begin? What should I ask her first...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Miss. Do you remember your name?</line>
<line speaker="???">My name...... I am terribly sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">She's been like this ever since yesterday, y'know?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hmm. So you found her yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Wooow! That's amazing! How'd you know!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wh... What a tiresome woman...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karin">I found her stumbling around late last night, so I took her in. I wanted to help her out, so I looked through her things.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, that's how you found my business card. Did she have anything else with her?</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Nothing to reveal her name or address... Ah! But! She was wearing this when I found her. It's an unusual design, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wha... Th-This badge is...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whaaaaaaat! Th-The Yatagarasu's...! That means... I-I-It couldn't be!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you Kay!?</line>
<line speaker="???">Kay......?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You are... Kay, right?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I am... Kay......</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Kay! Don't you remember me!? I mean, you'd always call me "Gummy", pal!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">G-Gummy... I would call one of my elders something so rude...? Aaah... I'm so sorry! What a horrible thing I did...! I feel like my heart is going to burst from guilt!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Just...... Just what happened to you, pal! You've become so sensitive! If you're this sensitive, and delicate, and frail... ...then you're not even Kay anymore! You're someone else, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Watch your words, Detective. If you say that... ...it almost sounds like Kay isn't sensitive or delicate at all. <thought>Though I can't deny there is some truth to what he says.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Umm... What sort of person was I... before I lost my memory?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, for starters, your name was Kay Faraday. A cheerful girl full of spirit and vigor, and a Great Thief.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Great Thief...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. To put it frankly... ...a Great Thief steals valuables from people's drawers and safes...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">St........Steal!! I caused so much trouble for others? Ahh... I'm so sorry! I never imagined I would be a criminal...! Maybe losing my memory was retribution for my crimes...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, you didn't actually...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Uuugghh... This is so messed up, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Karin">But it does sort of make sense, y'know. These gloves and stuff, they look just like what a thief might wear.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! Those clothes!</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Yes. She was wearing them when I found her. I had her change her clothes, so I'm holding onto them for now...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm...? Something appears to be stuck on her clothes. Perhaps it has something to do with Kay's memory loss?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'll send it down to the lab later and have them check it out, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Good. I will be counting on you, Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">At any rate... these really look like a thief's clothes, don't they!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I-I am... a criminal...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's true you were a Great Thief, but never once did you commit a crime. That alone I can assure you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Is that... so...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's probably better if I don't press this issue any further.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Is that a badge... for protecting someone? Like a badge worn by a hero of justice... right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No... This is called a Prosecutor's Badge. I think what you're referred to would be a defense attorney's badge, right?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I wonder...? This badge... makes me feel really nostalgic. As if someone really dear to me showed it to me a lot...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Kay's father was a prosecutor. Perhaps little bits of her childhood memories still remain.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Do you like badges, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm. Not particularly.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But you are always carrying around badges.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is just a part of my job. And this badge is also a piece of evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I see. So you carry around things that you don't like in order to train and strengthen your spirit!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That is just clearly wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the badge that Kay is always wearing. It's emblazoned with the mark of the Yatagarasu and it really stands out. I doubt there are any thieves who would actually wear it.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...I'm really sorry. For not remembering you. Umm... What kind of relationship did we have?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm. Well, that's... <thought>Rather difficult to explain.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Kay, you were... Mr. Edgeworth's assistant!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh my! So then, a prosecutor is the kingpin of a Great Thief?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Uh, no... That's not what I meant, pal...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The last time I met "Kay" was the day before yesterday... Just what did she do from then up until now...?</thought> Ms. Jenson, was the badge the only thing this girl had on her?</line>
<line speaker="Karin">She did have some other things, but I don't think they will be very helpful at all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't mind. Please show them to me.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Well then, I'll give them to you one by one, OK!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is a Jammin' Ninja mask. Maybe she went to a superhero show or something?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm. This seems to be a letter addressed to Kay. This is a ticket stub. And this is...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...a flower made of cloth! Like the ones you usually see in restrooms, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...A corsage. It is used primarily as an accessory for women.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Well, that's everything. Did you find anything out?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm, not really. They were just a bunch of random things.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'll have to look them over in more detail later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ooh.... This is horrible! Kay's lost her memory! How do we get her back to normal!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Calm down, Detective. I have already thought of something.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! As I would expect of Mr. Edgeworth! So, what did you find out, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Look at this ticket stub.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Oh, it's a ticket for the viewing platform of the Grand Tower!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm, Ms. Nurse? Do you know something about the Grand Tower?</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Of course I do! It's a super famous dating spot, after all! They say that if a couple holds hands up there, they will be together forever... Tee hee.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The time stamp on the ticket is from yesterday. Moreover, it is only valid on the day of issue.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Since she only has the stub... she must have used it, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is very likely. ...Well then, let's go.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ehh! Right now, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The cause of Kay's memory loss is hidden in her actions.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">B-But... What about the P.I.C.!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's still too early for me to be summoned there.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Errrm... So, should I leave Kay with you, then?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That is what I would prefer. Kay, you're fine with that, right?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah... Yes, please! Thank you very much!</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Well, I have to get back to work, so if anything happens, please contact the Dye-Young Hospital. If you guys need an injection, I'll be there anytime, please!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. I understand. <thought>I don't think I will call her for an injection, though.</thought> Well then. Let's go, Detective. ...And you too, Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yessir!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Thank you... for helping me.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm. According to the pamphlet... ...this building is 50 stories tall. It's mostly filled with offices though... Only the viewing platform is open to the public. Here you go, sir. I just got this at the reception desk.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Good. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well then, let us head inside immediately...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="???">No, you can't! Please stop! Please... I beg of you! Ugh, it's no good. Unless I drink fresh milk, my thoughts just won't reach...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What's wrong, pal!? Did something happen at the Grand Tower!?</line>
<line speaker="???">E-Excuse me! We're sort of in the middle of shooting a movie, and umm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Hmph. I suspected as much.</thought> We are sorry for any trouble we've caused you. ...Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-I'm so sorry, pal! I really thought the tower was gonna collapse or something...</line>
<line speaker="???">Whatever... Hey, director! I'm taking a break.</line>
<line speaker="???">I'm sorry... I'm really, really sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What a relief... It looks like the tower's collapse was prevented somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Explaining all this to Kay as she is now would take more time than it's worth...</thought> Well then. We should get going.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wow, what a view! I bet I can see my house from here!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eek...! Th-The wind... is really strong up here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Everything should be fine as long as you stay close to me and Mr. Edgeworth, pal. If you start to blow away, one of us will be sure to catch you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's not as if she's a kite!</thought> Kay, do you recognize this place?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...I-I don't know. Was I... really here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Maybe if I get her to talk a bit, it will help jog her memory...</thought> Kay. Just tell me whatever you remember. Anything will do.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">O-OK. But I don't know how much help I'll be...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Did I... really come to a place like this?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm. Her memory isn't clearing up at all, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...I'm so sorry. It's a bit pathetic, isn't it? You are both going out of your way for me, but I'm not helping at all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're doing just fine. You have memory loss, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Alright, Mr. Edgeworth! Remember to go easy on her, sir. Normally, you have this really intense and kind of scary look on your face.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...You're not helping, Detective.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Did I... really come to a place like this?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This ticket stub proves that you were indeed here.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But I really don't remember coming here at all. I don't think I would want to come to a place like this.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's so high up, and the wind is so strong... It's frightening.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You used to love places like these, though.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Was that... really me? We're so high up... Just looking down makes me dizzy. I think these kinds of places should be shut down. What if an elderly person or a small child were to fall off...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The railing here is quite high. I think your worries are unfounded.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Is that so...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...I just can't remember. I can't remember anything at all...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You say you don't remember anything... In that case, is there anything that looks familiar?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Looks familiar? Umm....... Ah! The cherry tree!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What about the cherry tree?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I was standing under that cherry tree... That's right, I was taking shelter from the rain because it was raining then... And there... A red... I saw... something red...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm. She was under the cherry tree while it rained... And... from there she saw something red...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Umm, is something wrong...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's nothing. Could you add that last part to your story?</line>
<line speaker="Change this statement to">"But... from under the cherry tree... I feel like... I saw something red."</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But... from under the cherry tree... I feel like... I saw something red.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A red... what exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">A red... something or other. It was something red. That's... all I can remember about it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Speaking of things that are red here...</thought> Could it be that stand over there?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Stand... A red... stand... ...Ahh, that's right! I saw someone walking towards me from the other side of that stand.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And then what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And then... Umm... .....I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's alright. Simply add everything you just said to your story.</line>
<line speaker="Change this statement to">"Umm... That's right, someone was walking towards me from the other side of that stand."</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Umm... That's right, someone was walking towards me from the other side of that stand.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">By that stand, do you mean the stand directly behind you?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes. From behind that red stand, someone came walking towards me... I saw it from under the cherry tree.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You've been saying that you saw "someone"... Does that mean you didn't see their face? Or was it a person you didn't know?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">.....I'm sorry. That much, I don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So "someone" came walking towards her from behind the red stand... ...and she saw that from beneath the cherry tree.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kay">.....I'm sorry. Just as I thought, it's impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is there nothing else that comes to mind? It doesn't have to be related to the case.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Even if it's not related.....? Umm... Well... Ah... I remember that the stand there was selling cotton candy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...If you're hungry, you should just say so.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'll make sure to buy one for you later, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Thank you very much. I look forward to it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's not much I can do unless I can draw out more information from her... For now, I'll press her for more details and see what I can find out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, you're saying that someone came from behind the stand... ...and walked directly towards you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes. Someone came right up to me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then that "someone" must have been a ghost.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">No, it was a person! I'm sure of it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If this is where you were under the cherry tree, then someone behind the stand... ...wouldn't have any ground to stand on. They'd be floating in midair! No person should be able to stand there!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But... I... I'm not lying! Someone... red... Someone in red... was on the other side of the stand... They were walking towards me... Ahh... Getting closer and closer, and then... ...that person... that person... AAAAAAAAAHHHH!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What's wrong!? Calm down! It's alright! Me and Mr. Edgeworth are both here for you, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I-I... I was... pushed off. That person... in red... Yes, they were wearing a red raincoat...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Someone in a red raincoat was walking in midair? And furthermore, they pushed her off this building? Nonsense. There is no way she could be alright after falling from a building this high!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Officer">Attention, everyone! Please remain where you are!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What's wrong, pal? I'm a detective! Tell me what's going on!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Sir! A body was just discovered in this building!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A-A body!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Who is the victim!?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">We're currently investigating the details, but the victim is a woman! We have verified that her name is "Kay"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">WHAAAAAAAAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Th-This room is...!</thought> Would this room happen to be...</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Yes, sir! It's the Prosecutorial Investigation Committee's meeting room!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whaat! It's here!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I had heard they recently moved out of the Prosecutor's Building. <thought>But to think that they moved here of all places...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karin">Mr. Edgeworth! Kay! What brings you here? How are you holding up?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We're in the middle of an investigation right now. Sorry, but who might this be?</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Ah! This is my Granny! Errm, let me just... "Hi there sonny, the name's Bonnie Young. Who the heck are you?" ...she says.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is a pleasure to meet you. My name is Miles Edgeworth. I am a prosecutor. Ms. Jenson, isn't Young the name of...</line>
<line speaker="Karin">*ahem!* Granny is the director of the Dye-Young Hospital!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This old lady... is the director?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karin">"Who're you callin' old!" ...she says.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Sh-She can read my thoughts?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! So that Granny is pretty important, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Ah ha ha! I wouldn't go that far... I mean, yes, she is. Aah, these people are... the patient's guardians. Y'know, the one with amnesia...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm. It seems she is a bit of an introvert.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karin">"Hey sonny, want me to cure that bad case of the frownies for you?" ...she says.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ha ha ha! I'm afraid that's an incurable disease for Mr. Edgeworth, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Eh? Really, Granny? You want me to say that... "I ain't got nothin' to say to you whippersnappers! You're free to do whatever you want. But you better not get in the way of my autopsy."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please wait. We're...</line>
<line speaker="Karin">"No means no!"</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, you don't have the right to decide that, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Karin">S-Sorry! Granny is the coroner, you see. And she's in charge of this case, so... Ouch! So, I'm very sorry, but that's the way it is.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whaddaya mean, "that's the way it is," pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Well... Even if you ask me, I'm not the one who said it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I kinda feel like..... I'm watching a comedy act, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Well, we need to get back to the autopsy, so please excuse us! And take care!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What was with her attitude!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We received permission to investigate. There shouldn't be any problems.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That atittude of hers is a huge problem, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth...? What do we do now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We'll investigate the scene, of course. As a prosecutor, I cannot stand by and do nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">.........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well then, let's begin.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But, the policeman said the dead person is also named "Kay"... Then, I'm pretty sure I'm not the Kay that you know, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We shall investigate that now. But... don't worry. There's no question that you are the Kay I know.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">.....OK!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>An amnesiac Kay, and a corpse Kay... Both are connected to the Grand Tower. I'm certain that this case will lead me to Kay's lost memories!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">For a homicide to occur out of the blue like that, it sure is surprising, sir! I may be a detective, but when things happen so suddenly, my mind goes completely blank! And that's why I haven't noticed anything at all, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It takes a certain kind of talent to be able to declare that so cheerfully.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">O... Oh...! Are you saying I'm talented!? I-I'm honored, sir! Being praised by Mr. Edgeworth! Those kind words... I'll never forget this moment!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...He looks so happy, I can't bring myself to tell him that it's all a misunderstanding!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I never thought the P.I.C.'s meeting room would be right under the viewing platform.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It sure saved us the trouble of getting here! In fact, the P.I.C. is actually mentioned in this pamphlet, sir. It's in the Grand Tower's Little Gossip Column. ...I'll read it for you! "The Prosecutorial Investigation Committee is located on the 50th floor of the Grand Tower! It's a place where Prosecutors turn into Ex-Prosecutors."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">"So come visit the 50th floor, and see the dejected looks on the Prosecutors' faces!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I am not making a dejected face!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! I'm just reading what's in the pamphlet, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The living Kay we have here, and the dead "Kay" over there... Why do they have the same name? It can't just be a coincidence, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. However, we won't be able to answer that question until we examine the body...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's all because of that crabby coroner!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">She is only doing her job. For now, all we can do is wait.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm... Th-Then right now, since we have some time... ...allow me to present one of my theories to you, sir! The answer is simple! With all the advancements in scientific technology... ...what if the two Kays are clones!? That's the only way any of this makes sense!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............ Let's investigate the other parts of the room, until the autopsy is finished.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aww, please don't ignore me like that, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If you're not going to be a prosecutor anymore, then what am I supposed to do...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now isn't the time to be thinking of such things, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But! It's not fair that the P.I.C. keeps on hounding you like this, Mr. Edgeworth! You haven't even done anything wrong! If anything, you just... rub people the wrong way.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You should watch what you say as well, so you don't rub people the wrong way.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's Kay's treasure. She always wears it on her clothes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even after seeing her own badge, she still didn't remember anything...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's just strange, seeing Kay acting so unlike herself. I'm not even sure how I should act towards her anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You should just be yourself, Detective. For her sake.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">! You're right, sir! Alright! Well then, time to start making some careless mistakes!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He's actually aware that he makes careless mistakes...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A letter has a stamp... right? And stamps... go right into my collection.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I never pictured you as a stamp enthusiast, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whenever I get a letter, I make sure to check the stamps very carefully. And, if I find one that doesn't have a postmark on it...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Are you saying that you reuse old stamps?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">O-Of course not, sir. I'm a law-abiding Detective, after all. Ha ha ha.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Something tells me that isn't completely true.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I wonder where Kay lost her memories. *sigh*... Maybe one of the security guards found it, and it's sitting in the Lost &amp; Found...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe... Are you joking around?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Not at all, sir! I just want to do something for Kay! Anything! Because... I just feel so bad for her.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that's how you feel, then devote yourself completely to the investigation... ...because right now, that's the only thing we can do.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes... Yes, sir! Just tell me whatever you want me to do!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ha ha ha! Mr. Edgeworth, you're such a joker! Even if you show that to me, I still have no idea what it is, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He proclaimed that quite proudly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">These books all seem really think and heavy, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The P.I.C. did just move in here. Moving all these books must have been a lot of work.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Moving heavy objects is my specialty, sir! If they had just called me, I would've helped!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh. Then perhaps I should ask the chairman if there's anything else left for you to move.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Whooooah! Th-That was just a joke, sir! If I had to carry something up 50 stories, I wouldn't be able to do any more work today!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Of course, I was joking too... But were you really going to carry things up the stairs?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's half of a large round table with 11 chairs. It seems to be based off a certain legend.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I know that one, sir! It's the famous Knights of the Brown Table!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-Huh!? Was I wrong? Knights of the Clown Table? Knights who say Ni!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He's getting colder... But I won't say anything.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes? Can I help with something?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Umm... This is an amazing room. There are large boxes filled with books, a stone sculpture, and sparkly windows.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It seems you have also forgotten the names of objects. This might be helpful for recovering your memories. Just repeat after me. Bookcase.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Broken safe.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Stained glass.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Stolen goods.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Books on the law.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Crooks on the lam.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Statue of the goddess.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Snatched loot of the Great Thief.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Are all her mistakes biased towards a certain way...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay. Until just a few days ago, you were calling yourself my assistant. Looking at me, is there anything you remember?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Things I remember, huh? Well, yes, just one thing... Mr. Edgeworth, on the viewing platform above us...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You pointed at me, and...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">With a really scary face, you interrogated me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...That happened just a few minutes ago!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, poor Kay! The terror of Mr. Edgeworth badgering you for contradictions is your only memory... It must be scary, pal! Hopeless! The end of the world, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I should show this detective what true terror really is!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay. Before you lost your memories, you got along well with Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Does looking at me help you remember anything, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Do I remember anything? Ummm... Hmmmm...... Ah! I know! For a while now, Mr. Edgeworth has been getting on your case!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Th-That's not a memory. It's just a pleasant part of my daily life. Isn't that right, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Oh? So Detective Gumshoe thinks it's pleasant... It seems I'll have to get on his case even more from now on!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">I was carrying this, right? ...I don't remember anything about it though.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you really don't remember? Not even a little bit?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well..... Ah! Maybe I just grabbed it without thinking, due to the shock of losing my memories! You know, like they say, "grasping at straws."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.....</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What's wrong? You have an awfully serious look on your face.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I won't tell you to be silent. But you should think before talking.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I-I see... I will keep that in mind.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The person in the red raincoat really was there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you sure that they were walking towards you from behind the stand?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's right... They walked straight up to me. There must be some evidence. Maybe that person... left footprints behind!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is no ground behind the stand. No one could have walked there...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Then, was that person... a ghost?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...There are no such things as ghosts!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">O-Oh... Is this one of those so-called "contradictions"...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">These bookshelves are very well organized. Looking at them feels good.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's true! ...There's not even a speck of dust on them. But I'm also extremely dedicated to cleaning your office, sir! First I sweep, then I vacuum, next I wipe everything clean, twice, and then I was the...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It'd be nice if you were this dedicated to your job...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karin">Um, I'm sorry. Right now Granny is in the middle of the autopsy, so... "Are you sonnies tryin' to get in the way of my autopsy!?" ...Is what she says. Could you please wait just a little bit longer?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I suppose we have no choice. We'll come back to investigate the body later.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is... Lady Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You sure do know a lot, sir. ...So, what kind of powers does she have?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">She is a symbol of justice, not a superhero. <thought>It's said the scales represent Justice; the sword, Power; and the blindfold, Equality.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is a really huge statue! Why's it in a place like this?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...She is known as the Goddess of Justice. You might call it a statue for judging prosecutors. It seems this statue was also made by Pierre Hoquet.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! You mean the victim of the IS-7 Incident, Isaac Dover!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Setting aside his background and personality... he really was a brilliant sculptor.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, they do say that artists are either geniuses or weirdos.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I suppose... Larry would fall into the latter category.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A pool of blood lies at the feet of the goddess statue. Hmm. Judging from the pool of blood, it seems that this was where the victim was killed.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But, sir... the body is over there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">After murdering the victim, did the killer move the body...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If things had gone as planned, I would have been standing here right about now.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, sir... I'm glad that the P.I.C. meeting was delayed, but the cause of the delay was due to a murder...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's troubling to think that the P.I.C. meeting could condemn my career as a prosecutor. In any case, my top priority right now is to find the truth behind this case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You there. Tell me the situation about the security of this room.</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Yes, sir! To enter this room, a special keycard is required!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. In other words, not just anyone can enter this room <thought>Security - To enter the meeting room, a special keycard is needed.</thought>. So... the person who found the body was also...?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Yes! It was a member of the P.I.C., who had come here for today's hearing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A member of the P.I.C... If not for this case, right now I would be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's rows and rows of books. This solemn atmosphere's kinda scary, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Scary? I would think that books foster a feeling of familiarity.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Actually, I once got in a lot of trouble for running through the library at full-speed, sir. But this isn't a library, so a light jog should be fine, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...... <thought>If I don't make sure to stop him, he might actually do it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">You are...? Oh, yes, what is it? "That voice... It's Von Karma, right?" Umm... Do you know her, Granny?</line>
<line speaker="???">Good to see you again, Doctor. And you as well, Miles Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh... <thought>What is she doing here!? Franziska von Karma... She is a prosecutor working with Interpol, and the daughter of Manfred von Karma. She should be jetting around the world right now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Wherever there is a case, I will follow. National borders mean nothing before me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your presence here must mean that this case has international significance...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You know well enough that I'm chasing a smuggling ring. I shall recover all the stolen goods and crush that organization!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then... does that mean the smuggling ring is also involved in this particular case?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Any further information is confidential. I am not obligated to speak of it with you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...! <thought>So, it won't be that easy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karin">Umm, Ms. Franziska... von Karma? Granny says... "The autopsy is complete. You're free to do what you want."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In that case, we would like to investigate as well.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">"I've heard rumors about you! No way am I letting you near the body! You're the prosecutor who's about to get the boot. You best run on home now, sonny!" Er, umm, just so you know, I wasn't the one who said that, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">P-Please, Granny. We need to investigate... No matter what.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">"Hey, lassie! Who you callin' Granny!?"</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eeek...! I-I'm sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>We're not getting anywhere... I guess I have no other choice.</thought> Franziska, please allow us to aid you in your investigation. We must examine that body in order to find out what happened to Kay!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">To Kay Faraday...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm asking you too, sir! Kay's in really bad shape!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">......... I don't know what's going on... ...but fine, I'll grant you permission.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...! You have my thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Of course, I didn't say it would come without a price. You will explain everything to me later.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We really owe you one, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I wasn't talking to you, Scruffy!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">YEEEEOOWCH!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">So that's how it is. If you would be so kind as to authorize them too, Doctor?</line>
<line speaker="Karin">"I suppose it's fine if he's with a prosecutor from Interpol." ...Is what she says. And I fully agree with Granny.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">By the Von Karma name, the entire world will be judged... That's just common knowledge.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's rather conceited for common knowledge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karin">"Well, it's none of my beeswax anymore." ...Is what she says. Um, I hope you don't get in trouble for this.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You needn't worry. My reputation will not be shaken by something so petty.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Unlike me, who is on the verge of losing his badge.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps the keycard the victim was holding is for this room.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'll go find out, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! From this room's security system... ...we were able to retrieve the data of the victim's card!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So that means, the victim was able to freely enter this room...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">If the card actually belonged to the victim, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Prosecutor von Karma just got here, and she's already hit me with her whip. Even if I stand further back, she always seems to hit me before I can get out of the way.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, it's worse than that. At times it feels like she'll even chase you down, if you manage to avoid her attacks.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! Yeah... That feeling of despair, I know it all too well, sir! I won't lose to you in terms of how any times she's hit me with her whip, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...That's not something to boast about.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Another Kay? I bet they look identical, sir! Like two peas in a pod.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They only share the same name. Please try not to jump the gun.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Jump the gun? ...Ahh! Is that like when you jump while you're holding a gun? The last time I did that, I accidentally discharged my gun and shot a hole in the ceiling!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's not what it means at all! It means to not be so hasty.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Understood, sir! Well then, Mr. Edgeworth! We have permission to examine the body now, so let's see what secrets Kay's pea-in-a-pod holds!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Someone's pod is missing a few peas...!</thought> Please Detective... There's no need to jump the gun...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The victim had Kay's notebook on her.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. And because of that, she was mistakenly identified as "Kay".</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">They shouldn't have botched it up so badly! It's unforgivable! I'll arrest them all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Before you arrest anyone for faulty logic, perhaps we should focus on finding the murderer?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm, yeah. I'll be helping with that too, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If botching things up were a crime, he'd be serving a life sentence...</thought> ...In any case, there may still be something we have overlooked. Let's carefully examine the body one more time.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">How do you think Kay ended up losing her memories?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Good question. Unfortunately, it will be difficult to answer at this point in time. However, the victim was in possession of the "Promise Notebook"... ...so it's possible that Kay is connected to this case in some form or other.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If her memory returned, there could be a huge breakthrough in the investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I don't imagine it will be quite that easy, though...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! I've got a plan to get Kay's memory back!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd leave that kind of thinking to the hospital staff.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Please sir... Just hear me out! First, we need to get a really big hammer...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Forget it, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">"You sonnies want something?" ...Is what she says.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Jenson. Could you tell me about your relationship with Dr. Young?</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Yes... Ever since I was little, I've always been together with Granny. Whenever I got lost, she would search for me until it got dark. And whenever I fell down, she would watch over me until I could get up on my own.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What a charming story. She sounds like quite the grandmother's child.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karin">And after I became a nurse, whenever I'm about to make a mistake with my injections... "Not there, THERE!" she'd say, as she'd grab the needle and... Ouch!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ouch! Just hearing it hurts, pal! Please keep those stories to yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Anyways, as long as I have Granny by my side, there's no nursing I can't do.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I... I see. I fully understand. Thank you for your cooperation. <thought>Regardless of her charming story, they do seem to share a very close-knit bond.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Dr. Young, you sure are a masterful coroner, pal! You work with such blinding speed and you make no wasted movements!</line>
<line speaker="Karin">"Whaddaya sonnies know about autopsies!? You don't know the first thing about my work!"</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">U-Ughhhhh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Allow me to apologize for his rudeness. I'll be sure to reprimand him later.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">"Hmph. Listen up, young'un. It is my duty to perform the autopsy quickly and accurately. That's why I have no patience with those who get in the way of my work." ...Is what she says. Are you satisfied?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, very much so. We only wish to investigate. We have no desire to get in your way. <thought>It looks like Dr. Young's stubbornness comes from her devotion to her work.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karin">The Dye-Young Hospital is a splendid hospital, and Granny is in charge of it. Well? How about it? Would you like to be admitted and experience it for yourself? "That's right. Right now, there's an opening in our hospital suite with the outdoor spa."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We are in good health. There is obviously no need for us to be hospitalized.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's right! We're perfectly healthy, pal! That's our sole redeeming feature!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Just what does he mean by that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karin">Well, you see, the Dye-Young Hospital also accepts healthy patients! We're currently in the middle of our "Full of Life! Healthy Hospital Stays" campaign. Those without injury or illness can stay at our hospital for half the price!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why would you need to stay at a hospital if you're healthy?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karin">This is the chance of a lifetime, so what do you say? Hospital stay! Hospital say!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm. You know, an outdoor spa at half-price does sound like a good deal...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Don't fall for it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karin">A Prosecutor's Badge? I've seen lots of those... Ouch! "A prosecutor who's about to get canned shouldn't be showing off his lingering attachments. If that badge means so much to you, maybe you should've lived a better life."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...What is truly important to me is not the badge itself.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Erm, I'm sure what my Granny meant to say was... There are times when you have to obey those above you... Or something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Thanks for the advice.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">I'm really glad we found Kay's father.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Um, I am an acquaintance of hers. ...I'm not her father!</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Whaaat!? Then, what about that business card?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I doubt there are many children who carry around their parents' business cards.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">But, I carry one around. Granny's, I mean. So, surely... Ouch! "I don't give a hoot how you're related! You took her in, so you'd better take good care of her!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course, that was my intention. Kay is in good hands.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">The victim was stabbed in the chest with that. See, there are three stab wounds in her chest, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Could you tell me the cause of the wound on her head?</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Sorry. We don't really know that. Although we are certain that it happened post-mortem.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Which means it may have occurred when the culprit moved the body? It would be nice if some evidence were to turn up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karin">"That's tied up pretty well, that frilly thing of yours..."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I would like you to look at this piece of evidence, rather than my clothes.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">"Not interested!" ...she says. I can't say I'm very interested either.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm. Perhaps I should try presenting a different piece of evidence?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This body...! It's not Kay, sir! It doesn't look like her at all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Of course it isn't. Kay is alive, after all.</thought> Her age is... I'd guess around 30. And she's wearing a pantsuit.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Maybe she worked in one of the offices in this building.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, her identity is still unknown. The question now becomes: why did the police believe her name was "Kay"...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is some blood on her head.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Maybe she was hit with something.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We don't know that for sure. Our investigation will ultimately clear that up.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The left side of her white jacker has been stained a deep red. This jacket... The buttons are on the right side.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Isn't that normal, sir? All of my cloths have the buttons on the right side.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For women, it is normal to have them on the left side.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth, you really do know everything.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's just common knowledge. Hmm... There doesn't seem to be anything out of place... Hm? There's something white in her pocket...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">They're gloves. Pure white ones. One for each hand, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...They don't seem to be dirty. Could they be the victim's?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Something seems to be pinned to her pocket. ...Hm. It's made out of purple cloth.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It looks like it's been forcibly torn off, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There doesn't seem to be... anything in this pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This pocket has holes in it, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Judging by how the cloth was pierced... ...she must have been stabbed by some sharp object.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">All your coins would fall out of those holes, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Detective. Haven't you ever heard of a wallet?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course I have, sir! I just use my pockets though. Most people do, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.....Never mind.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is a burn mark on her hand...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Is it conntected to the cause of death?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, it appears to be an old scar. She probably got it a long time ago. Hm. It seems there is something in her hand. Detective, could you open her hand for me?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yessir! Understood! This is... Oh, I know! This must be a gift card from a department sto- ...Yeeaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It seems to be a keycard.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Uuugh... Wh-Why...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The question is, what was this keycard <thought>Keycard - The victim was carrying a keycard. What could it have been used for?</thought> for?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! This notebook...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh!? Isn't that Kay's Promise Notebook!? This is the notebook she wrote all her promises to her father in! It really takes me back, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... <thought>When Kay was young, she and her father wrote the promises they made in this notebook...</thought> However... Why is it in a place like this...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! Now that you mention it... I once heard something from Detective Badd a long time ago. It seems that before anyone had noticed, Kay's "memento" had gone missing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What...!? So a piece of evidence that was in police custody went missing?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Detective Badd frantically searched all over for it, but it seems he never found it...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What could this mean...? Why was the missing notebook found here?</thought> You there, do you happen to know anything about this notebook?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">The victim was carrying this notebook when we found her. That was the only evidence we had to identify the body.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So that's why you called her "Kay"...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What a misleading victim, huh. Why did she have Kay's notebook...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I sure would like to have some information on the victim's identity, though...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Could this be the murder weapon, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A three-pronged candelabra. It's consistent with the number of stab wounds. She was probably stabbed by the prongs of the candelabra.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">.....A candy zebra?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'm afraid it's not quite what you're imagining, Detective. A candelabra... is a candlestick holder with multiple arms.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ahh, so it's a candle holder. You know, one time I forgot to pay my electric bill, and I had to get by only with candles.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What time period are you from...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this spot somehow connected to any of the evidence I hold...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe. Look at this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Is there something wrong with that piece of evidence, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Doesn't this piece of evidence have a connection with the situation of the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't think it's connected at all, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Argh! <thought>So I was wrong...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You should look at the evidence you have on hand again, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. There might be something that is connected to the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The purple flower Kay had with her... I wonder if that originally belonged to the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Now that you mention it... The cloth does look the same as the one on the pin!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Let's compare them without delay.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's a perfect match, sir! Way to go, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The fact that this flower belongs to the victim means...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That can only mean that Kay Faraday came in contact with the victim. And about that corsage, it looks like it was forcibly ripped off. There is a possibility that Kay Faraday is connected to this case. And depending on the situation... ...we may have to consider her as a suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What did you saaaaaaaay!? There's no way she did it! It's unthinkable! Kay could never do that, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>However, it's true we have no evidence to deny that claim.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">.........</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It's nothing more than a possibility at the moment. Isn't that right, Miles Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Indeed. For better or for worse.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is the investigation going well?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Sir! I am actually putting my job aside to do some brain training! By focusing on images instead of words, you can stimulate your right brain!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Please stop talking.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">A murder case at the P.I.C. meeting room... Since you asked to cooperate in the investigation, I do hope you will be able to produce results.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Naturally. Why do you think I am here?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well... Now that you mention it... Why are you here, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>! ...That's right. She still doesn't know about my P.I.C. hearing today.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The circumstances behind it are deeper than the sea, sir! Allow me to explain it on Mr. Edgeworth's behalf... YEOWCH!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! I do not care about your "circumstances". All that matters now is reaching the truth of this case. Am I wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. There is some truth in what you say.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If you ask me, I don't think that is totally righ- YEOWCH!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I'll say this. ...Whipping someone is easier than being worried!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But being on the receiving end of the whip isn't easy at al- YEOWCH!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska. Why are you here when you are supposed to be working with Interpol?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Curious, are you? But, it's confidential. I have no obligation to tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm. Her response was as I expected.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">More importantly, shouldn't there be a prosecutor in charge of this murder case? I don't know who it is, but I was hoping it wouldn't be someone completely useless. They're not even here yet... They're late! Just what is that fool doing!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">YEAARGH! I have nothing to do with it, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wouldn't think it's very commendable to just whip people at random...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I swing, therefore I whip! That is my philosophy. I will whip anyone who slacks off in their work!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>To the yet unseen prosecutor in charge, I hereby offer you my sympathies in advance...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Judging from your exchange just now, I take it you've met Dr. Young before?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">How astute, Miles Edgeworth. That's right. She is an acquaintance of mine. Back then... it's a long story.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It seems she doesn't intend to tell me any more. Shall I leave it at that, then?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So, what happened back then!? Please tell me all about it, sir! YEOOOWW!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">A foolish fool, shamelessly prying into other people's business. Watch what you say, Scruffy!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">How cruel! Whipping me out of the blue! With great whip comes great responsibility, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">One good whip deserves another! The scruffy fool gets the whip! Try harder, worthless whipbait!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">YEAAAAAARRGHH!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Hmm. It appears I was right to leave it at that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska, I would like you to take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...I'll ask, just in case. What is that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's my Prosecutor's Badge.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...And?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. That is all. Nnghoooh!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You should be relieved. You felt pain, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm...? What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Fools can't catch colds. So, I thought they wouldn't be able to feel pain either.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Kay Faraday lost her memories? How dare you let that happen to her on your watch!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hrm. <thought>I have no defense...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">E-Erm...! It's not Mr. Edgeworth's fault...!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">! You, are you alright? Being bandaged up like that...!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah... Yes. Thank you for worrying about me.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">......H-Her behavior is certainly strange. It's unusual to hear her give thanks like that. Miles Edgeworth! Hurry up and get her memories back!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why don't you just admit that you're worried about her?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">There's no doubt, this candelabra was the murder weapon. ...It pains me to see a woman end up like this!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let us find the true culprit, so that she may rest in peace.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The true culprit... I hope the truth doesn't turn out to be a cruel one.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! Unlike you, I am actually busy. I don't have the time to look at something like that. Why don't you just look at that evidence again by yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She is certainly... as harsh as ever.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prongs of the candelabra are covered in blood. And the shape even matches up with the victim's wounds... Is this the murder weapon of this case?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is a rare shape for a pedestal. If the spot where it was put on still has this mark... ...then it will become apparent whether or not it had been placed there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, the victim's identity remains unknown...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Umm... Should you really still be calling "Kay"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course! What are you saying, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Th-Thank you. But then, what about that woman...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">She is someone who you may have killed. That's all we know.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's no way that's true! Right, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I... also do not believe you killed her.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You are such a nave man, Miles Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="???"> Here I come to save the dayyy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, that voice...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste"> So don't be afraid anymooore! For The Best Prosecutor is here todayyy! </line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Pardon the interruption.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Mr. Edgeworth! Get away from the victim! I have inherited her dying wish! No one asked for YOU!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm. Did you know the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Just as I thought... The Goddess of Law will surely reveal the truth to us. So please, rest in peace.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">That's right, Justine! Now that I'm here, everything will be A-OK. The culprit will rue the day he crossed paths with MYARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! Who is this fool of a man!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wh-Why is she glaring at me!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Courtney">You are Franziska von Karma, am I correct? I apologize for my late introduction. I am Justine Courtney. And the deceased individual is...</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">...Attorney Jill Crane, one of the members of the Prosecutorial Investigation Committee!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I see. So that's why she had the keycard...</thought> I take it you're in charge of this case?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">That's right! And with me in charge, this case is as good as solv- YEOOOWW!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That reminds me... I haven't caught your name yet.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">If you just wanted to know my name, you didn't have to whi- YEAAAARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Just state your name. I will not tolerate any unnecessary remarks.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Uuugh... Sebastian Debeste.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It seems the pecking order has been decided.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karin">Mr. Sebastian Debeste? Here, this is from Granny.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">This is... the autopsy report! Wah hah hah... It seems you've been bested, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This wasn't a competition to begin with...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karin">"My job is done. May we meet again in front of another corpse." OK, let's go home quickly, and eat some noodles! I'll be leaving too! Take care everyone!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">...The victim's head wound was postmortem.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Sebastian.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">And the candelabra dealt the fatal blow. Estimated time of death is late last night... Wh-What is it, Justine?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">While I do appreciate your enthusiasm, perhaps you should give your tongue a rest. You might pull a muscle.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That would be painful indeed...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Anyways, it's quite clear now! Kay Faraday must be arrested!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whaaaaaaat! What's the big idea, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">It's just as he says, Detective. The culprit is Ms. Kay Faraday. The young lady in bandages over there... Although she's not wearing her usual attire... Are you not Ms. Kay Faraday?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..... And what would you do if she is Kay? If you're going to arrest her... ...then I will resist by any means necessary. ...That, I guarantee you.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">I am now convinced. The doubts surrounding your suitability as a prosecutor were indeed warranted.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's fine, Mr. Edgeworth. You can go. Don't worry about me... I'll be fine.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What are you saying, Kay!? You can't just go along with them, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But, I... I don't remember anything. What if I really did kill that woman and then forgot about it? If that's true...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Acknowledgement is the Goddess' mercy. Atonement is her will. The Goddess of Law will surely praise you for your prudence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sebastian. And Judge Courtney... If you believe she is the culprit, on what basis do you make your accusations? Unless I'm completely convinced by your explanation... I will not obey your orders!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Fine, have it your way! Now, sit tight and listen to the perfect reasoning of Debeste!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">I am the best in the world. No one else can do what I do.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">His logic's as awful as ever, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Harsh words... coming from you, Detective.</thought> I asked for some basis to your claims, yet your reasoning has told me absolutely nothing...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...However, we have no evidence to prove she didn't do it either.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">........</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't worry, Kay. I'm sure Mr. Edgeworth will pull off a miracle.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Y-You think my deductions are some kind of miracle work...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You'd better not disappoint me. Understand, Miles Edgeworth? Because if you do... this whip of mine won't stay silent.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">I am the best in the world. No one else can do what I do.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Already... I've noticed two contradictions in your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">My reasoning is flawless. It doesn't contain even a single contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm. The number of contradictions has just increased to three.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Oh, I get it! This is all a part of your plan to mislead me, isn't it? Well, too bad! Because "The Best" will not be lead astray!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Yes! That's why I was the first to realize that Kay Faraday is the culprit!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you believe Kay is the culprit, then I would like to hear the basis for your reasoning.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Wah hah hah... Just sit back and be in awe of my brilliant deductions! Nothing escapes the watchful eye of "The Best"! Before I had even laid eyes on the crime scene... No, before I was even aware of this case... Yes! I knew that she was the culprit! YEEOOOOOWW!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Basis of your reasoning.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Yeeees, ma'am! E-Ermm, well...</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">She broke into the meeting room in order to steal something.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To steal something...? Steal what, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">That's... Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">What Kay Faraday tried to steal... was a file. Its contents, to be exact... An investigation report regarding Prosecutor Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Do you have any evidence to prove she needed something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">I am not the one who needs to present evidence. Isn't that right, Prosecutor Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Um... Yes... I... suppose that may be true.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Wha...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">At any rate, Sebastian, please continue your reasoning.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">In other words, she's the only one who could have killed Ms. Crane!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you have any evidence to prove that no one else but Kay could have committed the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Nope!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.....Sebastian. Let me tell you what would be the best thing for you to do. Look into any other possible suspects besides Kay. Right now. Posthaste.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">"The Best" thing for me to do... Look into any other possible suspects...!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">According to the preliminary reports... there were no traces of anyone else besides her.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even so, isn't it too premature to declare that she is the culprit?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Declaring that she isn't so early into the investigation is a little premature as well, is it not?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...! If only I had evidence that could prove Kay's innocence...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Good grief... There is a limit to how much you can falsely accuse someone.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's fine, Mr. Edgeworth... You don't have to...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Fear not, Kay. The truth will be revealted soon enough.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Kay couldn't have murdered Ms. Crane... If I can just prove that, she will be cleared of suspicion.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It certainly sounds like... you are quite familiar with this room.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">The Best man for the job should know all about The Best places.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unfortunately, it seems that you are not The Best man for the job.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Are you mocking me!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's for you to decide. You didn't even know about this keycard, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Of course I know about that! You need it to enter this room... ......... Huh? Was it really needed?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">This foolish fool simply doesn't know when to give up!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">YEEEOOOOOOWCH!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sebastian, do you really suspect Kay?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Th-That's right! She's the only one who could have done it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well then, allow me to ask you... Since this room can only be entered by using a keycard... ...hoe did she enter the room without one!?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Gah...! W-Well, she probably used this and that, and... Nngh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? Did you pull a muscle? Allow me to explain then. The door could only be opened by members of the P.I.C. Which means...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Yes. That's correct.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? <thought>She... conceded so easily...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Take a look at this. It's a record of this room that I investigated just a while ago. At 12:52 AM, the door was opened using Ms. Crane's keycard.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">It's probable... ...that the killer entered the room together with the victim, Ms. Crane. After entering, the situation must have sourced, leading to the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your logic holds... but it is still merely conjecture. And it would imply that the killer and the victim were acquainted.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No way, pal! Kay doesn't even know the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">That is merely an assumption on your part... Unless you have any evidence to prove your claim? Evidence is everything, in court and at the crime scene. Without it, your argument is invalid.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">In that case... I trust that you have evidence... ...to prove that Kay Faraday and the victim were connected.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh... What!?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">This letter... ...was discovered by Dr. Young in Ms. Crane's breast pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...The victim's belongings? Why did she withhold such vital evidence until now? Could it be... she was waiting for the perfect time to reveal it? Come to think of it...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">And the candelabra dealt the fatal blow. Estimated time of death is late last night... Wh-What is it, Justine?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">While I do appreciate your enthusiasm, perhaps you should give your tongue a rest. You might pull a muscle.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Hmhm... I'll read it for you. "To Ms. Crane, Thank you so much for helping with my plan! I'm glad that we can help each other get what we want. It's like killing two birds with one stone! Please get revenge for 12 years ago!" - Kay" In other words, Kay Faraday and Ms. Crane were accomplices. They probably planned to steal something from this room.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">P-Preposterous!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">W-Wait! That means, the main culprit is...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">It's still Kay Faraday, of course. It just means her crimes have increased by yet one more.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'm... the main culprit...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't believe her, Kay! It's all a bunch of nonsense! There's no way Kay would do something like that!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Nonsense? Not at all. The evidence speaks for itself, wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh...! <thought>I knew that they wouldn't suspect Kay unless they had some sort of proof, but... ...to think they would actually have such decisive evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Nicely done, Justine!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Thank you very much.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your explanation is still insufficient! I cannot accept such an argument!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Sebastian. Would you please leave this to me?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Alright, make sure you shut Mr. Edgeworth up once and for all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't allow their allegations to gain any more momentum. I must turn it around here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Courtney">The relationship between Kay Faraday and Ms. Crane is as documented in the letter.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-Her testimony's even better than ever. Maybe the most perfect it's ever been, sir...! Are you gonna be alright, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Um, yes... Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">How unsightly, Miles Edgeworth. Save your stoic act for some other time.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ms. von Karma! Just whose side are you on!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I'm on nobody's side, Scruffy. When searching for the truth, it's best not to take sides.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">W-Watch what you say, Ms. von Karma, or else Mr. Debeste is gonna...</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">"Best" you say? Well, I can tell you that the side I'm on is always the BYAAARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...How irritating.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, I suppose that's one thing we can agree on.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">The relationship between Kay Faraday and Ms. Crane is as documented in the letter.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And just what kind of relationship did Kay have with the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">In the letter, she wrote, "Thank you so much for helping with my plan!" Their relationship should be quite obvious. That's right...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">She roped Ms. Crane into assisting her with her plan.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I would like to hear about Kay's alleged plan in more detail.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Just as she wrote in the letter, she wanted to steal something.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">What's more, the sender of the letter is Kay Faraday. So it's obvious who the main culprit is!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That letter could've easily been forged. It doesn't prove that she planned to steal anything.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">If memory serves me right... wasn't she a Great Thief?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-That's... She's... um, taking a break at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">I doubt there is any thief who would inform a prosecutor about their upcoming crimes. Perhaps she simply returned to her trade without you knowing?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I suppose I have no means of denying that possibility...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Kay Faraday planned the theft and Ms. Crane got caught up in it.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">However, for some reason, their partnership broke down.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"For some reason" you say...? It seems your explanation isn't very clear.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">I'm sure the reason will become clear upon further investigation. But more importantly... ...there is no evidence to prove that Kay Faraday did not commit this crime.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">While there is some evidence to suggest that she committed a crime... ...none of it can truly be called decisive evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">What about the letter that shows their complicity, and the scene of the crime... I think it's fair to say we cannot decisively rule out the possibility that she committed the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Ms. Crane was murdered... But with her dying breath, she managed to retaliate.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you have any evidence to prove that Kay was the murderer?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Haven't you been listening! We've been saying that this letter is the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? And where in the letter does it say that she planned to murder the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">...Huh? E-Erm, well, that's... I've got it! It's a hidden message written in invisible ink that can only be read by heating it up!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Sebastian. I wouldn't get your hopes up for something like that. There is, of course, evidence that points to her as the criminal.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Her parting gift is this letter, which she tucked safely away in her left breast pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We searched the victim's left breast pocket as well, but...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">You found nothing, I presume?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Naturally, the officer who found the letter immediately brought it to the Best man on the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">The letter was safely tucked away in her left breast pocket, right above her heart... I believe this letter carries Ms. Crane's will for the criminal to be arrested.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have no interest in your beliefs. What I'm interested in is the truth. You said that the letter was in the left breast pocket of the victim, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">I swear by the Goddess of Law, there are no lies or mistakes in my statement. The letter was indeed discovered inside the victim's left breast pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The victim had been stabbed in the left chest area where the letter was hidden... This may very well be an important clue.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I don't think that Kay wrote the letter... ...but unless I can draw out more information here, that thought means nothing. I should start by pressing her for more details.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The victim held onto the truth until her dying breath... A truly touching story indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">The voices of the dead are soft. One must listen carefully to hear their dying wishes... And Ms. Crane has spoken: Kay Faraday is the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Perhaps the voices you have been hearing are actually the whispers of the devil.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">H-Hey! Don't make fun of Justine!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's listen to the voice of reason. Judge Courtney, please take a look at the autopsy report.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">There is no need. I remember it perfectly. The victim was stabbed in the left breast...! N-No, it can't be...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The letter was found in the victim's left breast pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And that's where the victim was stabbed with the candelabra, right, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely. It wouldn't have been possible to stab her there without piercing the letter as well!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">.....!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, that begs the question... Why was the letter found in the victim's pocket? It's simple. It was placed there after the victim was murdered to throw suspicion onto Kay! Somebody intentionally wanted to create this very situation! In other words, there exists the possibility that the letter was forged by the true culprit!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Noooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The real murderer tried to pin the crime on Kay... That is the only explanation for the letter.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And in doing so, the murderer ended up digging their own grave, right, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">The culprit is Kay Faraday! The letter was... Yeah! It was actually found in the victim's other pocket!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Huh? What're you saying, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">The officer's report was wrong when he said the letter was in her left pocket! It's actually in the... YEOOOWWCH!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">A foolish fool who continues to make a fool of himself... Is there no cure for your foolishness!?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Why do you keep whipping me!? And quit calling me a fool! YEAAARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I saved you the trouble of punishing him yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-Indeed... <thought>Though I had no intention of punishing him...</thought> The letter is stained with blood, no doubt because it was found in the left breast pocket. There couldn't have been an error in the officer's report... Unless you were the investigator.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">U-Ugghh... Say something, Justine!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see you have no objections. ...Then allow me to continue. There is one more potential suspect in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Don't be ridiculous! The killer entered this very room! There wasn't anyone else who did that besides Kay Faraday and the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>To enter the meeting room, one needs a keycard... And their reasoning assumes that the murderer and the victim entered the room together. This is what we overlooked. If we just discard that assumption, then...</thought> This evidence reveals the other suspect besides Kay...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Judge Courtney, I'd like you to take a look at this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Is there something wrong with that evidence, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This evidence reveals the other suspect aside from Kay!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">I don't understand. I simply cannot allow you to submit that evidence to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnghhoooh! <thought>W-Was I wrong...? We were under the impression that the murderer didn't have a keycard. However, what if we assumed that they did have a keycard?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Looks like Kay Faraday is the only suspect after all, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No. There is one other suspect aside from Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the keycard record Judge Courtney handed me earlier. The victim's keycard was used at 12:52 AM... And there was one more person who also used a keycard.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">So you're saying this person was waiting to ambush the victim inside the meeting room? The keycard was used at 10:15 PM. I wouldn't say it's possible...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">No, it's impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And what makes you say that, pal!? You got any proof!?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Of course I do. I myself am that proof.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">I was the one who used that keycard, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Is there something strange about a P.I.C. remeber entering the P.I.C. meeting room?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. That proves nothing. The fact that you were in here at all makes you a suspect. Or do you perhaps have any evidence that you didn't kill your colleague?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Such nonsense. What would I gain by murdering her?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Allow me to reiterate what you said earlier. I'm sure it will all become clear upon further investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Why would I, a faithful servant of the law, commit a crime? True enough, I entered this room. However, that alone is not reason enough to suspect me of a crime.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that's the case, please tell me why you entered this room.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">I had some business to take care of, and some preparations had to be made.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Preparations...! That sounds pretty suspicious, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Unfortunately, I cannot disclose what these preparations were. However... I'm sure you could hazard a guess, "Prosecutor" Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...So she was preparing for my hearing. She must have gathered all the necessary materials... ...to take away my Prosecutor's Badge.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Wonderful, wonderful. It's good to see young people go head-to-head so ruthlessly.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Who is that...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">That takes me back. When I was young, I'd always butt heads with this brash detective. ...A-And then one day... ...He just disappeared. I hope... he's still doing well... Ahh, h-here come the waterworks.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Chairman Debeste...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Did she just say... Debeste?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Hello, Courtney. You sure are full of energy today. And if it isn't little Von Karma. Look how much you've grown since I last saw you.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">S-Sir... It has been quite a while...</line>
<line speaker="???">...A curtsy? You don't have to treat me like some sort of stranger, y'know. Remember back in the old days, when you'd sit on my lap and call me Unky Boo Boo? *sniff* ...Here I go again. Oh... How I cried b-back then...</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Pops! What are you doing here!?</line>
<line speaker="???">Hrm? A member of the P.I.C. was killed and I heard that you were in charge of the case.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...What kind of prosecutor is followed around by his own father?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Hold your tongue! Do you have any idea who this man is? Chairman of the P.I.C., former Chief Prosecutor. He's the right hand of the Goddess of Law.</line>
<line speaker="???">Now, now, Courtney. I'm just an old chunk of coal. There's no reason to speak so highly of me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please excuse my subordinate's behavior. I am...</line>
<line speaker="Blaise">Prosecutor Edgeworth, isn't it? Along with his trusty sidekick Dick Gumshoe. I am Blaise Debeste. I'm the proud father of that idiot over there. When that boy was born, me and the missus were happy as can be, y'see... But now... I-I don't even know where she's gone to... *sob*</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">P-Pops... You need a handkerchief?</line>
<line speaker="Blaise">Ah, yes. Sebastian is an idiot, but he's such a good boy, y'know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Quite the doting father and son.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blaise">Now then, Courtney. How's the investigation going?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Sir. We've established that the culprit is Kay Faraday. We are currently focusing our efforts...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There are too many uncertainties in this case! It's impossible to determine that she's the culprit! Surely you haven't forgotten the matter of the letter!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Debeste">I already told you, it was just a simple mistake. The letter was in another pocke- YEOWCH!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...You talk too much.</line>
<line speaker="Blaise">Now, now. Let's all play nice. Everyone, just calm down.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...I'm sorry that you had to witness such an unsightly scene, Mr. Chairman.</line>
<line speaker="Blaise">Don't apologize Courtney. I can follow everyone's logic. ...Except Sebastian's, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">H-Hey! Pops...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Chairman Debeste, I am a prosecutor. My duty is to bring criminals to justice. However, I won't make someone out to be a criminal without sufficient motive and evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Blaise">Hrm, I've heard about you and your relationship with the suspect, y'know. Ah, to share such a strong bond...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Kay has assisted the police in arresting criminals countless times, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There are too many facets of this case that remain unexplored...!</line>
<line speaker="Blaise">I see. The bonds of youth are a wonderful thing, indeed. ...But, that is that and this is this. Y'know?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What's that supposed to mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Blaise">The Prosecutor's Office needs to resolve this case as quickly as possible. I mean, just think of all the other cases that are piling up. There's no time to waste here. It's unfortunate, but... you understand, right, Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What...!?</line>
<line speaker="Blaise">Now then, Kay Faraday. I'd like to arrest you now.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">.....Okay.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No! I won't let you! Kay's innocent, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">To defy Chairman Debeste, is to defy the law. It would be a grave act of disloyalty. In other words, a hearing won't be needed. Are you prepared to lose your Prosecutor's Badge?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Th-That's...! Mr. Edgeworth's badge...! You can't do that!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Using a prosecutor's badge as a shield. What has the P.I.C. come to...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay...! You haven't done anything wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth... It was only for a short time, but... Thank you for everything... I'm sorry... I turned out to be a criminal...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">We will make sure to impart your confession to the Goddess of Law.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.....Nngh! <thought>What... should I do!? When I was young, I wanted to become a defense attorney like my father... Someone who can fight to save those in need...! And right now... this badge is holding me back. A mere badge, for the life of a dear friend... I don't even have to consider it...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Alright. Farewell... Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hold it right there! Judge Courtney!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">...What is it now, Prosecutor Edgeworth?&#160;! This is... your prosecutor's badge! Prosecutor Edgeworth! What is the meaning of this!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Consider this my resignation. I am... no longer a prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">M... Mr. Edgeworth...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Wh-What are you doing!? Explain yourself! Miles Edgeworth! You... you can't be serious!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! You... you're joking, right? If you aren't a prosecutor, then I...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">My only mission is to bring the truth to light. If it's the prosecutor's path to turn a blind eye to the truth... ...then that title is worth nothing to me! I... will walk in the path that I believe in. ...I will not be stopped here!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You, you're running away from Von Karma... from me!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.....No matter what you say, I don't intend to go back on my decision.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">So... you're leaving me behind again!? I'll never... Never forgive you for this!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">N-No... This is all my fault...! ...I'm sorry. If only I weren't here...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait! Kay! Detective Gumshoe! Don't follow me!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">B-But! Mr. Edgeworth...! Boss...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'm not your "boss" anymore, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Th-That's...! That's just too much, sir! It's always been you and me! We've always been a team!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe, you no longer need to follow my lead. You... should try to accomplish whatever you can on your end!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">.....!</line>
<line speaker="Blaise">Ahh, ahh, this is bad. We just let a dangerous criminal escape. How could I let her get away... and after all my hard work... Y'see...</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Rest assured, Mr. Chairman. This area will be locked down immediately.</line>
<line speaker="Blaise">Good. I expect the best from you, Courtney.</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">......</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay! <thought>She's not here either. Where in the world could she have gone...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Knock knock, I'm here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Shields...!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">What's going on, Miles? Why the long face...? Take it from Uncle Ray, you won't be popular with the ladies looking like that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why are you here? Did something happen?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">That's my line. Have you seen the news? About the murder at the P.I.C. headquarters? Your hearing... Wasn't it there today? I found myself wondering if you guys had somehow got caught up in it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait, it's already made the news?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I hear they're searching for a teenage girl suspected of killing an attorney... I can't imagine it could have been her, but... it has been bothering me. Could you give me the full rundown?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-The truth is...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">M-Miles, are you trying to give your Uncle Ray a heart attack?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm not joking. She really did lose her memory...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">On top of that, she's a suspect... That make things even difficult. Where would she have run off to? She lost her memory, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was hoping she would return here, but...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Not likely. She felt responsible for what happened to you, right? Then, there's no way she would come back here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know that! But, where else can I look...?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Calm down, Miles. This isn't like you. It's rare to see you get so heated up. Well... not that it's a bad thing. If you're trying this hard to save an innocent suspect from false charges... ...I'm sure you'd make a great defense attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Actually... just a while ago... I turned in my badge... ...but that doesn't mean I've decided to become a defense attorney. Besides, Kay isn't just a mere suspect. I may have only known her for a short time... but we've been through quite a lot together. And I know she isn't capable of murder!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">...I'm surprised. I never thought you would go so far to support someone else. I don't know if you even realize it yourself, but... ...it seems a deep bond has already begun to grow between you and Kay. I'd say it even gives my bond with your father a run for its money.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No... It's not that deep. She just keeps barging into my state of affairs.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ha ha. Yeah, that girl can be quite a handful. But I'm certain that something has changed inside you since you met her.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I'm really jealous, you know. After all, I lost my old partner. That's why you need to find Kay right now. I don't want you to lose your bond like your Uncle Ray did...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Well then, I have a proposal. We have no idea where she is. And searching around blindly won't get us anywhere. In that case... why don't we try searching for the cause of her memory loss? Maybe that could give us a lead?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... That might be a good idea. From what she told me, something must have happened to her at the Grand Tower...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Great, that's it! Let's get going then! Hey. At the very least, could you stop looking so grim? If you stay that way, Kay probably won't want to come back at all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.....Good grief. <thought>I'm not match for this man...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It seems it's already dark...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Still open on the day of a murder. You gotta admire their capitalist spirit... But there's no one here.... Looks like we've got the place all to ourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>To prove Kay's innocence, I'll need to investigate her lost memories...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hey, hey! Let's go, Miles! We can investigate the roof as much as we want! So let's do what we can.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do what we can, huh? I suppose that's all we can do for now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The person in the red raincoat who pushed Kay off the tower... She said they came toward her... from the direction of the stand. From that, we can deduce... ...Kay was pushed over the railing on this side <thought>Railing - Person in raincoat came over from the stand and pushed Kay over.</thought>. <thought>The railing is about as high as my chest... It's unlikely that someone could fall from here accidentally.</thought> Hmm... I don't see any particular problems with this railing.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Why do you think Kay lost her memories? Was there something she wanted to forget? Miles, did you say something horrible to her?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">O-Of course not! I would never say anything that cruel to someone. Well, I might've said some unkind things to Detective Gumshoe in the past, but...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I-I see... Now I feel bad for the big guy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a cherry tree with branches spread wide. The flowers are nearly in full bloom. <thought>According to Kay's testimony... ...before she was pushed, she was standing under the cherry tree (Where was Kay standing? - Kay testified that she remembers standing under the cherry tree.</thought>.)</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's a statue of a creature with the body of a lion and the beak and wings of a bird. These statues seem to be guarding the entrance to this peaceful park. It's an immaculate work, down to the last detail. But since it looks so fearsome... ...wouldn't it frighten away the visitors to the park?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's a statue of a pony, sparkling in the twilight. Hmm... the statue has wings. Perhaps it's Pegasus, the flying horse of myth... No... there's a horn on its head. Could it be the legendary unicorn? But I thought unicorns didn't have wings!</thought> ...Hm, what's this? There's a plaque at the bottom! <thought>The title of this work is written on the plaque.</thought> ..."A Magical Contradiction". <thought>I suppose the only part of this work I was able to understand was the contradiction part...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This TV seems to be used for showing advertisements for the companies at the Grand Tower. Right now it's just showing regular television programs though...</thought> ...................................Hrm. <thought>Wait! What am I watching this for? The Steel Samurai doesn't air today!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karin">Miles Edgeworth! So we meet again!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What are you two doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Well, we came all this way, so I thought we'd buy some cotton candy... "And what about you? You want folks to get the wrong idea about you?"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do not worry. I will decide my own actions.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">"You're just a no-good ex-prosecutor. It's no wonder you got the axe." ...Wait, what!? You got fired?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You needn't be concerned with what happens to me.</line>
<line speaker="Karin">A-Are you sure? Errrm... Oh yeah! What happened to Kay?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Huh? Was there some sort of trouble between you two?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Karin">Anything I can do to help? How about an injection?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I-It's fine. <thought>Are injections her answer to everything?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karin">Oh, right. It's getting cold, isn't it? Let's go home. Well then, Mr. Miles Edgeworth. Let's meet again soon!</line>
<line speaker="Shopkeeper">You, sir! How about some heavenly cotton candy, "Heaven's Tear"!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Heaven's Tear"? <thought>Did they name them after the shape of the clouds you can see from here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Shopkeeper">We tear a regular piece of cotton candy in half, and then sell it without changing the price. That's why the name is "Heaven's Tear". We tear the costs in half while crying tears of joy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...If the customers knew that, they would be crying tears of sorrow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If you insert a coin, you can use these binoculars to get a nice view of the city. I'm sure if Kay were feeling better, she'd be happily glued to them. For her sake, I must thoroughly examine every nook and cranny of this viewing platform!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aaaaah! Oww...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Um, um... Don't mind me! I was just admiring the view beneath the tree!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Did you just fall out of that tree?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I didn't mean to fall! ...My foot slipped.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're a suspect, and yet you remained at the crime scene... That's not a smart thing to do. Even if you have memory loss, shouldn't you have realized this much? This whole time, while you were playing this silly game of hide-and-seek... ...I've been worried sick about you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Are you angry with me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Of course I am. Answer me. What were you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">.....</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Did you think I'd let you off the hook that easily just because you have memory loss?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Th-That's not it!! ...I came here because I thought I could get your badge back.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">If I don't regain my memories, you'll never get it back... I thought if I went back to where I lost my memories, then maybe I would remember... If I could just remember... killing her...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.......... .....Heh.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You're still the same as you were before you lost your memories. Your thoughts and actions have always exceeded my expectations. Without a doubt, you are the Kay Faraday I know so well... However... I cannot approve of your recklessness.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Cuuuuut! You get zero style points, Miles. Or more like, negative points! Here's how it's done. Kay, how about a hug?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">O... Okay.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Oho! Well, then...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Shields!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">It was just a joke. Honest!</line>
<line speaker="Announcer">We interrupt this program with breaking news about the Grand Tower murder case... The police believe the culprit is a teenage girl who was present at the crime scene. She remains at large as the police continue to search for her whereabouts.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Oh dear... This is getting pretty serious. Well, gang, what's the plan? We don't have much time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. It's only a matter of time before they find us here.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">So then, why don't you tag along with us for a while, Kay?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But, I'll just cause trouble for you again...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It pains me to say this but I've got nothing left to lose at this point.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth...!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">This settles it. We're all in this together now. Miles, you're in charge of proving Kay's innocence. Failure is not an option.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Kay, I want you to help Miles with his investigation as much as you can!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Y-Yes! I'll do my best.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Let's be quick about it! Before the cops find us here! Unlike some people, Uncle Ray still has a lot to lose! Sheesh... If I lose the law office, I'll never be able to face Gregory...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This man... I'm glad he's on our side.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If I recall Kay's testimony... A person in a raincoat approached her from behind the candy stand. Then, this person supposedly pushed Kay over the railing opposing the stand. Moreover... ...Kay said she saw the moon over the person's shoulder. However, earlier I confirmed that the moon is floating in the opposite direction... And, on the night Kay lost her memories, it seems the moon was in the exact same spot. Therefore, the positions of the moon and the person in the raincoat don't match up. Her memories have probably become confused. After all, had she actually been pushed over the railing, she couldn't have survived the fall. Perhaps I should question Kay's memory of where she fell <thought>Where Kay fell? - Kay probably did not fall over the railing.</thought>...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay was not pushed over the railing on this side. After all, if you fell from here, you wouldn't even be alive in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But... I'm certain I was standing under the cherry tree. If I fell, then the only place I could have fallen was over the railing.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Well, maybe the ground just opened up from under you and swallowed you up?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The ground here can open up? How?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">No, no, it was just a joke, 'kay? Please don't take it so seriously.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No... Strange as it may sound, that may actually be the truth. Even if it's only a small chance, it matters not. Let's try searching the area around the tree.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Kay could not have fallen over the railing... There must be something around here that proves it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Flower petals are scattered all over the ground. The blossoms are not yet in full bloom, so the strong winds up here must be the culprit. Personally, I'd appreciate it if they spent a little more effort cleaning these petals up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">It looks like a maintenance hatch <thought>Fell down the hatch? - Did Kay fall down the hatch beneath the cherry tree?</thought>. Kay, maybe you fell down here? ...Nah, just kidding. There's no way something like that could happen.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'm sorry. I just can't remember if...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">No, that was just a joke. No need to take it seriously.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Right... So, when should I take you seriously then?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">When, indeed. Well, if you jumped into Uncle Ray's arms...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Shields!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Heh, come on, Miles. It was just a jooooke. A joke, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, I get it! No one ever takes you seriously!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ouch... Th-That stung a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">I can't believe this incident is already on the news. I wonder how they caught wind of it. Maybe they're doing a live report from that helicopter over there? Uncle Ray's gonna be on TV! Miles, make sure you tune in!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wh-What is he thinking at a time like this...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes? Can I help with something?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I came back here because I thought I might remember something.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Could you again go over what you told me before?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Umm, well... It was raining, so I stood under the cherry tree to take shelter. And then, a red... A person in a red raincoat appeared. That person pushed me, and I fell.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Can you tell me anything about the person in the raincoat?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...I'm sorry. I don't remember that much. No, wait... As the person approached me, I saw the moon just over their shoulder.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The moon?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes, that's right. It's just a faint memory, but... ...I think the moon was in the exact same spot as it is now... It was floating just above the cherry tree.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She could see the moon (Moon - Kay saw the moon behind person in raincoat. It's in the same spot tonight.</thought> behind the figure in the raincoat? This is a new piece of testimony. I'll be sure to keep it in mind.)</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Snatched loot of the Great Thief.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Are all her mistakes biased towards a certain way...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth, for a while now, I feel like I'm on the verge of remembering something.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What? Is that true? Well then, please speak freely. Say whatever comes to your mind.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Umm... OK. I remember a faint scent... It was a wonderful smell coming from the counter of a food stall... I followed the fragrance, only to find a perfectly sculpted burger, resting on two golden buns... The tender and juicy patty made my taste buds sing with joy... Yes, I can remember what I thought at that moment! ...I want seconds!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I-I... don't think this memory has anything to do with the case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You called yourself the Great Thief Yatagarasu. You prided yourself on being a "noble thief" who steals the truth. Do you remember anything about that?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well... Hmmmmmmmm..... ...Aha! Maybe I was called a noble thief because I won the Noble Prize!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's "Nobel", not "noble". And they don't give prizes for thievery...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">This letter... It's a promise I made, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you can call conspiring to commit a crime a promise, then yes.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">A crime... But I was the one who wrote this letter, right...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...This letter is not handwritten. We cannot be certain that you wrote it.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Is... that so...?</line>
<line speaker="Reporter">We're seeing live footage from the 50th floor! The investigation will continue through the night.</line>
<line speaker="Announcer">The 50th floor? Isn't that the meeting room of the P.I.C. Headquarters?</line>
<line speaker="Reporter">That's right! We can see the shadows of the investigators behind those blinds...</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Uh oh. Looks like making a clean getaway just got that much harder.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems we have no choice but to cleverly evade the eyes of the media.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Maybe Uncle Ray should have become a spy instead of an attorney...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If worse comes to worst, I may have to use Mr. Shields as a decoy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">...Miles. Just now, you were thinking of something terrible, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This appears to be a live news broadcast. In other words, what we see on the screen is how the Grand Tower looks at this very moment.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Does that mean we can be seen on the TV too...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No. The camera is too far away and it's too dark to see us clearly. There's no need to worry. <thought>It certainly would be bad if Kay were to be seen on TV right now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Reporter">We're seeing live footage from the 50th floor! The investigation will continue through the night.</line>
<line speaker="Announcer">The 50th floor? Isn't that the meeting room of the P.I.C. Headquarters?</line>
<line speaker="Reporter">That's right! We can see the shadows of the investigators behind those blinds...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It looks like they are still investigating the meeting room. As the reporter said, you can see the investigators' shadows moving around. Hm...? There is... a huge contradiction in this image! I should present that piece of evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The investigation is still going on in the meeting room, which is supposed to be the top floor. However... There is a mysterious floor above it... Just what is that floor used for?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The contradiction is found here...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This evidence clearly contradicts the footage on TV!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Umm... Miles. I don't see anything strange.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gah! <thought>So it wasn't this then... There's something about this TV footage that seems out of place. How many floors does the Grand Tower have again?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you know how many floors this building has?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Of course. 50 floors, right? Just above the place where the P.I.C. conducts their "Practically Illegal Coverups"... ...couples are wishing for love. Kinda ironic, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So, what's this dark area above the 50th floor?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Maybe it's the Tunnel of Love... Those are always dark, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The viewing platform we're on now should be directly above the P.I.C. meeting room. However, the late-night investigation is taking place two floors below us. This is a clear contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Was there a mistake in the pamphlet?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">No no, rather...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's more natural to assume this building has a hidden 51st floor <thought>Is there a floor 51? - There seems to be a 51st floor between the 50th floor and rooftop.</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I see! So that's where the Tunnel of Love is!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Awww... She's so pure and gullible, it's breaking Uncle Ray's heart.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then why don't you take this opportunity to be more serious for once?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">You just don't get it, Miles. I joke around to make things easier for you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>On the contrary, his painful jokes only make things harder for me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">An extra floor between the 50th floor and the viewing platform... Why didn't anyone notice it?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Normally, you'd notice it. I mean, how can you hide an entire floor?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That is where the problem lies. No one noticed something that should have been easily noticeable. In other words, it must be impossible to access the 51st floor through normal means!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I see. Maybe there's a secret portal or something!</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Kay... Now's not the time to be thinking with portals.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like you to recall the hatch at the base of the cherry tree. Isn't it normal to assume there's a room on the other side of the maintenance hatch?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Heh heh... Uncle Ray likes where you're going with this.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Let's hurry and check it out.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">There... we go. Now let's see...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is...!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Looks like there's a lot of stuff down there. Is this what they call... a storeroom?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is no doubt about it. This is where Kay fell down.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Of course. And with this the mystery is solved!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, not yet. <thought>We still have the mystery of the person in the red hood who was walking in mid-air...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Now, now. Let's not get greedy, shall we? We've found the storeroom, so let's wrap things up here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose... you have a point. <thought>Hmm. It does seem to warrant an investigation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Well, if it isn't Miles Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ema! What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I heard about the case from Detective Gumshoe! Since I was already in the area, I thought I might as well check out the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This girl's name is Ema Skye. She's a high school student studying in Europe to become a forensic scientist. She's the younger sister of my former boss, and a witness in one of my trials two years ago.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Detective Gumshoe told me everything over the phone! He sounded really upset! He said you lost your badge at the Grand Tower, and Kay became a mummy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">P-Please calm down. I thought you left for Europe just a few days ago... Don't tell me you've come back already?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yep! And I've brought my teacher from abroad too. He needed an interpreter, so I volunteered to help.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If your teacher cannot speak English, why aren't you with him right now?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He can still communicate with people! Don't underestimate the importance of body language!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...That doesn't really count as a language.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">But enough about that! What happened to Kay!? Is she alright!?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">My, my, what a good friend. Isn't this great, Kay?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Y-Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Umm, who are you? Are you Mr. Edgeworth's new assistant?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Ha ha ha! On the contrary, my dear. I'm Ray Shields, head of the Edgeworth Law Offices.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Edgeworth... Law Offices? Wait, you mean like defense attorneys!? Mr. Edgeworth, when did you suddenly become an attorney!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No, it's not like that... <thought>Now that I think about it, it is a rather complicated working relationship.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ray">Don't sweat the details. Let's start with an introductory hug...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Why'd you become a defense attorney, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Hey, don't just ignore me...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Because I don't approve at all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Uh. Hm... Well, why don't we continue this conversation down below?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's right. The police could arrive any second now.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...? Mr. Edgeworth, who's she?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll explain later. First, we have to go down the hatch.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah, OK. Guess I'll be joining the prosecu- err... defense team?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'll explain about that, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ray">Well then! Let's go go go to the storeroom!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, the pieces don't fit together quite right... I need to reconsider the information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't see a clear connection between these two pieces of information. I need to think this over one more time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Not exactly a shining example of the perfect line of logic.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay. Could you take a look at this piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Uuughh... My head... It's... a man in red clothes... Furrowing his eyebrows at me... It's kind of scaring me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnghoooh! <thought>That's me, isn't it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth. It seems that's not related to her testimony at all, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. I'll have to listen more closely to Kay's testimony again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay. Your testimony contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">A contradiction...? It could be because I just lost my memory... But I really don't think that has anything to do with what I just said...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnghoooh! <thought>So it wasn't this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth... Are you OK?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. There is no need to worry. I will definitely see to it that you regain your memories.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay. Have a look at this. Don't you remember something?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What about it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I would think the connection between you and this piece of evidence is obvious.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Kay's lost her memory, so you shouldn't say something so thoughtless!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnghoooh! <thought>So this wasn't related...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You can't be so rough on her in her condition, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's right. Maybe I should think a bit more carefully first.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Debeste. What do you think about this piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Why are you asking for my opinion?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't you see? This evidence contradicts your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">WH-WHAAAAAAAAAT!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">I don't believe this evidence has that kind of meaning.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Eh! Is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... <thought>With Judge Courtney here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Also, you don't need to yell ><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Debeste. There is a contradiction in your statement!</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Eh! Is that true, Justine?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">It is not, Sebastian. It is Prosecutor Edgeworth's statement that is contradictory.</line>
<line speaker="Debeste">Of course! There's no way there could be a contradiction in my argument!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh! <thought>Isn't it full of contradictions!? My real problem is her rather than Mr. Debeste...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Judge Courtney, could you take a look at this piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">I'm afraid I cannot accept that piece of evidence. I do not believe it has any relation to my testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnghoooh! <thought>As I expected, she's nothing like Mr. Debeste. However, I won't back down so easily!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Judge Courtney. Don't you have a problem with that statement just now?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Should I have a problem with it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Exactly. Because there's no problem at all!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">In that case, you should have refrained from speaking in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnghhooh! <thought>I don't think that left a good impression...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Judge Courtney. There is a contradiction in your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">I cannot authorize this statement.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... And why not?</line>
<line speaker="Courtney">Because it's obvious you're bluffing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nguuuoooh! <thought>Is that the impression I give off? ...Next time for sure, I will present evidence that will silence her for good!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh! To come this far, only to lose the truth...! But... it seems there's nothing I can do now...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's nothing unusual about this area.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's nothing interest of here.</line>
</xml>