<xml>
<title>The Stolen Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it? Is something wrong...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nah. But did you see all the people here? It's crazy! Oh! Look at this! I bought this Mask☆DeMasque publicity photo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You bought that...? Where!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">From the little tents in front of the courthouse. They have all sorts of things for sale!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know I'm sucker for this kind of stuff!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Who's screaming like that?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">...Oh! Mr. Wright! You made it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I did. But it doesn't look like things are going to get any less ugly for you.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Because I did it!! I'm the criminal! Me! Me! Meeeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ungh... He's at it again.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">I sent the calling card to Lordly Tailor! I admit iiiit!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... You don't have the Sacred Urn, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Well, that's true, but... That doesn't mean that I didn't commit the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Normally, when I say "Of course you didn't" I'm being sarcastic, but you... Yikes!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">Anyway, I admit that I'm guilty... So make sure they give me a guilty verdict! Pleeeeease!?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Oh, there you are Ronnie! Bonjour, sweetie!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Oh! D-Dessie honey! B-Bonjour! ...Well, actually... I don't really know why I should be speaking French to you at a time like this</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Leave it all to me, Ronnie! I swear I'll protect you!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Ummm, errr... Aaah... Well, ahh... You see... Actually the thief is err, me</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Can I tell you something, Nicky boy? I can guarantee that my Ronnie is innocent! If he's declared guilty, I'll be ever so cross with you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So, why are you smiling when you say it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Well, if you'll excuse me! I've got some errands I need to take care of! I'm counting on you, Nicky boy! Good luck!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>To be honest, I really don't know whether Ron is Mask☆DeMasque or not. But there's only one thing I AM sure of. He doesn't have the Sacred Urn right now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Mr. DeLite! It's time for you to enter the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>For the time being, I guess I'll have to trust Desirée...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Mr. Ron DeLite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is ready, Your honor.</line>
<line speaker="???">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What about the prosecution? Are you prepared to...</line>
<line speaker="???">...What a stupid question!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What did you say!</line>
<line speaker="???">Fine. Let me ask you then, Your Honor. Are YOU ready? Are you ready to pass judgement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh...! N-No, I... I'm not! I will pass judgement after I hear arguments from both sides.</line>
<line speaker="???">Well, if you're not ready yourself, you shouldn't expect others to be. That's a rule to live by.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Um, wh-who are you?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I am Godot. Legendary prosecutor. I've never lost a case.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! He's the one that Detective Atmey was talking about...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, your reputation precedes you. What kind of cases have you dealt with so far?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! None.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What did you say...?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I've never prosecuted a case before.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">N-Never? But you said you've never lost before.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...Exactly. I've never lost. I've never won before either.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Quite arrogant for a beginner, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Even the mightiest of Redwoods begin their lives as mere saplings.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, but... A mask? In a court of law?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Don't you know anything? No matter the man, we all wear masks... Either on our faces or ever our hearts.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This guy is the real deal alright, Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why does it seem like all prosecutors are the "real deal"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">So we finally meet... Mr. Phoenix Trite!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! Is he a friend of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No. I don't have any friends that call me "Trite". <thought>Just who is this masked man...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">I've returned from the depths of Hell... To do battle with you.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, err, Prosecutor Gobo.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">It's not "Gobo". It's Godot... Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In any case, please give your opening statement.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Opening statement? Those things are not fit for even dogs to consume. I have only one thing to say before we start. To you... Mr. Trite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Are you familiar with the saying, "A chain is only as strong as its weakest link"? I wonder... how much you can withstand before you and your case break in two...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well then, let's hear from the first witness!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, my name is...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">No one asked for your name, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Urk.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">The important thing is what you know... That's all. Start talking. ...We're listening.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yes, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Alright, witness. First, let's hear about... What you know about the thief that stole the urn.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mask☆DeMasque is a master thief that first started his crime spree 6 month years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So then the actual identity of this Mask☆DeMasque is... M-Mr. Godot! Y-You! W-We're in the middle of a trial here, Mr. Godot!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Blacker than a moonless night, hotter and more bitter than Hell itself... That is coffee. I'm sure you can grant me at least this much... Your Honor. Oh, please. Proceed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. It's only coffee, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What!? You can't be letting him slide this early in the trial!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Proceed with your cross-examination, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, Nick? What are you going to do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As long as they haven't brought up Mr. DeLite's identity... ...all we can do is show that it wasn't Mask☆DeMasque who stole the urn.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mask☆DeMasque is a master thief that first started his crime spree 6 month years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you been involved in the investigation from the beginning?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup! Nobody knows more about the thief than me, pal! It's true! I'm a... Zvarri...! "Author on thieves"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">An "author"...? He's written books about thieves?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, I think he probably meant to say "authority".</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The fact that this guy can slip through even my fingers shows how good he is, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's easy when those fingers happen to be "butter fingers"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So nobody knows more about the thief than you, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You got it, pal! Except maybe for the thief's mom, that is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But isn't there someone who knows even more about him than the police?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You don't mean... "Detective Zvarri", do you?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Who is this person? Zvarri? He sounds German...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">His name is Luke Atmey, sir. I guess I shouldn't have made up such a silly name for him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What the heck? I guess he's not all that famous after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Anyway, it's true that he did manage to retrieve the last item the thief stole.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Oh, I see. It seems you're not the expert you claim to be.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Urk! I-It looks like the thief is playing with me, even now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The real "authority" on the thief is the other detective. I don't need to ask this one any more questions...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He's so confident that he sends his calling card before he even commits the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you seen all of these so-called "calling cards"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course I have. Except... The person in charge of the Treasure Exhibit never brought their card to the police... So I didn't see this one until after the crime occurred.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's because Detective Atmey stopped Ms. Andrews from taking it to the police.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Was the calling card that Lordly Tailor received authentic?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, all the cards have one common, identifying feature. But we're not releasing that information to the general public...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But you're absolutely certain that this card is real?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gumshoe can't say it out loud but I bet he's talking about Mask☆DeMasque's emblem...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This was his fifth heist, and as usual, he sent a card on to Lordly Tailor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His fifth heist... And your fifth screw up, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Objection, pal! That ain't fair! Maybe you could say I screwed up four times! But this last time wasn't my fault! I didn't know about the calling card this time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You of all people shouldn't be chuckling about this, Detective Gumshoe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I just want everyone here in the courtroom to know something! If you ever get a calling card from this guy, don't call some stupid private eye! Call your local police right away. Got me?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, it looks like he's really got it in for Detective Atmey.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">His pattern is to always go after only the most precious art pieces.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Art pieces? Like what, for example?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, his first target was the famous "Tear of Emanon".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's that? Some kind of especially salty teardrop?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">N-No, sir. It's a blue diamond. A single, rare diamond. Next was the "Crown of Bongora"... You know, the thing you put on your head. After that was the "Left Hand of Hades" and then the "Portrait of Mejeena", sir. Detective Atmey retrieved the "Portrait of Mejeena" and returned it to the museum.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the target of his fifth and last robbery was the "Sacred Urn"... right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But isn't it difficult for him to dispose of such famous art pieces...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, we assume he must have some underworld connections.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Somehow, Mr. DeLite doesn't look the type...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, he's a little too sunny to be hanging out in the underworld...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's why we're sure it was Mask☆DeMasque, sir. It fits his M. O. to a T!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean when you say, "it fits his M. O. to a T"?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I was thinking of asking the same thing myself.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ugh... I wish you would listen a little more closely, pal. First of all, there's the calling card. We're 100% certain it's authentic. Then there's the fact that he seemed to know all about the security system. And finally, his target was an art piece. These are all part of the thief's modus operandi.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And so, since this robbery seems to fit all those conditions...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's right! It means that Mask☆DeMasque is behind it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! It definitely looks like it was Mask☆DeMasque who stole the urn!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But there's no real evidence either way as to whether Ron DeLite is Mask☆DeMasque.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But... But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Also, the urn hasn't turned up yet, let alone in connection to Mr. DeLite himself.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So even though we know it was Mask☆DeMasque that did it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe for the time being, I should try to show it wasn't Mask☆DeMasque that did it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Can I ask you a little something, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Just hearing the "little" in that question is making me nervous.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You said that he always "goes after the most precious art pieces", right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's right, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But there's one problem... That's not what he did in this case. The supposedly "priceless" urn doesn't exactly rise to the level of "precious art"!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! How can you say such a terrible thing!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No! I meant from a financial point of view! I mean, it wouldn't fetch a good price.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Prosecutor Godot? What is the value of that urn?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">The appraisers I spoke to said they couldn't attach a price to it. And I mean that in the worst sense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So in other words... It was not the kind of item that Mask☆DeMasque would normally go after!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... If I understand you correctly, Mr. Wright... ...you're saying that the theft of the Sacred Urn was not the work of Mask☆DeMasque...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes... That's what I'm saying. <thought>Actually all I did was point out the contradiction. The argument made itself, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... First of all, we need to get this issue cleared up. Was this last robbery the work of Mask☆DeMasque or not? What do you have to say about this, Mr. Godot?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">This coffee here... It's my own special blend. I call it Godot #107. I'm trying to decide whether to cut down on the acidity or the bitterness... That's the only thing I've got on my mind right now... ...Mr. Trite!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">If you're really a man, you should clean up your own mess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Sorry, but I didn't get what you mean.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">If you're saying it wasn't Mask☆DeMasque that stole the urn... ...then it must be someone imitating Mask☆DeMasque's methods... A fake.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-A Fake☆DeMasque?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Fake☆DeMasque? That sounds so ridiculous. ...But I like it.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Now, before I decide on my coffee, I believe some proof is in order, Mr. Trite. Proof that the person who appeared at Lordly Tailor that night was actually a fake.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Though I don't approve of Mr. Godot's behavior, his point is valid. Mr. Wright. ...We're waiting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looks like I'm going to have to prove it... I need proof that the person at Lordly Tailor that night was in fact, Fake☆DeMasque!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is this evidence supposed to prove?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Well, it proves someone here is a fake alright. ...It proves that this lawyer is a fake.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>These prosecutors sure know how to twist the knife...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is no time to be impressed! Think it over again! When he stole the urn, his photo was taken, right? Who knows? Maybe there's something on there that shows he's a fake...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Is she talking about that photo we got from Atmey?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you ready yet, Mr. Wright? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The proof is right here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This looks like... a photo taken by a security camera.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But if you look closely... you'll notice something peculiar about it.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Well then, why don't you go ahead and show us what it is. Go on. Use this pointer and show us just what about this picture is so "peculiar".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's right here. ...I think.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is that what was so "peculiar"?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! The place that you're pointing to is all wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh... What do you mean!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">The only thing "peculiar" in this courtroom... is on top of your head.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Are you going to let him get away making fun of your hair!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yes... At least until I know he can't use his goggles to fry me or something...</thought> W-Well anyway! There is a strange spot in this photo!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Still haven't given up? So what is it then?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's right here, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You mean... Mask☆DeMasque?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have here a piece of reference I would like the court to take a look at.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Isn't that the publicity photo I bought this morning...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The problem I have with the security camera photo is the broach on DeMasque's chest.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A Breach? Here!? Bailiff! Get my steed! We need to retreat at once!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...A broach, Your Honor. It's a sort of clasp for holding one's cape on.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A clasp, eh... Ah! I see now!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But the Mask☆DeMasque in the security camera photo... Ahh!! He has no broach!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That broach is the same as the emblem on DeMasque's calling card and serves as his symbol. But the thief that broke into Lordly Tailor wasn't wearing a broach... In other words, this "Mask☆DeMasque" is a fake!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...! I-I've been fooled agaaaaaain!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Order! It's true... Undeniably true... Detective Gumshoe! How... How could you have overlooked this!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-I'm sorry, sir! I don't know how I...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Hey now... ...If you're gonna have a pity party, invite me, too!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Godot! You deserve some blame in this, too! How could you have overlooked such a large broach...?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! The broach you're talking about... Do you mean this?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That's...! Mask☆DeMasque's broach!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Where did you find it!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Well I've always had a good nose for evidence... I got it at the crime scene. It was hidden in the shadow of a big female Buddha statue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Buddha statue"...? He must mean the Ami Fey statue.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-Why didn't you tell me about that, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...I always put evidence away in my pocket. ...After all, it's the safest place for crucial evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Grrr... This guy is one cool customer.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">It's a little early to be shaken up, isn't it, little lady? ...That friend of yours left pretty little hickeys on there, too.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">H-Hickeys?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Figuratively speaking, of course... I'm referring to Ron DeLite's fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whaaa...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What!? The defendant's fingerprints are on the broach!? Order! Order in the court! Mr. Godot! Let's see that broach!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I've grown attached to my metallic girlfriend here. ...Take good care of her.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... She-- I mean, it appears to have been torn off some clothing. There's a little bit of cloth left on the back.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Obviously there must have been a big struggle that night at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh... Phoenix, we have a problem...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! You mess with Godot... ...and you get burned.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grr... He's been playing me like a violin...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Well Judge, I'm about ready to call my next witness.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? You're done with me? But I haven't proved anything yet.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You've proven your own incompetence. That's good enough.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...That doesn't sound good at all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Bring the next witness into the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Finally time for the Ace Detective to make his appearance, huh...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">One second is one drip of the coffee pot. Let's hurry it up.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">SHHH! SILENCE!... Hee hee hee hee hee... Now I see. It's all becoming clear.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's clear?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...Zvarri! The truth has once again been elegantly revealed to me! What we have here is... A judge and a prosecutor. ...A coffee maniac, at that! ...Am I correct?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Well, yes. That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Not bad. Not bad at all. You're the first person that's ever been able to penetrate my secret veil.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Well, Sir Prosecutor. Let me introduce myself. My name is Luke Atmey, Ace Detective and rising star illuminating the heavens.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Boy, these two make a prefect pair...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They'd either be best friends or they'd tear each other's heads off.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I've heard that on the night of the crime, you were all alone on security detail.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...You have heard correctly. My specially-made monocle is worth more than a hundred Detective Gumshoes. ...If Detective Gumshoe was worth anything, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why was this guy all by himself anyway...? There must be some reason. I'm sure of it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, tell us what this special monocle of yours witnessed!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">It was approximately 1 o'clock in the morning... just after the date changed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So you didn't get a clear look at the criminal?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">My specially-made monocle never misses a thing. However! That is limited to things that fall within my own visual range! But of course, that's only natural.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I fall to see why the witness seems so proud of his performance that evening.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Well, Sir Old-timer, let me explain. We are not speaking of any ordinary thief... ...but of the kings of thieves! The great Mask☆DeMasque, my arch-enemy! That is what my instincts and my years of experience tell me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well. Proceed with the cross-examination, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">It was approximately 1 o'clock in the morning... just after the date changed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that would be one o'clock on the morning of the 12th, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">That's an impressive deduction, Sir Lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were on security duty that night. Where exactly were you at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">A penetrating question! I was in the basement warehouse, near the computer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Near the computer, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So then you weren't trying to remain hidden, I take it?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Up to this point, I have tried to remain concealed while waiting for the thief...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, he said the same thing yesterday, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Gumshoe also said that he never saw him at the crime scene...</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Precisely! That is precisely why I chose NOT to hide last night. I knew that by NOT concealing myself, I would be putting pressure on the thief.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like the thief was the one applying pressure... On your pidgeony head, that is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">In any case!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">That's when my nemesis, the infamous Mask☆DeMasque, dancingly descended upon me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Dancingly descended"...? From where exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Well... From the entrance, I suppose. Where else?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So in actuality, he neither "danced" nor "descended"! ...Someone please save me.</thought> Um... So how is it that you didn't notice the thief?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">My eyes were looking for the thief's shadow while my ears listened for his footfalls. But even so, the dastardly criminal managed to sneak up on me... It can only be due to his subtly camouflaged cape and soft-soled shoes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>... I hereby dub you "Ace Dunce".</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Just as I began to turn, the coward struck a fierce blow upon my noble head!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You didn't see the criminal's face when that happened?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...Well, that's difficult part. How should I put it... I saw his mask... That's all that I can recall.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That's not very solid as far as testimony goes.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">However... Fortunately I had my third monocle, the security camera, at the ready. It captured his image perfectly... This should be sufficient, I believe?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, well, as long as this photo is authentic, I don't see a problem here. Well, Mr. Godot? Do you have a problem with the photo? Good. Then let's continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Darkness swallowed me before I could land a single strike. When I awoke, he was gone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Attacked and knocked unconscious? And you weren't able to do a thing? There's certainly some very impressive detective work.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Hmph! Well, Sir Lawyer! Have you ever been suddenly struck on the head?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!? W-Well.. Actually, yes. By a fire extinguisher.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">And what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I-I was knocked out.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And you lost your memory, too!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">You see? You have no right to look down on me then, do you? The only reason I didn't lose my memory was because I have more brains to begin with.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He may have brains, but the wiring to the self-reflection part seems to be served...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">In any case, that was how I was knocked senseless. And then...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Thirty minutes later, I used an emergency phone to notify the police!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About this "30 minutes"...</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">My silver cord was loosened and my soul fled to the Golden Halls of Elysium...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">As usual, I have no idea what this guy is saying.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think he's saying that he was out cold.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So... What happened during these 30 minutes?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">No one can say, Your Honor... That span of time has truly vanished into the ether!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just what is he going on about!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's something suspicious about Detective Atmey... How could he not have noticed when the thief came in?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Also, he says he was knocked unconscious before he could fight back... But that can't be right. It contradicts the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Which piece...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The real question is... Why would he tell such an obvious lie?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Mr. Atmey. Could you take a look at this with that special monocle of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Aha! This belongs to the criminal mastermind, my arch-nemesis, Mask☆DeMasque! It is, in point of fact, Mask☆DeMasque's broach!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was found on the floor of the basement warehouse. I wonder how that happened?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Ha... Elementary, my dear lawyer. Obviously it wasn't glued on well enough.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not quite. It clearly shows signs of having been ripped off a piece of clothing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ripped off...? Aha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...We can only deduce that the thief struggled with someone that night! That's the only thing I can think of. And there's only one person that was in a position to have a struggle with the thief. The only person that was on security duty that night...You, Detective Atmey!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...Urk! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Atmey! You must have fought with the thief last night! So, why did you lie in your testimony to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! Giving false testimony is a serious crime!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Err, I... N-No! W-Wait just a moment, Sir Old-timer!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Don't talk to me like I'm living in a nursing home!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Hee hee hee he he he... I just remembered, Your Honor. I was just confused because I've been dealing with so many cases lately.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">The true measure of a man is in the amount of work he does. That's what I always say.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, you can only handle one case at a time... Isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You talk too much.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! So are you now saying that you and the thief fought?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Hold on. That's quite enough... Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">E-Excuse me...?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Save the big questions for the testimony. That's one of my rules.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Indeed! I understand! I, Luke Atmey, agree completely!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Indeed, it's true that I looked away from the door for a brief moment.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So in the end, you did catch a glimpse of Mask☆DeMasque?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Correct. It was during his third crime that he struck me from behind. It seems that my memory has become a tad jumbled, so to speak.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Well, that's certainly understandable. I, myself, always get confused about which testimony goes with which case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Th-That can't be good...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Indeed, it's true that I looked away from the door for a brief moment.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So why did you look away from the door anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">In addition to the camera, I had prepared a variety of other sensors as well. The alarm on one of those had gone off, so I had to check the data. That's why I went to the computer! ...Elegantly, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you were momentarily vulnerable when you were working on the computer? <thought>What should I do? Should I ask some more questions...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, we know for sure that Atmey looked away from the door. I think I should ask about something else now...</thought> Alright. So you looked away from the door. ...And then?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What kind of sensors are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">There are other places in the basement that someone could enter and exit from. There are air conditioner ducts, sewer pipes... And a cat door as well. I hooked up heat-detecting, infrared and ultra-violet sensors to each of them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a lot of hardware... Was it all yours?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Lordly Tailor Department Store was kind enough to provide the monitoring hardware. Naturally, the security camera that look the photo belongs to them as well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>In other words, he couldn't have rigged the equipment, huh...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Hee hee hee hee hee... Has that cleared up any doubts you had about me, Sir Lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So did that computer belong to Lordly Tailor as well?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Correct. Well, except for the program that manages the data. That was specially designed by me, Luke Atmey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>In that case, he could have easily manipulated the data.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Hee hee hee hee hee... What's wrong, Sir Lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">However... Luke Atmey cannot be so easily discombobulated!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... What does that mean? "Discombobulated"?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Young people these days... They really irritate me. They allow perfectly good old words to die until everyone forgets what they mean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but what exactly DOES it mean anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Now I've forgotten. What was I saying?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Jeez. It's better than old people who forget what they were saying 5 seconds ago!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">...Well, it looks like we've cleared that up. You can go on with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Unfortunately, the thief grabbed a weapon from the side and... rendered me senseless.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean by "weapon from the side"?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Naturally, that thief had no idea that I, Luke Atmey, was hiding in the area! He grabbed the sword from the statue that was standing by the door to the warehouse.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sword...? You mean the sword that was all twisted like a tree branch?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Correct. Fortunately for me, the blade was not sharp.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>OK. so he IS talking about the Shichishito...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So the thief armed himself with a sword. And what about yourself, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">A true gentleman fights only with his own fists... But they were not enough.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You had that much faith in your own fighting abilities?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">But of course. In college, I was the 2nd in-charge of the boxing club.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sorry if I fail to find that appropriately impressive.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">However! My opponent in the ring this time was my arch-nemesis, Mask☆DeMasque!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This guy is a real piece of work...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">His first blow struck true! Bam!... And that's all she wrote.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you tell us a little more about what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">My opponent was both powerful and vicious. You might say he was... "powericious".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"P-Powericious"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">I assumed the "Atmey Fighting Stance", but a sudden flash of light behind me! That of course was checkmate! My opponent had bested me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What do I do now? Should I ask more about this...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I guess it's true that Atmey was knocked senseless after all. I'd better ask him about something else instead...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what was this flash of light that blinded you?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...I was bathed in a golden light that seemed to come from the statue of the woman.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The statue of Ami Fey, I'm guessing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well that wasn't very much help at all...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is this "Atmey Fighting Style"?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">I'm sorry but that's a trade secret... I really can't say any more. But, I suppose I can tell you if I absolutely must. The main thing is to put your back to the wall. That way no one can get behind you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's it...? That's the "Atmey Fighting Style"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Well, Mr. Wright? What about that testimony...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I guess it's true that Atmey was knocked senseless after all. I'd better ask him about something else instead...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course it's important! We've learned a detective's SECRET technique, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, indeed... I'll remember to use it if I ever take a walk alone late at night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why the heck is he eye-balling me like that...? It's creeping me out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Now then, witness! We'll go ahead and add that secret information to your official testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">I put my back to the wall to fight, but the thief's blow landed upon my third eye.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Where is this "third eye" you're talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Oh... it's right between my right and left eye brows. ...It's quite invisible to the unenlightened. You may call it the forehead, if you like.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why didn't you just say that in the first place!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Sir Lawyer! It looks like the creases in your own forehead are getting deeper!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So Mr. Atmey got hit on the forehead then?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what he says.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... I've got a funny feeling about that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Actually, so do I.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well what do you think, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, there's one thing that I'm absolutely sure of now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah? What is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Luke Atmey guy... He's definitely hiding something!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-But why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think I'm starting to figure out what really happened that night. <thought>...And about the true nature of this "detective".</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Atmey! Your testimony is crumbling like a house of cards.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">What fun this is, Sir Lawyer! It is truly a pleasure to cross swords with you! And now, once again, you have thrown down the gauntlet at my armored feet...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe this is what you said yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">No, the coward must have wormed his way in through somewhere besides the door... Perhaps the air ducts or the sewer pipes... Then my arch-nemesis struck me on the head from behind with this gruesome item here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">From behind, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But just now you testified that he struck you on the forehead... I hardly think you could forget where you were hit on the head!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...Urk! It seems... I-I've made another mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Detective Atmey. That's not the only strange part of your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">For example... The very fact that you hid the calling card from the police itself is strange! It's almost as if... You were afraid they were going to help with security!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">U-Urk...! Geniuses such as myself have always been misunderstood! How sad...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">...To err is human, to forgive divine. Humans aren't machines... They have souls, feelings. They live, they die, they love, they hate... And yes, they even make mistakes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, hold on! It-It's not as pretty as that!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Really? What is it like then!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Always chase a riddle down to the end. That's one of my rules.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is it... This might just be my chance to turn things around!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Mr. Wright. What exactly is it that you're asserting?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Very well, Your Honor. The defense asserts that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The truth is... this witness is no Ace Detective at all!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...So then what exactly are you saying that I am?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, umm... Well, an average detective...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hardly see the relevance of that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-What are you doing, Nick!? Weren't you going to go on the attack?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was planning on it, but it looks I'm the one who got attacked instead.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Think harder next time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This witness isn't Luke Atmey... He's a fake!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...So now it's not just Mask☆DeMasque. You're saying I'm a fake, too?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An Ace Detective could never be as forgetful as this guy!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Imposters like you are often suspicious of others as well.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Really, this is too much. Next you'll be calling me a fake, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The answer is simple! It's all clear to me now! Detective Atmey's true identity is actually... Mask☆DeMasque!</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Yeeeeaaargggh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court! Mr. Wright! What is the meaning of this!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are too many unnatural parts to Mr. Atmey's story. He says he was "hiding" at the crime scenes, which is why no one ever saw him there. And then, in his last case, he manages to outperform Detective Gumshoe and... ...the entire police force to "miraculously" retrieve the stolen treasure.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Th-That's because... I analyzed the crime scene data and made an exquisitely elegant deduction. I picked up clues that the police overlooked in order to arrive at a...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, please! The explanation is far simpler than that, "Detective Atmey"! The truth is that you are, in fact, Mask☆DeMasque.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Gurk...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But Mr. Wright! Th-This photo! It clearly shows Mask☆DeMasque! This security camera belongs to Lordly Tailor Department Store! He shouldn't have been able to manipulate it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He didn't need to manipulate it! He gained access to the warehouse under the pretense of providing "security"... Then he simply dressed as the "thief" and stole the urn.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So... the Ace Detective is actually an Ace Thief! Is this true, witness!?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">... Aha... Hee hee hee ha ha ha Aha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Ho ho ho hee hee hee! DeMasque's M. O. is pure genius! And so am I, Luke Atmey, Ace Detective!! You're very clever to have come to such a conclusion! I am impressed, Sir Lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Whaaaaat!? Witness! You... You're admitting it!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! Now's your chance!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes! Time to put the last nail in this guy's coffin! Detective Atmey! When you assumed the thief's identity--</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Godot Blend #102... ...My personal favorite.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Godot!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">"The Ace Detective is actually an Ace Thief!" I smell a best-selling novel! There's only one problem... It simply isn't true.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But Mr. Godot! Mr. Wright has made some very strong points and I...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I will admit my opponent has woven a compelling narrative out of whole cloth. But it is, in fact, nothing more than a patchwork quilt. Mr. Trite... If this detective really is the thief, then show us the proof of your claim. But it had better be as hot... and as perfect as the coffee dripping down your face!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright!? Don't just stand there! This court would like to see this decisive proof you have! Quickly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!? Oh! Y-Yes, of course! <thought>Wh-What's the big rush...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Are you alright, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Atmey looks pretty rattled right now... I'd like to finish this right now if I can. But can I really do it?</thought> The decisive evidence that proves Mr. Luke Atmey is in fact Mask☆DeMasque...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As usual, the defense comes prepared, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well then... Let's see what you've got. Please present proof that Mask☆DeMasque is actually Mr. Luke Atmey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here's your proof!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you think, Mr. Godot?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">It looks to me like Mr. Trite is still a mite sleepy. Perhaps he'd like a big mug of my special Godot blend? Well?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No thanks, I'm fine! Really! <thought>What do I do now? Another mistake like that and I'm through! Without some decisive evidence, I could be risking everything...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Proof? Of course I... I... ...I've got nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Just what I thought. A man has to told his head up high no matter how bad things get, after all. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uuugh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... I thought perhaps you had some evidence to back up your assertion...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is no good! I've got to stay on the attack! I'll never get another chance to prove that this guy is the thief!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't give up, Nick! Think harder and try again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's no good... I'm just not ready yet...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-But... Are you going to just give up and let us lose this?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">So, you've come to your senses, have you Sir Lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... Unnngh... <thought>Argh! I can't think of a counter-attack at all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems the cloud of suspicion surrounding this witness has lifted. Mr. Godot. If you have anything further to add, then--</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh... Wh-Who... ...Who are you?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">That doesn't really matter right now, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. DeLite! What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Nicky boy! The thing you've been looking for... I think I found it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You mean... that bag!?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">No, not the bag! What's in the bag! ...Well?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That's...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">the Sacred Urn!! Nick! It's the urn!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! ...You! Madame...! That urn... Where did you find it!?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">You'll never believe it... It was in the office of Mr. Fancy Pants Ace Detective! ...Luke Atmey!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Oh, Dessie! You're the best!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well? How do you explain that one, Mr. Atmey!?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even you are going to have a hard time weaseling out of this one!</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Pathetic...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Godot...? Do you have something you wish to say?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Yes, Your Honor... It simply amazes me how quickly times change... In the old days, a man was to be taken at his word. It's truly sad...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're still denying that Mr. Atmey was involved!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Before casting aspersions at Detective Atmey, consider the young lady here. Your name is Desirée... Desirée DeLite. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Y-Yes! What about it?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! How charming... The lengths that a woman is willing to go to save her husband is truly inspiring.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Wh-What are you insinuating!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">As the wife of the criminal, you could have "discovered" that stolen urn anywhere. Including the office of the good detective here. So you found the urn. What does that prove? It certainly doesn't prove where the urn was before you "found" it.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">What...? I just brought it here from the detective's office!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Please Madame... This town is already filled to the brim with lies. Any more could only compound the tragedy we have been witness to.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">You're wrong! I would never...! I would never do such a thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. DeLite...</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Please, Nicky boy! You've got to help me talk some sense into these people!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There must be some way! I've got to prove that urn was actually in the Atmey Detective Agency...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">What's wrong? Isn't it your job to come up with something to say...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Come on! It should be easy to prove! After all, we checked out that bag, didn't we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're right. I remember doing that. Whatever was in there, it was hard and round... And smooth, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes! It must have been the urn! It must have!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... I never actually saw it with my own eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Atmey walked in just when I was about to have a look at it... So even if it was the urn in there, I can't testify that it was.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ack! You're right!!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! It looks like I was wrong about you, Mr. Trite. In this town overflowing with lies, there's still a single flickering candle of truth.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Nicky boy...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, it's true that I never actually saw the urn... But maybe I can still testify about it from another angle!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What about it, Mr. Wright? Have you given up yet...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can prove where the urn was... ...by the fingerprints on it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Fingerprints, eh...</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Oh come now! Now you're really making me laugh, Sir Lawyer! Fingerprints indeed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">May I go on? Good. Now it would be perfectly understandable if my fingerprints were on the urn. After all, it was I who was guarding the urn in the first time! In any case, I am always in the habit of wearing gloves as you can see. So unfortunately, my fingerprints wouldn't be evidence of anything.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What about it, Mr. Wright? This witness's fingerprints would mean nothing anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick, what are you going to do now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've come too far to turn back now! Atmey must have brought the urn back to his office yesterday... And there, I'm sure someone must have left their fingerprints on it...!</thought> The defense proposes that the fingerprints of this person should be on the urn!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Let me give you an important piece of advice. The one who keeps a cool head all the way until the game's end is the winner.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let me give you an even more important piece of advice, Mr. Wright... You are not going to win this game with that answer.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow... Even the judge is making cool, snappy remarks now...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>D-Does that mean I was wrong again? Hmm... The urn was put in that bag and carried to the detective's office yesterday. That means the person I should be fingering is... the person who left their prints on the urn yesterday at the Atmey Detective Agency!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you really think there's someone that could fit the bill?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright? What have you decided?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! Please give me just one more chance!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright? What have you decided to do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Forgive me, Your Honor. I've decided to think the whole thing over again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't prove anything yet.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well... It looks like that's all then.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Exactly... And this urn is all the proof I need to make my case...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You still don't get it, huh? Listen closely, Mr. Trite. This is the urn that Mask☆DeMasque stole, right? Now the wife of the accused comes strolling in here with the very same urn, correct? Now, who would you think is the thief?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">No! That's wrong! That's not why I've got it...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! Y-You can't let him do this...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, this isn't good... There has to be another way around this...</thought> Your Honor! Please let me think it over one more time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. It's high time that you learn your lesson. The courtroom is no place for poorly thought-out or rash declarations!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to be careful... He won't be so nice next time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">So what is all this fuss about fingerprints anyway...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Atmey... Do you recall the events of yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Come on! Open it up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! Wait a minute! We can't just open his private property!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't be such a fuddy-duddy! This is an important investigation! Well? What's in there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Hang on a sec. I'm taking it out now... <thought>Whatever it is, it feels... kinda hard... and smooth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">...Well, hello there!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's true that I didn't get a chance to look in the bag at that time. But! I did touch what was inside.</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Wh-What!? Y-You touched it...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And I remember it very well. It was "smooth and hard".</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">W-Well, err... Th-That was just...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! I'd like the court to examine the fingerprints on that urn. If my fingerprints are on there... Then it proves that the urn was in Detective Atmey's office!</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Well, even if your fingerprints are on the urn... ...it still doesn't prove when they were put there, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course it does.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Wh-What did you just say!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not what I said, it's what Adrian Andrews, the person in charge of the exhibition said.</line>
<line speaker="Andrews">I polished it until it was just about glowing... I thought maybe I could make it looks more valuable!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If she polished it that much, she must have removed any and all fingerprints on it. And the only chance I had to get my fingerprints on it after that was... Yesterday! At the Atmey Detective Agency!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! This blend... Godot Blend #107... I've decided... It's a little too bitter after all!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! I accept the defense's request! Bailiff! Take this urn and...</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Wait! Wait a moment, Your Honor! ...There's no need for that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">N-No need you say...?</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Precisely... I already know Mr. Wright's fingerprints are on the urn...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What are you saying!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yes! I've finally broken him down!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atmey">Hee hee hee ha ha ha Aha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Ho ho ho hee hee! Take a good look, everyone! Unable to find a rival worthy of my genius, I was forced to create one by myself! Here I am! The tragic clown... </line>
<line speaker="Maya">This guy is nuttier than a fruitcake...</line>
<line speaker="Atmey">You see! It was me all along! I am the one and only Mask☆DeMasque! Ha ha! I hope you all enjoyed my little performance! Hee hee hee ha ha ha Aha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Ho ho ho hee hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Godot... What's Mr. Atmey's condition?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">He's still in the lobby, laughing insanely, Your Honor. I wish I could enjoy the joke as much as he seems to be.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, it looks like the matter has been settled. I came perilously close to besmirching the record of an innocent young man. Besmirching him with the title of "thief"!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, you were right after all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah! I guess Mr. DeLite really wasn't the thief!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court finds the defendant, Mr. Ron DeLite...</line>
<line speaker="Ron">You're wrong! Wrong I tell you! Err, umm, I mean... Not exactly wrong so much, but actually not right is what I really trying to say</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh no... He's not... This can't be happening...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">The thief... The sneaky, odious thief who's been stealing all the treasures... It's me! I'm him! I'm the one you want! I'm the thief I tell you! So do it...! Pronounce me guilty! Pleeeease!! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't know what kind of a kangaroo court you all think this is, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The true identity of the thief has already been proven! Please hurry and pass judg--</line>
<line speaker="Ron">What are you talking about!? I already confessed! I'm the thief I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Mr. Godot! Don't just stand there drinking coffee!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! Hey there, Mr. Thief...</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Y-Yes! Yes, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">If you're really a man, then clean up your own mess.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">I-I'm sorry... I'm afraid I just don't have any idea what do you mean.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">If you are Mask☆DeMasque... then prove it. That's what it means.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Y-Yes, sir! I'll be happy to!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He says he'll be happy to, Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's kinda cute... He's 100% committed to his fantasy.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Good boy! Just remember one thing. A boy only gets one chance in his life to become a man!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">I-I know that! I-I won't fail! I swear!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">OK, then... Talk! ...We're all listening.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh well... Let's all have a listen to this "confession"...</line>
<line speaker="Ron">The truth is, I've been Mask☆DeMasque all along!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I don't like the direction this trial has taken...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But this is how every trial goes... At least with me, anyway...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! You're doing great!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Hee hee hee... Stop it, Mr. Godot... You're embarrassing me.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Like I said, you're only going to get one chance to testify, alright? But if you make it through this with flying colors, I'll keep my promise, too. I'll make sure you stay locked up in prison as the one and only true Mask☆DeMasque!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Thanks so much, Mr. Godot! I... I'll do my best!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Alright, Mr. Wright. I'm afraid it's time for the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Ron">The truth is, I've been Mask☆DeMasque all along!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You may think you're real Mask☆DeMasque... but your wife thinks you're delusional.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">I haven't told Dessie yet... About my true identity, I mean... Believe me, I've got my reasons.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>With the way your room is decked out, how could she NOT know about it...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Even thieves have complicated family situations, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What should I do? It sounds like we're about to get sidetracked... again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So why are you withholding the truth from your wife?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Well... first of all, I don't think she'd believe me anyway... And second... If there's one thing that Dessie absolutely detests... ...it's criminals.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that's the case, then why did you ever start thieving to begin with?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Well, Dessie is crazy about shopping. She's a real shopaholic... But she's the love of my life, Your Honor. I guess you could say I'm a "Dessie-aholic"...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So you do have a complicated family situation after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Alright, that's enough. Please continue with your testimony. I beg of you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's no point in digging through any more of their dirty laundry...</thought> Well, why don't you continue with your testimony for now.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">I mean, you can't prove that I'm not actually Mask☆DeMasque, can you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... I thought you were going to be the one to show US the proof. You know, that you're the real Mask☆DeMasque and not just some kind of obsessed fanboy.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Hey now, that's not fair. Why do I have to do all the hard work anywaaaaay!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe because you're the one making the outrageous claim... for a change.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, Nick! You know that Mr. DeLite couldn't have committed the crime! You're the one with the fancy law degree! It's time to put it to work already!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I need some kind of proof that Ron couldn't possibly be Mask☆DeMasque...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, I guess if you had that kind of proof, we wouldn't still be here, would we...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>For the time being, maybe I need to shift strategy... I should try to show that Mr. DeLite couldn't have stolen the urn.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">Anyway, I...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ron">I don't have an alibi for the night the urn was stolen, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've got no alibi...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I've been a judge for a long time... And this is the first time I've ever heard a defendant brag about having no alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">But I tell you I was in Lordly Tailor that night! ...Errr, no. That's too vague, even for me. To be more precise, I was down in the basement warehouse.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hold on...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What is it, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Where was Ron DeLite when the crime happened anyway...? If we can prove he had an alibi after all, this case will be a piece of cake.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-Well, you're right, but...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! You think you can prove that? Wake up and smell the coffee!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well, I think maybe I can...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, do you have any evidence that shows the defendant has an alibi?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course not! Don't be ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I'm sorry! ...Say! What am I apologizing for!? You! Witness! Hurry up with your testimony already!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">I-I'm sorry! ...Why is it that I'm always the one that has to apologize to everyone in the end.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have the evidence! Or do you think I'm still some sort of third-rate rookie!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh...! I-I've never seen you this angry before!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...I'm not surprised. Anger is the last refuge of the pathetic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I thought I was more confident than angry...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, let's see this evidence already. Show to this court evidence that proves where your client was on the night of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here's the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! It looks like I was right. ...Mr. Trite. The more pathetic a man is, the more likely he is to start pointing fingers!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">For some reason, the good Prosecutor really wants to prove that I'm "pathetic"...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's because you are pathetic! And so is your "evidence"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oops. I guess I was wrong... Again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">Aha! I told you I didn't have an alibi!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ron">I donned my costume that night and dancingly descended upon the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Dancingly descended"...? From where exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Well... From the entrance, I suppose. Where else?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So in actuality, he neither "danced" nor "descended"! ...Someone save me. Again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess he thinks "descended" sounds more heroic or thief-like or something.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">A-Anyway! I was there at the crime scene! Just like I said!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Look! You can see right there in the photo! That's me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the photo that was taken by the security camera at the crime scene...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No doubt about it. That's Mask☆DeMasque.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, but don't forget there's something important missing. The real Mask☆DeMasque has a big broach on his chest!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">As for my broach, I snagged it on the door handle and it got torn off, that's all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You didn't notice it when your broach was torn off?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Huh!? W-Well... I'm always a little nervous when I'm working.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's a bit of clothing left on the back side of the broach. I don't think it could have been torn off that easily...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes, but... I don't see what that has to do with anything. Right now we're trying to prove that Mr. DeLite isn't the thief, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I guess so. <thought>Let me hear that testimony one more time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why does Mr. DeLite want to be Mask☆DeMasque so badly anyway? It's kinda disturbing. He doesn't seem like your typical attention whore to me. Unlike, say... you, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I am nothing of the sort, thank you very much. <thought>But I gotta admit it is kinda scary the way Ron acts...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Anyway... Time to poke some holes in that testimony of his!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. DeLite. This wallet belongs to you, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Ah! Y-Yes. It-It does. I-I had lost it somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! When you find a wallet, you should report it to the police right away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah! No! You don't understand. This is an important piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Evidence"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. DeLite... When did you first notice that you'd lost your wallet?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Err, let's see... I think it was on the night of the crime... But I know I still had it when Dessie and I went out for dinner.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This wallet was found at approximately 1:00 AM at KB Security headquarters.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What...!? Surely you're not serious!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... I am serious. This proves that Mr. DeLite was, in fact, at KB Security that night!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Noooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So if the defendant was at KB Security at 1 o'clock in the morning... ...then that proves that he has a watertight alibi!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Noooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Furthermore, considering the distance between Lordly Tailor and KB Security... ...it would have taken 30 minutes to get there by car! <thought>According to Larry anyway...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Godot!? Do you have anything to say? And stop drinking that coffee!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...Come on, Mr. Thief. Don't let this guy beat you! Tell him why he's wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">You're the only one who calls me "thief", Mr. Godot... ...Alright, I'll try! I-I'll do it! I will!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...He's really got Mr. DeLite all worked up...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, he's like a kid at his first day of school...</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Look, it's just ridiculous! Why would I have dropped my wallet at KB Security!? Someone must have planted it there to make it LOOK like I was there and not at the heist.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Planted" it there? He's really reaching now...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. DeLite. You probably dropped your wallet when you took it out to use this, didn't you? The key card to KB Security's CEO's office.</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Noooo!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! That was a pretty good try, Mr. Trite... Unfortunately, you've overlooked one small thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What...?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">"Motive" of course! Why would this thief go to KB Security in the middle of the night anyway!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, Mr. Wright? It looks like you need some more evidence after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grrr! This stupid kid...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then. Let's see your evidence. The evidence that shows why Mr. DeLite went to KB Security at 1 AM that night!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here is your evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">...What is this supposed to mean, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!? Well, um... Don't you know?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Mr. Wright... If you're a real man, you should clean up your own mess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Doh...! <thought>For some reason, it bothers me more when HE says it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. DeLite... I believe you've seen this before, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Ah...! Th-That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A blackmail letter. That's what it looks like from the contents.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">B-Blackmail...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, basically it says, "bring $50,000 dollars".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That certainly sounds like blackmail alright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At the time of the theft, Mr. DeLite was dealing with the blackmailer himself... ...in KB Security's CEO office, a full half an hour away from the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...Ungh... Urk... No No No No No NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! OOOOORDER!! So when the theft of the urn occurred, the defendant was at KB Security... It looks like a perfect case for the defense!</line>
<line speaker="Godot"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Godot">...You may see it as a perfect case, Judge, but to me... Well, let's just say that my Godot Blend #107 impresses me a lot more.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What are you trying to say?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You say the thief was being blackmailed by the CEO of a security company... But... Did you actually investigate this CEO at all?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!? Well, umm... No... I guess not.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Accusing a man of blackmail with no proof? I'm not sure what I think of that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Not sure what I think of that?"... At least I know what I think of you...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Good point. I'm not sure what I think of it myself... You claim that the defendant entered the CEO's office... ...but you will need at least one witness to corroborate your claim, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! I think we're going to have to track down the CEO guy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, we don't have to track down the CEO at all.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">What do you mean by that, Mr. Trite?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is someone else who can testify. This is the person who can testify that the key card was used at 1 AM that night!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! That's the first time one of your jokes actually made me truly laugh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Umm, I haven't actually made any jokes... Not intentionally anyway...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, perhaps you find it funny, but I fail to see any humor in it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The problem is the key card that was in Ron's wallet... Somehow I need to prove that the card was used at 1 o'clock in the morning.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Who is this useless-looking young man?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't remember him, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmm... Not exactly... But just looking at his picture makes the bile start to rise in my throat.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It looks like he doesn't remember the case from 2 years ago...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He probably blocked out that memory on purpose. Anyway, this man was working as a guard at KB Security that night.</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Oh...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The question at hand is this key card.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yup. That's the key card they use at the building I work in. According to the serial number, this one is for the CEO's office. You need it to get into that room, and every time you use that card, it leaves a record.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As you can see, there's no need to investigate the CEO of KB Security! We should be able to discover the truth simply by analyzing this key card's data!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Bwaaaah...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Godot?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">The name of the CEO of KB Security is Kane Bullard. I was unable to contact him directly, but... I got the key card data. ...Here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-So what does it show!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Each key card has its own serial number and they leave detailed records of their use. According to this data... this card was used at 1 AM on the morning of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But that means... it can't be Mr. DeLite dressed as Mask☆DeMasque in this photo!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ha...! It looks like you're right. Two minutes isn't even enough time to brew a good cup o' Joe...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... So then...!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ron DeLite was clearly in the office of KB Security's CEO at the time of the crime. ...The prosecutor's office is ready to admit that fact. Therefore, it's impossible for the defendant to be Mask☆DeMasque.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Good job! You did it, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...That's enough! I came perilously close to besmirching the record of an innocent young man. Besmirching him with the title of "thief"! ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What's wrong, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm ready to pass judgement... But before I do that, do you have any further objections?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Hrpmh...!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Unnnggh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. The court finds the defendant, Mr. Ron DeLite...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! You did it! You were right after all! Actually... I'm a little bit ashamed of myself.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Nicky boy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh! Ms. DeLite...!</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">I knew you could do it! I believed in you all along, Nicky boy! ...I don't know how I can ever repay you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aww... Shucks... Thanks, Ms. DeLite. <thought>I just know I'm blushing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Congratulations, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh! P-Pearls...! <thought>I've got a bad feeling about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">*gasp!* Wh-Who is this woman!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, she... She's nobody... She's just ahh...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You're blushing! How dare you do this in front of Mystic Maya! You should be ashamed of yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeowch! She slapped me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm, Pearly... This woman is Ms. Desirée DeLite. She's our client's wife.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">*gasp!* Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You're even worse than I thought! Going behind the back of your own client...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-N-No! You've got it all wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'll never forgive you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Owww... A double slap...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, anyway, All's well that ends well, right? We got the Sacred Urn back and the thief has been caught!</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">You're so right! And it's all thanks to Nicky boy here!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But actually it was you, Ms. DeLite, that brought us our urn back! Thank you from the bottom of my heart!</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Oh, please... You're embarrassing me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If we won the case... ...then why does this guy still looks so glum...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ron">Ugggh... But I am the thief... Actually, what's the point now</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">...What is it, honey? I did my best for you, Ronnie!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">I-I know that and I appreciate it, Dessie... But the thing is...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Come on... Give the kid some time. He's just got a little touch of the blues. You know about feeling blue, right, amigo?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mr. Godot! What are you doing here!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Oh come on! I just came here to say thanks to my newest buddy... ...You, Mr. Trite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe you should learn my name before you call me "buddy"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Well, playtime is over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Early this morning... the body of Kane Bullard was discovered.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Kane Bullard...? Where have I heard that name before?</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">Isn't that... the name of the CEO of KB Security?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-Body...?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">The estimated time of death was 1 AM on October 12th.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">1 AM on October 12th...? Y-You don't mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">...That's right, amigo. At the same time that a cheap little urn was being stolen... ...the CEO of KB Security was being murdered.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-So then... What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Oh come on. You've figured it out already, haven't you amigo? Or... Have you already forgotten about that piece of info I helped you out with today?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Helped me out"? What!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">On October 12th, at 1 o'clock in the morning... Ron DeLite was in the CEO's office... ...The scene of the murder. After getting that blackmail letter, he must have been imbrued with utter rage.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-What are you saying!? Imbrued with rage...?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Come on! Don't tell me you didn't know it! Ron DeLite was once an employee of KB Security... He was a professional security guard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>An employee of KB Security!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">It looks like the alibi that saved him from being convicted as a thief... ...is going to be the noose that gets him hanged. Kind of an "anti-alibi".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No way...</line>
<line speaker="Godot">He can't be the thief because he was at the murder scene when the murder occurred!</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">N-No! Th-That's a lie! It can't be true!</line>
<line speaker="Ron">Oh! Ohhhh! B-But I... I am a thief I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">Ron DeLite. You're going back to prison again. This time the charge is much more serious. This time you'll be tried for murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What!? This can't... This is impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I'm looking forward to another exciting showdown, Mr. Trite!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Godot">You and I aren't through with each other yet. Surely you won't back down from a challenge! You've never been a coward!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! Is there something personal between you two...?</line>
<line speaker="Godot">I've returned from the depths of Hell to do battle with you. ...At least let me have some fun while I'm here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This guy... Who the heck is he!? He may be quiet... But he's the most dangerous enemy I've ever faced...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Godot">Well then... Time to say goodbye to Mr. DeLite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick...! How could this be happening?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right in front of our every eyes, our client has been arrested for murder. And the one who established his presence at the scene... was me.</line>
<line speaker="Desirée">EEEEEYYYAAAAHHH! R-RONNNIEEEEEEEE!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Arrested for murder on the very same day he's declared innocent of larceny... What the heck's going to happen next!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't sound very sure, Mr. Wright. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This evidence clearly reveals the contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are the evidence and the statement just now related?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They aren't, are they...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Wright, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness's statement is clearly faulty, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry, but I can see nothing faulty. Unfortunately, I will have to penalize you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh, I must be on the wrong track...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! This court sees no reason to further prolong the trial. Nor is there any need for more time to decide the case against the defendant. This case is extremely clear. I see no room for mis-interpretation of the facts. This court finds the defendant, Ron DeLite...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accused will surrender to the court immediately... ...to be held pending trial at a higher court within a month from today's date. That is all. This court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>