<xml>
<title>The Adventure of the Clouded Kokoro</title>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">These are the Scales of Justice. They're a symbol of the defence, aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's right. The scales are a symbol of fairness, to show that all are treated equally in the eyes of the law. And they're a warning to those who enter the courtroom without an impartial mind. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But if they're the mark of the defence... ...it would be more auspicious if they were weighing more heavily on the 'not guilty' side, I think. </line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Very impartial, I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The lawyer's name is embroidered on the inside here, look. 'Kazuma Asogi'... This was his band, of course. </line>
<line speaker="Susato">He had his heart set on this study tour in Great Britain. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm sure he would have found the truth he longed for here. <thought>...But he lost his life before he even had the chance to see the place.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I have such a strong sense of his hopes and dreams when I look at this armband, though.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Did you sleep last night, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No...not at all.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was an enormous hotel, wasn't it? The rooms were so luxurious! I felt like we were staying in a palace! And with all the gas lights twinkling, it was brighter than day even in the middle of the night!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What about the enormous beds? After my time on the SS Burya, I wasn't going to waste a single inch of that space. I spent the entire night rolling from one side of the mattress to the other.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes, it really was the sort of night you can only dream of normally. Except... ...when I learnt that we owed three pounds for the rooms, that dream quickly turned into a nightmare.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oops! ...Sorry about that. The building was so impressive, and the entrance so inviting, I just...wandered in without thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">In a lodging house in Japan, that sum of money would put a roof over your head for a whole year. I did try, but...I'm afraid I couldn't help my tears when we were presented with the bill.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... I really am sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, never mind. We must find some more affordable lodgings straight away, though. If we're not careful, our entire stipend will be used up in ten days or less.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... London is a scary place...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Yes! Um...we...erm... Well!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Good morning to you, Lord Chief Justice. We have come to report on the outcome of the trial at the Old Bailey yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Susato-san is amazing. She doesn't bat an eyelid, even in the presence of the imposing Lord Stronghart.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Yes, I believe you had a very comprehensive initiation into British courtroom practices.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes! It was very...eye-opening, thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And...in accordance with your instructions, Lord Stronghart... ...Mr Naruhodo performed his duty to the end.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Yes...I've already been apprised of events. You conducted a remarkable defence. ...You may consider the test passed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">No longer are you a student from the Empire of Japan... You may henceforth claim to be...a fully fledged lawyer! My country is delighted to welcome young talent from such a remote Eastern land.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...thank you very much! <thought>So...I'm a lawyer now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Now, in view of your new appointment, I have a fresh case in mind for you. I'd like you to take it on at once. ...I trust that won't be a problem?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Another case? Already?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Nothing trains a lawyer better than practical experience. ...I'm sure I don't sense dissatisfaction, do I?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... It's just that yesterday's trial ended...unusually. I haven't quite come to terms with it.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">What's to come to terms with? The man was cleared. ...What more were you hoping for?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The culpability of the defendant has not, at the present time, been established by this court. Consequently... ...the jury will not be required to proffer judgement.</line>
<line speaker="McGilded">Well, Lord van Zieks...it's been a pleasure, so it has. And as for you, my dear fella...I couldn't have asked for a better defence!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I just can't help wondering... if Mr McGilded really was innocent?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's just that I never managed to ascertain the truth. And then the trial ended.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">......... Well, you needn't let it trouble you for a second longer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What do you mean, Lord Stronghart?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Magnus McGilded passed away. Immediately following the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! Mr... Mr McGilded is... ...dead?!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I have nineteen minutes and forty-one seconds until my next engagement. ...Time enough to talk.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just look at all the knotty books packed together on these shelves! They go from floor to ceiling!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And they're all books that you couldn't hope to come by in Japan. It's like a dream!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...a very bad dream.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">They're not all about British law, either. There are books about the judicial systems of other Western nations. France, Germany, Spain, Holland...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What about Russia?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Why do you ask?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I was wondering about asking the Lord Chief Justice how you say 'wardrobe' in Russian. What do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I think, perhaps, it's a thought best abandoned.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at these menacing metal giants facing each other across the room!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I believe they're... Yes, they're suits of armour.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, right... I thought maybe they were like the lion-dogs we have in Japan guarding shrine gates.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, not at all. In fact, in Europe, suits of armour like these are always possessed by evil spirits, you know. And they roam around in the middle of the night.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? ...Is there nothing you don't know, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">This book tells me everything I need to know about everything. If you're ever unsure, just ask!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Where did she get that incredible tome?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is this...some kind of clock?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Actually, I, I think we might be INSIDE some sort of giant clock. But those gears are larger than anything you'd find on a steam locomotive, even!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's...eerie. Do you think clocks are some sort of hobby of his? The Lord Chief Justice, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, boys do enjoy fiddling around with machines, don't they?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm not sure you could 'fiddle' with cogs that size! And I'm certain you couldn't call him a 'boy'! <thought>Still, it's amazing how little noise the cogs make, considering how large they are. There's actually something quite soothing about their precise rhythm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">This must be the Lord Chief Justice's desk. I believe it's made of marble.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It looks more like an over-the-top tombstone that's toppled over to me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think that's your fanciful imagination at work again, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It feels like everything that's normally made of wood and paper at home... ...is made of bricks and stone here.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I know. That's why this place feels so overbearing, I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't understand! What happened?! How can he be dead?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">After the trial concluded yesterday, there was a great commotion in the Old Bailey. As you'll presumably recall, an omnibus had been wheeled into the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, of course. That was the scene of the crime which Mr McGilded had been accused of.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Precisely. Well, while the bailiff's attention was diverted by some other matter, the omnibus went up in flames.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">How could such a thing have happened?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">That is being investigated as we speak. But already... ...the police have identified a corpse found inside the charred shell of the carriage as that of McGilded.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's awful!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">The man must have slipped inside whilst the bailiff's attention was elsewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...That bailiff really needs to pay more attention.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">And how could THAT have happened?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">That is also being investigated as we speak.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Thinking back now... ...immediately after the trial, Mr McGilded did mention going back into the courtroom to look at the omnibus.</line>
<line speaker="McGilded">Well, I must be makin' tracks now. 'Tis time for the inspection.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry? What inspection? </line>
<line speaker="McGilded">They're goin' to examine the omnibus again, so I'm told. I asked if I could be present for it meself.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">An inspection of the omnibus? Not to my knowledge. I don't believe Scotland Yard had any intention of re-examining the carriage.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But... Then who was Mr McGilded talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Never mind that now. The Yard is making a thorough investigation. This matter is no longer any concern of yours. Leave it to the police.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Poor Mr McGilded...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">So...how did you find your first taste of our country's supreme court?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Well, um...I don't know... I mean! It was...wow!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Mr Naruhodo means that the whole experience was steeped in the solemnity of Great Britain's long history. It's really a world apart from our own judicial system in Japan, which is only a few short decades old.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Wow, Susato-san has such a way with words.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">...And you seem to have a way of failing to find the right ones.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">The judicial system here is the most advanced in the world. ...Learn all you can.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>The most advanced in the world, is it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">It was fortunate... ...that your very first trial was a simple affair.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Simple? That was simple?!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">As I believe I mentioned yesterday morning...it was a trial you couldn't lose.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I don't mean to be contrary, Lord Stronghart, but... the case was anything but simple!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The circumstances of the case were so incriminating, I was stunned when I first heard them. In fact, I'm still finding it hard to believe that we managed to get a favourable verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">......... Heh heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is, is something funny?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">No no, my apologies. However, the fact is that you did receive the not guilty verdict you set out to achieve.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">And that can only be attributed to exceptional talent... wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I, I don't know about that...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">......... Well, never mind. You exceeded my expectations, I freely admit. ...That much at least is an undeniable truth. Which is precisely why I have prepared the new case for you that I mentioned before.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What's going on? What was he going to say before?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Could you perhaps give us some more details about the new case you mentioned?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Don't tell me, it's a murder and the trial starts in ten minutes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Don't worry, it's nothing so alarming or quite so urgent as your last assignment. In fact, this case is completely different.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, I see. <thought>Did, did he just read my mind?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">That is to say, no one has died...as yet. And the trial will not be today. There is plenty of time to research the case thoroughly. ...Twenty-three hours, forty-three minutes and nineteen seconds to be precise.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah... <thought>So the trial's tomorrow then.</thought> .........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Is everything alright?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes. I'm just a little confused, that's all. Yesterday's trial was... Well, it's left me wondering if I'm really cut out for being a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I don't know if I could face standing in that courtroom again after Mr McGilded's trial.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Ah yes, I nearly forgot... There is one similarity with yesterday's case. Once again, there is currently no one to advocate for the defence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">If the situation remains unchanged, the trial will start tomorrow with the defendant unrepresented. And if that happens, I need not remind you of the inevitable outcome.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The most terrible end awaits the defendant...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Yes...that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... <thought>Here we go again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord Stronghart, may I show you this?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">To accept this item, issue a receipt, examine it thoroughly and make a formal statement of my findings... ...would require something in the region of twenty-four seconds of my time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Does the item warrant twenty-four seconds of my time, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Let's leave it for now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Last time he mentioned the twenty-three hours, he said there was plenty of time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">And one more thing...Mr Naruhodo... There is something I should like to ask you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Um...what's that?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Yesterday, you remarked upon something... That you intend to see through the will of your late compatriot, Mr Asogi.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I would be interested to hear what exactly you mean by that... ...inside thirty-four seconds.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, well, erm... Kazuma always used to say, you see... ...that he wanted to learn how the greatest justice system in the world worked so he could change ours in Japan. Now that he's gone, I'd like to work towards that myself. ...And...there's another thing...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">'Another thing'? Continue...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">On the way here, on the steamship, he said something to me...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">'Something very important'? And what, exactly, would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He...never had a chance to tell me. I suppose he would have done...if he'd ever made it to Great Britain.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...You're out of time. Well, thank you for an enlightening discussion.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! What's all this about?! Mr Asogi never once mentioned anything of the sort to me!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I urge you both to focus your attentions on the matter at hand. I've taken the liberty of summoning the police inspector in charge of the case. He'll be able to apprise you of the details.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>How long has he been there?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">So...I wish you the best of luck...and bid you farewell.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... 'There's something very important that I have to do.' Kazuma-sama... What did you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I wish I knew. But honestly, he never told me. ...Anyway, we had better talk to the detective, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, you're right!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I hope I'm just imagining it, but I wouldn't say he looks pleased to see us at all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Um, could we trouble you?</line>
<line speaker="???">What do you think?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh! Erm... Um... Lovely weather, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="???">What's the weather got to do with anythin'?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="???">Listen to me, you young Japanese upstart! Some frippery about the weather doesn't get every English gent eatin' out of your hand, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... But Susato-san told me it was foolproof...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">I'm a busy man. A very busy man! There's a crime scene to investigate, but I'm here havin' to give the likes of you a talkin' to!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh... I'm ever so sorry...</line>
<line speaker="???">Can you imagine what the other officers there will be sayin'? Hm? 'Haven't seen Gregson anywhere, have you?' 'No, he's too busy with the bigwigs these days.' And all because of some bumpkin who's here on a jaunt from a country I've never even heard of! Hear that rippin' sound? That's my reputation at the Yard goin' to tatters!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>There's no need to rip us apart as well...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I don't believe we've been introduced. This is Mr Ryunosuke Naruhodo, a defence lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="???">...Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance. I'm Mr Naruhodo's judicial assistant, Su-</line>
<line speaker="???">...Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's lovely weather we're having today, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="???">......... It is unseasonably fine, I grant you. London winters don't see a lot of sunshine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Unbelievable! How did she pull that off?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">So... Ahem! Lord Stronghart has asked me to fill you in on the case.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">The name's Tobias Gregson. Inspector Gregson to you. I'm from Scotland Yard.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gregson?! ...Um, Inspector...Gregson...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What's the matter with Susato-san? Does this detective's name mean something to her?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Inspector...are you perhaps... ...THE Inspector Gregson?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're acting like you know this man, Miss Susato. But he's a London detective.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, I do know him! Very well, in fact!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Very well?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! He features prominently in 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, in that publication. What's it called again? Randst Magazine?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's right. Inspector Gregson and Mr Sholmes enjoy a wonderful friendly rivalry!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? YOU rival the great Mr Sholmes? That's incredible!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Oh, um...well, I don't know about that... Mr Sholmes isn't a professional like myself, of course. But he does come up with the goods from time to time.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes is equally complimentary about you, Inspector, isn't he? You've earnt his highest praise! 'Gregson is the pick of a bad lot of all the Scotland Yarders!' Those were his own words!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That's his highest praise?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, Mr Sholmes isn't particularly known for giving compliments, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">That he is not! And thanks to that magazine, my name's known all over London town now!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's great, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Hmph. I have to admit that to start with I was a little... well, flattered by all the attention. Everyone wanted to shake my hand, and my reputation at the Yard went through the roof.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well that's wonderful!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">No it is NOT! There's nothin' more sinister than the man on the street! People are always lookin' at me now. They're whisperin' rumours about me under their breath, I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Rumours?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Are, are you quite sure?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">'He's changed since he started appearin' in those stories... The fame's gone to his head.' Stuff like that.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gosh, do you really think people are saying such mean-spirited things about you?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">...Like I said, they whisper! So I can't catch exactly what they're sayin'. But I know what folk are like. I'm sure that's what they're sayin'! As sure as eggs is eggs!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I get the feeling this detective could be very hard work...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... Perhaps a sudden rise to fame does change people...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So, um...about the case that the Lord Chief Justice mentioned before...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Nothin' to tell, really. As far as we're concerned at the Yard, it couldn't be simpler.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear. That probably means... ...that as far as we're concerned as lawyers, it couldn't be more complicated.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I wish you were wrong about that, but I have a nasty feeling you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">A young woman was walkin' along the pavement on Briar Road when she was stabbed from behind. Fortunately, it wasn't fatal, but she's still laid up in hospital, unconscious.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's despicable! What sort of coward would attack the poor woman from behind!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I suppose you would have finished whoever it was off with a Susato Takedown, would you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That is neither here nor there, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Brace yourself, Ryunosuke! You've angered her now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Anyway, after somethin' of a whirlwind investigation, the criminal was arrested. He barely had time for a cup of tea after the incident took place, to be honest.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...there must have been something left at the scene that led you directly to the culprit?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Or perhaps a reliable witness who recognised the person in question?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Let me stop you right there. ...You're wastin' your time on this one.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">There's nothin' you can do. There's no way to help the bloke now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why ever not?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Simple... The prosecutor that's been assigned to the trial tomorrow...is Lord Barok van Zieks.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Sounds like you've heard of him then.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes, we are very familiar with Lord van Zieks. Believed to be the harbinger of death itself...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The Reaper of the Bailey...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord Barok van Zieks... <thought>...who we faced in court only yesterday.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr McGilded told us about him before the trial, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This Reaper of the Bailey nickname... I suppose he's earnt that because every defendant he advocates against is found guilty, is that it?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, if that's the case, we should inform you, Inspector... ...that in yesterday's trial against Lord van Zieks... Mr Naruhodo secured a verdict of not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Haah... And what of it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Well, um, I think... ...that means that even against the Reaper of the Bailey, it's not impossible to save the defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">No, you really don't have a clue, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">What happened to that bloke in the end, eh? He's dead.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Magnus McGilded came a cropper in that omnibus when it went up in flames. So you can't rightly say you saved the defendant, can you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What...what are you saying?!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Look, if van Zieks could get the dirt to stick on everyone, he'd be a miracle-worker. But that's not how it goes. He doesn't work miracles; he works magic...black magic. I'd have a good, long think about that, if I were you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Are we really supposed to believe that?</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Gregson">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was Briar Road, you said, didn't you? Where the incident took place.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">That's correct, ma'am. And if you head over to the holding cells you can meet the criminal himself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You've branded him a criminal already?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">He's as good as. Shakin' like a leaf in his cell, he is. ...It'll give you a chuckle if nothin' else. He's inmate fifty-three. Speak to the jailer and he'll show you the way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Inmate fifty-three... Thank you. ......... <thought>...So there's no helping anyone against the Reaper of the Bailey, they say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Is something troubling you, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">..........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">To tell the truth, when I recall the trial yesterday, I can't stop myself from shaking. The idea of facing the Reaper in court again is... Well, if you think it's too much for you, there's no shame in turning the case down. That takes courage, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... But if the man they've arrested is innocent...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You could well imagine he would be shaking like a leaf in his cell. And I for one wouldn't find the sight of that funny.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If I'm honest, I'm still reeling from the shock of yesterday's events myself. And I'm really not sure if I'll be able to help this man, whoever he is. But I'd like to try. So I think I'm going to make some enquiries. ...Will you help?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you... So then...shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So these are British prison cells...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, they're ghastly. It feels just like a dungeon.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. And having experienced it in Japan myself... ...I can assure you that our wooden cells feel a lot cosier than these cold, stone walls.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, don't, Mr Naruhodo! You're making it seem worse!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Apparently, our client is in this cell here. But it's so dark at the back there, I can't make him out. I wonder what he's like...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Inmate fifty-three! Your legal representative is 'ere to see you! Stop 'iding at the back of the cell and show your face at once!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Mr Naruhodo, what...? What do you think is going on here?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I have no idea. But I wasn't just hearing things, was I? That tirade of complaints was in Japanese!</line>
<line speaker="???">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm, excuse me, but who-</line>
<line speaker="???">Shh! Quiet! ......... They're all around. Hiding. I know they are! They're watching...listening...even now... I... I can sense it! .........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...right... So, could I ask you, who exactly-</line>
<line speaker="???">There you are! You've come to curse me, haven't you? Don't try to hide it! You're a ghost!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A ghost?!</line>
<line speaker="???">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... We mean you no harm, prisoner-san. Are you... ...Japanese, by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="???">......... This is... This is... BEYOND MY WILDEST DREAMS!!! Forgive me for that outburst before. I'm so sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, it's...fine. We were just a little surprised, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="???">Imagine it! It's been twelve long months since I left my hometown! And here I am, in a frightful fix in a foreign land! So hearing the sweet, sentimental tones of a compatriot's voice here in this damp, dark hellhole was a...a...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Who could have guessed that this new client Lord Stronghart assigned to us... ...would turn out to be a fellow Japanese?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Ah... ...what compassion my fellow countrymen show! To dispatch a first-class lawyer all the way from Japan to defend a mere foreign student!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A, a first-class lawyer? <thought>Oh dear, I think there's been something of a misunderstanding here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I wonder... Would you be so kind as to tell us what's happened? Why you've been detained as a suspect, for example.</line>
<line speaker="???">Yes... Yes! I can! I will!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm not quite sure I understand what he means, but...he seems happy!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, he does... <thought>I just hope he actually has a good reason to be...</thought> Thank you for your cooperation. I am a lawyer, as you said. My name is Ryunosuke Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And I am Naruhodo-san's judicial assistant, Susato Mikotoba.</line>
<line speaker="???">I am... ...a visiting student, sent here by our government.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Notably, Notoriously Named Natsume! ...Soseki Natsume.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Soseki Natsume...san? What an unusual name.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Call me Soseki, please. I'm a poet, you see. A writer of haiku. It's something of a nom de plume.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A nom de plume? You mean, an alias?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's right, Naruhodo-san.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">No no NO! Don't be so prosaic! It's MUCH MORE REFINED than that!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...And haiku? That really reminds me of home.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Did I hear you say that you were a visiting student, sent over here by the government?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Yes yes, that's right. A year ago, I was told to go and study English. First I had to suffer that misery, and now this! It's beyond the pale!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Suffer that misery'? Did you not want to study here?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">No! I mean, I've had an interest in Great Britain for some years, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">But! Just because the government tells you to do something, does it mean you CAN do it? No!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">If they'd told me to study English literature, THAT I could have understood. That's my field. But no, they told me to study the English language!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Only the other day, I was told to send a report about my first year here. I tendered a blank piece of paper.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...You must be a man of great standing.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh yes! ...So I'm often told.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And often like to be told, it seems...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Could you perhaps tells us exactly why you've been arrested, Soseki-san?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I didn't do it! I didn't commit that atrocious murder!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Murder?!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh! No... No no, it's all alright. The woman didn't actually die, did she? But she was stabbed! With a knife! Right before my eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Before your eyes'? You mean, you saw the attacker?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... I didn't see anyone.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">If I'd seen the person who did it...do you think I'd be locked up in here?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear, it seems this case is becoming rather complicated.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Why me? WHY ME?! ...Why did that silly woman have to be stabbed in front of ME?! It's the curse! The curse of London! It's...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So Soseki-san was there at the scene, but he didn't see the attacker...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's vital that we find out more about the case!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">It was an accursed evening, just after the snow had started to clear and heavy with fog. I'd been to the bookshop to buy some books, and I was on my way back to my accursed lodgings.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Sure the bookshop wasn't accursed, too?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">As I was walking along that accursed pavement, I could make out the sole silhouette of another ahead of me. A woman, wearing a green overcoat, she was. And just as I went to overtake her... ...she suddenly let out a little scream, and collapsed onto the cold, hard slabs of stone at my feet!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">How terrible!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I called out to the woman, but...she didn't move! It, it was like a...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Slight exaggeration there, perhaps...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I was terrified! I had to get away from there! So I ran! As fast as my legs would carry me back to my accursed lodgings!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's...not good.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">They'll, they'll say it was shameful, I know. To run away like that...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Tell me, Soseki-san, was the victim an acquaintance of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Don't be ridiculous! Do you think I know nay of these fair-haired English?! And a young woman at that! I'm diffident! Shy! Timid! Unsure! I can't TALK to people!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I...I see... <thought>A young woman, unknown to Soseki-san...</thought> And at the time it happened... ...who else did you see nearby? Did anybody pass you?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... Regrettably... ...apart from myself and the woman...I didn't see a soul.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No one?! <thought>Oh great...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">So the victim was unknown to you, and there was nobody else on the street at the time... That creates something of a conundrum, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm? <thought>What conundrum?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean, Susato-san? What's the conundrum?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, if what Soseki-san has just told us is true, there's something I can't explain. He says that he didn't know the victim, and that there was no one else at the scene. Then he apparently fled without having been seen.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I did, I did!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...But if that's the case... ...surely this man has to be the culprit?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">AAAAAARGH! You... What did you just say?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Nothing! I, I didn't say anything! <thought>Oops. Perhaps I thought that a little 'loudly'...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Actually, that's not what was troubling me. What I was thinking was, how did Soseki-san actually come to be arrested?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">He didn't touch the victim, and there was nobody at the scene to see him. So how did the police ever discover that he was there in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes! <thought>She's right!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... It......... It was him... That accursed 'great detective'... He led the police to me! Of all the bad luck!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Accursed...'great detective'...? <thought>Could it be...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I shall never forget that man's name as long as I live! With his haughty laugh and his self-proclaimed greatness!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I... I knew it!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr... Mr Sholmes?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well, I didn't expect to hear that name from this man's lips, that's for sure.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">It was the morning after that nightmare had unfolded on the pavement before me. I was gnawing on a sliver of hard cheese when some men suddenly burst in through the door. They started shouting at me! 'This is the police! Put the weapon down!' Yes, it was a thin sliver, and yes it was hard... But I wasn't eating a weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You...clearly had a trying morning yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">And there he was, in the middle of all the policemen, grinning like a Cheshire cat! That...Herr Lock Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's, it's actually just 'Herlock Sholmes'. He's English.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I've since found out that he's a famous name in detection here in London.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, the great detective is really very well known.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">And his overly sharp mind managed to deduce my whereabouts apparently. He thinks I'm the knife-wielding madman! Me?! This weak, stooped kitten of a man!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I wonder what great deduction process led him to his conclusion this time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Do you mean to say... ...that Mr Sholmes's deduction was the only reason the police arrested you? That would be really most unreasonable!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... Well, um...the thing is... I was...I was thrown into a panic when they barged their way in.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Of course you were! That's only natural.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I was terrified and trembling. And they kept throwing question after question at me. In impossible English!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...we are in England. You can't really blame them for questioning you in English.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Good point, good point. But my mind went blank. I, I knew I had to answer, but I didn't know what to say. So I just kept repeating things like, 'Yes, I do!' and 'I'm fine!' The next thing I knew, I was in manacles. And before I knew it, I was thrown in here.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear. I'm afraid...that's hardly surprising.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>'I'm fine'? He's not fine now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Yes! YES! The symbol of one of our great empire's first-rate lawyers! Which means! Of course! You'll stand by my side! You'll defend me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh... No, sorry, that wasn't why I was showing it to you.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... THEN WHY ELSE WOULD YOU SHOW ME THAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Oops. In hindsight, that probably wasn't the best idea.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Oh, you can just call me Naruhodo. And when we're speaking English, a simple 'Mister' is more than enough.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh. Yes. Um... Alright. Yes... They've, they've really got to me. This country is poisoning my mind! ......... But please, I beg you to defend me in court tomorrow. You can tell them what really happened. You'll do it...won't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, erm...</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Why?! WHY?! Why is it so hard to say 'yes' to me?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, the thing is...I'm just a student like yourself. On a study tour.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">A, a student...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I have defended a case in the Old Bailey. Only the one, though. But at this moment in time, I really don't know what I'm supposed to believe in. I'm...confused about what justice in this country even means.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Naruhodo-san...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm not even the foreign student who was supposed to be here. I'm...a sort of locum lawyer, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">But! But that armband! That's the mark of a defence lawyer from our great empire!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's a keepsake from the man who should have been here. ...He was my best friend.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">A, a keepsake? ......... I know exactly what they're saying about me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh... Who do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">The lawyers. All the British defence lawyers. They won't defend me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Goodness! Why...why do say that?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">For the same reason as you noted before. When it happened... ...there was only the victim and myself around. And I ran away from the scene of the crime. I'm not a fool. I know it looks as though I must be the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It must be very hard for you, Soseki-san...</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">And anyway, I'm a student from overseas. I'm just a foreign nobody to them. Someone not to be trusted. I heard them openly laughing about me before. In my earshot, without any compunction at all. 'Any trial for this man would be a waste of time,' they said. And, 'Of course the foreigner did it!' They even had the gall to say, 'The man doesn't understand half of what's being said anyway!'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's awful...!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">They're wrong! I've studied more English than half of the policemen out there on the streets! I've travelled halfway around the world to learn about these people's country and its great history! But no one here wants to listen to a man with a strange accent. They all hate me! So...at the very least... ...I'd like to entrust my fate to someone who can listen to me, in my native tongue.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">You could do it. ...Couldn't you? When I look into your eyes, I can see it. I can see what you've been through.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Soseki-san, it's just that... ......... Give me a little time, please.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'll do what I can, for the time being.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We shall investigate the case as thoroughly as possible. If we can find some clues, it will give us a much better chance, I'm sure!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... Oh yes! Yes! Thank you! I'll be here! All alone! Waiting for you...Locum Student Mr Naruhodo Esquire!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We should be going then, Naruhodo-san. We have a case to prepare for!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So this is where it happened. Briar Road...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah! Look, Mr Naruhodo! Look at that regulation metal helmet! It's unmistakable! The men of Scotland Yard are here! They're investigating as we speak!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That...is their job, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But Mr Naruhodo! To see one with my own eyes! They're often depicted in 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes' but I never dreamt I'd ever come this close... ...to a real bobby's helmet!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? The, the helmet?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Hee hee! Of course! ...I have to try one on one day!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I...hope your hatty dream comes true. Hm, I don't see Inspector Gregson anywhere. Shall we see if we can sneak past and investigate the scene of the stabbing?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Why should we sneak?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't want to upset one of those bobbies and be butted on the head by one of those metal helmets. My skull would crack in two, I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no, an English bobby would never do such a thing! This is a land of gentlemen, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So this is where it happened. Briar Road...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah! Look, Mr Naruhodo! Look at that regulation metal helmet! It's unmistakable! The men of Scotland Yard are here! They're investigating as we speak!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That...is their job, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But Mr Naruhodo! To see one with my own eyes! They're often depicted in 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes' but I never dreamt I'd ever come this close... ...to a real bobby's helmet!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? The, the helmet?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Hee hee! Of course! ...I have to try one on one day!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I...hope your hatty dream comes true.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's a rather typical old brick building, isn't it? I'm sure it has a long and interesting history.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, time certainly seems to have taken its toll on the place. It's crooked and sagging all over. <thought>In fact, it looks in decidedly worse shape than the other houses around here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">We must find some cheap lodgings ourselves as soon as possible.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, you're right. Cheap, but ideally with reasonably level floors...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, look at the windows of that building there.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Are you sure they're windows...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, but they're all filled in with bricks!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! You're right! ...I wonder why. Perhaps it's an empty property where nobody lives at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's smoke coming from the chimneys, though.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear, everything still feels very foreign. There's so much we have to learn about this place.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! A British bicycle, look! Although the wheel is so misshapen, I'm sure it couldn't possibly be ridden any more.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Someone must have been doing some breakneck cycling.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It seems bicycles have become extremely popular in London recently. There's even a movement to change women's dress to allow them to ride as well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The bicycle fad won't last. I don't see why anyone would want to ride something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Goodness! Do you dislike bicycles?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No! Not at all! I mean, it's not that I dislike them exactly. It's just that any occupation that involves taking both your feet off firm ground seems...reckless. If you'd ever tried walking on stilts and fallen into a river, I know you'd agree with me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...We'll have to hire a bicycle sometime. You can sit behind me while I ride you around.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The clouds look so big and heavy in the sky, don't they? And with the dense fog as well, everything looks hazy.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, it is known as foggy London town.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can just make out some sort of spire through the fog. It looks like it's still being built, though.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah-ha! Yes! That must be the Crystal Tower, being built for the Great Exhibition that's to open in six months' time. Apparently it's going to be very striking. Glazed on all sides, and the symbolic centrepiece of the exhibition!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's to be the largest exposition in history, is it? <thought>I can't even begin to imagine it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you see all the black smoke rising from the chimneys over there?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It says here that in Great Britain, many people heat their homes in winter using coal.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The only chimneys I really remember seeing in Japan were on top of the bathhouse. Do you think some of those houses could be on fire?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Not at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, even so... ...that much thick smoke billowing up to the heavens is surely going to turn the whole sky black sooner or later.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gosh...you may be right about that...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There are piles of snow on the pavement here and there, but the road itself is covered in carriage tracks.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It seems carriages often travel down Briar Road. It soon disperses all the snow.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I slipped over when I was walking down the pavement earlier. It seems like it would be far safer to walk on the road instead.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, but you're rather small, Mr Naruhodo. And dressed all in black. I worry coachmen might not see you, and you could be flattened by horses.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Well, thank you for the 'rather small' concern.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's one of the officers from Scotland Yard. The police are making sure the crime scene is undisturbed. I have a feeling that if we wander too close, we'll be clapped in irons.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think perhaps you're being a little overcautious. We've done nothing wrong, so we have no cause for concern.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh no, I'm not getting caught out again. Twice is enough! Twice I've found myself in handcuffs despite not knowing a thing about what was going on.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, you've had some dreadful experiences... I'm sure that it's that wide-eyed look of panic you're so prone to. It does you no favours at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This patch of pavement must be where the incident occurred.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes. It's a very wide, open space, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's true. I can't see anywhere an attacker could have been hiding.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bobby">Oi! What are you foreigners doin' 'ere?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Um...erm...we, um... J-Just investigating the scene, Officer!</line>
<line speaker="Bobby">Conspirin' with that moustached fella from Japan, are ya?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Conspiring?!</line>
<line speaker="Bobby">Come 'ere to destroy evidence, 'ave ya? Get out of 'ere before I give you an 'idin'! Go on!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...He shooed us away like rats.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, we should give him a wide berth, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What a disappointing experience...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Hee hee! What a delightful snowman!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I didn't realise the English had a tradition of making snowmen as well. It looks a little creepy, though.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, it has a scarf, look!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You'd need one if you were out in this freezing cold all the time. I wish I had one.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm afraid our budget is somewhat frozen at the moment, too. We certainly can't afford a scarf.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Surely the snowman here wouldn't miss his...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">But the person who made the snowman certainly would.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I know. You're right. Anyway... ...even if I borrowed it, it wouldn't do much to warm my neck, would it? It's covered in snow.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! That's a Scotland Yard carriage! They use vehicles like that to rush to crime scenes and cart away criminals!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're very well informed, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's long been a dream of mine to ride one of those through the streets of London!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, just pick up a stone and throw it through one of the windows, then.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...But that would mean being arrested in order to ride it... ...wouldn't it? Still, if it's the only way... Help me find a good stone!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no no! I wasn't serious!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">What's the Japanese delegation doin' here?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Inspector Gregson!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">This isn't on the tourist trail, as I'm fairly sure you're well aware.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! Of course! We're here to investigate.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">So you've been to the holdin' cells, then? What d'you make of the criminal?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">He's not a 'criminal' as you put it, Inspector. He's a suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Hmph. We'll see about that. You Japanese like to stick together, I s'pose. Well, do what you will. It doesn't bother me. The bloke's in court tomorrow whatever happens. And the verdict's a foregone conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh...the stone-cold air of rejection...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Take heart! London at this time of year is full of stone-cold air!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That...makes it worse somehow...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Tell me about Scotland Yard, Inspector! Ever since I read about it in 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes', I've been fascinated by the place!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">The Yard...is the most sophisticated policin' organisation you'll find anywhere in the world, ma'am.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, and you know I've always dreamt of wearing a real bobby's helmet!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It does make them look the part. Seeing that policeman there with his helmet on... ...you certainly get the sense that this is a man who will take no nonsense in his duty of protecting the city.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes! Doesn't he look wonderful?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Bein' a London bobby is hard going, I can tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, really?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">First thing in the mornin', you know what he does? Goes round and rouses all the labourers on his beat so they can get off to work.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? He wakes people up?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yup. Raps on their windows with a long pole. Did it myself, goin' back a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I had no idea...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">The bobby works for the people of the town. It's just another one of his duties. After that, he starts tirelessly patrolling the streets all day long. He has to cover twenty miles a day. That's the regulation distance.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't really imagine how far that is, but it sounds like a long way.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Let me see... Twenty miles... That's approximately the distance from Tokyo to Yokohama.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">On foot?! That's...that's definitely taking things a step too far!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">And when it gets dark, of course, he has the important job of lightin' all the gas street lamps.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my... </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And I suppose in between all of those duties, bobbies are expected to investigate cases as well?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And chase after criminals trying to evade the law!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I'm not sure you could call it 'in between' exactly. More 'alongside'. But yes... ...they're expected to handle those jobs as well. We do have men keelin' over from time to time, I admit.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... I'd always dreamt of wearing one of those helmets, as I said. But it's with a heavy heart, that I shall have to relinquish that dream to you, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Your heavy heart will be my heavy head if you do.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">It happened at around five in the evenin', two days ago. Just there, on that open bit of pavement. The victim - a young woman - was stabbed with a blade from behind.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is it right that the lady is still unconscious now? You mentioned that she's being treated in hospital.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">...I never said she was a 'lady'. Truth is, unless she comes round pretty smartish, we won't be able to find out much about her at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I suppose that means they haven't been able to take a statement from her, of course...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Here's a map of the local area I happen to have on me. You can take it if you want.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">It's Yard policy to give lawyers defendin' suspects the odd bit of information to go on.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I haven't actually accepted the job yet, but still...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Thank you, Inspector! We gratefully accept!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Anyway... ...as far as we know, there was no one else on the scene other than the victim and your fellow countryman. So who did it, do you think? Not much of a head-scratcher, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I know Mr Natsume is also claiming not to have seen anyone else around, but-</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But just because he didn't see anyone... ...it doesn't mean we can be sure that nobody else was present!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I'm sorry to have to tell you, but we most certainly can be sure.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...How?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Because, ma'am... ...the precise moment of the stabbing didn't go unnoticed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It... What?!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">We have two very reliable witnesses no less!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">It was a typical foggy London day, and your client obviously didn't see them.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>There were witnesses now...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Who are these witnesses, Inspector?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">A fellow and his wife. And the man's one of the most reliable and respected citizens in all of London. He's a copper from Scotland Yard.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A, a policeman? <thought>That...might change things.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">And this policeman just happened to be there at the exact moment the woman was attacked?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Nothin' peculiar about that, ma'am. Part and parcel of bein' a bobby. Catchin' them bang in the act and all that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, do you think it might be possible... ...for us to ask that policeman a few questions?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Be my guest. You can ask him what you like...in court tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I've no doubt he'll be summoned as a witness. So, that'll give you something to look forward to!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's that then... He's got no intention of letting us meet the man beforehand, it seems.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">A policeman witnessed the incident... As your judicial assistant, I must warn you that this could make our job very difficult indeed!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes, as a non-judicial assistant, I could have warned me of that, too. Oh yes, one more thing, Inspector...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The person who led you to the suspect... I hear that was Mr Herlock Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">......... What are you bringin' him up for? .........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Was it something I said? The colour has drained from his cheeks...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">That twitchy Japanese bloke goes on trial tomorrow. Are you goin' to defend him or not?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, erm...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">......... Makes no difference to me, but I will just say this: No London lawyer worth his salt would touch that case with a barge pole.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Because the prosecution is being handled by the Reaper of the Bailey, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">There's no way to save the man now. It's a waste of time tryin'. It is all a bit strange, though...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">The Reaper... He hasn't appeared in court once for a good few years now.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, we did hear something to that effect.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">And the only people he usually bothers with are the real scum. The master criminals. The violent ones.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">M-Master criminals?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The, the violent ones?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">That's right. He hand picks his victims. Only deals with those guaranteed to go to the gallows for their sins.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But! Mr Natsume wouldn't hang for what he's accused of, surely?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">That's just my point, sunshine. Yes, the young woman was stabbed, but it didn't kill her. Couldn't even say the intent was there. So this isn't the sort of case I'd be expectin' the Reaper to want to sink his teeth into, for want of a better phrase.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, it's not exactly a minor infraction, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">...No, there's got to be more to it. Some reason he's takin' an interest...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Really? What sort of reason, Inspector?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">You think I can tell what's goin' on inside the head of that lord of darkness? You'll have to ask him yourself...at tomorrow's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Are we really going to have to face the Reaper again? The lord of darkness, as he put it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">......... Who did you hear that name from?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, well, um... It was Mr Natsume who mentioned it. He said that Mr Sholmes was with the police when they entered his lodgings.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm sure it was the result of one of Mr Sholmes's inspirational great deductions!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Fiddle-Faddle!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">The man's an amateur! And I'm gettin' sick and tired of him showin' his mug everywhere!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I don't know where he gets his information from, but he turns up at the scene of the crime... ...wanders around spoutin' incomprehensible rubbish, and before you know it... ...he claims to have solved the case!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes... He's quite...astounding, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">He, he is a great help to Scotland Yard though...isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Gibble-Gabble!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Ever seen this before?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, yes... That's Randst Magazine.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The wonderful publication in which 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes' appears!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yes, well, that 'wonderful' publication, as you put it, sees fit to include several of the Yard's detectives in its stories. And the so-called great detective makes a mockery of all of us! If you ask anyone at the Yard, it's a misadventure to be included in any Herlock Sholmes tale at all!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well...I suppose there is an element of that...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">We work our socks off, every one of us! Only to be frumped by the public thanks to that obnoxious detective! The man's as dangerous to us at Scotland Yard as he is to all our criminals!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That can't really be true, can it, Inspector?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Clearly the great detective and the police have a... complex relationship.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Inspector Gregson, could I show you this?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Am I supposed to know what that is? I've never seen that insignia before.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's worn by defence lawyers in the Empire of Japan. As a symbol of their profession.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">...In other words, it's a worthless trinket here in Great Britain.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh no! It's very important to me. It, it shows my spirit!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">An English gentleman keeps things like his spirit very much to himself, I'll have you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Don't give up, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's too late... He's crushed my spirit already.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you again for this.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Hmph. Don't mention it. I had someone at the Yard fish it out for me. But in the end, I didn't need it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Well, the case could hardly be simpler, could it? I don't need a map to work out what happened. You can throw it away when you're done with it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... Cold...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo, can I make a suggestion?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, it seems to me... ...that we MUST speak with him about this!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... By 'him', do you mean... ...Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! Mr Herlock Sholmes! Exactly!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Look at those shining eyes! You can't wait, can you?</thought> Well, Mr Natsume did blame Mr Sholmes for all of this, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, he did! He really did! Which makes him an involved party in the case. Are you just going to ignore that? ...I hope not! ...I assure you, it's not simply my selfish desire to meet with Mr Sholmes again!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The trouble is... ...we have no idea of the man's address, even. So how-</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's Baker Street!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">H-How do you know that?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's in the stories, of course! 221B Baker Street... The most famous address in the world!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...I see... Well, there's nothing to stop us from going, I suppose... <thought>We'd better try to find our way there before Susato-san gets any more excited and unpredictable...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Hurrah! I'll summon a carriage!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So, we're to have a reunion already... ...with the great detective, Mr Herlock Sholmes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">...It seems that we can't meet with Mr Natsume at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">He's being briefed about his appearance in court tomorrow, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I see. <thought>Yes, the trial is only a day away...</thought> Alright then, let's come back later.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I really hope he's not answering any more questions with inappropriate textbook answers like, 'Yes, I do!'</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you very much.</line>
<line speaker="Man">It's just up there, overlooking the street. Good day.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thanks again. This is it...the residence of Mr Herlock Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So this is where the great detective makes his living... <thought>It feels surreal to be here somehow...</thought> Is it as described in the stories, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...Susato-san?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Many, many famous cases have been solved here in this very room.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! I, I suppose they must have been, yes... <thought>I've never read the stories, so it's hard to get quite as excited about it as she seems to be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">The detective chases the villain relentlessly as he disappears into the fog down an unlit London street... Oh, the thrill of it! The romanticism! Can't you feel your heart thumping in your chest? Can't you, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! I, I suppose I can, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So, if you don't mind... ...I'll just stand here and soak up the atmosphere for a while longer. Please, don't mind me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah... <thought>She's obsessed... Well... ...it looks like our detective friend isn't home at present.</thought> Excuse me! Is anybody home?</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh! Do we have a visitor? Hello! Is it a big new case for Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm...hello. ......... Wait. Aren't you...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh! How rude of me! I'll go and make some tea at once!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'm sure it's the same girl...</thought> Miss Susato! Did you see the girl who was just here?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes... Isn't it truly extraordinary? To think that the King of Bohemia came to this very room to ask Mr Sholmes to take on his case...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The, the King of Bo-where-ia?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">King Wilhelm Gottsreich Sigismond von Ormstein, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Sorry, I'm drawing a blank. Forget 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes' for a moment, and look over there!</line>
<line speaker="???">The tea's brewed! And I have a freshly baked cake as well!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah! It's you!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I knew it. Susato-san recognises her, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Ah! There you are!And taking that with you as well! I was looking forward to the trial run of my experimental smoke grenade launcher! Oh, good day to you! I'm...well, the inventor, I suppose, of that machine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It's the girl who turned up at the end of Mr McGilded's trial in the defendants' antechamber.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">I've never met a lawyer from the Far East before! Poor you, having to get straight to work when you've only just arrived in London.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes, it was...challenging.</line>
<line speaker="???">Well, try this tea. It's my special blend, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...um, thank you. <thought>Is tea supposed to look that colour?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! What a fragrant yet mellow flavour!</line>
<line speaker="???">Hurray! It's a winner! I tried blending different leaves designed to alleviate fatigue, you see. You must be exhausted after your long voyage here. And you have another ticklish trial tomorrow! Oh, and you're to defend a Japanese man. I do wish you lots and lots of luck!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Did Mr Sholmes tell you about us, by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh! You know Hurley, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...'Hurley'? 'Mr Sholmes' to you, surely?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes was a fellow passenger on the boat that brought us to Great Britain, you see.</line>
<line speaker="???">Was he really? Well, I had no idea! I'm afraid Hurley's out on an errand again today, even though he's just returned from overseas.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Wait a minute... We met this girl for the first time ever yesterday after the trial. And only briefly at that. How on earth does she know so much about us?</thought> Did she...deduce...all those things, do you think...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And perhaps more to the point... ...why is she here in Mr Sholmes's suite?</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh! Silly me! I haven't introduced myself, have I?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It's a great pleasure to meet you both. My name is Iris Wilson. I live here together with Hurley.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, Iris, is it? What a lovely name!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, wait, this, this can't be... Did, did you... Did you say that your, your name is...'Wilson'?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What's the matter with Susato-san? Why is she so flustered all of a sudden?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, that's right! And what are your names?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, um...I'm Ryunosuke Naruhodo, a lawyer from Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Oh! Sorry... I'm Mr Naruhodo's judicial assistant, Susato Mikotoba. It's wonderful to meet you!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Lovely! Susie and Runo... Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">'Susie'...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And 'Runo'...? <thought>There's more to this girl than meets the eye... I have so many questions for her, I don't know where to start!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, and so do I!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What on earth is this huge, over-the-top machine?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's the 'Great Analytiscope'. It can analyse anything, really. Anything at all!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's... That's absolutely incredible!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It's one of Hurley's inventions. It took him a whole year! He said it was to help him with his investigations.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What sort of things has he analysed with it? Do you know?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well...actually...he hasn't used it for anything yet.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Apparently, on the evening he finally completed it, it suddenly occurred to him... 'I don't actually have anything I need to analyse.'</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">How about you, Runo? Do you have anything you'd like to analyse?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...The only thing that springs to mind is this machine itself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's all sorts on these shelves: chemistry apparatus, books, papers and...lots of things I've never seen before. It's all heaped up so high, I can't help feeling that the whole lot is going to topple at any moment.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I keep telling Hurley not to cram so much on those shelves.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Good advice.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">He wanted to look something up in one of those books a while ago. But it was so tightly wedged in, he couldn't get it out. So he went and bought a new copy instead.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, I've seen pictures of Western musical instruments like this. It's called a violin, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Of course it is! Mr Sholmes is renowned for his violin playing!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, really?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Absolutely! It's often explained in the stories. It's inspirational, Mr Naruhodo. Inspirational! I immediately started playing the koto, which was the closest Japanese stringed instrument I could find.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...What a shame you couldn't bring it with you to London.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, yes. Well... ...Papa was beaming when I asked him if he would buy me one. But after a while, he asked if I would only practise when he was out of the house. So...now it's merely an ornament in my room.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That must have been an awkward conversation...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, I've seen pictures of Western musical instruments like this. It's called a violin, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Of course it is! Mr Sholmes is renowned for his violin playing!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, really?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's right. I just sort of slipped that in.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You did what, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I didn't really give it a lot of thought, and just started adding it in to the stories.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes. Mr Sholmes's exceptional violin playing has been mentioned a number of times.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But the truth is, Hurley had barely touched a violin in his life up to that point.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Of course, people started asking him to play for them after my stories were published. And he wasn't able to tell them that he didn't know how.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What did he do?!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">He went straight to the pawnshop and bought himself a very nice violin. And then he practised. He practised until his fingers very nearly dropped off.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Must be why he's so highly strung.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Before I knew it, he'd become rather good. The greatness of the great detective really shone with that experience, I think!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...It was a great deception, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why...why are there all those bullet holes in the wall up there?! Was Mr Sholmes trying to shoot a pestery fly or something?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes...would never do something so reckless.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Those are the letters 'V.R.', standing for 'Victoria Regina'. It's Latin for Queen Victoria.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you mean...he shot the Queen into the wall?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">In a moment of boredom, Mr Sholmes adorned the wall with a patriotic sign, that's all. As pistol practice.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right, that...makes perfect sense now.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's exactly as it's described in the stories! Oh, this is delightful!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm not sure that the real explanation is any less reckless than shooting at a fly, personally.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's patriotic, Mr Naruhodo! Patriotic!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I do like this fireplace. It's one of the best things I've seen since we arrived in the country, in fact. Lingering beside the fire and watching the flames flicker and dance in the grate... Ah, it's so relaxing...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We can't relax! Not when there are so many interesting things on the mantelpiece! Oh, it's just as it was described in the stories!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It is?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! Exactly! Inside that Persian slipper, for example-</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...Are my chocolates for elevenses!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And transfixed by that large jackknife-</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...Is my shopping list for the market!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Oh, it's...not quite how I remember it being described in 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes'...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Poor Susato-san. She looks crushed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It looks like that huge metal chest is being used as a table for tea and coffee. It seems very sturdy, with an equally sturdy lock.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! You mustn't go around opening things! I always have to keep an eye on you, don't I? You're very mischievous.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...How did you come to that conclusion?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ooh, that chest... ...contains some of my most valuable things!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And that smile tells me you're not going to give us any clue about what they are...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">A mystery shoe, a curious hammer, some mysterious dancing men, a bust of Napoleon... Aah, what an entrancing collection!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...This is the first time in my life that I've seen a lonely old shoe displayed as an ornament.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, those are all mementoes that Hurley has collected from his past cases.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? Even the bust?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, that's right. When the mood takes him, he likes to throw it on the floor and smash it to dust.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The poor, defenceless emperor? ...Mr Sholmes destroys it?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, and then he buys a new one.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You make it sound like he has the temperament of an insane sculptor.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Aah, how entrancingly bohemian of him!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What a beautiful English tea set. And so neatly arranged.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It's a favourite pastime of mine, a cup of herbal tea in the afternoon.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Tea...made of herbs?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's right. I grow all sorts of herbs in the garden, so I can experiment with different blends. One moment! Don't go away! I'll brew a pot of the special blend I came up with earlier today!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>She looks delighted. ...I only hope it's safe to drink.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah, that's my blackboard where I note down ideas.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ooh, interesting. Let's see... 'Black Peter'...? <thought>What does that mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Don't you want to hear what Iris has to say, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...I'll come back to that blackboard later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah, that's my blackboard where I note down ideas.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Black Peter'...? <thought>What does that mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ooh, how intriguing! It must be the title of Iris's latest work! Oh my! I wonder what fantastic tale awaits us!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Susato-san looks like an angel, but I bet she's dreaming of the most grisly crime you could imagine.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">It's a case that Hurley solved just recently. A black cat called Peter went missing in the neighborhood. Hurley tracked it down at the fishmonger's in the end.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well! I can't wait for the story to be published!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's a charming little white shelf. And full of charming little bottles, too.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh yes. But don't touch any of those. They might explode.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">E-Explode?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Are they exotic chemicals? Do you use them for exciting experiments?!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, indeed! And as Hurley always says... 'Chemistry is an explosive science!'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I agree! A single discovery can trigger an explosion of innovation all around the world!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Or perhaps he just meant it literally. <thought>...Either way, mental note: Do not touch any bottle that belongs to Iris.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What on earth is that big black lump over there?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah! That fascinating thing is called a typewriter. It's a machine that allows you to write on paper without needing a pen! And wizardly quick, too!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ooh, that sounds like it could be very useful for someone like me with terrible handwriting.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What on earth is that big black lump over there?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah! That's a typewriter. It's a machine that allows you to write on paper without needing a pen! And wizardly quick, too!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ooh, that sounds like it could be very useful for someone like me with terrible handwriting.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Wait! Iris, are...are all the stories from 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes'-</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes! Every one typed on this trusty machine!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! My! Goodness! ...How wonderful!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Susato-san looks like she's been shown into the Tokyo Imperial Palace gardens.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It was you that we ran into yesterday, wasn't it? At the Old Bailey.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, that's right! You were ever so helpful. Thank you so much!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no, not at all. I'm so sorry we couldn't have been more welcoming.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Though, at the time, we did have a rather large gun pointed at us.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...Like this?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">*Gulp!*</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, thinking back now, you left with Miss Lestrade in tow, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Oh yes, that awkward witness, Gina Lestrade...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, Ginny? Yes, she's a professional pickpocket.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So we found out.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It was very naughty of her to pinch my invention like that!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Are you referring to that trial disrupting, gun-like contraption?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Exactly! So I followed her, you see, to get it back. Hm...perhaps I should think about fitting a self-destruct mechanism in my inventions...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This girl is dangerous.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Anyway, I brought Ginny back here after that. So she could apologise to my trusty technician.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry, your technician?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hurley, of course, silly!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Hurley...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, Herlock! Herlock Sholmes. We live here together.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I had no idea the great detective had such an... interesting young daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Daughter? Not likely!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I wouldn't call him Hurley if he was my father, would I?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well then...what is your relationship with Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, I expect you've found out that lodgings of any kind in London are very expensive. So the solution is to share the cost with a partner. A roommate.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're...roommates?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I hope you don't mind me asking, Iris, but...how old are you?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ten at last this year!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, what of your mother and father?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, no... They're not around.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, I see... <thought>I wonder what the story is there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes! There's something I must ask you!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Of course, of course! Go ahead, Susie!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I am a very great fan of 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes', and-</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! You have a copy of Randst Magazine!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! I read every issue! It's delivered all the way to Japan on a ship.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, this is so exciting! My stories are being read on the other side of the world!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'My' stories?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's right. Hurley is always solving such amazing cases, you see. And he tells me all about them. They really are quite fascinating! It would be such a shame if I was the only one who ever heard them, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Goodness!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Last night, he was telling me all about a new case he just solved on a steamship travelling from a faraway land. So I was just in the middle of typing up the manuscript for the next issue before you came.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So you... You...are the author...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes. I'll let you in on a secret, if you like. I'm going to call this latest adventure, 'The Speckled Band'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'The Speckled Band'?! <thought>That's...certainly very familiar.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Of course, I always change one or two details in the stories. Here and there. This time, I had the idea of making a venomous snake be the cause of all the trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! That was Mr Sholmes's first thought as well, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes. And of course I know that a snake might not be a credible fit for the facts of the case exactly, but... ...it's a story! Some poetic licence is justified to make it more thrilling, I think! Don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So, do you mean to say...? Are the stories about Mr Sholmes that are published in Randst Magazine...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...All written by me? Yes! On my wonderful and very modern typewriter!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But! But all the stories I've ever read... ...are written by a doctor of medicine! Dr John H. Wilson!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Susato-san's getting more and more worked up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah, yes... That's me! I mean, my name really is Wilson.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But! But what about the doctor of medicine part?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's all true, too. I am a doctor of medicine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No! At ten years old?!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">At ten years old!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well... That's quite incredible.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But! ...But, but... Dr Wilson is an English gentleman!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah, yes... I did alter the setting slightly, for the stories to be more compelling.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, it sounds a little strange, doesn't it? A great detective with a ten-year-old girl in tow.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... I...suppose it does, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Poor Susato-san... She looks like her whole world has just fallen apart.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...about before...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes? Yes? What's on your mind, Runo! Do tell me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How did you know? That I was a lawyer, and we'd just arrived in London, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes... Oh! And that we have a difficult trial tomorrow! How did you know all of that?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, that's what you mean.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Please! Tell us how you did it! Explain every detail!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Of course! I'd be delighted. Although...there's really no mystery. Now...let's begin! Iris Wilson is proud to present...her 'Logic and Reasoning Spectacular'! First of all, I knew already that you were a lawyer, Runo. After all, I met you yesterday at the Old Bailey in the defendants' antechamber.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But you also said that we'd only just arrived in London. How did you know that?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I observed a passport and travel ticket protruding from your breast pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">So I was reasonably confident that you must have only just arrived in the country. And on top of that... ...you accepted a case against that particular prosecutor. Telling me you were unaware of London's court affairs.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The Reaper of the Bailey? I walked right into that one, didn't I...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Then I noticed a red ink stamp on the back of Susie's hand. You were given that when you visited the local prison to meet with a suspect, weren't you? Earlier today.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">They use those stamps to keep a close eye on comings and goings, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I, I didn't realise...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And a red stamp is only used for people visiting foreign inmates. So...that told me that even though you had only yesterday concluded the trial of Magnus McGilded... ...the two of you had already had cause to visit a foreign inmate at a local prison. However, neither of you was wearing a particularly sad expression on your face. So I concluded that the prisoner was unlikely to be a friend or a relative. That led me to believe that you must have accepted a new case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But how could you have known that the trial is tomorrow?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, having barely been home a few hours yesterday, Hurley solved yet another case. It obviously amused him. He told me that he'd caught a Japanese man who was bawling and trembling.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A Japanese man? <thought>Well, clearly that must have been-</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Natsume!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Now, Runo has that fancy Japanese sword. And I think your outfit is called a kimono, isn't it, Susie? Well anyway, it was clear to me that you both come from Japan yourselves. So I put two and two together and decided you must be defending the Japanese man Hurley caught! And there was only one conclusion those facts could lead me to: You both came here to ask Hurley about the case! There's a note on the mantelpiece that says the man's trial will be tomorrow. Hurley is always stabbing his notes with a knife, you know. He is silly. And...that's all there was to it, really. Thank you for listening! I'm Iris Wilson, and that was one of my 'great deductions'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well? Was it a winner? Were my deductions correct?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">They... They were spot on!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That was amazing, Iris! Truly a great deduction!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You even managed the 'certain something' of Mr Sholmes's delivery!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, well...I was just copying Hurley's style for that!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">This is really very good news! You could tell us all about the case involving the Japanese man. You will, won't you, Iris? Please!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So yesterday, Mr Sholmes apprehended a Japanese man, you were saying...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes. Hurley had just arrived back in London after his sea voyage. But the police were waiting for him at the railway station to take him directly to the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah... <thought>The great detective is a popular man, it seems.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Apparently a woman was stabbed on a quiet street somewhere in town. There were witnesses who had seen a short, shifty-looking, stooped man running away from the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">A short, shifty-looking, stooped man...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Natsume, beyond any doubt. <thought>Soseki-san said that he didn't see anybody else on the street at all. But it seems there were witnesses after all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hurley used his great deductive powers to determine the man's address. It was a lodging room, very nearby. He went directly there with the police, and what did they find? A short, shifty-looking, stooped man, shivering in fear.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... Mr Sholmes's great deduction certainly hit the mark that time.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Of course it did! He's a great detective!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Still, that means the incident occurred only two days ago. Surely tomorrow is too soon for the trial, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Definitely. We have no time to investigate properly!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hurley says that London is rife with crime.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Scotland Yard is doing its best, but they can't stay on top of it, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear. I hadn't realised the situation was so dire.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's why they can't afford to spend too much time investigating cases and trying the criminals in court. Staff and money are both short. Crimes are usually pinned on the first suspicious person.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's terrible! I suppose it's the harsh reality of the workings of the world's greatest justice system...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I suppose it is... <thought>But in that case... ...I don't hold out much hope for Soseki-san.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Iris, could I show you this...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, how exciting! What is it? Tell me all about it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, actually, I was hoping you might be able to tell me something about it, if anything comes to mind?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Why would it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well... No, I suppose it wouldn't.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Tell me, tell me! I want to hear everything!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This hasn't gone according to plan...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, you're most welcome! I've had so much fun!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Do you happen to know where Mr Sholmes is at the moment? As you guessed, we'd like to ask him some questions about this case as well.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah well... ...I expect Hurley is still investigating the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of the case involving Mr Natsume, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, Mr Nuts...ooh-may? Hurley said he was going to the man's lodgings. If you leave now, you'll probably catch him there.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Iris! Do you know where those lodgings are?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well...I imagine the police are still investigating the scene of the crime themselves, aren't they? Did you happen to come across a detective by the name of Gregson when you were there?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, we know Inspector Gregson.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah, goody. In that case... ...give Gregsy this from me, would you? If you do that, I'm sure he'll tell you what you want to know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What is this?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">A five shilling piece and a postcard, it seems...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It reads: 'Tell the gentleman in black whatever he wants to know. I trust that won't be a problem?' Gosh! This will make the inspector help us, will it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Well, thank you, Iris. We'll give it a try.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Good luck, then! I'm going to return to writing my manuscript. 'The Speckled Band'! And I'll be making more special blends of tea, so come back again soon!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We'd be delighted! Thank you so much, Iris. Well, Mr Naruhodo...it's back to the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So, somewhat dubious that they would exert any influence over the men of Scotland Yard at all... ...we headed back to the scene with Iris's curious note and one of the world's heaviest silver coins in hand.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It looks as though the police are still here, carrying on with their investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perfect! So let's find Inspector Gregson as quickly as possible!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes... And let's see if he'll take a break from his chips to look at that silver 'tip' Iris gave us for him!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm, Inspector Gregson...do you have a moment?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I'm sorry to say I don't. I'm a very busy man. Much too busy to talk to a pair of foreign gadabouts, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We have these for you. A present...from Miss Iris Wilson.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">WHAAAAAAT?! For me?! From Her Ladyship?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Her Ladyship?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Give that here! At once! Come on! Hand it over! That's for me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh! <thought>Don't wait for me to give it to you, will you?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...what was that coin exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">It's a silver crown, obviously. But it's a lot more than that. It's...well... It's an appearance fee, that's what it is!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">An appearance fee? ...Oh! I see. You mean...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">That's right. For 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes'. Her Ladyship always offers me a little financial reward for featurin' me. Every time!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! Yes, of course! ...I know all about your exploits, Inspector! I read them avidly!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">'Course, her usin' my name without my say-so does make me the butt of a lot of unpleasant jokes, but still.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I am sorry, Inspector. That must be difficult for you.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Never you mind that! So...what d'you want to know then, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">'Tell the gentleman in black whatever he wants to know. I trust that won't be a problem?' it says. Well obviously it's not a problem! Go on, fire away. What d'you want to know?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, if you wouldn't mind, Inspector... ...we'd very much like to know the address of Mr Natsume's lodgings!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Ah, the little knife-wieldin', moustached Japanese fellow? He lives in a right old hovel. It's just over there, look. On the first floor of that house on the corner where that wreck of a bicycle's propped up.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...That is nearby indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">If I remember rightly, the landlord is a Mr John Garrideb. ...Right, well... If you see her again, you make sure you give Her Ladyship my regards, you hear? I mean it! You tell her that Gregson sends his very best wishes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">D-Don't worry, Inspector. We will.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Goodbye for now then. And long live Her Ladyship!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, at least he told us what we wanted to know before he left.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. So then, shall we go and see what we can find in Mr Natsume's lodgings?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Definitely!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's a rather typical old brick building, isn't it? I'm sure it has a long and interesting history.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, time certainly seems to have taken its toll on the place. It's crooked and sagging all over. <thought>In fact, it looks in decidedly worse shape than the other houses around here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">According to Inspector Gregson, that's the house where Mr Natsume has lodgings.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just across the road from where the incident took place, I see. <thought>It must be awful for Soseki-san, getting caught up in something like this in a foreign land.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maid">...May I help you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, yes, would this be the residence of...Mr John Garrideb?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Indeed it would, sir. And who may I say is calling?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My name is Ryunosuke Naruhodo. I, erm...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo is representing Mr Soseki Natsume. I believe he takes lodgings here?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">...!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We would very much like to ask him some questions about our client.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">...! ...One moment, please. I shall convey the message to Mr Garrideb.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Did you see that, Miss Susato?! That was a real-life English maid!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I know! As I understand it, anyone of standing in English society employs a number of household staff. But that was the first time I've ever seen one in the flesh! Oh, this day keeps getting better!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It certainly feels like we've really arrived now, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We need only to meet a butler, and the experience will be complete!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I'm not sure if I'd go that far, but...I understand the sentiment.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Thank you for waiting. Mr Garrideb will see you now. This way.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Good day to you. John Garrideb, at your service.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Pleased to meet you, sir. This is Ryunosuke Naruhodo. He's a defence lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Do excuse me not getting up. Took a shot to the knee a few years back in the Battle of Maiwand, don't you know. Earned a medal for my pains, but had to withdraw from service. Handed over the reins to the up-and-comings.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So he's a retired soldier...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">It's a hell of a job getting up and down stairs now, I can tell you. Don't get out much, as you can imagine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, it's quite a climb up here to the second floor, isn't it? I was panting at the top of the stairs.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You really must take more exercise, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...do you think so?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, Mr Garrideb, no doubt you were very courageous to earn yourself a medal.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Oh, it was nothing. The medal's just a folderol, really. Wouldn't like to offend the general, though. So I grudgingly displayed it on the wall. Why don't you fetch it down, Joan? Let these good people see it properly.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">.........</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Joan! Fetch the- AAAAAARGH!!! Dash it all, woman! Be careful!</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Oh! Dearie me! I do beg your pardon, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Hmph! You jolly nearly took the skin off my hands!</line>
<line speaker="Maid">I shall be more careful, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">So anyway, there you have it. Living the quiet life now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...I see.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Now then, I hear you want to know about the chap lodging downstairs. Is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! We would be very grateful if you could answer some questions for us.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Only too pleased, naturally. Especially if it helps to keep the peace here in Blighty. We've forged an alliance with the Empire of Japan recently, as I'm sure you're aware. So this case is very much in public eye, as it were.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Oh, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Even had some famous detective poking around, you know. In this old house, would you believe?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! Mr Herlock Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Hmph, could have been. Didn't catch the chap's name. Not really my cup of tea, all that detective business.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, but...you have a copy of Randst Magazine here, so...</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Eh? Hm? Ah...no, erm...</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Anyway, the chap's investigating the foreigner's room as we speak.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So he's in Soseki-san's room...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">It's a bally nuisance, is what it is. The whole neighbourhood's twitching its curtains now. I don't like all this fuss. It's jolly unsettling.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">About Mr Natsume then, Mr Garrideb! Please, do tell us!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Ah yes, the Japanese chap. Only been lodging here for a week.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, just one week? So he moved in very recently, then.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">I have two lodgers most of the time. One on the ground floor, and one just below us. The first floor room became available a week ago, you see. There'd been- AAAAAAAAARGH!!! Dash it all, Joan! Do be careful!</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Oh! My goodness! I'm terribly sorry, sir! ......... If you want to know my opinion... ...I thought he was a shady sort from the moment I set eyes on him.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">He seemed to have a most nervous disposition. Always shaking, and looking over his shoulder. The man had 'shady' written across his sweat-soaked brow, if you ask me. I said to myself, 'Joan, that man is trouble. Sooner or later, he's going to do something untoward.' ...And I'm rarely wrong about anything.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>We won't be calling this maid as a witness, that's for sure.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Was there anything else that struck you as suspicious about the man at all?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">...! Yes! Oh, yes, indeed there was!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And she's dying to tell us...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Had you noticed anything else at all about your lodger, Mr Natsume?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">...! Oh my word, yes! The man was shadier than an orchard!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Could you elaborate?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Well, take the man's room. Absolutely stuffed full of books, it is. More than anyone could ever read! And he never so much as passes the time of day with another living soul. I haven't seen a single visitor call. He just trots off to that old bookshop every single day, and comes back at five to light the gas fire. And the funny little man is up long past the time everyone else in the house has gone to bed, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! I, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">The gentleman on the ground floor goes to bed at around nine each night. But I've never known that Japanese fellow to retire any earlier than two in the morning.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Could you clarify something, I wonder?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">What, pray?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">How do you know so much about Mr Natsume's routine?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'd understood that neither of the lodgers live on this floor of the house. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">That's right, yes. They're both below us. On the first floor and street level.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Then...how is it that you know so much about the lives of your lodgers? The precise times that they come back in the evening, for example. Even the times they go to bed.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">.........</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">AAAAAAAAARGH!!! Good grief, Joan! Be more careful, woman!</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Oh my goodness, sir! I'm terribly sorry, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Hm... Something doesn't add up here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maid">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It seems that the incident took place at around five in the evening. Did you happen to look out of the window at around that time?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Hm? The window?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, we noticed that the window over there looks out over Briar Road. The incident took place on the pavement just on the far side of the street. Was there anyone suspicious loitering nearby?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Five o'clock is dinner time in the Garrideb household. So I'm afraid I don't remember seeing anything. How about you, Joan?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">No, sir. It would have been dusk outside already at that hour. And with the fog as well, I should think it would have been quite impossible to see the other side of the road.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Did you notice anything else out of the ordinary, then?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Such as...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Anything at all! Even if it seems unrelated.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Hmph, well...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! Yes? Was there something, then?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Well, it's nothing particularly significant, but at around that sort of time in here, there- AAAAAAAAARGH!!! For the love of God, Joan! Watch what you're doing!</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Oh dearie me! What have I done? I'm awfully sorry, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Do be more careful, woman!</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Of course, sir. If I may, Mr Narrow-Hollow...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh. ...Err, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">I have an exceedingly good memory, and as far as I remember... ...nothing of any significance took place here at that hour. Nothing at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh. Really? Mr Garrideb? The way you were talking before, it sounded rather like there might have been.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Oh, well. As I was saying, it was just a trifling matter really. Nothing of- AAAAAAAAARGH!!! Joan! Dash it all! What is the matter with you, woman!</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Begging your pardon, sir. ...Nothing happened.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">......... Hm, yes. Quite. Nothing happened. We sat down to a quiet, uneventful meal, hm, Joan?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Thaaat's right, Mr Garrideb.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>What is the matter with these two?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It sounds like something happened here in this room on the evening of the incident...but what?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I wish I knew...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Could you tell us which floor Mr Natsume's room is on?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Why, certainly. Just below us on the first floor.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And Mr Sholmes is investigating there, even as we speak?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Yes. Told me Nats-his-name had asked him to look into the matter, so I gave him the key.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Natsume has engaged Mr Sholmes's services?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's a blatant lie.</thought> Would it be alright if we also had a look around? In Mr Natsume's room, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">...Hmph, don't see why not. It's just down one flight of stairs.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Who knows if we'll find anything that could help us with the case, but we have to try.</thought> We need all the clues we can lay our hands on. Shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes. And while we're there... ...we can speak with Mr Sholmes again! Perhaps he'll be able to tell us more.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's a full-sized cannon! What's it doing in here?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my... It's real! I thought it might be a replica.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">That old thing? Bah, that's little more than a toy.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">The army was selling it off when I retired, so I decided to give it a new home. Never know when the enemy might attack next! Jolly useful to have a cannon about the house.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? It isn't...overkill?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Be prepared, I always say. You never know what this twisted world is going to throw at you next, boy.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Do you think there may be trouble brewing, Mr Garrideb?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Always is! Take Joan here. Never fails to have a clean apron in reserve. Dries them over the barrel, you see. They dry very well on the cannon there, Joan tells me. Which rather proves my point, I feel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...It's been reduced to a drying rack. No wonder the huge cannon looks like it's hanging its head in shame.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I notice you have a pile of books here, Mr Garrideb. Do you enjoy reading?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Ever experience a London winter, boy? The nights are long. No better way to pass the time than in front of the fire with a jolly good book.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! There's a copy of Randst Magazine here, I see. No doubt Mr Garrideb enjoys 'The Adventure of Herlock Sholmes', too!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...The great detective has a great many followers, it would seem.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That uniform looks fairly ancient, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's clearly been well looked after though.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">That old thing? Pah! Not much better than rags, really.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Wore that ceremonial garb at my retirement bash, you know. But I'm not one for dwelling on the past, me. Would have gladly thrown it out, but you know how it is. Anyway, doesn't hurt to have the odd piece of memorabilia lying around, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...I see.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Perhaps we should leave the past in the past...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Are, are those mortar shells? They're enormous!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah! I hadn't noticed! What are they doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Ah, those old things? Couple of little rounds I accidentally fired into the barracks during training, you know. Became a bit of colourful regiment folklore, that incident.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean, you deliberately hunted out the spent shells?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Well, I wouldn't say 'deliberately' exactly. They're only scrap iron, after all. Usually just thrown away, I believe. But you never know when things might come in useful, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Useful for what, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Hmmm...yes...well... Joan here did manage to knock one of the bally things on my foot the other day while she was dusting!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Hadn't shed a tear since 1869 before then, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Maybe reconsider throwing them away?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">That looks like a medal of honour. And it's showcased on a very grand banner.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. It's displayed with some pride, I would say. ...Although it bothers me that it's not straight.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">What, that old thing?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">I should be glad to see the back of it, but the general would turn in his grave if I disposed of it. The wall's the best place for it. Keeps the bally thing out of my way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So it's just been polished to shine by accident, I suppose?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">...There appears to be an inscription on the medal itself, look. Let me see... It says, 'For Distinguished Participation'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Sounds like the kind of honours even I could be in line for.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Well, one doesn't like to blow one's own trumpet. But I was given that for my time in the army. Can't measure an officer by the number of medals to his name, of course. Common knowledge in military circles.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That portrait of Mr Garrideb is glaring at me, I swear.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Have you noticed that all the little frames contain photographic prints of Mr Garrideb as well?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, and...there seems to be a statue of a lion on the mantelpiece as well.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Ah, yes. Seemed to come back from the local pawnbroker with that little trinket.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Seemed to come back'? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">The chap who runs the place is a bally wizard! Went in to sell him something and came out with that thing! In point of fact... Now I think about it, I rather often find myself leaving the place with something I don't need.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The lion ornament certainly does seem surplus to requirements.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Susato-san doesn't pull her punches! ...Or her throws, for that matter.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Look at that enormous screen! It must have been put there deliberately, surely.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. It certainly seems like someone's trying to hide something from view. <thought>What could be behind it, I wonder...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm going to have a very quick look. Just a little peek!</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Ahem! Ahem!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Maybe let's not, Miss Susato. I think the maid is going to head us off with a cup of tea.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Ahem! Ahem!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">This window looks out over Briar Road, where the young woman was attacked.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes... I can make out the policemen on the far side of the road investigating the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The glass is rather murky, isn't it? You can't see very clearly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Does this thing open at all, I wonder...</line>
<line speaker="Maid">I shouldn't underestimate the bitterness of a London winter, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">As soon as you open that window, the tea will freeze in the pot! No Londoner would go opening windows at dusk in the middle of winter, I assure you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It seems very unlikely that these two would have seen anything of the incident, then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, look! What a wonderful collection of cakes lined up on that gleaming silver cake stand!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>'Lined up'? It looks more like someone has half demolished them to me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maid">Afternoon tea is a time of indulgence, you know. It is quite the English way. It is Mr Garrideb's custom to take two cakes with his tea.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That sounds delightful!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh... Wait a minute, though... There are at least ten cakes on this cake stand.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Well, naturally! And it would never do to waste the leftovers. So whatever Mr Garrideb doesn't eat, I say to myself, 'Joan, you shall have to tidy up.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How...magnanimous of you.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">This old candle holder looks a little out of place here, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, you're right. It's clearly supposed to be gold, but it's almost completely black for some reason.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Ah, um...that old thing, yes. Just a cheap of ironmongery. Gimcrack, really.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Used it when I was studying, don't you know? For my commission. I know it's old. Hardly worth hanging on to, really. But...well, still has its uses sometimes.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Does everything in this room have some elaborate story behind it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">They're memories, Mr Naruhodo... Memories.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at this crockery on display here. It's rather...unusual, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! A genuine London dresser! Isn't it delightful?! ...Although the shelves seem to be broken, and the crockery is... Oh dear! It's in pieces!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It really is. The word 'cracked' wouldn't do that chinaware justice.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Ah! I wonder... Perhaps the cannon was fired at it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, probably something like that. <thought>But let's not delve too deeply here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Iris is hard at work at her desk, look. She's tapping away on her typewriter so fast, her fingers are a blur.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Sorry, I can't stop! I have to meet the deadline for the next issue!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, I see. You must be very busy then.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Don't disturb her, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I won't! So you can lower your arms now, please.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...? Just look at this place! <thought>And smell it! It's so musty in here. I suppose it's the mountains of old books that are responsible for that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... I don't think I've ever seen so many books in all my life!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, me neither. It's so dark in here, too.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Is that the window over there?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, it WAS the window, I think, yes. Once upon a time. <thought>But for some reason it's been closed up with bricks and mortar.</thought> So this is where Mr Natsume lives...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">By the way... ...I haven't spotted Mr Sholmes anywhere, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, that's true. But according to what Mr Garrideb told us... ...the great detective should be around here somewhere investigating.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That desk seems to be wedged into a crevasse between the mountains of books on either side.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I suppose Mr Natsume would sit there and read while stroking his cat. But surrounded on all sides by these towering old tomes... Surely he dreamt of books every night as well.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes...he must have done, mustn't he? ...Oh! What's this? It's a receipt from a secondhand bookshop. 'Yore Books'...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes. Mr Natsume's name is on it, look. And the date of purchase... Ah, two days ago at 4:45 p.m. <thought>That's the day of the incident!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's just a short while before he was embroiled in the terrible attack! He must have been on his way back from buying some old books.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That desk seems to be wedged into a crevasse between the mountains of books on either side.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I suppose Mr Natsume would sit there and read while stroking his cat. But surrounded on all sides by these towering old tomes... Surely he dreamt of books every night as well.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes...he must have done, mustn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh look! It's a beckoning cat from home!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's a bit big and bulky, isn't it? Surely Mr Natsume didn't bring that maneki-neko all the way from Japan with him.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I hardly think you're in a position to comment, Mr Naruhodo. Are you forgetting the enormous daruma doll that you brought in your luggage?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Well, it can be dangerous travelling abroad. I wanted a lucky charm.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, I imagine Mr Natsume wanted the same. And this cat is sure to beckon good luck to him.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It's not doing a very good job so far, is it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">You mustn't say such things!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I didn't say a word! <thought>...Why are my eyes such a giveaway?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at all those books stacked up there! They almost reach the ceiling.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">They're all works of English literature. ...And they all smell so musty.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">With this volume of books to hand, you'd never be short of reading material, would you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, what a dreamy idea!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...A bad dream, maybe. For me at least.</thought> Mind you, I don't imagine the book that's at the bottom of the pile now will ever be read again.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, so reading is an experience that comes but once in a lifetime. Just as the tea ceremony teaches us.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I certainly didn't expect the conversation to turn down the path of tea ceremony philosophy.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Could you even call this a window?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think so... It was a window at one time, after all. Although all that remains is a frame around some bricks now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So really it's just a wall then, isn't it? But why would anyone deliberately brick it up like that?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm afraid I have no idea. Ah! Perhaps Mr Natsume painted the brick design on in a fit of whimsy.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... That's alarmingly feasible. Anyway, whatever the reason, the lack of ventilation in here makes the place very oppressive.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It does. I imagine being cooped up in a room like this would be extremely trying.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! What an adorable little cat! Perhaps he's looking after all the books while his master is away.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't know about that. He disappeared into that pile of books as quick as a flash. It was a tricolor 'mi-ke', wasn't it? Do they even have that sort of cat here in Great Britain?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps Mr Natsume brought the little creature with him from Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That's made me feel homesick now.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Already? We've only been in the country for two days.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at all these balls of paper on the floor. There are notes scrawled all over them. In English. It looks like the wastepaper basket is so full, they've just fallen out.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think Mr Natsume must have been deeply immersed in his research, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Or deeply averse to tidying up his mess.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... I...wouldn't like to speculate which is closer to the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Aaah! Look, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah-ha! There he is! <thought>Where did he appear from?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">He seems to be engrossed in the pages of an old book. I hope heh won't mind if we disturb him... Hellooo! Mr Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...! Ah, you two! Good day. Now, let me see... Where was it that we met?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Mr Sholmes! We were together on the SS Burya.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, of course! The Burya. And let me see... What happened on that voyage?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It was Kazuma Asogi. He died...tragically. But you were a great help to us.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah yes, but of course! The case of Mr Asogi! It was the one with the snake, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...you seem to remember...something of it, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What an honour, to be remembered vaguely by the great Herlock Sholmes! This is Mr-</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Oh no no, my dear madam, hold your tongue! I pride myself on my superior powers of recollection. Your names are safely recorded in my brain-attic. Miss Naruhodo... ...and Mr Susato!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Try the other way around, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah ha ha ha ha hah! I lose the first round!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...In truth, I had hoped to invite you both to my Baker Street suite the day we arrived in London. But some Scotland Yarders ambushed me at the railway station and whisked me away to a crime scene. It was an entirely trivial case, of course. I solved the matter in no more than thirty minutes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So they apprehended Soseki-san in THAT short an amount of time?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm afraid the pursuance of a new case has dulled my recollection of my past involvements a little.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'A little'?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It is a mistake to think that one's brain-attic has elastic walls and can distend to any extent. I do my best to forget useless facts, lest they should elbow out the useful ones. Yes! Those are my own words of inimitable wisdom, you know. From an adventure entitled, 'A Study in Scarlet'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Please, there's no need to quote yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I don't always remember my pearls of wisdom, but fortunately, my associate pens them beautifully.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He means Iris, I suppose.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes... ...we have some extremely important questions to ask you about the 'trivial case' you just mentioned!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Goodness! What an earnest expression. My dear madam, I should be only too pleased. And this murky room is an apt place to discuss the murky case!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We know this to be the lodgings of a Japanese foreign student by the name of Soseki Natsume. It seems that you assisted in his arrest, Mr Sholmes. For the stabbing of a young woman outside here on Briar Road.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm, Natsume... Yes, I believe it was a name rather along those lines.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But Mr Natsume denies it! Was it really justifiable to arrest him on so little?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... I'm sorry, Miss Susato... ...but I have not the slightest idea what you mean.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I can't believe he was looking Susato-san squarely in the eye while feigning ignorance.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I assure you, I am not merely feigning ignorance. It would appear as if the pair of you are under some misapprehension.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh? How?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I assure you I have no recollection of accusing your stooped compatriot of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But that doesn't make sense!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The good detective of Scotland Yard made the following request of me, and I quote verbatim: 'We need you to ascertain the identity and whereabouts of a man seen fleeing the crime scene.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah... A man...seen fleeing...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">There were a number of books scattered on the pavement at the scene. From the bookplates, I was quickly able to determine the bookshop from which they had been purchased. On speaking with the proprietor, I was immediately led to this address. ...Elementary, wouldn't you say? I believe there is a receipt around here somewhere from the establishment in question.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you don't think Mr Natsume is the culprit then!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm...that I could not tell you. But it was aggravating my faculties. Hence why I returned here. However, this place is such a trove of fascinating books, I found myself quite lost in bibliophily. ...Do not be deceived into believing that I am a man of leisure. No no no!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah...tell me... ...have you encountered the landlord of these lodgings?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. Mr Garrideb. ...A retired military man.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was the first time I've ever met a soldier from the great British institution that is the Services.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And it was the first time I've ever met a maid from the great British institution that is...service.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Ah ha ha ha ha hah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I-I didn't think it was THAT funny...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I do apologise. As you may well be aware, many households in London employ a maid.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! I read as much in my 'Great Britain Primer'.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And so conversely... ...whether or not a household employs a maid has come to betoken the social standing of those dwelling therein.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Betoken their social standing? ...Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Put simply, my dear fellow... ...those who employ at least a single maid are considered middle class. Those who do not, are beneath that. In the upper echelons of society, of course, households employ enough staff to constitute a large family. </line>
<line speaker="Susato">Goodness! How extraordinary...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As you can appreciate, for those on the precarious boundary between the middle and lower classes... ...being able to afford just one maid is of the first importance.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I...I had no idea.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And it is for precisely that reason, that I find great stimulation in the situation upstairs. Specifically, in the retired army veteran, Mr John Garrideb.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Affable as he is, the fellow is hiding something. Whether or not it imposes on the circumstances of this case, I am as yet unable to ascertain.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...I'm thoroughly lost on what he means to say.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...This room is thoroughly suffocating for the soul, my dear fellow. I assure you, any man whose lot is to dwell in a place such as this will stab somebody sooner or later.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Natsume has stabbed no one!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, but 'sooner or later', as I said...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I don't believe that's the issue here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...About this dark little room, Mr Sholmes... Why is there no longer a window? Do you have any idea?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">No window?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I mean, I can clearly see that there is a window... of sorts. But it's been completely blocked with bricks.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, I see. The answer to that question is quite simple: Window tax.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Window...tax? What is that?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Surely...not a tax on windows?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Precisely that.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my goodness!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Until relatively recently, a tax was levied on households in this country by the number of their windows. Those of lesser means, having inherited a sizeable and costly family home perhaps, rapidly closed windows up. While the rich opened windows here, there and everywhere... ...in an effort to curry favour with those in power by furnishing them with large sums of tax money.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">How awful! ...And unjust! Forcing people to live in rooms devoid of light!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed, disease was rife as a result. So some forty years ago, or thereabouts, the window tax was abolished. But its legacy remains, as you can see. In squalid lodgings such as these, for example.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I suppose Mr Natsume's stipend for living here in London isn't very generous perhaps...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It would appear so. I've done a little digging... ...and discovered that these lodgings were offered at an extraordinarily low price.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Because the room is so awful, I should think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Apparently Mr Natsume only moved in here about one week ago.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, that's correct. However... ...I don't believe the low rent is explained by the shabby nature of the accommodation.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Still, that is of little relevance here. A matter not worthy of further attention.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Are you sure? I'm curious now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo, please! Despite aversions to the contrary, I am a professional. If I am to unleash my deductive powers on that trinket... ...I must ask for a sum of three pounds in cash.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, I don't need you to make any deductions about it. I was just wondering if you might know-</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo! As a professional, I insist that if I am to offer my opinion on that trinket... ...I must ask for a sum of three pounds in cash.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I believe Mr Sholmes has his eye on an expensive copy of 'The Complete Works of Shakespeare'.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, to stand on the stage amid rapturous applause... It has long been a dream of mine, as you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I literally had no idea.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, the receipt for the books our stooped Japanese friend purchased. I uncovered that yesterday morning. A marvellous find, wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes. The work of a truly great detective.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What a scatterbrained individual he must be to have left it behind. ...Curiously, there was no mention of this publication on the receipt. Odd, when you consider how fascinating it is.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean not everyone in London buys Randst Magazine every time they visit a shop? Yes, odd indeed...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Mr Sholmes! How expertly you slipped that into the conversation!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, I'm glad you agree! Detective stories can be great works of literature, too, my dear fellow!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Um, have you seen this, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Shh! I must have silence! It is of the first importance when I am in the throes of deduction that nothing irrelevant distracts me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Cloudy changing to fair, perhaps...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>You were in the throes of deducing the weather...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah yes, Mr Naruhodo... ...was it not your intention to become a practitioner of law?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>You remembered that, did you?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Will you perhaps be offering your services in this very matter, I wonder? To the occupant of this room, Mr...Natsume, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I'm not sure.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Not sure? On what grounds?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I actually defended someone in court here only yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Really? Well then, I congratulate you, sir, on an ambition realised. And so promptly, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The thing is... ...it's really made me question things. Am I right to believe in my clients? To trust in their innocence?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Hm, yes. Trust...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes... ...Mr Natsume didn't do it, did he?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Ah ha ha ha ha hah! My dear fellow, I haven't the first idea!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! But... ...I thought that's why you were here. Didn't you come back to investigate?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah yes, that was indeed my initial intention. But there are simply too many fascinating books here. I couldn't possibly ignore them.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...I see.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Nevertheless, there are two facts that I can state quite unequivocally. The man who fled the scene of the crime two days ago was the Japanese occupant of this room. And... ...there are witnesses who swear to having seen the same man commit the crime. ...That is all I can say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, and one more thing...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! What is it, Mr Sholmes! Tell us!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I cannot say with any certainty whether or not it is of relevance to this case, but I am quite sure... ...that the retired army man who owns this property... is hiding something.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Garrideb is...? <thought>Mr Sholmes said as much before actually, didn't he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Anyway, at present, that is really all that plays on my mind in relation to this case.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo... ...as yet our investigations have uncovered nothing that could help establish Mr Natsume's innocence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, you're right. <thought>Perhaps it's time we probed a little deeper into Mr Garrideb's secret...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Just remember, I cannot be sure whether the landlord's secret will prove to be of relevance or not. But I wish you every success, of course, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Hm, a busy man, indeed... He's gone back to his book in the corner of the room.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Excuse me, Mr Sholmes...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm, yes, so true. To be, or not to be... ...that is indeed the question...Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>To be, or not to be brushed off. That is the question. And the answer is all too clear.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Let's leave Mr Sholmes in peace, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Ah, you pair again. Tell me, was the detective chap - I forget his name - still hard at work down there?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Herlock Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Ah yes, rings a vague bell. All that detective business isn't really my thing, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, Mr Sholmes is...in his element down there.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Jolly good show. Another cup of tea, if you please, Joan. ...Now then, why don't you tell me what- AAAAAAAAARGH!!! For the umpteenth time, woman, will you watch what you're bally well doing?!</line>
<line speaker="Maid">I shall be serving dinner shortly, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Hm? Ah... Yes, of course. Frightfully rude of me, but I'm afraid I shall have to ask you to take your leave, if you'd be so kind?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, yes, of course. We are deeply grateful for all your assistance.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Not at all, not at all! Don't get much chance to talk with young foreigners like yourselves. It's been a pleasure. Best of luck, and all that. ...Perhaps you could see yourselves out.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>According to Mr Sholmes... ...Mr Garrideb is hiding something. And since no other avenues of investigation seem open to us at the moment, perhaps we should do some digging.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah... <thought>What's he doing over there?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">M...Mr Sholmes?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah-ha! We meet again, my dear fellows!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Good gracious! When did you sneak in here?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Herlock Sholmes, sir, at your service.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Whatever were you doing over by the window?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I am given to watching the evening sky as the sun sets, madam. Yet sadly, cheerful as the room downstairs undoubtedly is, it lacks an aperture for such observation. So I took the liberty of borrowing a small corner of space by the window up here.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Hmph. Well...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Keeping an eye to one's windows at dusk is the prudent thing to do in London, I'm gathering...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, and one other thing, Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Me?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I thought perhaps you might be in need... ...of a certain great detective's...great mind!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>Wait, he's not talking about...? Is he? I, I didn't expect to be going through that again so soon...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Do you mean, Mr Sholmes...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">There is a mighty secret in this modest room. My eyes see even the most trivial of trifles. I take it you're prepared, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I think so!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">There is just time enough for one of my greatly admired great deductions. Let us conclude the matter before dark! Mr Garrideb... ...though it would seem you are a military man of considerably distinguished service... ...your standing as a landlord is most certainly not what one might call, 'first-rate'.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm afraid, sir, that it is all too clear to me. There are two conclusions I have been able to draw by careful observation of your living arrangements.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">I beg your pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The first... ...is that even as we speak, you are concealing the presence of a ferocious beast in your care!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And the second... ...is that as a result of the beast's violent rampage, you have lost something very dear to you!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Ah! Er...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo, look!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The old man's broken out in a cold sweat... Unbelievably, it seems Mr Sholmes's conclusions...are both spot on!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">...How? How could you possibly...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">'How could I possibly know?' you mean to enquire? The answer couldn't be simpler, sir. For in the dense jungle of logic and reasoning...I am the king of beasts!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And I know only too well, that wild beasts are not easily tamed. So...shall we begin? Once again, Herlock Sholmes is proud to present...his 'Logic and Reasoning Spectacular'!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It certainly shouldn't take a great detective to see... ...that a fearsome beast has been on the rampage of late within these four walls. Thus we are faced with the question: What form might this beast take? Ah, for a man with a military breeding, your eyes are uncommonly candid.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">I...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Your furtive glance, Mr Garrideb, leads us directly to the answer. The true nature of the beast that has run rampant here is revealed by that lion statue! Yes, though an army man, you appear unimposing at best. A fact that has fuelled your admiration for the mighty lion, the king of beasts.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">What is this piffle, I ask you?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In the end, your admiration became so great, in fact... ...that you had a living, breathing specimen shipped from India, which you tried to keep in this very house!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">WHAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yet living with such a wild beast proved more difficult than you had imagined. The chilling traces of a wild rampage are still very much in evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Well!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yet as we look around, the beast in question fails to present itself. Where could this angry creature have disappeared to... madam?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">M-Me?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I pray you do not consider me unchivalrous, but it is plain to me with one glance in your direction.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">It...it is?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Your dress pocket gives us a handsome clue as to the beast's current whereabouts! For protruding from it is a handbill advertising a circus show.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, you sought to dispose of this terrifying lion, Mr Garrideb. At 'Batty's Circus'... ...a travelling show currently sojourning in a nearby park. I have observed the tents. You sold the savage lion, sir, to the circus troupe!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">I, I most certainly did not!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...I believe I have made my point. The fearsome beast which ran amok in this room...was an Indian lion! And a simple visit to the circus now will reveal the lion prancing jubilantly through a ring of fire!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Now...Mr Garrideb... ...it is plainly clear that you still have deep feelings for this formidable 'beast'. Indeed, in that blithe pose, the distress this loss has caused you is veritably tangible.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Your head weighs heavy on your shoulders. The pain you feel being revealed by that supporting arm. Amid fits of tears, you let your beloved beast go. The strain of losing something so dear to you is clearly visible in your visage.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Nonsense man! I, I simply...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But what, we must now ask ourselves, is the true cause of this pain? And we need only follow the direction of your gaze to find the answer. Yes, it is this pile of bills that has given rise to the pain you suffer. Every envelope contains another demand for payment.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">For cart-loads of meat, potatoes, wheat and tea. Indeed, feeding your beloved has had a devastating impact on the financial circumstances of your household. And so you had no choice but to let it go.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Yes, well, erm...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Now...in a final fit of rage, the ferocious beast carried out one last, unimaginable attack...</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Un-Unimaginable...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...The aftermath of which can be clearly seen by observing the carpet over there! A very expensive woollen carpet, if I am not mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Oh dearie me...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What could have caused such a destructive outburst?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...This time, madam, I'm afraid it is you who has inadvertently revealed the truth to me. Your wandering eye has settled upon the answer very neatly indeed. Yes, to explain the dire state of the carpet, we need only look at the tower of cakes!</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">There is no creature more dangerous on this earth than a beast with an unsatiated appetite. Was it or was it not once said by a noblewoman, 'If they have no bread, let them eat cake'? Food is at the heart of all tragedy, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Whatever do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Having tired of the taste of cake, the beast began to stalk its next prey. I'm sure I need not spell out the nature of this final act of destruction carried out by the beast. There is only one logical conclusion: Worked into a frenzy by hunger, the lion attacked and ate the carpet! The teeth marks in the carpet...are a perfect match with those of a lion I once saw in India.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Thus concludes Herlock Sholmes's great deduction...of this beastly puzzle!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">AAAAAAAAARGH!!! What is the matter with you, Joan?! You're pouring scalding hot tea all over me!</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Oh...I'm sorry, Mr Garrideb. I'm afraid I didn't notice.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My deductions can be startlingly sharp. It stands to reason that your cup runneth over. Indeed, my revelations can make people spill tears at times, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm, Mr Sholmes, sorry to butt in...again. But could I make an observation?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Why certainly, Mr Naruhodo. What is it...again?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, your deductions just now... Do you really think a lion could have fit inside a room of this size?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed. It is the only explanation for the facts. The terrifying truth all too often lies beyond the realms of common sense!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>But wouldn't it be an idea to consider what lies inside the realms of common sense as well?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">But...if an uncaged lion had run amok in this very room... ...surely Mr Garrideb and his maid would have been hurt...or worse.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, that's where you are stuck. No doubt the former military man held his own against the beast using that large cannon.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I thought you said that they sold the lion to the circus...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And what about the food? Meat and potatoes are one thing... ...but I don't believe I have ever heard of a lion that drinks tea.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, my dear Miss Susato. It occurs to me with some regularity... ...that irrespective of race and breeding, whenever anyone lands on Great British soil... ...they are infused with a highly appropriate taste for afternoon tea!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! ...What a glorious notion! Well then, Mr Naruhodo! It's your turn to shine again!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I...had a feeling that was coming.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">A slight massage, that's all Mr Sholmes's deductions need. You can do it!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Excellent. I've been waiting for my trusty partner in deduction to step forward, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...We don't even know yet whether or not this is going to help with Mr Natsume's case. Still... ...uncovering the truth is always worthwhile, whatever the motivation! ...At least, that's what I want to believe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Let us start again from the beginning... ...of Herlock Sholmes's 'Logic and Reasoning Spectacular'!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It certainly shouldn't take a great detective to see... ...that a fearsome beast has been on the rampage of late within these four walls. Thus we are faced with the question: What form might this beast take? Ah, for a man with a military breeding, your eyes are uncommonly candid.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">I...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Your furtive glance, Mr Garrideb, leads us directly to the answer. The true nature of the beast that has run rampant here is revealed by that lion statue!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I really didn't see the lion thing coming.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, but if you observe Mr Garrideb's reaction... ...it rather seems as though some beast did indeed run amok here in this room.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, something with a very fierce nature.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But it couldn't have been a lion transported from India.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So what was it, then?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We must follow Mr Garrideb's gaze. That will lead us to the true answer!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, this is the lion statue that Mr Sholmes picked out.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes... I wonder... ...perhaps if you did live with a lion, it would prove to be a rather sweet companion.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think... ...that's like a mouse trying to tell its family that the cat around the house is sweet.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I supposed it IS a bit of a flight of fancy, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Anyway, the beast we're looking for is something else. Let's have a good look around!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Th-These are shells for the cannon, are they? What a strange place to keep them.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I imagine they have some significance to Mr Garrideb. From his time in the army. ...Ah, of course! He mentioned a battle to us before, didn't he? Do you remember? He said that he'd been shot in the knee. Perhaps it was one of these that hit him?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...If a round that size had hit his knee, there'd be nothing left of it...or Mr Garrideb for that matter. <thought>Mr Sholmes has a Persian slipper... ...and this man has spent shells. Perhaps it's customary in Britain to display...well, rubbish, on the mantelpiece...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's this photograph?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It appears to be from Mr Garrideb's wedding. He looks very happy, doesn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He does, but...you can't make out his bride.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, how unfortunate. Something must have struck the glass directly over the woman's face.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I wonder what happened... Probably best not to delve too deeply there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">The glass is broken, so you can't see the bride's face at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But no amount of cracks could hide the woman's plump form.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think 'powerful' would be kinder than 'plump', Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, she certainly looks that. There's a lot of horsepower here. Not someone you'd want to upset, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh look! Have you noticed her wedding ring? It's very large, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's an unusual design.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It looks like some sort of embellished sunflower.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">This must have been when Mr Garrideb was still in the army.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He seems to be carrying his rather stout bride effortlessly, and beaming a smile at the same time.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I suppose he was very strong in his younger years.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hard to imagine now. He's as thin as a rake.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Are you quite concentrating? You've identified exactly what I did originally.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes...so I have. Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, I do understand. As inimitable as I am, people do like to try. But you won't make a great detective like that. Nor even a great detective's assistant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">An assistant's assistant, then...? ...Alright, I'll think again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, what we do know with some certainty, is that a destructive creature has been at work in this room.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And that Mr Garrideb inadvertently looked in the direction of something that gives its identity away. <thought>Yes, if we investigate thoroughly enough, we ought to find the answer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">What did Mr Garrideb turn to look at? It's here somewhere. We simply need to find it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The true nature of the beast that has run rampant here is revealed by that newlywed bride!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Precisely, Mr Naruhodo! No other explanation could possibly fit! Yes, this framed print pictures your wife, Mr Garrideb. And while we lament the fact that her face is obscured...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...we can still make out her mighty arms, and note the considerable horsepower they must contain.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Oh, um...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed! Surely any woman of such powerful constitution would be honoured to be described as a 'beast'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...'honoured' might be stretching a point...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Too late! The fact remains that the beast, which so clearly savaged this room... ...was your wife, Mr Garrideb!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">GYAAARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The chilling traces of a wild rampage are still very much in evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Well!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yet as we look around, the beast in question fails to present itself. Where could this angry creature have disappeared to... madam?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">M-Me?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I pray you do not consider me unchivalrous, but it is plain to me with one glance in your direction.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">It...it is?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Your dress pocket gives us a handsome clue as to the beast's current whereabouts!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The poor, fragile, defenceless woman is beside herself!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well... ...I don't know about 'fragile'.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...dear... Anyway, Mr Sholmes is quite right. There's no sign of a Mrs Garrideb anywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But it seems there may be a clue as to her whereabouts. A clue that this maid is trying to hide! <thought>I wonder where Mr Garrideb's wife could be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Two tightly shut eyes to avoid even the chance of a giveaway glance. Pursed lips to prevent any secrets from slipping out. Rounded cheeks to deflect any abuse that might be hurled her way. ...Yes, this is an unnervingly powerful woman, Miss Susato.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...It's your turn of phrase that's unnerving, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What a charming little teapot. And it's in pristine condition. Joan has been pouring some deliciously fragrant tea from it for Mr Garrideb, hasn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, not so much 'for Mr Garrideb'... ...as 'on Mr Garrideb'. Wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I wouldn't dream of drawing attention to it!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That certainly does appear to be a circus handbill poking out from her pocket. 'Batty's Circus'...currently performing shows in a park not far from here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You don't think...? Surely Mr Garrideb didn't sell his wife to the circus!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! How could you even think such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I was only joking.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Besides... ...I would have gone with 'Do you think he fed her to his pet lion?'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That's somehow worse.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">She's wearing a very large ring, look.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes. A sunflower design, with some rather nice embellishments. And it's on the ring finger of her left hand, which means... ...it's surely a wedding ring!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It looks like it's on there for life, too. I can't imagine it would slide off a finger of that size.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...That's something to think, Mr Naruhodo, not to say. ...Do you know, Mr Garrideb's wife in the photograph had a ring very much like this one. It was a large sunflower design as well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? You have a great memory for these things. Hm, a large sunflower wedding ring... <thought>It's quite a coincidence that they have the same ring, isn't it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Are you quite concentrating? You've identified exactly what I did originally.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes...so I have. Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, I do understand. As inimitable as I am, people do like to try. But you won't make a great detective like that. Nor even a great detective's assistant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">An assistant's assistant, then...? ...Alright, I'll think again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We've already established who it was that caused all the damage in this room.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, Mr Garrideb's wife.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's just a question of finding out where she is now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">For some reason, I feel as though she's very nearby. <thought>I just need to find the evidence to prove it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your wedding ring gives us a handsome clue as to the beast's current whereabouts!</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed it does! That flowery band gleaming on your finger gives you away! For it is identical to the one shown on the hand of Mr Garrideb's bride in this photographic print!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In other words, you are no ordinary household maid.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">No... You are Mr Garrideb's lucky bride. You...are Mrs Garrideb herself!</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Oh my... WOOOOORRRRDDDD!!!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">...Well. Jolly fine detecting, sir. As you rightly surmised, this is the wife, yes. My Joan. Rather let herself go, you might say, but she was a bally corker back- AAAAAAAAAAAARGH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...It would appear that you don't live in the most comfortable of circumstances. After all, you are a retired army man, yet you are in the business of renting out rooms.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Tsk...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I would assume, therefore, that you have insufficient means to employ a maid. ...Would that be correct?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">It's not right, I tell you! I was second lieutenant of the third regiment! A man has his pride, don't you know! By golly, it's a sorry thing when a chap can't even afford to have a single maid in his employ!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, here in London, one is rather judged. A household cannot be considered worthy of society if it employs no staff at all. Though in my considered opinion, such concerns about appearances are a folly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You, you mean Mr Garrideb has his wife...work as his maid?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Precisely. ...Am I right, Mr Garrideb?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Only in company, obviously. But listen here! This must remain a secret! Tip-Top secret! Please!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Now...Mr Garrideb... ...it is plainly clear that you still have deep feelings for this formidable 'beast'. Indeed, in that blithe pose, the distress this loss has caused you is veritably tangible.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Your head weighs heavy on your shoulders. The pain you feel being revealed by that supporting arm.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes is quite something. He's still calling Mr Garrideb's wife a 'beast'.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, as a woman, that feels rather uncomfortable.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But Mrs Garrideb is standing beside her husband as we speak. In other words...he hasn't lost his beloved at all, has he?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, how true! So perhaps that supporting arm that seems to be propping up his head... ...has some other significance, then!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">According to Mr Sholmes, Mr Garrideb's pain is tangible, though. <thought>What could that pose of his really signify...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Garrideb certainly looks glum.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">According to Mr Sholmes's deduction... ...that's because he's having to endure the acute pain of losing something dear to him. But we know that he hasn't lost his wife.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So that means... ...there must be another cause for the pain he's suffering.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh my! Look at that bright red mark!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gosh, that's quite something! And clearly made by somebody's hand.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, Mr Garrideb has been slapped on the face, it seems. Hard!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I've never seen such a clearly defined mark. Whoever could have done such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...there's a very limited number of candidates, I'd say.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's a very large pipe, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, anyone who has something that size hanging out of his or her mouth on a regular basis... ...is sure to have a serious chin like Mr Garrideb's. <thought>But what's that white binding around it all about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Are you quite concentrating? You've identified exactly what I did originally.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes...so I have. Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, I do understand. As inimitable as I am, people do like to try. But you won't make a great detective like that. Nor even a great detective's assistant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">An assistant's assistant, then...? ...Alright, I'll think again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What is the cause of this acute pain that Mr Garrideb obviously feels?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's rather strange, you know. He always seems to look at us only out of the corner of his eye.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Maybe something is stopping him turning his head? <thought>Perhaps we need to consider what this pain is from another angle...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your head weighs heavy on your shoulders. The pain you feel being revealed by that slapped cheek!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And of course, the deliverer of that impressive mark on your cheek that refuses to fade... ...was you, Madam Joan Garrideb!</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Well, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You have been desperate to hide the slap mark on your cheek, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Agh! How the blazes...? How did you work that out, man?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Nothing escapes the notice of one trained in the art of observation, my dear fellow.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's why you haven't looked directly at us even once... To keep your other side from view!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Well, um... Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Now then, let us proceed to the next conundrum. Why were you subjected to such a violent slap? In other words, we must ask ourselves what caused Madam Garrideb to fly into a rage? And we need only follow the direction of your gaze to find the answer. Yes, it is this pile of bills that has given rise to the pain you suffer.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Didn't Mr Sholmes say that the bills were all for lion fodder?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, but now we've established that the lion never existed. Which can only mean that the thing responsible for gobbling up all that food... ...was Mr Garrideb's wife.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! She's a person, not a 'thing'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, well... She's also a person who gave her husband a mighty slap round the face. One so hard that it left a perfect hand mark, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, why would a woman want to hit her husband with such force, I wonder?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'd love to know the answer to that question.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Looking at all these bills, it certainly amounts to a great deal of food.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Meat and potatoes by the cart-load, wasn't it? Well, looking at the two of them... ...you can tell immediately who eats the lion's share in this household.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Well at least we're no longer talking about an actual lion any more.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, someone must be reading this book at the moment. There's a bookmark here, look. Mr Garrideb is clearly an avid reader.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...wait a minute... I...don't think this is a bookmark.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no, so it isn't! It's a note, written in a woman's hand. 'Oh James, I love you. Yours, Mary'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And look next to the signature here...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Lip marks! Made with lipstick! Oh, what a passionate and romantic gesture!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Don't get any ideas, Susato-san...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear...I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So this bookmark is actually a love note, then. Hm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So this card that looks like it's being used as a bookmark is actually a love note.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, reading, 'Oh James, I love you. Yours, Mary'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But Mrs Garrideb's first name is Joan, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes... I believe we may be heading into dangerous territory here. It's very conspicuous after all, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean the bright-red lips next to the woman's signature?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, it's the first thing you notice, of course. And it rather makes your heart skip a beat.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear, this plate has been smashed to pieces. And nobody seems inclined to tidy up the mess.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Perhaps it's some sort of high art.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Really, Mr Naruhodo...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well! Anyone who has a cannon on display in their living room is clearly a little...eccentric.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Yes, let's call it eccentricity.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There are a lot of books stacked up on the shelf here, look. All novels that I've never heard of.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It would appear somebody has purchased them all from a secondhand bookshop. I think Mr Garrideb is something of a book lover.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Are you quite concentrating? You've identified exactly what I did originally.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes...so I have. Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, I do understand. As inimitable as I am, people do like to try. But you won't make a great detective like that. Nor even a great detective's assistant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">An assistant's assistant, then...? ...Alright, I'll think again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We already know what the cause of Mr Garrideb's pain is, of course, don't we?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The slap across the cheek which left that bright-red mark.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Garrideb and his wife seem to share a very deep and loving bond.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Perhaps. But it's said that the stronger people's feelings are, the more fiercely they react to betrayal.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You seem to know a lot about the ways of the heart, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I read it in a popular novel that I borrowed from Kazuma. <thought>So we're looking for a reason why Mrs Garrideb would have felt betrayed by her husband, then!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, it is this love note that has given rise to the pain you suffer.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">'Oh James, I love you. Yours, Mary'. ...Passionate indeed. Perhaps the sender of this note, a certain Miss Mary, is the fly in the ointment here?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">GAAARGH! But! I don't know the bally woman!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You don't know her?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">That note wasn't written to me! It was just in the book. I don't know how it got there!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It was 'just' in there, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">That's right! That's what I've been say- AAAAAAAAARGH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Maid">A likely story!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Now listen here, Joan, old thing! I explained at the time! I bought the book at that secondhand place. And that note must already have been in there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...the previous owner of the book was using the note as a bookmark, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">That's right! That's what I've been say- AAAAAAAAARGH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Maid">A likely story!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">For heaven's sake, woman! Look at the name! It's written to 'James'! My name, in case you'd forgotten, is John! AAAAAAAAARGH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Maid">A likely story!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Are, are you questioning my name now?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And there we have it... Arouse the suspicions of the female heart, and you unleash a beast with a most ferocious bite.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Now...in a final fit of rage, the ferocious beast carried out one last, unimaginable attack...</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Un-Unimaginable...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...The aftermath of which can be clearly seen by observing the carpet over there! A very expensive woollen carpet, if I am not mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Oh dearie me...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What could have caused such a destructive outburst?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...This time, madam, I'm afraid it is you who has inadvertently revealed the truth to me. Your wandering eye has settled upon the answer very neatly indeed. Yes, to explain the dire state of the carpet, we need only look at the tower of cakes!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But...but surely Mrs Garrideb didn't...eat the carpet?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, of course not. But there doesn't seem to be any doubt... ...that the state of disarray that this room is in is a result of her wild temper.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...No, that's true. So, this is the last part of Mr Sholmes's deduction that we need to fix. We need only to follow Mrs Garrideb's gaze, and that will tell us the real answer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright. Let's see what we can see!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Aah... So many cakes...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah... Is that all you can think about?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well look at them, Mr Naruhodo! There is a mountain of them, and they all look so delicious!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's more of a tower than a mountain, I'd say.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's a mountain. And it's my hope that one day, in our very homeland... ...I will be able to perform the tea ceremony at the foot of such a mountain!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...It's definitely a tower.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">This looks like a very old candlestick, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The base looks too small. Surely it's very unstable. It looks to me like even the slightest knock would make it topple over.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear, that would be dangerous.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Wait, take a closer look at this! There's one candle missing!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I didn't notice that before.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Why is that, I wonder? Why is one candle of the three missing from its holder?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">This is an advertising handbill for the circus. 'Batty's Circus'... It's in a nearby park.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Isn't this the same as the one we saw earlier? The one that was folded up in Mrs Garrideb's pocket?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps they're very great circus-lovers?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... It...it couldn't be that the hungry lion is somehow involved again here, could it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear. I do hope not.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The carpet here has been ripped to shreds.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, and according to Mr Sholmes's deduction... ...the tears match those made by an Indian lion's teeth exactly!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Oh, look here!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you look closely at the edge, you can see scorch marks.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes, so you can! In that case... ...perhaps the carpet wasn't 'eaten' in the normal senses at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Let's rethink this with that in mind...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Are you quite concentrating? You've identified exactly what I did originally.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes...so I have. Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, I do understand. As inimitable as I am, people do like to try. But you won't make a great detective like that. Nor even a great detective's assistant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">An assistant's assistant, then...? ...Alright, I'll think again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The real question here is... ...was the carpet actually eaten by something, or did something else happen to it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps that would be answered by examining the carpet in more detail. If we can find another possible explanation, maybe it will lead us to the right answer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Good idea! <thought>Yes, the point is, how did the carpet end up like that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, to explain the dire state of the carpet, we need only look at the candlestick!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Most illuminating, my dear fellow! And of course, the only possible way out of this logical labyrinth.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, the remnants of a ferocious attack in which the carpet was devoured are clearly visible.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed they are. The scorch marks at the edge clearly give the truth away.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Scorch marks?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It would appear that this room was the scene of a little marital altercation.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mrs Garrideb's mighty arm muscles left an impression not only on her husband's face...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...but on the entire room. The force of her strike caused a candle to fall from the holder...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...and in seconds the carpet was alight, and the whole corner of the room in flames!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Yes, erm... Hm...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">For the most ferocious beast in this world is neither a violent lion nor a vengeful woman...but fire.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And in this room, that ferocious beast bared its claws and ran amok.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Eloquently put, my dear fellow. So you see, there is but one conclusion here:</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Mr Sholmes, sir... I salute yooooooooou!</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">It's these dashed long winter nights, you know. Nothing to do but read in front of the fire. Luckily, there's a jolly good secondhand bookshop just around the corner. Buy all my old novels there.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And in the pages of one particular novel, you discovered some rather illicit material?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">For which your wife admonished you harshly, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">I don't know about 'admonished'. 'Demolished' might be rather closer to the mark. And 'beast' is most certainly an apt des- AAAAAAAAARGH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Here we go again...</thought> And the carpet? Was that destroyed by fire when a candle fell on the floor?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">'Fraid to say it was. Happened in the blink of an eye, you know. The whole place filled with smoke. Couldn't see a bally thing. I was caught between the old stick's rage and the raging flames.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You paint a torrid picture, sir. ...One that would have been most entertaining.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's sympathy for you...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Didn't take long for the fire to spread, of course. The bally furniture started going up as well! We've had to hide the mess behind that screen for the time being.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Over here, Mr Garrideb?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, you have nothing more to hide now. If you'll allow me...</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Had all my favourite old novels in that case. But as soon as the fire got hold of them, that was it. Whoosh! Up in smoke!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gosh...</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Then the wife started hurling things at me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What a terrible sight it must have been.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">There was I, back up against the window, under heavy enemy fire! Incendiary books incoming ten to the dozen. Worst of it is, I lost my favourite. Book called 'The Lion's Pride'.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">'The Lion's Pride'? Ah yes, your notorious love of big cats coming through again.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">I assure you, the title didn't influence my choice in the slightest.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So the poor man really did lose something dear to him as a result of the ferocious 'beast's' rampage.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes's deductions turned out to be correct once again!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...It can only be described as a great British wonder.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">I tell you, it was total carnage. Flames everywhere and the old stick in full fettle!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Out of interest, what time of day was that?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Hm, not sure I can remember. It was two days ago now. Let's see... Around five o'clock, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So at exactly the same time... ...as a terrifying incident was unfolding outside your window on the street below.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Hmph. Even more terrifying on the inside, I can assure you. The whole of Blighty could have been flattened outside my window at that moment... ...and I wouldn't have noticed a dashed thing!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...really?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">.........</line>
<line speaker="Joan">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Mr Sholmes...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, Mr Naruhodo? What can I do for you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I think we've got to the bottom of Mr Garrideb's situation now. But what does it have to do with Mr Natsume's circumstances?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I can't help you there, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow, if you recall, I did say as much from the outset. I warned you that although I knew the retired army man to be hiding something... ...I could not be sure whether his secret would prove to be of relevance or not.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I... I just knew you were going to say that!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah ha ha ha ha hah! Now now, Mr Naruhodo. You mustn't lose heart. Bear in mind... ...that all things fall into one of only two categories: Those relevant to the case, and those not.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That makes no sense to me.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, no matter. It is of far greater importance that you make up your mind now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Visiting hours at the prison will soon be over.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>Oh no! Is it that time already?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">If we're to accept Mr Natsume's case... ...we have official paperwork to attend to.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>So that's it. No more time to think.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Joan">Perhaps you'd like to betake yourselves to bidding us farewell now? I must prepare supper for Mr Garrideb.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, oh yes... I'm so sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Thank you both very much for your time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Soseki-san will be waiting for us. And I'm going to have to give him an answer...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Joan">I'm terribly sorry, Mr Narrow-Hollow... ...but I'm afraid it's suppertime now. I'll have to ask you to leave.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes... I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">If we linger too long, Mrs Garrideb will start pouring tea again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...No one wants that. Alright, shall we go then? <thought>No doubt Soseki-san is beside himself in his cell, waiting for us to return. I can't afford to spend any longer making up my mind...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What a miserable sight.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear. But at least the whole room wasn't engulfed in flames.</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Hmph. I suppose so. But my whole collection went up in smoke, you know. All those novels I adored so much.</line>
<line speaker="Joan">Tsk. Well, John, whose fault is that?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Not mine, that's for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Joan">......... Well...whoever may or may not be to blame... ...I'm quite sure you can buy some new old books to replace them, can't you?</line>
<line speaker="Garrideb">Hmph! 'New old books'? Bally nonsense!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It does sound like a contradiction in terms. But then these two are full of contradictions.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Hee hee, that's couples for you, Mr Naruhodo. ...Or so I've been led to believe.</line>
<line speaker="Move to any other location except Mr Natsume's Room">19th February</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's time, Mr Naruhodo. We must hurry back to the prison!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I know. Let's hail a carr- ......... Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What's the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It looks like something's going on over there in front of the Garridebs' house.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...?</line>
<line speaker="???">I know thee not, old man: fall to thy prayers!</line>
<line speaker="???">Who are you calling an old man...you rum-lookin' niminy-piminy?!</line>
<line speaker="???">'There are more things in Heaven and Earth, Horatio,</line>
<line speaker="???">Who's this Horatio fella, eh? What are you on about?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="???">Eh? What the...? Who are you now?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm sorry, it just looked as though there might be some problem here. And my associate here, Mr Ryunosuke Naruhodo, is a lawyer, you see.</line>
<line speaker="???">Eh? A lawyer? ...What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If I can be of any assistance, I'd be happy to help. I'm from Japan, but I have studied English law.</line>
<line speaker="???">Tsk! Fine! I'll be on me way for today. But you mark my words! This ain't over yet!</line>
<line speaker="???">Get thee to a nunnery!</line>
<line speaker="???">Do I look like a bloomin' nun to you?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I do hope you're not injured?</line>
<line speaker="???">O, fair Eastern maiden, thou art so gentle! Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What was that all about?</line>
<line speaker="???">'There are more things in Heaven and Earth, Horatio,</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm...I'm not Horatio, either.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Forgive the enquiry, sir, but... ...are you a lodger here? In the Garrideb residence?</line>
<line speaker="???">O, fair Eastern maiden, thou art so right! Yes, I do dwell in this humble abode.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Mr Garrideb mentioned that he had another lodger, didn't he? This must be the man.</thought> Do you happen to know the other lodger, who lives on the first floor?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, yes. A gentleman named Natsume? O, more worthy a polemist in my battle of words ne'er could there be!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry? Battle, did you say?</line>
<line speaker="???">Who is the stronger, Hamlet or Macbeth? Mr Natsume and I sparred long into the night!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I see.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I, I don't fully understand, but it seems Mr Natsume and this gentleman are acquaintances at least.</line>
<line speaker="???">So, fair maiden! So good gentleman... ...I can tarry here no longer! Fare thee well!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I didn't really understand him, but I think he's returned to his room.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It seems he's unaware of what's happened to Mr Natsume, so he can't really help us. <thought>With Soseki-san and that man as lodgers, the Garrideb house is certainly full of eccentrics.</thought> Anyway, I'll go and find a carriage.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes. I'm sure Mr Natsume is eagerly awaiting our return!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Let's hope we can get to the prison before visiting hours are over.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... Oh! It's you! You're here! You came! Locum Student Mr Naruhodo Esquire! I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU CAME BACK! I'M SO TOUCHED!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We are so sorry to have kept you waiting, Mr Natsume.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh! No! Th-Think nothing of it! R-R-R-Relax! If, if I were a cat, I would purr with pleasure at the company of such fine compatriots.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh now, let's not get carried away.</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, I quite agree. There is nothing more reassuring than the familiarity of one's native land. On the other hand...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...it is through friendship transcending international borders that one truly appreciates the fact. Such is my belief, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Ah! Oh! It's... Yes! Agh! It's... It's YOU! THE MISERABLE, ROTTEN SPY! HERR LOCK SHOLMES!!!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes! What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I have no intention of 'doing' anything per se. Save observing, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Whatever do you mean, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, having encountered some curious reading material in that gloomful room... ...and having unmasked the secret identity of that eccentric pair... ...I decided I should drop in on my way home. To see how our divested friend is faring.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Gloomful room?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">At least your accommodation here offers a window, my dear fellow. In that sense, it is the superior option. Anyway, I must commend you on your taste in books. My day has been a delight, and cost me not a penny.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">AAARGH!!! YOUUU!!! HOW DARE YOU, HERR LOCK SHOLMES!!! ......... .........Ugh. I've had it. I'm through. I'm at the end of my rope. I should never have come to Great Britain. It was a terrible mistake. Haunted by spirits in those accursed lodgings... No doubt my luck will be cursed in tomorrow's trial as well... MY WHOLE LIFE IS BEDAMNED!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What are you thinking, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...He mentioned that once before, didn't he? That his lodgings were cursed, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And there is much truth in Mr Moustache's words.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">'Cursed' is a wholly appropriate description, I would say. For the man's lodgings...and indeed for tomorrow's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...What's that supposed to mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Natsume, what did you mean by what you said just now? About the trial tomorrow being cursed?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh no! Why, why are you looking so grave? You're m-making me nervous! I was just getting carried away, that's all! I, I didn't mean anything by it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...I see. <thought>That's really agitated him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">You... You... You don't mean...? The trial really IS cursed somehow?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Are you referring to the prosecutor? The Reaper of the Bailey?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">The, the reaper?! Oh no! What do you mean? Please! Tell me! Summarise it succinctly in sixteen salient words!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No defendant has ever survived a trial in which the Reaper stands for the prosecution...ever.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... OH MY GOODNESS! CAN IT REALLY BE TRUE?! THAT WAS SIXTEEN WORDS EXACTLY!!!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yesterday, Mr Naruhodo successfully defended someone against the Reaper. But then...after the trial was over... ...the defendant passed away in...unusual circumstances.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Mr McGilded...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Wha... Wha... Wha... WHAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, I am impressed, Miss Susato. You have an eye for detail.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Actually, the Lord Chief Justice told us.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes... ...surely it can't be that having failed the have the accused convicted... ...Lord van Zieks killed the man himself?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no! He couldn't have, surely?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Ah ha ha ha ha hah! You have some wonderful notions!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The man isn't a mass murderer; he's a court prosecutor, my dear fellow!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...yes... Why, of course he is!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Argh! 'Of course he is'?! THEN WHY ARE YOU TRYING TO SCARE ME?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It could be said, however... ...that the real truth about the man is even more terrifying than your hypothesis.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What on earth do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Van Zieks is a quite exceptional man. However, in London courts of law... ...'exceptional' does not equate to winning every case without exception.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Aah! That's, that's good!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Soseki-san looks like he's going to cry tears of joy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As you are no doubt aware, in a British criminal trial, there is both a judge and a jury. The judge officiates based on the letter of the law, whilst the jury offers public opinion and common sense. It is an excellent system, whereby the defendant's guilt is considered from several points of view. However, public opinion, in particular, is somewhat easily manipulated.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Criminals, and corrupt lawyers for that matter, can use it to their advantage. By any means at their disposal. Contriving evidence, calling imposters as witnesses, and so on. By such underhand means, those who would want to are able to sway the jury. Which means that even in the light of irrefutable evidence, the prosecution can fail.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But it means the wrong verdict can be passed!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And sadly is from time to time, my dear madam. It is simply the reality of the situation.. [sic]</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And that's alright?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">However... ...those indicted by Lord van Zieks cannot escape justice. Their fate is sealed.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Though the adjudication may see them leave the courtroom with their freedom... ...within months, they all...disappear! It is most striking.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">D-Disappear? But, but how?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, by all manner of misfortune, sir. Perhaps they are trampled under a passing carriage. Perhaps they fall into the Thames and drown. Perhaps they are suddenly overcome by a raging fever. Or perhaps attacked by highwaymen.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh no no no...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">All examples of the reality here in London, I'm afraid, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Haah... I knew it. I'm...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When you said 'accursed lodgings' before, you were referring to your room at Mr Garrideb's house, I assume? Do you mean to say you believe the place is cursed?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... It's been a year now since I came to Great Britain. But I'd only been in London a week before I started to notice strange feelings in myself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That didn't take long then.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Everywhere I looked there were foreign faces staring at me... Laughing behind my back... I, I was sure people were talking about me. I started to become nervous about going outside. They were always staring at me! All the time! From dawn till dusk! So I shut myself away in my room. ...But even that didn't help. The fear wouldn't go away.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You must have been very lonely, having been away from your homeland for such a long time.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I've had to move a number of times. Most recently, to that room on Briar Road, a week ago now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, why did you choose there? It seems a little...inconvenient.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">The rent is cheap. I have so little money, it appealed to me straight away. Of course, I asked why it was so affordable. The landlord just simpered and said: 'The room is cursed. ...Oops!' He quickly tried to cover his mistake, but it was too late. So I told him... ...if you have something to say, then say it! But if not, DON'T MENTION IT IN THE FIRST PLACE!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. ...Well said.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">But it was true! It was all t-t-true!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean... <thought>...the room really is cursed, then?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Ever since I moved into that windowless hellhole... ...my sleep has been plagued with nightmares! I awake feeling as though I'm being choked to death! And in my waking hours, people are stabbed in front of me as I walk down the street... I'm branded a killer... Thrown in prison... Nobody wants to know me... I'm, I'm...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>To believe... Yes, to believe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Mr Sholmes...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah. Me, Mr Naruhodo? Pray, what can I do for you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's about the case on the SS Burya. If you recall?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The Burya... The Burya... ...Ah, that case!  The one with the snake?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Well, yes. At that time, I was the suspect. But you believed in me and listened to my side of the story. And you helped us to investigate.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...I did, did I? Interesting.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What I want to know is...why? Why did you believe me?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I see, yes. You mean... ...because you were a grimly dressed, shady Eastern fellow found with the victim in a locked room?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, well...if you like, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm a little surprised that the answer requires explanation, my dear fellow. It's quite simple, really. You said, 'I didn't do it.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But! I could have been lying! Surely you must have had your doubts? You must have suspected me a little.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... I think perhaps you have misunderstood. I neither recall believing in you, nor in that which you were telling me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You see... ...the only things I believe in...are those I choose to believe in!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What... What do you mean, Mr Sholmes?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I make up my own mind about what is to be believed and what is not. If I should like to believe in something, I do. The circumstances can hang as far as I am concerned.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...I could have betrayed your trust!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah ha ha ha ha hah! In that case, I should have made an elementary error of judgement, nothing more. Betrayal of trust is an overused excuse, in my opinion.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Meaning...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Whether or not one should trust another is, in the final analysis, down to oneself. It is a matter of whether or not one can trust oneself.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Yes! YES! He's right! He's RIGHT, Locum Student Mr Naruhodo Esquire!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>Whether or not I can believe myself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">'A defence lawyer is only as good as his faith in his client. And that comes down to how much faith he has in himself.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>You were so right, Kazuma...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We found this receipt in your room, Mr Natsume.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">That's right. I went out to buy some new old books.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Isn't that a contradiction in terms?</thought> And, it was on your way back to your room that you saw the woman being stabbed?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">'She's dead!' I thought to myself. 'SHE'S DEAD!!!' My mind went completely blank. B-Before I knew it, I was back in my room, t-trembling like a leaf.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The bookworm hoping to worm his way out of a bad situation...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Mr Naruhodo... ...please do be careful not to think such disparaging thoughts.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>How could you possibly know...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Mr Natsume, would you take this and-</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh! The joy! The sheer joy of a gift from my fellow countryman! The Complete Kindness of Kith and Kin!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh no... Sorry, I just wanted to show you.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... The Complete Cruelty of Kith and Kin!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Oops.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Already?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Visiting hours are over. The guard will be here shortly to escort us out. There is a restaurant near here that serves excellent trout. Would you care to join me?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">...!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear. There is never enough time, is there?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... .........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm...Mr Natsume... ...if you'd like, in the trial tomorrow... ...I'd be happy to represent you.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">L...L... Locum Student Mr Naruhodo Esquire...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... As I said, I only experienced a British courtroom for the first time yesterday. And although the man I was representing was found not guilty, I lost sight of something crucial.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Something crucial?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What to believe in: the defendant, justice or the truth. How to believe, even. But...I think I've finally worked it out. I've decided I must believe in myself above all else. To trust my instincts.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And my instincts are telling me that you, Mr Natsume, are innocent of this crime. And it's imperative that we prove that in court.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Locum Student Mr Naruhodo Esquire...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I will fight for your innocence until the bitter end, with every weapon available to me. So I hope you'll permit me...to represent you tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... As I said when we first met... ...I'd like to entrust my fate to someone who will listen to me...in my native tongue.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of course, Mr Natsume.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It would be fair to say, Mr Naruhodo... ...that your mind was, in many ways, made up from the outset. You merely needed the events of today to fully realise it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes... I think you're right about that. <thought>It's been a roundabout journey, but I got there in the end.</thought> Miss Susato...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Would you be willing to stand by my side tomorrow and help me in court?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Absolutely! As I said this morning... ...you may consider me your personal judicial assistant!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The shocking events of yesterday's trial still weigh heavily on my mind. But it's time to stop looking backwards. Kazuma believed in me. And Mr Sholmes believes in me now, too. So it's time... Time that I learnt to believe in myself. Soseki-san has no one. He's all alone. So it's my job to help him. To fight his corner. Tomorrow. In the courtroom. With all the strength I can muster!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't find anything out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I've investigated thoroughly, but... I can't find anything out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What precisely was your intention with that, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just following the natural progression of the deduction! Sometimes the truth hurts!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, the truth is, you do not have a turn for observation or deduction. ...Did that hurt?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes... A lot...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What spectacularly contrived logic led you to this mindless conclusion?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, well, um...it's supposed to be a 'Logic and Reasoning Spectacular', so...I thought I'd contribute to the show!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">This is my show, Mr Naruhodo. Kindly perform any peculiar experiments on your own stage.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">That 'deduction' was wanting in every way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I was wanting you to hear it. I'm quite proud of it!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I find myself wanting never to have heard it. I'm quite pained by it, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh... Sorry. I'll try again.</line>
</xml>