
<xml>
<title>The Magical Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm fine... I'm fine... I'm Apollo Justice, and I'm fine...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Is Apollo okay? He's been muttering to himself all morning...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He's been like that since yesterday. Guess the pressure of today's trial is getting to him.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Poor Polly... He's really tearing himself up over all of this.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Get it together, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yikes! Athena! Wh-When did you get here?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Try to relax a little bit, will you? You're getting yourself way too worked up.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yeah... But I'm all right. I'm fine!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You know, I did a little digging on this Nahyuta Sahdmadhi guy... He's apparently not your run-of-the-mill prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Oh, yeah? What did you find out?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, they say he wields an incredible power... ...to accurately read a trial's karma and its ultimate fate.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What is THAT supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't have all the details, but apparently... ...he can foresee how the arguments will go, and even lead his opposition. So the defense basically ends up going in whatever direction he has in his head</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Man, this isn't going to be a cake walk, if that's true...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ema DID say she'd talk to him for us, though. Here's hoping that went well.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>In any case, it sounds like he's going to keep us on our toes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Mr. Wright is putting his faith in me. I can't let him down now!</thought> I'm fine... I'm fine. I'm fine!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">There he goes again. It's almost like he's chanting a prayer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm fine... I'm fine... I'm Apollo Justice, and I'm fine!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If you say so, Apollo...</line>
<line speaker="Guard">The trial will start momentarily. Is the defense ready?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes! WE'RE FINE! <thought>Trucy's fate and the fate of the agency rest on this trial... This is it, Justice! If ever there was a time to shine, it's now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Trucy Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And the prosecution?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Um, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi...?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...A thousand pardons. It was rude of me to keep you waiting. I was praying for the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! Praying... Yes. Yes, I see. You're a Khura'inist monk, correct, Prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Yes, that is correct. I am but a lowly monk from the Kingdom of Khura'in. I beg in advance for the forgiveness and kind patience of everyone here in this court. I am unfamiliar with the proceedings of this country, and may make many blunders.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... He seems like such a gentle-mannered soul, doesn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I wonder if Ema had a chance to talk with him about Trucy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi, your opening statement, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Certainly. In the name of the Holy Mother... ...I vow to guide the victim's soul to a land of eternal peace known as the Twilight Realm. Now, let the last rites of the victim begin.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Nahyuta Sahdmadhi... He's really been making a name for himself apparently, but... ...that nickname -- "Last Rites Prosecutor"... I wonder how that will come into play today.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The incident took place in the middle of a spectacular magic show. The accused performed a magic trick in which she thrust a sword into a coffin... ...a coffin from which the body of the victim then spilled out -- dead from a fatal stabbing. The victim's name was Manov Mistree, otherwise known as "The Great Mr. Reus." His blood was found on the sword that was used during the magic trick.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So his death was just an unfortunate accident?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It is only natural for one to assume as such, Your Honor... ...however, it was no mere accident, but rather... a homicide. The prosecution's position is thus: that this was a murder made to look like an accident.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. And you believe this crime was committed by the defendant?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...After a thorough consideration of all possible scenarios... ...I, unfortunately, had no other choice but to conclude as much.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So that's how it's going to be, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess Ema couldn't convince him after all...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. And now, let us hear from the defense.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Naturally, we maintain that the defendant is innocent, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...If the defense wouldn't mind... ...could you please explain your reasoning?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">My reasoning...? Um, well... I would have to say that my main reason is because... I believe in the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...I see. So you find it difficult to come up with anything more concrete than that, do you? What a fine demonstration of the fact that you are indeed a lawyer of putrid mind.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">..."P-Putrid mind"...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">P-Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">E-Excuse me, but I don--</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">A sutra of the Holy Mother that guides those of tainted soul toward enlightenment. It is a Khura'inist incantation to awaken the foolish from their fruitless slumber. Fitting for a lawyer who indulges in such fancy as the innocence of the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I see... So basically, you're asking the defense to "get real"?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Allow me these few words, defense. It is my duty as a monk to punish sinners, and to guide victims' souls to the Twilight Realm. Should you show repentance and admit to the accused's guilt now, no harm will come to you. But... should you interfere with my sacred last rites for the victim... ...then I shall cast you down into the pit of hell, along with Trucy Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............N-Now wait just one minute here! "Putrid"?! "Pit of hell"?! Is that any way to address someone in a court of law?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Prosecutor Sahdmadhi... That may be the way you conduct trials in Khura'in... ...but I would appreciate it if you would refrain from such charged language here.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Your Honor, that was but a Khura'inist sermon for those who have strayed from the path. Harsh words are often necessary to admonish contemptible deviants who cannot see reason.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Oh, I see... I-I didn't realize...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess they really do hate defense attorneys in Khura'in, huh. Even still, that was way, way over the top as far as verbal abuse goes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And the trial's only just begun...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, defense, I suppose the way a prosecutor does things varies by country. Why don't we look at this as cross-cultural exchange and try to be open-minded about it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff, please bring in the first witness. </line>
<line speaker="Ema">MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Uh-oh. I thought she'd "said goodbye" to the Snackoos...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............Detective Skye! The courtroom is no place for gorging yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">......What's wrong with having a little snack? Girl's gotta eat, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">She, uh, seems a little stressed out.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Detective Skye, your testimony, please.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Y-Yeah, about that... I just want to state for the record that... I believe Trucy Wright is innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I'm sorry?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Detective Skye, this path you seek to follow is misguided. Giving the wrongdoer false hope will only deepen her despair in the end.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But I...!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Let it go, and move on. Acts which go against your duty will earn you divine punishment from the Holy Mother.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">! ............MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH CHEW CHEW CHEW... ...Fine. I don't know about the "divine" part, but I get the "punishment" bit loud and clear...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess Ema got assigned tons of paperwork or something for sticking up for Trucy...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She and Prosecutor Sahdmadhi don't seem to get along very well, do they?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Shall we continue? The prosecution contends that the accused had a clear motive. The evidence, if you would, Detective Skye.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">All right... Please take a look at this poster. It's a Troupe Gramarye poster from thirteen years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hm?&amp; Is it just me or is it a little different from the one in Ms. Wright's dressing room?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This is a revised version of that poster.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This one says "CANCELED" under Mr. Reus.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's right. Mr. Reus left the troupe after the first version of the poster was printed. Take a look at Mr. Reus's right forearm, near his elbow. See the big scar there? He apparently got that when he made a mistake while practicing a magic trick.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ouch. That's quite a scar...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Because of the accident, Magnifi Gramarye concluded Mr. Reus was too unskilled. Just before the show was to open, Magnifi announced Mr. Reus wouldn't be appearing. But in defiance of Magnifi's decision, Mr. Reus tried to go on stage anyway. This, in turn, caused Magnifi to oust Mr. Reus from the troupe on the spot.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He kicked Mr. Reus out? That seems rather extreme. Did he really have to go that far?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">When it came to magic, Troupe Gramarye was so passionate... ...or should I say "extreme," about it that it caused problems for them from time to time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, they even caused this court a mountain of trouble with their extreme antics.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And now, the troupe's successor has committed a murder. It seems the troupe's rare talent was inherited by the right person after all. A putrid talent for criminality.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............Y-You sound rather extreme yourself, Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Criminals with impure souls do not deserve sympathy, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ahem! As I was saying... After his expulsion, Mr. Reus apparently went on to hold a grudge against the troupe. He would tell those close to him, "I will get my revenge on Troupe Gramarye someday!"</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Revenge, hmm? That certainly sounds antagonistic.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And then, his chance for revenge finally came. If you would be so kind, Detective Skye?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...I guess I don't have a choice, do I?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The victim planned to get his revenge on Troupe Gramarye during Trucy's magic show.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">By the time the accused had discovered the notebook's theft, it was too late. Her only option was to kill Mr. Reus, and make it look like an accident.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... Well, that isn't exactly a great starting point for a rebuttal, is it...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're telling me...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Allow me to give you one piece of advice, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh? And what's that?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Let it go, and move on.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Helping a sinner will only sully your own soul. One possessed of an unclean soul will burn in the flames of hell... ...and then be ever burdened with that sin in their next life.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But I don't believe in that sort of thing... Besides, I have no intention of giving up!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">O Holy Mother, grant me the strength to deal with this putrid lawyer. All actions have consequences, and yours will surely earn you the honor of being... ...a mere stink bug, at best, in your next life.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A stink bug?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Stink Bu-- I mean, Mr. Justice. Your cross-examination, please.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The victim planned to get his revenge on Troupe Gramarye during Trucy's magic show.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...I know, right? I thought that was pretty sketchy, myself. I mean, wouldn't he have done it a long time ago, if he was gonna do it? After all--</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Detective Skye, self-indulgent outbursts such as those will earn you divine punishment. In the form of a salary evaluation.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Eep! .........MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait, THAT'S what "divine punishment" means?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Let the detective have her snack. This humble servant of the Holy Mother shall explain. Over a decade ago, Troupe Gramarye was at the height of their popularity. But then their reputation declined, and they had all but faded from public memory. Until recently, that is, when Trucy Wright sought to recapture their former glory.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defendant? And at such a young age, too! How impressive!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Yes, the accused's skill at magic is undeniably impressive. If she hadn't fallen onto the path of sin, she would have had a bright future ahead of her.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It's always sad to see such promising young potential go to waste... Now, then, Detective Skye. How did Mr. Reus plan to get his revenge? And please put down the Snackoos before you continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH. ...Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Reus was going to first steal the Gramarye notebook from the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...Well, you see... I... ...MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, whenever you're ready, Detective...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Fret not, Detective Skye. You have nothing to repent for. You should be proud of the fine forensic discovery that you made.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Forensic discovery"? And what did she discover, specifically?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Detective Skye identified a certain set of fingerprints on the notebook. Upon further inspection, she determined that they belonged to Mr. Reus.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The detective found the fingerprints entirely of her own volition. For that, I must say well done, Detective Skye.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Urk! ...MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Get a little too addicted to using your precious white powder, did you, Ema?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Now, Detective Skye, I would ask you to explain... ...exactly how Mr. Reus intended to use the notebook to exact his revenge.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">All right... Well, first, he stole the notebook...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He then intended to reveal the secrets behind their magic tricks during the show.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Right, but he didn't exactly specify which "Gramarye secrets" he was talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But the prosecution thinks he was referring to&amp; the secrets behind Troupe Gramarye's magic?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Yes, that is the prosecution's assertion. When the accused realized that Mr. Reus was to reveal... ...her family's most closely-guarded secrets, she naturally panicked.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So basically... ...Trucy's notebook was hiding in Mr. Reus's things because he had stolen it himself?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... Truly, a motive that only a magician could have.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...Yes. That's what the prosecution believes, anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That was the victim's plan for revenge. And while he did, in fact, steal the notebook...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">O-Of course I don't think that! The Trucy we know would neve--!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............Keep your private considerations separate from your public duty. I warned you about this very thing before the trial began, did I not, Detective Skye?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">! ...Y-Yes, you did.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Please recite my exact words to you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">"Ema Skye, you are a detective first and foremost, not the accused's friend." "Remember your duty and fulfill it faithfully."</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Excellent. So you DO remember what I said to you. Your devotion to your work will be rewarded, for the Holy Mother sees all.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH... This "Holy Mother" is no scientific concept I've ever heard of.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Those two REALLY don't get along, do they?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, science and religion go together about as well as oil and water...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um, as I was saying...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...the defendant murdered him before he had a chance to reveal the secrets.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">............Beats me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What...? The basis is "beats me"...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You'll have to ask Prosecutor Sahdmadhi over there, because... ...he hasn't told ME his reasoning, either. ...MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Detective Skye. Your feeding of information to the defense has not gone unnoticed by my eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ulp!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The bad karma of acts which go against your duty will impinge upon you in your next life. But, even before that, it may impinge upon your job in the form of a transfer...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ack! P-Please don't get me kicked out of the forensics unit! Anything but that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Poor Ema... She's really been risking everything for us.</thought> Well, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi? What are your grounds for claiming homicide?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It was the luminous tape in the understage passage.I realized that it had been moved. Moved so that Mr. Reus would climb up into the downstage coffin by mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Mr. Reus, who was waiting in the understage passage... ...was supposed to have used the upstage ladder, shown here on the left. He was to climb up into the coffin that had been set up in the backstage area. After being turned into a stuffed dragon during Act One... ...Mr. Reus was supposed to come back to life and emerge from that coffin. But the luminous tape had been moved to mark the downstage ladder... ...so the victim climbed up into the coffin on the stage itself by mistake. The very same coffin the accused thrust her sword into.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A-And you have proof that it was my client who moved the tape?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">But of course. ...Detective Skye?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hm? ............Oh, that's right! ...I identified the defendant's fingerprints on the luminous tape.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-You WHAAAT?! <thought>He actually had proof?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Well, defense? Are you finally ready to let it all go, and move on?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A-Absolutely not!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Detective, please add the information about the prints on the tape to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The defendant's prints were on the tape. I guess she must've moved it during the show.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...W-Well...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I bet it was "detective's intuition"!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...I dusted not just the tape, but just about everywhere for fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I dusted pretty much every single surface in the theater. I mean, it was so nice to be able to dust for prints without anybody getting mad at me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's great that you're enthusiastic, Ema, but there IS such a thing as too enthusiastic...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to: </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's try to draw out all that we can from Ema's testimony. Knowing her, I'm sure she'll try to help us out as much as she can.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right. As long as Prosecutor Sahdmadhi doesn't cut her off at the pass, that is...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The tape was moved... ...to guide Mr. Reus into the coffin that was downstage...? If that's true, it DOES sound like a murder rather than an accident.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It certainly doesn't help that Trucy's prints are on the tape.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I wish I knew what sound would even be appropriate to make in this situation...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sorry, Detective Skye, but there's a flaw in your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh! Really?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The prosecution is claiming that Ms. Wright moved the understage tape during the show... ...in order to guide the victim into the coffin downstage. But it doesn't make sense that she would leave prints on the tape at that time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It doesn't?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Please consider the fingerprinting results of the main coffin... ...which shows that not one of my client's fingerprints was found on or in it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's true... We didn't find any of her prints on that coffin. ............Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think you've realized what the flaw in your testimony is. Claiming Ms. Wright left prints on the tape during the show is inconsistent with the facts. Because she was wearing gloves during the show.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She must've left the prints sometime BEFORE the show started. In other words, her prints do NOT prove she moved the tape to mislead the victim. The prosecution's investigation was insufficient!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, my! ............But, on a personal level, I'm very happy about that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi? If the defense's argument is true... ...then you have no evidence the defendant moved the tape to deceive the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I see... Apparently, the defense is more intelligent than I had thought... More than a stink bug, at any rate.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Come on. You can bump me up to at least a stag beetle now, can't you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Would that really be any better?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of course! WAY better! Stag beetles are cool, with those huge mandibles of theirs!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">If the defense wishes to be promoted to a stag beetle... ...then answer me this question.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All right. Shoot.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Even with no evidence that the accused moved the tape to misguide the victim... ...the victim still climbed the ladder, using the tape as a guide... ...and entered the coffin on the stage. The accused then thrust her sword into said coffin with the victim in it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So what you're saying is, the fact remains that the victim was stabbed to death, right?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Precisely. However, this does drastically change one aspect of this case: If the accused did not lead the victim into the coffin on purpose... ...then it means the victim's death could have been accidental. If it was indeed an accident, the defense can argue that it was involuntary manslaughter.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... If it was involuntary manslaughter, they could plead extenuating circumstances. And the severity of the crime could be mitigated.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Defense, if you believe the accused did not murder the victim... ...then do you argue that it was an accident?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is it -- the all-important question.</thought> The defense argues that Mr. Reus's death was...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense believes this incident was an unfortunate acci--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Oops.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So the defense argues that the victim's death was an accident, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>No, because I definitely can't allow Trucy to be implicated in the stabbing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense maintains that the defendant is entirely innocent. We believe that it wasn't an accident, but murder. And, what's more, we believe it was committed by a third party.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A-A third party?! As in the true culprit is someone else?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Hmph. That is quite a brazen claim to make -- and one wholly without grounds. our voice is as loud as your suit, and your mind echoes just as loudly in emptiness. Surely, you were but a loud red pepper in your previous life.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I've been demoted to a vegetable?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow... I didn't know a person could be reincarnated as a non-sentient plant...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-In any case! I DO have grounds to make this claim!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............Let us hear this reasoning of yours, then.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All right. But before I give it, there is one question that we need to address. If the victim was killed by some third party... ...then the sword the defendant thrust into the coffin wasn't the cause of death. If that's the case, then how did we wind up with a dead body inside the coffin?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now let's hear your opinion, Mr. Justice. How did the victim's body wind up inside the coffin?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I suppose the victim might have been killed inside the coffin.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Exactly. And who was the one who thrust the sword into the coffin?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It was Ms. Wright, of cour-- Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Your Honor, it would appear the defense has finally given up. Please render your verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Did you really think such verbal acrobatics would get you off the hook?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, if only I could've stuck the landing better...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why don't you try again, defense?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense would like to contend that it was magic. I've seen that kind of trick before. Money appearing in an empty box, for example.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. And how does a trick like that work? What's the secret to it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The appeal of magic is in the mystery, wouldn't you agree, Your Honor? Sometimes it's better to just accept it for what it is -- enjoy it, and move on.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...The real mystery here... is how you passed the bar exam, Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All right, let's just move on then, shall we...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why don't you try again, defense?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What if the victim was killed under the stage before being put into the coffin? In other words, what if the victim was already dead in the coffin from the get-go?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, I see! In that case, the defendant's sword wouldn't have been the cause of death. How do you respond, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............That is the third time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The third time of what?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Hyah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ Wh-What the heck is this?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh! Owowowowow! M-My heaaaaaaaad! What do you think you're doing?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">"Even the merciful Holy Mother loses patience if she is struck three times." Since you never learn, you needed to be punished.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why don't you let ME worry about what I need and don't need?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It is what you deserve for interfering with my sacred last rites for the victim. You are a brainless lawyer chasing phantoms. You know nothing. Let this humble servant of the Holy Mother give you an edifying sermon.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A sermon? Now?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">There is a passage in the sacred scriptures of Khura'inism. "A cornered frog will swallow even a snake."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........A cornered lawyer has unexpectedly struck back hard against the prosecution. Did I get it right?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">No, for I am not done with my sermon. "And yet, the frog still dies, its belly bitten and torn from within."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just great...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And in this case, you are that frog, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um, what exactly is your point, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Let us assume for a moment that the victim was killed under the stage. Who, then, had the opportunity to do so during the show?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's see... The people in the show were...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Bonny de Famme, the victim Mr. Reus, and Trucy Wright. Bonny de Famme was onstage throughout the entire show... ...as easily confirmed by the footage from the show. Which leaves us with only one suspect: Trucy Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Agnk!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Now do you see? The accused killed Mr. Reus as he waited on standby in the understage passage... ...and then placed his dead body in the coffin above. Thus making the murder look like an accident!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nooooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">O great and merciful Holy Mother... Thus, another putrid mind has been guided toward enlightenment.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh... I can't believe I swallowed his trick question whole.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena? What are you...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There's something I want to point out, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And who might you be? You strike me as a mere child in countenance.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I may be young... ...but I have an attorney's badge just the same!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And you would contribute to this discussion in that capacity?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I most certainly would! You just argued that the defendant killed the victim under the stage. But let me remind you that Ms. Wright... is a girl.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Clearly. Surely you didn't raise an objection simply to point out such an obvious fact? Your Honor, please send for this little child's guardian to come take her home.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You don't need to talk like Prosecutor Sahdmadhi, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Listen. If the victim was killed in the understage passage... ...then his body would then have to be hauled up to the stage, right? However... ...Ms. Wright is a young girl -- and a pretty petite one, at that. She couldn't possibly have hefted that large body up and put it in the coffin!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's true! It does seem like it would be a rather difficult task for the defendant... I don't think even I could do it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What do you think of that, Prosecutor?! Who's the child now?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">In my religion, the priestesses of Khura'inism are revered as the pillars of our beliefs. So I naturally hold nothing but deep respect for women. I also think highly of the female perspective.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Says the man who called this fair maiden a "little child"...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Who's a "fair maiden"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I agree that your point is worth discussing, defense. How, indeed, was the dead body raised up into the coffin? By the accused, Trucy Wright, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're committed to pointing the finger at her no matter what, huh! Then YOU explain how that'd even be possible!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">But of course. There was a way for even a small creature like her to raise the victim's body up.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Wait! You really CAN explain it?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I foresaw that our arguments would come to this, so I have prepared a witness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, well. I admire your readiness, Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It is really not that difficult when one can read the ultimate outcome of any trial.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He couldn't have REALLY predicted that things would turn out like this, could he?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's pretty hard to believe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">...Excuse me, but may I step down now?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes, I suppose you may.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">One moment, Detective Skye.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">! U-Um... I'm sorry... for, you know... the way I handled all of this...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You did a fine job, Detective. Your testimony was invaluable.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It was?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Yes. You served well as a detective, and did not allow your personal feelings to interfere. You overcame the conflicted emotions you felt and performed your duty admirably. You will be rewarded for your fine work.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">............Oh! Uh, thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I hope we can work together again in the future.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ema seems bewildered by the unexpected praise.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess he's a pretty nice person like they say -- as long as you're not up against him.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then. Let us call the next witness.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Witness, please state your name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Hello, ladies and gentlemen of the court! It's very nice to meet all of you! I'm a lagomorph-ing illusionist from the land of fairy tales, Bonny de Famme! I can't wait to do some magic tricks for all of you!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Please, witness... There is a time and a place for all things, including magic.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Aw! B-But... But it would be okay if I do just a LITTLE magic, right? Come on! Please? Look! Everybody is waiting! Now's my chance to shine!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">That is your second time...</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">My second time doing what?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...There will be no further warnings. You should know that from our preparatory meeting, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Yeep!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is no one exempt from His Holiness's rosary of suffering...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">May we have your testimony, witness? Once you've recovered from your disappointment...</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Well, as a huge fan of Trucy's... ...I don't really want to testify against her... But I guess I have to... don't I?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>As a "huge fan of Trucy's," huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I hate her. I LOATHE her! I can't stand that Trucy Wright! Just because she's a little good at magic, she thinks she's all that! So this is exactly what that sniveling brat deserves!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sure, you're a real fan, all right... Of destroying Trucy, you mean.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I really can't believe that Trucy killed Mr. Reus...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were onstage the whole time...? And you're sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">There is no question. The entire audience could testify to that fact. What's more, she is shown clearly in the TV show footage as well.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I couldn't possibly have killed Mr. Reus! Not little old me!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Therefore, the only person who could have killed the victim understage is the accused. Furthermore, by using a stage lift, even a petite young lady... ...could have raised the body up to the stage without difficulty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>You've gotta be kidding me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The defense may now cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I really can't believe that Trucy killed Mr. Reus...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Oh, yes! I even became a magician because I wanted to be just like her! The first time I saw her, she was performing at the Wonder Bar. She was only in junior high back then, but she got up on stage with tons of confidence. And then, she proceeded to win my heart with her astonishing tricks and winning smile!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... She certainly sounds like she means all of that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, finally being able to perform with her must have been quite a treat for you, right?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Oh, yes! After all, it was my chance to have her see me... ...not just as a fan, but as a fellow magician! ............But then that horrible accident happened...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............It was not an accident. It was murder. Witness, please explain, if you would... ...how a small young woman such as Trucy Wright could have raised the body.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I guess it's possible for a small girl to lift a dead body up if she used a stage lift...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Well, uh... Actually, we did try it out for ourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You did?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Detective Skye, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh! ...S-So that's why you made me do that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Detective Skye, what did he have you do?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The prosecutor asked me to try raising one of the male police officers with the stage lift. Without a single word of explanation as to WHY he was making me do it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're kidding...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's as if he really CAN foresee all of our counterarguments...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Hmph. Do not underestimate this humble servant of the Holy Mother.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">More like "haughty"...</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I guess that means Trucy COULD have lifted the dead body up... Does that mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Is it possible...? Could Trucy really have...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Eek! Well, I-I...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't try to beat around the bush! Come right out and say it. Why not tell this court what you REALLY believe?!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">What I REALLY believe? Of course I... Of course I don't believe Trucy could ever commit murder! Such an amazing and wonderful magician would never do such a thing! But... taking all the facts into account... what else can I think?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I know of at least three other unflattering things you REALLY think about Trucy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">How can you attack this girl when she is obviously speaking with reserve?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There is such a thing as "reading between the lines," Mr. Justice. It's sad how the youth of today lack the ability to do such a basic thing. ............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Looking at me like that isn't going to help me stick my foot in my mouth less, Your Honor.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Witness, please describe what the accused might have used to lift the dead body.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">All right...</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">If Trucy did use a stage lift, I think she must've used stage lift #2...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">That's right. With a stage lift... ...I'd think even a small girl could easily lift a dead body up to the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And so that makes her the murderer, in your opinion?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">O-Of course not! I believe in Trucy! Like I said, I'm a huge fan of hers!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, brother. How long is she gonna keep this act up?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Defense, what position was stage lift #2 in after the show?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's see... If I recall, it was in the fully raised position. ...AHHH!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And the reason why it was fully raised... ...is because the accused used it to lift the victim's body. Wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nnngggh...!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Feel free to slowly mull it over while you roast over the flames of hell, you evil red pepper!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So now I'm also "evil"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I was onstage for the entire show, by the way.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">D-Don't tell me you suspect ME now?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm just trying to do my job by fully examining our alibi. Depending on how solid it is, I might have to suspect you, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">...You gotta be kidding me! Don't spit on my head and tell me it's raining, lawyer boy! I'm right there in the footage! Or are you too much of an idiot to see?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Ms. de Famme? Are you feeling all right? You seem... suddenly different...</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">............Oh, uh, oops! Where did THAT come from, right? Oh, my! I seem to have snapped there for a second, didn't I? Tee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>You didn't just snap -- you broke character just now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">In any case, I was onstage the whole time, performing magic! I mean, you saw me in the footage, right? My dazzling and flawless performance?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Flawless"? That's odd, considering what you told me. You said that you'd made a mistake with where you positioned Mr. Hat.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Ngh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. de Famme, to what is the defense referring?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">W-Well, I made a little mistake on stage... I was in charge of operating Mr. Hat, you see. According to the script, I was supposed to place him to the left of the coffin. But I flubbed it up, and made him stand to the right of the coffin instead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And because of that mistake... ...Trucy had to move the stage lifts around.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I feel really bad about messing Trucy up like that with my goof. Tee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wonder if it's really possible for a small girl to lift a dead body up like Bonny claims.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess it's possible with a stage lift...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prosecutor Sahdmadhi also said Trucy was the only one who could've done it understage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This testimony sure isn't doing our case any favors...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Hee hee hee! NOW do you know who the real killer is?! C'mon, Gramps! Don't just sit there! Hand down your ruling, pronto! Do it quick, before you keel over up there!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I beg your pardon?!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Oops! Oh, what's gotten into me? I'm so sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I give her another five minutes before she tears off that mask...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Well, defense? Are you ready to let it all go now?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">O-Of course not! l I'll never give up!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I see. I suppose this too, is fate. The sacred scriptures of Khura'inism describe a variety of hells for the damned. For someone like you, who struggles ceaselessly against his fate... ..."Pahpul Boljhig" seems most appropriate.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"People boil--" WHAT?! <thought>Oh, wait, that's Khura'inese...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What sort of terrible place is "Pahpul Boljhig"?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">A place where the more one struggles, the further one falls into the abyss. At the bottom of the abyss, a ferocious beast awaits. Think of it as something akin to an antlion's sand pit trap.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, there's one of those in my backyard!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow. Khura'inist hell is closer to home than I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then. It would appear that the witness's testimony supports the prosecution's claims... ...that the defendant is the only one who could have killed the victim understage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Grk... <thought>How are we supposed to get out of this jam?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Hey, Apollo? If you can't find any contradictions... ...maybe it's time to use analytical psychology!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I heard some discord in Bonny's voice while she was testifying.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">See? Widget is picking up on the noise in her heart, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's right. Athena can hear things others can't with her super-sensitive hearing. She can hear the emotions people suppress as a kind of noise or discord in their voices.</thought> ...All right, Athena. Let's give it a try.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You got it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">She is?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, what with that terrible death on stage... ...and her beloved Trucy getting arrested, she's under awful strain and shock. In fact, I don't know how much more she can take before she is unfit to testify.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I've heard of that. What is it called? "Postal Stress Disorder," right? It's where a person becomes uncontrollably angry, I think... I read about it somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...That's "going postal," Your Honor. This is PTSD.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my. So that's why the witness acts so hostile at times -- as if she were a different person.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes. And I think her condition is clouding her memory of the incident. Therefore, I suggest a short therapy session for the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Bonny:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Cykes, please do whatever you can to help this unfortunate young lady.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And what exactly is this child planning to do, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">With her super-sensitive hearing, Ms. Cykes can hear a witness's true emotions. Simply from tone and inflection, she can tell exactly what a person is feeling.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can even pick out feelings that a witness is trying to suppress or hide. Widget projects the emotions I hear into the Mood Matrix, where I can analyze them.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It sounds like some sort of spurious devilry. Though I find it hard to believe, I must ask: How do emotions constitute evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... While I won't say that emotions can be taken as evidence, per se... ...I have seen how instrumental Ms. Cykes's work has been in cracking a case. Therefore, I wholly support giving it a try.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...I see. If you are in favor of it, Your Honor, then I have no objections. Even this mere monk can see that something disturbs the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Hmph! I'll disturb YOU!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, thank you for understanding, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi! Apollo, you remember how to conduct a therapy session, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You want ME to lead the session?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course. You're the lead on this case, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Fair enough. But, hmm... Do I need a refresher?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, but I think I could use a refresher. So Bonny's emotions are shown here in the Mood Matrix, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Exactly. The emotions I pick up on from her testimony are projected into this program. The Mood Matrix gives a visual representation of a witness's testimony and emotions. These four mood markers reflect fluctuations in a witness's emotions. As testimony unfolds, the mood markers flash in reaction to the witness's feelings. When the witness feels happy or is enjoying the memory, the "Happy" marker will light up. When the witness feels angry or frustrated, the "Angry" marker will react. When the witness feels sad or is scared by a memory, the "Sad" marker will blink. And when the witness feels surprised or confused, the "Surprised" marker will tell us.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay. I remember now. I need to find a conflict between what she's saying and which mood markers are blinking?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right. And Ms. de Famme definitely has some conflicted emotions! See?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Widget reacts to the suppressed emotions I pick up and projects them as noise. If we can pinpoint the inconsistencies between her testimony and her feelings... ...the noise level should drop to 0%, and the therapy session will be a success! When you find an unexpected emotion, touch "Pinpoint" <thought>L</thought>... ...and then select the unexpected emotion or reaction from the four mood markers.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Okay. Now to give it a whirl.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think I still remember from the last time, let's get right into it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okey-dokey. You ready, Widget?</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Let's do this!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I guess Trucy is the one who killed Mr. Reus...</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Even she could move the body with that lift.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I was onstage at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">But that terrible mistake...</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">...My stupid flub caused Trucy so much trouble!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I feel so bad about it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, so I look for inconsistencies between her testimony and her emotions, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right. Like if she says "I was so happy!" when the "Sad" marker is lit up... ...or if the "Sad" marker doesn't react, even though she says she was feeling down. When you find an unexpected emotion, go ahead and "Pinpoint" it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Okay. I'll give it a try.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I have to say, Ms. de Famme, you certainly are a strange one. Even though you said, "I feel so bad about it," it seems you were feeling happy about it.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Nnnnnngh... Ouch!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think I can guess why you were feeling happy. It must be because...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think you were happy because it was Ms. Wright's big debut. You're a big fan of hers, after all, right?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">You kidding me, forehead boy?! Why in the world would I be HAPPY about HER debut?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What did you just say, Ms. de Famme? I thought you said you were Trucy Wright's biggest fan?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Oopsy! Y-Yes, of course I was happy for her! Ho ho ho!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Her act is starting to get pretty sloppy...</thought> All right. If that wasn't it, then maybe it was something else.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think you were happy because of your own mistake. Maybe you don't have confidence in yourself, so your mistake gives you a reason to quit.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Me? Lack confidence?! What a bunch of hooey! I've got confidence oozing out of every pore on my body! If I could bottle it, I'd be rich!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... Well, it certainly wouldn't be off of MY money... Look, just let me try one more time, Ms. de Famme.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think you were happy because you messed the defendant up.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Nnnnnnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm right, aren't I?!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Y-Y-You gotta be kidding me! Why would I be happy I messed Trucy up?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Because we saw you.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I hate her. I LOATHE her! I can't stand that Trucy Wright! Just because she's a little good at magic, she thinks she's all that! So this is exactly what that sniveling brat deserves!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We saw how you said you hated Trucy Wright. How you were glad she was in trouble and even how it was "what she deserved."</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Ouch.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It looks like I hit the bunny on the head, so to speak.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">............Nnngrr...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, the noise level dropped! Now if we could get it down to 0%...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Well, Ms. de Famme? Are you ready to confess how you really feel?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">...Wh-What? What do you mean? I'm Bonny -- the sweet, cute little bunny! I'm a rookie magician working hard to be just like my idol, Trucy! That's the character I'm supposed to be!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Wh-Who I really am?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The two sides of you are fighting each other and doing you psychic harm. I can hear them -- two distinct voices battling inside you.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Sh-Shut your pie hole, you know-nothing know-it-all! Urk! I-I mean, you mustn't say things like that, or I might get flustered!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ms. de Famme, how long do you insist on maintaining this wolf in sheep's clothing act? We can't end this therapy session until you get real with us. Set the wild beast inside you free!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Ouch. Urrgh... ...Grrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Don't make me laugh! You don't know a dang thing about me. You wanna see who I really am? Fine! Take a good look!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Kee hee hee... Kee kee kee kee!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What in the world...?!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Sheep's clothing?! You've got it all wrong! It's a rabbit suit I've got on! And I'm not a wolf. I'm a blood-sucking vampire! A bat with fangs and wings! Kee hee hee! Kee kee kee kee kee!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeek! I-I think we just opened Pandora's box...</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Kee kee kee kee! I'm finally done with that goody-two-shoes cottontail act! I feel free as a bat! Kee kee kee!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defense! Your "therapy session" has taken a turn for the worse, from the looks of it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-There's... a perfectly good explanation for this... isn't there, Ms. Cykes?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um... Eh heh... Methinks I created a monster...</line>
<line speaker="Widget">We blew it!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Hey, you! Lobster boy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Who, ME?!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">You think I'm glad Trucy is in trouble -- that I think she's getting her just desserts? Well, guess what... ...you're right! Kee hee hee! Kee kee kee kee!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... Does this mean you admit to wishing the defendant harm?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Well, the bat is out of the bag now! Kee hee hee! That mistake of mine was a work of art! Thanks to my goof, poor little Trucy had to do all of that hard physical labor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When you say "hard physical labor," what are you referring to?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Because of Mr. Hat's new position, Trucy had to move both of those huge stage lifts!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">They must've been sooo heavy... What a riot! Kee hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's strange...</thought> Athena, could you please add that last statement to Bonny's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">All right. I'll update the Mood Matrix with the new info. ......Hm? Hey, Apollo. Now there's a new inconsistency in the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. She finally slipped up. So what do I need to do now?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, from this point onward, you just do what you do best. Find the contradiction in the testimony and present evidence to refute it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>All right. I've got you now, Bonny de Famme!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I guess Trucy is the one who killed Mr. Reus...</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Even she could move the body with that lift.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I was onstage at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">You know what? Serves her right! Kee kee kee kee!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Thanks to that, she ended up having to move the stage lifts.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's definitely a contradiction in her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So just present evidence like you always do. And since we finally found something, I'd say we can call the therapy session a success!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You call Batsy McBatty over there a "success"...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That doesn't make sense.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">What?! So you think I'm crazy now?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No. That's not the point I was trying to make.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">But I don't hear you denying it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ms. de Famme, allow me to repeat your statement: "Thanks to that, she ended up having to move the stage lifts."</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Kee hee hee! That's right! And I still say that's just what she deser--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But how did you know? How did you know Ms. Wright moved the stage lifts?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">According to her own statement... ...she didn't tell anyone that she had done so.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">WH-WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So how could you possibly have known what she had done, unless... you saw her...? You saw Ms. Wright moving the lifts in the understage passage, didn't you!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You did it, Apollo! Noise levels are at 0%!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But, Mr. Justice! Wouldn't that mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, Your Honor. Ms. de Famme herself was under the stage where the victim was killed. And I hardly need to tell the court what that means...</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Nnnnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You are one artful liar, Ms. de Famme, and one spectacular suspect!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Keeyaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh! Wh-Why, you shiny red lobster boy! You're saying I killed Mr. Reus?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm saying that it's a possibility. What's more... ...I say you had a solid motive to frame my client for the murder as well.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, really?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The TV footage. As you can clearly see... ...Ms. de Famme was on the stage the whole time. The entire audience can bear witness to that fact -- including you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You have just taken a long and senseless journey, only to return to the starting line. The witness could not have been in the understage passage, which means... ...the only one left who could have killed the victim is the accused!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Guess the party's over.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nnngh... B-But... ...Ms. de Famme knew something she couldn't have known unless she was under the stage! How do you explain that, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It's quite simple: The accused must have told Ms. de Famme about it, but then forgot.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hrrrmm...</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Ha! Open those useless eyes of yours and take a good look at the footage!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... If Ms. de Famme really WAS in the understage passage... ...it would mean she was onstage and understage at the same time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean, she was in two places at once? ...........That does seem to be the only explanation that makes any sense...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It may be an "explanation," but I'm not so sure about the "makes sense" part.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then we'll just have to MAKE it make sense! Your Honor, the witness was both onstage and understage at the same time. That is the defense's assertion!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........Hmm... I've heard some illogical things come out of you before, but this is absurd.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sure you'll change your tune once you hear my reasoning, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">My gut tells me you're bluffing but I'll bite. Very well, Mr. Justice. How do you explain how the witness was in two places at once?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's not forget that Ms. de Famme's specialty is teleportation magic. With teleportation, she can be in two places at practically the same time!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............So you believe that teleportation actually exists?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, you know what magicians always say about their magic: "It's all real! No tricks or gimmicks involved!"</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............Well, I have listened patiently to your reasoning... ...and the only thing dispelled is the false air of competency you tried to project.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ha ha, I see what you did there. Good one, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho ho. You might be surprised to hear this, but... ...I used to be known as the "Jokester Judge"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Well, at least I avoided a penalty with some well-placed brown-nosing.</thought> Please let me try again, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The Bonny de Famme onstage was fake.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">F-Fake? Really...?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Such an assertion is not something one would expect to hear from a genuine lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! Maybe YOU are the fake, and your attorney's badge is made out of cardboard!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, no! I'm the real thing, I swear! ...And why cardboard, specifically...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's just say I had an infuriating experience once thanks to one... In any case, your fake Bonny theory doesn't sound very convincing.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's not a bad idea, in theory... ...but I think the one on the stage was the real Bonny. You can just tell.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If the one on the stage wasn't fake... ...does that mean the one understage was real, too...?</thought> Please let me try again, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............There were two Bonnys, Your Honor. If that were the case, it would all make sense, wouldn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There were...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Two of them?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I suspected you had a few screws loose, but now I see some are missing altogether. Is there a tool kit in this courtroom, Your Honor? I suppose two... no, three screws to the head should righten his putrid brain...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well. Bailiff, could you--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. I suppose it wouldn't hurt to at least give it a listen.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">As was argued earlier... ...Ms. de Famme is shown in the footage the whole time. But, at the same time, she was also watching Ms. Wright in the understage passage. The only possible explanation is that there are two Bonnys.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That almost sounds like it makes sense...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you think, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............This humble servant of the Holy Mother is of the opinion... ...that we should lose no time in replacing the defense's many lost screws.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But, Apollo, it goes against reality itself to say that one person is actually two.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But we don't have to be bound by reality -- after all, we're talking about magic here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, if the Bonny de Famme in the footage is the real Bonny... ...then the Bonny here on the witness stand, the one who must've been understage... This Bonny de Famme... ...is our "second Bonny."</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Keeeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">She is?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Say we call the one in front of us "Bonny #2." I believe I have just the piece of evidence to prove that a Ms. Bonny #2 exists.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh? Then please submit your evidence, Mr. Justice. What proves the existence of a Bonny #2?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Isn't it obvious, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Not in the slightest.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What a coincidence... I was thinking the same thing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But THIS should be plenty obvious!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yikes. I really made him mad this time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, another Bonny, huh? A "Bonny #2"... She's basically some yet unknown third party that was there in the theater, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Exactly. And I believe we have a piece of evidence that proves such a person exists. Your Honor, please let me try that again!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. But be warned that I won't let you get away with further shenanigans. Now then, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">During our investigation, we found a set of unknown prints on the coffin on the stage. These prints were most likely left during the course of the show. But they didn't match the prints of any of the people involved in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">A-An unknown third party's fingerprints? ............I was not told of this.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ema must've kept it from him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So the question is, who could these prints possibly belong to?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ms. de Famme... or should I say, "Bonny #2"... These are your fingerprints, aren't they?!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Keeyaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Enough of this foolishness! One person could not possibly be two! Those fingerprints could have been left, not only during the show, but at any time!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And I'm sure you know that... ...exactly WHEN the fingerprints were made is not the main issue.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean by that, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The issue is WHO do these unknown prints belong to? They're certainly not Bonny de Famme's. But what if they belong to the person standing right in front of us?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! You mean, Bonny #2 is the "second Bonny"? Is that what you're implying?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">......Nngh. It's preposterous to suggest that those prints belong to the witness. I say they must belong to some other unknown individual.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor Sahdmadhi, can you really look at her and still say that?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">............What're you lookin' at?! Take a picture -- it'll last longer!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">How could this be...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If we check her prints, I'm sure they'll match the unknown set. Well, "Bonny"? The prints that don't belong to the real you... ...belong to you, don't they, Bonny #2?!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Keeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Witness! Is what the defense has said true?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">............Kee hee hee. Fine! I admit it! The fingerprints are mine!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then does that mean... you AREN'T Bonny de Famme...?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">What?! Ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are there really... two Bonnys?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Nope! There's only one Bonny. That's because... I'm Betty! Betty de Famme!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?</line>
<line speaker="Betty">......Ladies and gentlemen of the court, it's time for a wondrous magic show! Gasp in amazement as this lagomorph-ing illusionist performs her teleportation magic! Watch closely! It's showtime!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What an amazing trick! The witness has suddenly split into two people!</line>
<line speaker="Betty">It's not a trick! No gimmick to it, either!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">We're simply... twins!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">WHAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Twins?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So that's how the teleportation trick works...</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Ever since our debut, I've had to hide or pretend I'm Bonny. All cute and sweet and goody-goody... I can't tell you how stressful it's been! But I don't have to hide anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">That's right! Our days of sneaking around are finally over!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Their cover is blown, but they actually seem pretty happy about it...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So which one of you is the nice Bonny de Famme we met in the dressing room?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">That would be me...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And the sharp-tongued Bonny we saw with the Ratings Rajah understage was...?</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Hey! Who are you calling "sharp-tongued"?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's all starting to make sense now...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, Mr. Justice, this changes the facts of the case rather dramatically, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It certainly does. During the show, it was Bonny who was onstage the whole time. So Bonny couldn't have committed the crime. But Betty, on the other hand, who was understage, DID have the opportunity.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Ngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Well! So we now have two suspects!</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Betty:</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">That's right. Betty might have a foul mouth, but she'd never kill anybody!</line>
<line speaker="Betty">...Hey! Who's got a foul mouth here?!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Oh! Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Well?! Speak up! Huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Betty">............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Betty, you must've been in the understage passage during the show. Otherwise, you wouldn't have known about the stage lifts being moved. So what exactly were you doing down there?</line>
<line speaker="Betty">...Fine! I'll testify! Anything to get you off my back!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor Sahdmadhi, Betty de Famme is ready to testify. What do you say?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............Betty, you lied to this humble servant of the Holy Mother.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Hey, what else could I do? I couldn't blow our cover and ruin our magic act. Kee hee hee! Besides, am I gonna go to your twilight hell or whatever for being a liar?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...You will indeed. However, it won't be after your death. Rather... ...I shall give you a taste of your punishment on this mortal coil -- in interrogation hell.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then, Betty de Famme. Please explain to this court... ...what exactly you WERE doing under the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">It's true. I had business in the understage passage because of the upcoming trick.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">It was the fire trick, right? The one Mr. Reus was supposed to do?</line>
<line speaker="Betty">That's right. It's a very dangerous trick, so I had to make sure we were prepared for it.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I-It was in the script... and I really wanted to see it... but I couldn't because of the accident.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Shut up! You're gonna give it away! ...Anyway, I was real busy.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Yeah... Way too busy to have the chance to kill Mr. Reus...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ <thought>Well, that was certainly... different.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Betty">Kee hee hee! How's THAT for a flawless testimony and alibi?! Our magic is real! It's not a trick or a gimmick!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Oh, my! She's floating!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............Um, Your Honor... You can see she's being held up from below...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You were supposed to pretend you didn't see&amp; that. It's a little something called "etiquette."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But... <thought>I can't help it! Whenever I see a contradiction or inconsistency, I just HAVE to point it out!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then. The defense may begin its cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">It's true. I had business in the understage passage because of the upcoming trick.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Betty">But I don't have any motive to kill Mr. Reus.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But you, by your own admission, hate Ms. Wright. When she was arrested as a suspect... ...you said it was "what she deserved."</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta"> </line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">So you believe the witness killed a man, simply due to her dislike of Trucy Wright? As a motive, is that not improbable at best?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But what if her hatred caused her to bear a strong sense of malice against my client?</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Look, Trucy just made me mad, that's all. I mean, even though she's younger than me, she's got so much skill and popularity! And she's cute, besides! Grr! She makes me so mad, I wish she would drop dead!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">B-Betty, don't talk like that.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Shut yer yap!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So was it just simple jealousy?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Say, Betty, that next trick you were getting ready for...</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">It was the fire trick, right? The one Mr. Reus was supposed to do?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Oh! Right. I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You can step down if you'd like.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I'm worried about Betty, though... She can lose her temper and say awful things sometimes...</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Hey! What are you, my mother?! Don't forget! I'M the older sister! You got that?!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Meep! Y-Yes, I got it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess I'd worry about Mt. Betty constantly blowing her top if I were Bonny, too...</thought> So, Betty, you were down understage getting ready for the fire trick, were you?</line>
<line speaker="Betty">That's right. It's a very dangerous trick, so I had to make sure we were prepared for it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Of course! Every precaution. After all, it's a very dangerous trick that uses real fire. I mean, we had to be ready in case the curtain caught on fire or something, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">By the time people realized it wasn't a part of the act, it might be too late, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If by "people," you mean "Athena Cykes," then yes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wow, a fire trick... That sounds really impressive!</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Kee hee hee! Your beard would go up in smoke, old man! bet people'd mistake you for a cue ball or something without it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-A cue ball?!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">B-Betty, don't be rude to the judge.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Kee hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">U-Um, B-Betty, you know that fire trick...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I-It was in the script... and I really wanted to see it... but I couldn't because of the accident.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">No. During rehearsal, he said he didn't feel well, so he couldn't breathe any fire for me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, let me get this straight: He couldn't breathe fire because he wasn't feeling well...?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">"My magical powers appear to be on the wane today." That's what he said.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>S-So it was just a part of his usual The Great Mr. Reus shtick...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">It's really too bad I didn't get to see the trick because of the incident... Wh-Which was completely unexpected, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">! H-Hey!</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Shut up! You're gonna give it away! ...Anyway, I was real busy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Betty">............! See, Bonny?! You and your big mouth! Now lobster boy wants to know what we're talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Eep! I'm sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes, well, if you were preparing for the next magic trick... ...I'm sure you wouldn't have had the time to commit murder.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Wow. Looks like the old geezer isn't senile just yet, huh! I bet you'll live a good, long life.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho ho. I plan to be sitting up here at least another ten years.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ten more years? I don't know about that...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What did we discuss about inner monologues, Athena?!</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Welp, more power to ya, I guess. I was so busy, I didn't have the time to off anybody!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Yeah... Way too busy to have the chance to kill Mr. Reus...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">N-No, of course not! I believe in my sister! I know she'd never murder anyone.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But you think my client would?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">No! I believe in Trucy, too. I know she'd never murder anyone, either.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, we just ran out of suspects, in that case.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Y-Yes, but...</line>
<line speaker="Betty">See? You should've just kept your mouth shut, dummy. You're just making a fool of yourself. Just be nice and quite like a good little bunny, got it?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">...All right. I guess I'm no help...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, boy... It's impossible to get anything out of Bonny with Betty right there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So Betty was too busy getting ready for the next trick to have time for murder, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There must be some way to prove that that wasn't the case...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I hate to break this to you, Betty, but there's a big flaw in your testimony. As big as the one in that "floating" trick you did earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Ooh, harsh words! Well, lemme tell you something, forehead boy! No one has ever figured out how we do our teleportation trick!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No one except me, you mean.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Well... hmph! We have even better tricks up our sleeves!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">...Huh? We do?</line>
<line speaker="Betty">I told you to keep it zipped!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, now. Don't fight, you two. Mr. Justice, what's this about a flaw in the testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The script has this to say about the fire trick: "This will be dangerous. Make sure the fire bucket is ready!" However, we found the fire bucket lying empty backstage except for a layer of dust.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Ack! I... I...</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Ouch!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You didn't even ATTEMPT to get ready for the next trick, did you, Betty?!</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Y-Ya got meeee!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Betty de Famme! You will explain yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Nnngh... T-There's nothing to explain.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Come on, Betty. We can't hide it any longer. We might as well tell them.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Shut up! You can barely take care of yourself! Don't try and tell me what to do!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, if neither of you will explain, I guess I'll have to. The reason Betty didn't prepare for the fire trick is because she...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's because you're afraid of fire, right?</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Kee hee hee! Are you kidding?! What kind of magician is afraid of fire? I should burn your hair off right now for that, starting with those stupid lobster antennae!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid the loss of one's hair is too great a penalty for anyone to pay, Ms. de Famme... I hope you can be satisfied with this penalty for Mr. Justice instead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Now I really want to know how His Honor and his hair parted ways...</thought> Your Honor, please let me try again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were supposed to prepare for the next trick, but you were slacking off, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Betty">............Yeah, okay. Whatever you say.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You should be ashamed of yourself, neglecting your duties like that.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Oh yes, I'm veeery sorry. It'll never happen again, honest.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yes! I got a sorry out of her!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh... Good point... I'm veeery sorry, Your Honor. It looks like I made a mistake?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, it looks like your brain is the one slacking off. You should be ashamed of yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yipes! Your Honor! Please let me try again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You didn't prepare for the fire trick because you knew, didn't you? You knew that the body would be found, and that the show would then be canceled!</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Aaaaaaaaaaaaagh! D-D-Don't be ridiculous, you insignificant speck of a man! I'm gonna yank those lame bangs of yours off. Is that what you want?! Huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Betty">...Ngh! I-I can't reveal my secrets! I'm a magician!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">!</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Exactly! Where's your proof?! Huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And yet, I concede that the witness's taste for false words has also been proven. I advise you to confine your deceitful trickery to your magic act, witness!</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Grrrrr! D-Deceitful trickery?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Hmph! But all these questions mean you're trying to put me in prison for real! So I'll be behind bars either way!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Does that mean you're admitting your guilt?</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Of course not! I can't believe you people! Every one of you thinks I did something I didn't do! You... ...lobster boy! Cue ball geezer! Head case brat! Cerberus monk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Cue ball... geezer?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">H-Head case brat? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Bonny:</line>
<line speaker="Betty">*huff*... *huff*... *huff*... L-Look... I'm not the murderer, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then how did you know the show would be called off before the fire trick?</line>
<line speaker="Betty">I... I told you. We can't reveal our secrets. We're... under contract.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Contract? What is she talking about?</thought> Be that as it may, you're obviously a suspect in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Exactly. What's more, Betty knew that the body would be found... ...and that the magic show would then be called off. Therefore, it's reasonable to conclude that Betty killed the victim understage. </line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">But what if Betty knew that the show would be called off for some other reason?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Like what?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............In the course of my investigation... ...I found it strange that the dragon set piece fell when it did. That, in conjunction with the body tumbling from the coffin in such a dramatic fashion... ...all seemed too perfect for mere happenstance. It was as though the entire chain of events had been planned out in advance.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">K-Kee!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Ouch!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Planned out?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">After deciding to take this case... ...I scrupulously studied everything I could about the mass media in this country. I read the newspaper, old news reports -- I even browsed tabloid magazines.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How very industrious of you! I'm impressed.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">During this process, I learned about a strange practice favored by the TV world. A practice called the "hidden camera prank." </line>
<line speaker="Betty">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Betty and Bonny, you knew about this, did you not? About the dead body appearing, the set piece falling, the show being suspended... You two were informed of this plan... ...by Take-2 TV in advance, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-Is that true...?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Betty! Please, let's tell them now! I can't hold it in anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Nnnnnnnnnnnggggrrrrrrrrrrrr! D-Dang it! F-Fine, you got us! Everything the prosecutor said is true! The TV station paid us to cooperate with them on this plan! It was all a prank -- a big setup planned out in advance! Mr. Reus showing up dead in the coffin... The set piece falling down... It was all... completely scripted!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-It was all... ...A PRANK?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bonny! Is this really true?!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Yes. Mr. Reus was supposed to pretend to be dead. That's how it was supposed to go.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So he was in on it, too?</line>
<line speaker="Betty">That's right. He was supposed to show up "dead" in the coffin... ...and then the set piece would fall down. Trucy would be shocked and start to panic.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?! <thought>What the heck kind of prank is that?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Betty">But we never thought... ...he'd actually wind up dead...</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Yeah... That was the only thing that was different from the script. Poor Mr. Reus...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm so completely lost right now...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Betty and Bonny, it certainly sounds like you have some explaining to do!</line>
<line speaker="Betty">All right, all right. I guess desperate times call for desperate measures! Kee hee hee! Just this once, we'll share how it was done with you. So listen carefully! You'll never hear this kind of thing anywhere else! After our teleportation trick, I went down understage.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">When Mr. Reus's body appeared from the coffin on stage... ...it was time for Betty to do her job in the understage passage.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">That's right. I used the remote control for the winch connected to the dragon set piece... ...and made it fall down.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">And just before the dragon fell... ...I called Trucy to the backstage, so she wouldn't get hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">After that, the plan was for Mr. Reus to come back to life in front of a panicked Trucy. He was supposed to laugh and fly up and away. That was how it was scripted, anyway. But for some reason, he really DID turn up dead, so he kinda just stayed on the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ <thought>Wh-What kind of sick joke is that...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It sounds like a terribly mean-spirited prank to me. The poor defendant was trying to do her magic show!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I guess so... I'm sorry, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Hmph! Whatever. It was all the Ratings Rajah's idea anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah... It sounds like just the kind of thing a guy like him would come up with.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Um... This is the prank plan script we got from the Ratings Rajah.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Dang it! You made us break our contract! Now we won't get paid!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... But where does this all leave us? Who killed the victim... and when?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Yes, exactly. Those are the key questions If Mr. Reus was only pretending to be dead in the coffin as a part of the prank... ...then when he was understage... ...there would still be life within him. And if that is the case... ...then Betty, who was also understage, may be excluded from our list of suspects.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah... AAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Witness, was the victim alive up until he entered the coffin?</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Oh, well. Now that we've spilled the beans, we might as well show you this video.</line>
<line speaker="Mr. Reus">Greetings, viewers! It is I, The Great Mr. Reus! We are currently in the middle of Trucy's escape trick. Having snuck through the understage passage undetected, I am now hiding backstage... ...preparing to play a little prank on Trucy! I'm about to hide in the coffin, which Trucy will stab with her rubber sword. And when the coffin opens -- ho ho! I will be in it, acting as though I've met my maker! Can you imagine the look on Trucy's face then! Ho ho, I can hardly WAIT!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He's "about to" hide in the coffin...?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...It would seem the threads of karmic destiny... ...have led us to the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The victim passed through the understage, where Betty de Famme was... ...and came up into the backstage area. We know this because Mr. Reus appeared to be backstage when he shot the video we saw.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It appears that way, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And defense, you proposed the following, did you not? "What if the victim was killed under the stage before being put into the coffin?" But then, what about this video? This footage was taken just before Mr. Reus entered the coffin.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! So does that mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Yes, it is horrible, but true. The tragedy did indeed play out right there on the stage... ...when into the coffin where Mr. Reus was hiding... ...Trucy Wright thrust her blade!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Arngh... AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Kee hee hee! Seeee? Told you so!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So are you saying the incident was a tragic accident that happened during a prank?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It would be an accident... if the accused had no knowledge of the prank beforehand. So let us ask the accused herself: Ms. Wright, did you have prior knowledge of the prank?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What?! I... I...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tell him, Trucy! You didn't know anything about it, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Of course I didn't... I didn't know a single thing about it!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It looks like... some sort of note?</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Aaaaaaaaaaaagh! Th-That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I found this note in the dressing room after the incident. At the time, I did not understand what it meant, but all is clear to me now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's this? </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's see. "Get the video camera after Mr. Reus comes tumbling out."...?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It is a note signed by the accused... ...instructing Bonny to collect Mr. Reus's video camera from him, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">......I don't get it. It doesn't make any sense...</line>
<line speaker="Betty">I found it in the dressing room before the show. When I saw it, I realized that Trucy knew about the prank.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It does bear her signature... I'll give you that much... </line>
<line speaker="Judge">So the defendant had prior knowledge of the prank?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It would appear so, yes. When she learned about the plan to trick her, she decided to use it to her own advantage. So she thrust the steel sword into the coffin where the victim stood chuckling to himself... Is that not what happened, Ms. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">O-Of course not! And I didn't write or sign that note!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Ah, but the handwriting matches yours. All of the evidence and testimony points to you being the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">B-But... I didn't do it! It wasn't me!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Then explain the existence of this note! You can do that, can you not?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I...I can't explain it. I didn't write it, so I don't understand... I didn't kill Mr. Reus! You have to believe me! </line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ <thought>The silence is deafening...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Continue struggling against the threads of your own karma if you wish, accused. Even as you are inescapably caught in the web of fate you've spun for yourself. ......Ms. Wright. It is time to resign yourself to your fate.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">N-No... I didn't do it... I...</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Ha! I knew it!That sweet-looking girl? A murderer?She took all of us in with that act of hers!I knew she was a homicidal little witch from the start!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But I didn't do it... I really didn't... Why doesn't anybody believe me?</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Shut up, you killer!We won't fall for that anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-This is bad...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Your Honor, I suggest we put an end to this tragedy now. Give your official ruling, and let us offer the victim's soul the last rites it deserves.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......Very well. I suppose I have no other choice. ......This court hereby finds the defendant, Trucy Wri--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Y-You! Even now, you would...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...I won't give up. And I refuse to let either of them down... Mr. Wright, who's counting on me... And Trucy, who's put all of her faith in me...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">......Mr. Justice, the fact that you have raised an objection... ...means that you have evidence with which to refute the prosecution's claims, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, of course, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Do we really have anything, Apollo...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......Actually, we do! There's one piece of evidence we can present here! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Justice. You may proceed. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">As we saw in the show footage... ...there's no question that the defendant thrust a sword into the coffin. The defense doesn't dispute this point. But let us not forget that this was a magic show, filled with tricks and illusions. We can't take everything we see at face value.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So you're saying some sleight of hand was somehow involved?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes. The defense contends that the sword the defendant used was not the cause of death. <thought>Now what was it Trucy told me she did just before she thrust the sword into the coffin?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">......Very well. Let us see your evidence, then, Mr. Justice. But remember: you interrupted my verdict to make this claim. You will be severely penalized if I find you are bluffing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ngrk...! Th-That's fine, Your Honor! This shows that it's possible that the sword Ms. Wright used was not the cause of death!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Huh? <thought>Uh-oh. Looks like I got it wrong.</thought> As I said earlier, Your Honor, you can't take everything at face value. All I was trying to say with this is... that it's not the evidence we are looking for.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And just as I said earlier, Mr. Justice, I have a whopper of a penalty for that bluff.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Owie... <thought>I guess I can't always have it my way... There's only one piece of evidence that makes sense here... Now, what was it that Trucy said she did... ...just before she thrust the sword into the coffin?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">See to it you do better this time, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this? A sword from the show?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right, Your Honor. This rubber sword was in the sword stand understage. Ms. Wright was supposed to swap the real sword for a rubber sword. And she told us on record that she remembers very clearly that she did.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. So the sword the defendant thrust into the coffin was a rubber sword, was it? But then why was a steel sword found lying on the stage?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Somebody must have put the steel sword there by swapping it with the rubber one. Just after the incident occurred, the dragon set piece fell, and the theater was evacuated. The real culprit must have used the resulting chaos... ...to swap the rubber sword for the steel one!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let me express my opinion. By all accounts, it is certainly reasonable to suspect the defendant based on the evidence. But as to the question of whether the sword the defendant used was rubber or steel... ...I believe further discussion is warranted. I suggest we hear from the defendant herself on this issue.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">......Very well, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yes! I saved it... somehow! Too close for comfort, but still...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's adjourn for a brief fifteen-minute recess. I advise the prosecution and the defense to use this time to prepare.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whew... That was hairy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tell me about it. We barely made it through by the skin of my teeth.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I can't say I'm crazy about that Prosecutor Sahdmadhi, either... You know, with the way he says "let it go, and move on" as if it's nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>"Let it go, and move on," huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Whoa boy, am I interrupting a secret conclave of villains or something?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Got your next evil scheme in the works already?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...What do you want?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Heh heh. Keep making that face, champ, and everybody's gonna change the channel. Look this way, Trucy! Now, smile for the camera! Let's see those pearly whites! Isn't that what the Gramarye creed tells you to do?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">............</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">How does it feel, Trucy? Everybody online can't stop talking about you! They're calling you a real witch out there! Could this be the end of Troupe Gramarye?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">GO AWAY, YOU CREEP!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Oh, what's this? Something just charged into frame! It looks like a yellow gorilla or something. Could it be Trucy's pet?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Filming is prohibited inside the courthouse! Do you want me to get the bailiff?!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Huh? Filming? What are you talking about?I don't even have a camera on me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? What happened to the camera...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It just disappeared, right before our very eyes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Heh heh. I'll be enjoying the rest of The Trucy Show from the gallery. I put out a call for Trucy's fans to come and support her earlier, by the way. Bet I'll get some great footage outta them! This is gonna be good! Hang loose, baby!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He called in some of Trucy's fans? <thought>But for what purpose...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Apollo? That thing Mr. Retinz just did... that was some high-level sleight of hand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Why would he know how to do something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I don't know, but he definitely has some serious magic skills.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>No way. But I thought he said magicians were all "a bunch of good-for-nothings"!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Mr. Lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, hello, Bonny. Can I help you with something?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Uh, well... There's something that's been bothering me...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Well, you see...</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Hey, dummy! What are you whispering to lobster boy about?!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">B-Betty... </line>
<line speaker="Betty">Who the heck do you think you are?! Are you crazy?! You want a piece of this?! You KNOW you have to talk to me first before you do or say ANYTHING! You harebrain!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Meep! B-But I- I...</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Shut your mouth, you dumb bunny! Come with me -- NOW!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wonder what was bothering her?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">There's no way we're finding that out with Betty constantly hovering over her like that...</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Court is about to reconvene.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Will you be all right testifying?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yes... It's just... ...I wonder what Mr. Retinz has up his sleeve. I doubt he's bringing in actual fans...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yeah, probably not... <thought>I wonder what he has up his sleeve, too. He'd better not be trying to get under Trucy's skin right now, of all times.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............You're Trucy Wright, and you'll be FINE!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There goes Apollo with his best trick!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right. Whenever I'm feeling down, I always tell myself I'm fine.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......All right. I'll give it a try! I'm Trucy Wright, and I'm FINE! ......Thanks, Polly! I think I can do this now!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thatta girl! Good luck up there on the stand. You'll do great!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Thanks! I'll be fine! can do this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>All right, Justice! You can do this, too! Time to focus on the rest of the trial!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now back in session. Defendant, please step up to the witness stand.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Trucy Wright. Magician.</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Here comes the liar! The deceitful witch!Throw the murderer in jail!The last member of that criminal troupe!Boooo! We don't wanna see you on any stage!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! The gallery will be quiet, or I will have you all thrown out on the spot!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What's with all the hecklers?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I bet they're the "fans" Mr. Retinz invited.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What a Grade-A jerk! He's not going to psyche US out!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court would like to know if you switched from the steel sword to a rubber one onstage. So please testify about this issue.</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">She's just gonna try and us again with her magic!Hurry up and convict her already!Give 'er the death penalty! Nya haa haa haa haa!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Silence! All of you! I won't tell you again! Ms. Wright do you feel able to testify?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......Yes. I'm... fine, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Trucy... I knew I shouldn't have let her go through with this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......Um... I'd like to make a small request. How about, instead of testifying with words... ...I show you exactly what happened. Would that be all right, Your Honor? You can witness my stupendous sword-switching magic and judge for yourselves!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">! <thought>In spite of everything, she's still smiling...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Our Trucy is amazing, isn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She sure is. She's doing just fine up there. <thought>"A true entertainer always keeps a smile on their face." She's faithfully following the Troupe Gramarye creed even now... She really is something else.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's showtime for Magical Girl Trucy Wright! Watch carefully now, everybody!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ladies and gentlemen! Please focus your attention on this sword!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-B-B... Bravoooo, Ms. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Wow! She switched them in a flash!I couldn't see her do it at all!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She's completely turned the room around...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The hecklers are being drowned out by all the cheering!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Where did the steel sword vanish off to, Ms. Wright? ...In order to deepen our understanding of the case, please tell us, if you would. I-I'm not asking out of mere curiosity, just so you know!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I usually hide the steel sword backstage when I switch them during the show.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So when you thrust the rubber sword into the coffin... ...the steel sword wasn't even onstage, but behind the curtain?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Exactly. So, you see, there IS a trick and a gimmick to it after all. And as for where the steel sword went when I performed the trick just now... It's a secret! Wouldn't want to spoil the magic for you, now would I!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's our Trucy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... Still... ......Ms. Wright? hat part where you spun around... ...that's an actual part of the sword-switching trick you do for the show, right?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Right. The other parts, like the apple, were just to help with my explanation here in court.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's funny. I think I found an inconsistency in her testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And it looks like I'm not the only one... I don't know what it's doing there... ...but now that I've found it, I have to get to the bottom of it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then, Mr. Justice. You may go ahead and question the witness. But try not to ask dumb questions and spoil this wondrous magic!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I thought this was supposed to be MY cross-examination...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ladies and gentlemen! Please focus your attention on this sword!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't worry. I've practiced this trick a thousand times.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right, Apollo. You have to give Trucy some credit. She knows what she's doing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know, I know... but it still makes me nervous every time.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But that's what magic is all about. A truly great magician... ...can make her audience experience all kinds of thrills and chills!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess you're right. <thought>I'd better try not to interrupt her too much while she's doing the trick. I don't want to distract her or break her concentration...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And now, ladies and gentlemen, back to the exciting world of magic!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Allow me to demonstrate... just how sharp this blade truly is!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Please don't shout when I am swinging said blade around! Somebody could get hurt!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Oh. Ha ha ha. Y-Yeah. Sorry about that. I couldn't help myself...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmph! You should know better than to talk to me when I'm on stage!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Mr. Justice, I'll see you in my chambers after court is adjourned.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Uh-oh. I don't suppose somebody could make me disappear before that happens...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's just watch quietly, shall we, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And now, back to the show!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">See that? No tricks or gimmicks! A very sharp sword indeed!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Now, now, Apollo. I know you're excited, but you have to control yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice. If you needlessly interrupt this wonderful magic show again... ...I will be forced to bring my very real gavel down on your head!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The judge seems to be completely taken in by Trucy's magic.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. It's like she's cast a magic spell over him. <thought>I'd better not interrupt her any more. There's no telling what the judge might do to me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Wright, please ignore any further outbursts from Mr. Justice... ...and proceed with your spectacular trick!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">All right Here I go, then!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Now then, ladies and gentlemen. Watch as I take this sword aaand...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I've had it up to here, Apollo! Can't you listen quietly like a big boy?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh heh heh. Sorry about that. I got a little too worked up.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Now, boys and girls, watch carefully, and please don't kick the seat in front of you! I will now take this sword, aaand...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Presto sword-o! I've switched it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right. It's the same way I do the trick in the actual magic show, too. But I'm also doing a lot of extra things that I don't do during the show right now, though.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The key point is the sword switching... If only we could prove she did it during the actual show, too...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. Prove that she switched them during the show... Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's the matter, Apollo? You look troubled.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, it's nothing... <thought>Uh-oh. This is quite the pickle... How should I go about handling this...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Wright, please continue with your trick.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So you've all just witnessed me switching the swords.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And now... hup!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eeeeek! What do you think you're doing, Apollo?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But you were putting yourself in danger! I couldn't just stand by and not say something!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice, you're putting your head in danger of meeting my gavel.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, you'd better apologize before you become this case's next victim!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I-I'm very sorry, everyone. <thought>How did it come to this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">All right, boys and girls! If you want to ask for an encore, wait until the end, okay? Now, then! My sword was sharp as steel just moments ago, but...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">As you can see, the blade is not steel, but rubber!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh? But I explained it once already...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, could you show it to me again?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Sure. But, remember: A magician doesn't usually share her secrets... ...so this is a very special exception!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And I'm very grateful for your generosity. Believe me. <thought>I'd better take a good, hard look at the instant she switches the swords.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Even though she explained how she does it, I still can't SEE her do it! It blows me away no matter how many times I watch!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, me, too. But...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What is it, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......Did you notice anything about the way Trucy moves during the trick?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You mean like her movements?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't get it. What's the real story, Trucy?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......Ms. Wright, there's something I'd like to confirm with you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">! Wh-What is it, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There seems to be a discrepancy between the way you performed the trick for us just now... ...and the way it appears in the show footage.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What? But that can't be! I performed it exactly the same way both times!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Then what's going on here?</thought> Ms. Wright, I have the show footage right here... ...and the part where you twirl your cape around is missing from it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What?! But I did it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-So... ...it really is the exact moment you switch the swords?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yes, th-that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">! <thought>I-I knew it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Well, I certainly never expected the defense to expose the accused's lie for me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice, does this mean that you are arguing... ...that the defendant did NOT swap the swords during the actual magic show...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......N-No, Your Honor. That wasn't my intention. I-I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I DID swap them! I know I did! I'm absolutely sure of it!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">B-But...!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Now that it has been proven that the accused did not swap swords... ...it means that the use of the steel sword to pierce the coffin was wholly intentional.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gurk!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And by the way, was it not you, Mr. Justice, who argued... ...that Mr. Reus's death was not an accident, but murder? I assume you have no objections to that still? It was, after all, our own assertion.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense, um...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But there IS a discrepancy, and it MUST mean something! I'm sure of it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Would the defense team kindly save their spat until after court is adjourned? ...Now, after all of this debate, it seems we've come back around to the original argument. The defendant knew about the prank plan that would place the victim inside the coffin. What's more, the defendant did not perform the sword-switching trick onstage.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Through her actions, I'm afraid I have come to see the true intentions of the accused. Her murderous intentions.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's such a shame...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">B-But... But I did switch the swords! I swear!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Y-You're knee-deep in it now, Justice!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Bonny:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's see. You are... which one again? "Benny"...? No, that's not right. "Botty"...?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">It's "Bonny." You were mixing the two names together, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, pardon me. And do you have something you wish to say, Bonny?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Yes, Your Honor. I'd like to testify.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>About what...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">The more I think about it, the less possible it seems. I don't believe Trucy killed Mr. Reus.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Bonny?</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Betty:</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Such an incredibly gifted and talented magician... ...would never commit murder. I refuse to believe it!</line>
<line speaker="Betty">What are you talking about, you harebrained hare?! You keep your trap shut! I got a bag of baby carrots for you, go chew on those and pipe down!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">............No. I won't be quiet.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">What's the matter with you? Didn't you hear me?!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">............T-Trucy said something to me once.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">She said, "No matter how scared you get... no matter how mean people are to you... ...you can't give in or give up! That's what being a professional magician is all about!" Isn't that right, Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">! Th-That's right, Bonny!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I've always been afraid to stand up to Betty -- afraid to defy her -- so I did what she said... But when I saw Trucy today, she gave me strength.</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">She's just gonna try and trick us again with her magic!Hurry up and convict her already!Give 'er the death penalty! Nya haa haa haa haa!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">............</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......Um... I'd like to make a small request. How about, instead of testifying with words... ...I show you exactly what happened. Would that be all right, Your Honor? You can witness my stupendous sword- switching magic and judge for yourselves!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Seeing her courage, the way she kept smiling despite everything.... She's just incredible. I'm scared, but, for once... ...I'm going to be brave!</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Grrr! What have you done to my sister, Trucy Wright?! You've practically brainwashed her!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's the power of Trucy's conviction -- that's what it is! It's touched Bonny's heart! </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. Trucy really is one magical girl. Bonny, is the topic of your testimony related to that thing that was bothering you? The thing you tried to tell us about in the lobby during the recess?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Yes. Ever since I saw the show footage, something's been nagging at me. I'm not exactly sure what it is, but something is off. I feel like something about it is different from what I saw on the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean by that, Bonny?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I wonder if what was shown on TV is really the same as what happened onstage.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... But what can we check it against? Do you have some other footage of the show?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Well...</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I have some show footage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You do?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">One of the TV station's cameramen said he was a fan of mine. He kept his camera on me throughout the entire show. And then, afterwards... he gave me the footage he shot as a present.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">H-He did...?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">To tell you the truth, I thought it was kind of creepy, so I was going to get rid of it...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then. Let's take a look at this new footage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Wow...Okay, then...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He really did keep his camera on Bonny the whole time, didn't he!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think this cameraman needs to keep his personal feelings out of his work.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Well, defense? Do you still believe this new show footage is worth inspecting?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">O-Of course I do...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, so how are we going to go about this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's try comparing the two. We just might find an inconsistency between them.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">An inconsistency, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes. The two pieces of footage are of the same scene, so they should match up. But Bonny felt there was something off about the original footage. So if we can pick out what's different between the two...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...We'll know what Bonny found strange.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Exactly. Plus, we may figure out why the original doesn't show the sword-switching trick. Your Honor, the defense would like to compare these two pieces of show footage!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. I will allow it.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">What a waste of time...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, do you know how to compare the two pieces of footage?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, I've never done it before...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'll give you a little lesson, then! Use the buttons on the bottom screen to operate the playback. When you want to speed through, touch the "Fast Forward" button <thought>A</thought>. And if you want to go back, touch the "Rewind" button <thought>Y</thought>. If you want to halt the playback, you can touch the "Pause" button <thought>B</thought>. Oh, and, by the way, if you fast-forward or rewind when the playback is paused... ...you can do a slow, frame-by-frame playback.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay. And so how do I switch between the two videos?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Just touch the "Switch Camera" button <thought>L</thought> at the top left. Now, if you find a difference between the two pieces of footage... ...put the cursor over what's different and "Present" <thought>X</thought> it to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thanks, Athena. You really know your stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Not really. I just gave it some gusto, and then went with my gut on most of it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?! <thought>I-I sure hope she guessed right... Anyway, let's give it a try.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! You're right.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh... I-I guess you're right... <thought>But still... ...there's definitely something different between the two -- I can just tell. Is there something else? Something that's shown in one of the videos... ...but not in the other?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... While I think that Mr. Justice's claim is not totally without merit... ...I'm afraid it's not quite strong enough to constitute proof of his claims.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Please let me try again, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I'm afraid I don't see any difference there...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Blink and you'll miss it, Your Honor. So, don't blink!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......Hmm... Staring so hard at these images for such a long time... ...is starting to make my eyes feel funny. Is this what they call "eye strain"? But besides that, I don't sense anything else strange with this footage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess it was too much to ask of His Honor's ancient eyes...</thought> Um, would you like some reading glasses, Your Honor? S-Sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So we're looking for some kind of difference or discrepancy between the two, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right. Something that's shown in one of the videos, but not in the other. If we can find something like that, it'll prove that the two videos are different. Let me try that again, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is it right here! Take a good look at this scene and compare it to the video shot from the front.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! The playing cards don't appear in the video shot from the front!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, you're right! What's going on here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ms. Wright, what can you tell us about these playing cards?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh! Those? They're the cards I throw when I do the sword-switching trick!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice! Does this mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, it means that the sword-switching trick... ...was cut from the TV show footage.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">So the footage was edited?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, with malicious intent.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...That is absurd.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well! We must get to the bottom of this right away! Bailiff, the TV station might still have the unedited footage. Go see what you can find out!</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Yes, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Retinz:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And who might you be?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Right, right! Sorry about that -- got ahead of myself there. Here is my business card. Chaaarmed to make your acquaintance, Your Hooonor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! Well! How very polite of you.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">It's looovely to meet you, too, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi! Please, take my caaard!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">A business card...? Ah, yes. I read about this custom among businessmen in this country. I have even familiarized myself with the various replies. "How do you do, good sir?" or, "What's crack-a-lackin', homie?" for example.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-ho! You're from Take-2 TV, are you, witness? Come to think of it, I believe I've seen you on television before.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Yes. Roger Retinz -- otherwise known as the "Ratings Rajah." He is a TV producer, and appears on many of his own shows as of late. He is best known for his catchphrase, "Hang loose, baby!"</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! So YOU'RE the Ratings Rajah!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Hang loose, Judgey baby! Nice courtroom you got here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I never thought I'd get to meet you in person! But Prosecutor Sahdmadhi, how do you know so much about him?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">In preparation for the case, I watched all of his shows. I found "The Ratings Rajah Goes to Burger Barn" of particular interest. It inspired me to visit that restaurant straight away to learn more about the local cuisine.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?! YOU went to Burger Barn?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Who would've thought...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">You must've really wanted to try it, huh, buddy. 'Cause that line -- whew.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Compared to my ascetic training, an hour's wait is nothing. I recommend the Southwestern burger with Jalapeno Jack cheese, by the way.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm having a really hard time picturing him in line for burgers...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem! Prosecutor Sahdmadhi's unexpected enthusiasm for food aside... ...Mr. Retinz, what is this "misunderstanding" you mentioned?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Well, for starters, it's true that the footage was edited. You'll get your hands on this anyway, so I might as well show you the unedited footage. It's a pretty long video, o I'll just show you the part with the playing cards. You can see the cards when Trucy spins around, so keep your eyes peeled.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Did you see the part that was cut where Trucy switched the swords? She spins around and the playing cards go flying -- everything's like it's supposed to be.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Then it seems the defendant really did swap swords during the trick.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Which means the sword Ms. Wright thrust into the coffin was the rubber one. In other words, Ms. Wright couldn't have killed Mr. Reus!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Retinz:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Well, Trucy definitely did swap swords, as you saw. So, yeah, maybe she didn't kill Mr. Reus when she stabbed the coffin. But that just means he was killed AFTER he showed up pretending to be a corpse.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you're saying that up until that point, everything was going according to the script? If that's true, then when and how exactly do you think he was killed?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">It was after the dragon set piece came crashing down. I say Trucy murdered Mr. Reus when she was hidden from view behind the set piece. She could've easily done it behind that huge dragon, and nobody'd be the wiser.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Hmm... I see. Indeed, there is a ring of truth to your assertion.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">You bet! Plus, there's a suspicious-looking shadow in the footage, too! It's toward the end of the footage, just before the dragon hits the stage. It might be easier to just see it for yourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">It's only for a split second, so it's hard to catch, but... look here. This suspicious shadow must be Trucy. She's using the steel sword she hid behind the curtain during the trick to kill the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Now that you mention it, I suppose it does look that way...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Retinz:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That would be fine with me. Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...This is quite unexpected. It threatens to disrupt the karmic course of this case.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Hey, lighten up, pretty boy! You're gonna LIKE what I've got to say! Promise!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............Very well. However... ...if you do anything to impede the last rites for the victim... I will have you removed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right. With Prosecutor Sahdmadhi's permission... ...please give us your testimony, Mr. Retinz.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Roger Retinz, the Ratings Rajah! Now, Kaiser of the Courtroom! I'm taking over the floor, so listen up, loyal viewers!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Footage is meant to be edited, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. So you're saying it was a coincidence that the sword swapping scene was cut.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">That's right! Glad you got the picture!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Ooh! An "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>" How cool! It sure packs a lot more punch when you hear it live! I wanna get another shot from a different angle.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">My "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>" is not for your entertainment!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Aaand cut! There! I got some good stuff there!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Retinz, filming is prohibited inside the courthouse.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Whoops. My bad, judge!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And if the defense has an issue, it can point it out during its cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Footage is meant to be edited, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">It's common knowledge in the TV world! You got any idea what a snooze cruise it'd be to watch a magic show without editing? ...A magic show like that one, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That was ice cold.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Anyway, editing is what makes TV worth watching!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Scenes are spliced together, and long or boring scenes are cut out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">You gotta ask? That script and presentation deserve a place on the cutting room floor. Broadcasting that mess as-is would've been a complete disaster. That's why I had to edit the footage. It's just what a TV man does!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What didn't you like about the show, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">The whole thing -- it was a major snoozefest. Maybe common folk like you don't get it... ...but a show's only as good as how loud, flashy, and trashy it is.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It was plenty loud and flashy on its own. All you did was add the trash.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I suppose each industry has its own way of doing things. Just as we in the legal profession focus exclusively on evidence and testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Exactly. Whether it's show biz or the legal biz, we do what we gotta do to get the job done. Anyway, editing footage is just a matter of course in the TV industry.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">All the stations edit footage this way! It wasn't like it was done maliciously or something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">...Huh? What makes you think that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The things that you yourself have said.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And I also get the impression that you've felt this way for a long time.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You bear me no ill will...? Could've fooled me.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And yet, it is the truth. I am only strict on you as it seems you have strayed from the path.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you have any objections, Mr. Justice, please make your case with evidence in the future. Mr. Retinz, please continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">It was just a coincidence that particular scene was cut. It wasn't intentional.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Oh, so now you're gonna tell me how I'm supposed to edit my programs, big shot? It's hard being the boss, kid. You gotta make the tough choices, like which content gets cut!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then let me ask you this: Why exactly did you make such a "tough choice" in this case?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">You wouldn't understand, champ. It's all about artistic vision. I tell ya -- people tell you how to do your job when they don't know the first thing about it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I may not know TV, but I know evidence law. And boy do I have some for you, "champ."</thought> I might not be able to show that your "selective editing" was intentional. However, I know you bear the defendant ill will. And this is the evidence that proves it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Retinz:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is the contract you had Ms. Wright sign just before the magic show. This contract between the first party, Take-2 TV, and the second party, Ms. Wright, reads: "If, through the fault of the second party, the show must be canceled in part or in full... ...the second party will pay three million dollars as compensation to the first party."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-Three million dollars?! That's a completely unreasonable sum.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I couldn't agree more. And of course Ms. Wright doesn't have that kind of money. Nevertheless, Roger Retinz had her sign this unreasonable contract anyway. Or, more accurately, he conned her into signing it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Conned her? How did he do that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a trick to the clipboard that was used by Ms. Wright to sign her contract. It houses carbon paper that can secretly copy her signature onto other documents.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Oh, c'mon, now! That's quite a nasty accusation you're slinging my way. For starters, you don't have any proof I had anything to do with that carbon paper stuff. Just because Trucy and her agency can't pay up, that doesn't mean I conned her!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... But three million dollars... That's totally out of reach for the average person. In any case, this is important new information. Please add it to your testimony, Mr. Retinz.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Hmph. That thing? What could THAT possibly prove?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But take a good look right here. Wouldn't you agree that it puts you in a bad light?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">But looking bad and having evil intentions are two entirely different things! Look at me, for example. I'm not evil, but I AM a bit of a bad boy.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, if I could be a bad boy myself...! But bad lawyers get penalties for presenting bad evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ngh. <thought>Yeah. That was my bad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Look, I didn't mean anything by it. It was just a coincidence I edited out that scene.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">My assistant must've picked that paper up in the dressing room thinking it was some prop. He's a new guy, you see, and he's pretty incompetent. He's always making mistakes. I'll make sure to give him a good talking to later.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Poor new guy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Please continue with your testimony, Mr. Retinz.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Sure, but I don't like the way the defense is trying to paint me as the bad guy here.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Where's your proof linking me to that tricked-out clipboard? You don't have any, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Well, it belongs to the TV station, anyway. That much I know. Maybe it was an old prop from one of our TV shows that got used by mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Or maybe you used it on purpose... to con Ms. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-That's not what I'm doing!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... Proof Mr. Retinz is connected to the carbon paper, huh? If Trucy's signature was copied onto the fake contract... ...then there must be an original contract that Trucy actually did sign...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">True, but I bet Retinz is too savvy to leave something like that behind as evidence. But what if her signature was copied onto more than just the fake contract?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Like a third document with Trucy's signature on it? Have we seen anything like that, though...? </line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Hey, what are you guys whispering about? Lemme continue my testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Or, what? You got some proof that I had an ulterior motive for editing that footage?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">...Huh? Oh, no others, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean you only edited out the sword-switching trick scene and nothing else? Don't you think it's too much of a stretch to claim that as mere coincidence?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, uh...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">If you have a valid criticism of Mr. Retinz's testimony, feel free to counter with evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, Apollo? Hmm... It would sure make things easier if we had some.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">I think the defense team needs to be edited out of this trial -- that's what they need! I'll have to clean up this footage later...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He isn't really gonna put this on TV, is he?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trying to prove malicious intent is tough. All he has to do is say it was all a coincidence.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We'll need to find some kind of foothold if we want to make any progress.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">True. But this guy doesn't seem like the type to slip up. So we'll just have to get the information out of him bit by bit.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Proof that Trucy's signature was copied, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But we don't have proof. That's why our agency is under seizure right now!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>True... Or do we...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You must be quite the con man if you can fool a magician with a simple trick. But if you think you can con a lawyer, you're very much mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Hey kid, would it kill you to enunciate in front of the camera? You know, like a newscaster!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz [on cue card]">THINK OF THE VIEWERS!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'd like you to take a look at Ms. Wright's signature here on this note. Now let's compare that signature to the one here on this contract.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well! Would you look at that?! They're exactly the same.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right, Your Honor. Not just similar, but exactly the same. Nobody can sign their name in exactly the same way twice -- unless it's a copy!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">............</line>
<line speaker="Retinz [on cue card]">YES, KEEP GOING...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">These signatures are proof positive that you conned Ms. Wright. And they definitively prove your malicious intent!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Say! Not bad, lawyer guy! Didn't know you had it in you! This is really getting interesting now! It'll get great ratings for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't try to dodge the issue, Mr. Retinz! The fact is that you bear ill will against my client! So the show footage was definitely edited with malicious intentions. Isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">That's right. I just wanted money, baby! Fat stacks of cheddar, that's all. After all, I'd never even crossed paths with Trucy before this magic show. So I'd have absolutely no reason to bear her any ill will, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ <thought>He didn't bear her any ill will, huh? Hmph. Fat chance. This guy definitely has some major hate for Trucy... I can't prove it with anything but the things he's said all point to that fact. There must be something between the two of them that gave birth to this grudge. Some sort of connection that not even Trucy is aware of...</thought> ......Your Honor. I'd like to argue that Roger Retinz and Trucy Wright must have crossed paths before. There must be some hidden connection between them!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hidden...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Connection?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">*sigh* What is it now?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Just what are you getting at, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It is futile to even ask, Your Honor. Surely, it is just another one of the defense's feckless claims.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Will I really? Very well, then. Do proceed.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Did you figure something out, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......Nope, not a thing. That was just some good old-fashioned bluffing, courtesy of Mr. Wright's fine training.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I hope you know what you're doing...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you're going to make such a bold claim, Mr. Justice, I hope you're ready to elaborate. What is this "hidden connection" between the defendant and Roger Retinz?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Roger Retinz is Ms. Wright's biggest fan.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Thaaat's right! Huge fan! Huuuge fan of hers! So, naaaturally, I don't bear her any ill will or malice whaaatsoever!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ <thought>All right, I set myself up for that one.</thought> Um, can we edit that scene out?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No. This isn't The Public's Court, and I'm not Judge Wackner!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ngh... <thought>I know, 'cause his penalties would hurt less.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, why don't you try again, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't even like to imagine this, but could it be possible the two of them are dating?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If Mr. Retinz and Ms. Wright were in a relationship...</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Oh, that's good! Viewers love a secret romance to dish about! Yes, Trucy and I looove each other sooo much! She's gonna introduce me to her father sometime reeeal soon!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice! Are you aware that you're objecting to your own argument?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sorry, Your Honor, but when I saw Mr. Retinz's antics, I just had to speak out!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I can't say that I blame you for wanting to do that... ...but you're the one who came up with such a disturbing idea in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What was I even thinking?! All that ended up doing is grossing everyone out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, why don't you try again, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That sleight-of-hand trick Mr. Retinz did during the recess earlier...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Filming is prohibited inside the courthouse! Do you want me to get the bailiff?!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Huh? Filming? What are you talking about? I don't even have a camera on me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What if... Mr. Retinz is a magician, too?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"What if"...? I believe it's up to the defense to fill in the blanks, not me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, if he is, he may have had some contact with Ms. Wright somewhere along the way.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Yeah, it doesn't matter what you say to a dimwit. He isn't gonna get it anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But we saw Mr. Retinz perform a magic trick! He made his video camera disappear in the blink of an eye!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">While I think it would be pretty funny if I were a magician... ...you must've been seeing things. Want me to introduce you to a good eye doctor?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">If a connection as tenuous as that is all it takes... ...then every magician in the country could potentially bear ill will toward the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I... I guess you're right...</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">You're not the sharpest knife in the drawer, are you, short stuff?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You would do well to cleanse that putrid mind of yours in the holy waters of Mt. Poniponi. Three days under a frigid waterfall, and even you should rise to the level of a monkey.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Ha ha ha! A numb skull for a numbskull!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urrrgh... <thought>Well, this numbskull has thick skin, so there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think I get what they're driving at... Even if he is a magician, it's not exactly a reason to bear a grudge against Trucy, is it? </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............Hold on! I can think of one person... ...one magician who has a reason to bear a grudge against Trucy. Or, rather, one magician who has a reason to bear a grudge against Troupe Gramarye... </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............! N-N-N... ...NO WAY!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is something wrong, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......Your Honor, the defense wishes to submit evidence at this time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what sort of evidence do you have for us?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Evidence that points to the real killer -- the one who had a motive to commit this crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...*sigh* And what have you come up with this time, defense?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy Wright is the sole heir to Troupe Gramarye and its name. This puts her square in the crosshairs of one particular magician. And this piece of evidence points to that one person with a grudge against Ms. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That it does, and it does it surprisingly well.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh...? How?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, well... you'll find that out after this short intermission. See you in Act Two! ...is how it goes, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......Keep this up, and it's curtains for you, Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All right... Guess I WON'T be seeing you in Act Two then...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But you're right, Apollo. There IS someone with a grudge against Troupe Gramarye.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... Your Honor. Please recall that... ...Trucy Wright is the sole heir to Troupe Gramarye and its name. This puts her square in the crosshairs of one particular magician.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And who exactly are you naming, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thirteen years ago, The Great Mr. Reus belonged to Troupe Gramarye But then, the troupe ousted him, and Mr. Reus vowed to get revenge on them someday. And what better way to accomplish that than through the ruination of their sole heir?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But Mr. Reus is the victim, Mr. Justice! You've named a dead man as your suspect!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...But is he really dead?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......What do you mean, "is he really dead"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If the fact that Mr. Reus is the victim is what's throwing you off... ...then how about we consider this possibility? What if the man who died on that stage yesterday... WASN'T Mr. Reus!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wh-What...? You mean the victim was an imposter?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not Mr. Reus?! Then what about the real Mr. Reus...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It would mean the real Mr. Reus is still alive.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...That's absurd.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice! Who is the real Mr. Reus, if not the victim of this case?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>......It's all coming together now... I finally see the gimmick -- the trick to this entire case!</thought> ...This should explain everything, Your Honor. The real killer -- the one who hated Troupe Gramarye and wanted to sully its name... The magician lurking in the shadows who set up a fake Mr. Reus in his stead... The real Mr. Reus is...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You look like you don't get it, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It looks to me as if YOU are the one who does not "get it"...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, you saw right through that one. You Khura'inist monks sure are perceptive!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Your Honor, do I have your permission... ...to hasten this foolish lawyer's descent into hell?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I wish I could say yes, but... I hope this will do instead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nrgh... <thought>Okay, if that person wasn't it, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But that's...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, yes it is. Roger Retinz... is the real Mr. Reus!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WH-WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">HIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIM?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">It's not a bad idea for a soap opera... ...but not even die-hard fans of the genre would stick around past the pilot.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............You want proof? Well, I've got proof. I can prove it by... ...proving that the Mr. Reus in yesterday's magic show was a fake. And to do that... ...I just need you to look at this spot on this poster.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Retinz:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Me? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Yup. "Misguided Guys." We'll gather up a bunch of big ol' dumb-dumbs who like to spew idiotic nonsense... ...and then let you all jabber on like gibbons for hours about the future of the Union!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I doubt this is how the Founding Fathers expected the country to end...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You may be misguided, Mr. Justice, but there is nothing misguided about this penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You said it yourself earlier, but... ...all we have to do is prove that this fake Mr. Reus... ...and the real Mr. Reus here are two different people, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... And I see one very obvious difference between the two men. I can prove that the Mr. Reus in yesterday's magic show was a fake, Your Honor. And to do that...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is the injury Mr. Reus sustained while practicing a magic trick thirteen years ago. However... ...the video the victim shot of himself shows no trace of that injury.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! You're absolutely right!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now, Mr. Retinz, what do you suppose we'd find if we took a look at YOUR right forearm? Is there by chance, a nasty, thirteen-year-old scar under that sleeve of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, Mr. Retinz?! Why don't you roll up your sleeve and let the court have a look?! Or are you hiding something else up there!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">............ Ha ha ha ha. Come on, now! I have nothing up my sleeve. I don't NEED to hide anything up there... because I require no tricks or gimmicks. For you see... my magic is the real deal. Is THIS what you were hoping to see?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">OH! There it is! The scar!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just as I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">That's right! I am the forgotten magician -- abandoned to the dark understage of history. The Great Mr. Reus!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-Th-This...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Is totally...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Absurd!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Ho ho ho. How ironic, wouldn't you say? That this odious mark, carved into me by Troupe Gramarye... ...would bring me back into the limelight once more.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Strange are the karmic threads before me... If the witness is the real Mr. Reus, then who is the victim who perished in the magic show?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">He was but a fan. I met him on one of my programs several years ago. He said he had become a magician out of admiration for The Great Mr. Reus. In confidence, I told him my true identity, and let him take on my mantle.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And when did this man take over for you?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">About two years ago. I taught him my tricks, and even acted as his producer. And so, a mere amateur became a popular magician overnight... ...courtesy of my magic, on the stage we call television. Hope you enjoyed the show!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You really had us all fooled.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Retinz... or, should I say, Mr. Reus! In your hatred of Troupe Gramarye, you killed the victim, Mr. Mistree... ...and then set up Ms. Wright to take the fall, didn't you? You did it all just to tarnish the Gramarye name!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Ho ho ho. I have no idea what you're talking about, lad. I set up the prank, that much is true. But it was simply a harmless joke on Trucy, I assure you. Yet, she learned of the plan, and made use of it to commit murder. That is how strongly the criminal element runs in the blood of these Gramaryes!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Gaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yikes!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Eeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">H-His head...!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Heh. Just kidding.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What the heck was that?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Heed my words, lawyer lad, for I fear your grasp on reality is slipping. I do believe I told you that my magic is real! It employs neither tricks nor gimmicks.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Enough with the ambiguity. Why don't you make your point already?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">My alibi is as pristine as ever. Wouldn't you agree, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">......Yes, I suppose that is correct. The witness does have a solid alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Recall, defense, that at the time of the magic show, Mr. Retinz was at Take-2 TV. A fact that many people can easily attest to.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gah! <thought>That's right... I forgot all about that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Ho ho ho. So what do you think, Your Honor? Would you like me to testify on the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I think you'd better. Please tell the court more about your alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Very well, then -- on with the show! Are you watching, Magnifi Gramarye?! The time has finally come for my magic to snuff out your precious pedigree! The Gramarye line will be no more!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">I was at the TV station at the time of the Penrose performance.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Do you understand now, perhaps? I did not grace the theater with my presence until after the incident. So how could I have committed the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... His staff did say he was there at the station... ...so it sure does sound like a rock-solid alibi...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">But that can't be right. If Mr. Retinz is the killer, he'd had to have been at the theater.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's gotta be a hole somewhere in his story...</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Heh heh heh. I assure you there are no holes on Mr. Reus's stage. No tricks, no gimmicks. True magic doesn't need trapdoors to escape through! Do enjoy my show to the fullest... ...and my real alibi!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">I was at the TV station at the time of the Penrose performance.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Indeed. Anxious to see how the show was progressing, I made my way to the theater. Let's see... My journey took about ten minutes by car.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Could he actually have been at the theater during those ten minutes, killing the victim?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Ho ho ho. Allow me a stab at reading your mind. ......A-ha. Could I have been at the theater during those ten minutes, killing the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How in the--!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">But no, I took a taxi. The driver can attest to that. Feel free to call the taxi company, if my word does not satisfy you. The driver is a big fan of the Ratings Rajah. I even gave him my card.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He gave the driver his card? That was very clever of him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">You might as well give it up, lad. Questioning real magic is a fool's errand. Besides, you know very well what I was doing at the time of the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">I was busy working on another TV program. I could spare no time for the magic show.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">My own special project, you see. I... Ah, one moment. Perhaps this is more appropriate... It's a Ratings Rajah special production! Yeah! Hang loose, baby! It's called "Desperation Regeneration!"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He switched personas just to say that?</thought> What's the show about?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Washed-up, has-been singers and comedians get together and play musical chairs. The winner of the game is given a second chance at their career. A priceless prize for chumps who washed up too early in life. Sounds great, right?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Might I suggest you appear on that show, Mr. Justice? As the ex-lawyer who used to make ridiculous bluffs in court, and faded sadly into obscurity.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And let the Ratings Rajah produce my TV debut...? Not in this lifetime.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">You have great reactions. Who knows? TV might be your true calling.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey! Whose side are you on?!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">In any case, I was overseeing production of this program during the Penrose performance.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Do ask my staff if you doubt my claim.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">I make it my business to perform solo. My magic has neither need nor want of assistants. After all, one of them could reveal the secrets behind my magic, could they not?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So he doesn't trust anybody, huh? He's the complete opposite of Trucy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">There were many people there in the studio audience who saw the witness as well. Even if he had been able to persuade his own staff to cover for him... ...he could not have convinced so many complete strangers to do the same.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He really has made a rock-solid alibi for himself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. It's almost... too good, you know? <thought>It's eerie how perfect it is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Has all been revealed to you now?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">And there it is: a simple and perfect alibi. No tricks. No gimmicks. Just the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Again with the twins business?! You think the audience will let you get away with using the same gimmick twice in a row?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">If you do not believe him, defense, why not investigate for yourself? Though I am sure your efforts will prove to be thoroughly fruitless.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yeah, I guess the twins theory is a little far-fetched...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">The perfect alibi, huh? It's no good, Apollo. I can't find a hole anywhere...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's gotta be some kind of trick to it. I just know there's a trapdoor in there somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe we've heard enough. While I believe the witness does indeed harbor some ill will against the defendant... ...there is no reason to doubt that he was at the TV station at the time of the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Yes. The facts prove it was impossible for the witness to have been involved with this crime.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nnrgh...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">These last rites for the victim have dragged on long enough. The soul of the victim himself is so bored that it is resting on top of Your Honor's head.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I-It is?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">......The time has come. Let us punish the sinner and guide the victim's soul to the Twilight Realm.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! Trucy will be thrown in prison... and we'll be out of a job... But if you catch tasty fishies, will you sell me some at a good price?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I told you! I have absolutely zero intention of going off on a tuna boat! <thought>Think, Justice! You have to figure this out!</thought> ............ <thought>It's no use... I can't find a single flaw... So what now?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Ho ho ho. Behold, my never-ending magic show! Come for the awe-inspiring showmanship of The Great Mr. Reus! And stay for my grand illusion until the end of time!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">........... <thought>Wait, is he saying... ...that we're still trapped inside some sort of illusion of his?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's what professional magicians do.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">They make their audience see something that isn't really there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You make us see illusions, right?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">We call it "misdirection." While we keep you busy believing one thing, we're busy making something else happen. What we say is there really isn't, and what we say isn't there actually is!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ <thought>Could it be...?</thought> ......You know what, Mr. Retinz? I guess we HAVE all been spectators to the elaborate illusion you've prepared for us. An illusion that has subtly turned our attention toward something you wanted us to see.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">......What are you going on about, lad?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Have you got something, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I just remembered something Trucy said about... ...misdirection. What a magician says is there really isn't, and what they say isn't there actually is! If we've all been taken for a ride by Mr. Retinz's magic... ...then maybe he's made us see something that wasn't really there. <thought>It's time to rethink all of my assumptions about this case. What have we been made to believe was there when it actually wasn't? What have we taken to be the "absolute facts" of this case...? If I reevaluate the validity of all of these things... then just maybe...!</thought> ......Athena... There's something uncanny about this case.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Retinz's alibi. It's TOO perfect.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...That's true. It's like it's impossible to break, no matter how hard we try.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But maybe THAT'S the trick. Maybe that's exactly what he wants us to think.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um... I'm not following...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We're not making any headway here because we've been so focused on breaking his alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">......Oh, I think I get it. You're saying he's using misdirection on us, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's definitely a possibility!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*ahem* Would the defense care to share with everyone what it's discussing over there?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor, we believe that if we were to reconsider a certain assumption... ...we may finally arrive at the truth. In fact, I think we'll even finally see who's hiding behind the curtain, so to speak. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... And what is this "certain assumption" you're thinking of?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is the one key assumption we've been taking for granted this whole time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Roger Retinz isn't the culprit after all.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">So you finally came to your senses! As thanks, lemme reduce your agency's debt by... 100 bucks.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We deserve a bigger reduction than that, buddy!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hope you're not implying that you'll retract your accusation in exchange for a reduction.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh heh heh! No, of course not.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, you certainly haven't given me any reason to reduce your penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yeah, just a reason to up my micromort count for today.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The actual scene of the crime wasn't the theater, but the TV station. If Mr. Retinz brought the victim's body to the theater after the fact...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......Don't you know it's rude to ask how a trick is done, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And don't you know it's rude to make far-fetched claims, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I-I'll brush up on Courtroom Manners 101 again -- just for you, Your Honor. All right... So the murder could've really only taken place at the theater, which means...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What if the culprit was somewhere other than the theater at the time of the crime...? What if there was some way to commit the murder without actually being there...? If that were the case, then Mr. Retinz's perfect alibi would become irrelevant!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">............</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, if it's not the culprit's, then whose is it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm not one hundred percent sure yet... ...but I'm pretty sure I'm on the right track!</thought> We've all seen something that looks like this shadowy shape before, Your Honor... ...during the magic show itself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In that case, please point it out in the show footage for us.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is the thing that looks suspiciously similar to the shadowy figure of the "culprit."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I thought it looked pretty similar. Do you not think so?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not in the slightest.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? That's funny... It looked pretty shady to me! Heh heh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And your logic is even shadier!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh... Maybe I should try slowing the video down and taking a better look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Doesn't this shadow resemble the suspicious shadowy figure?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Now that you mention it, it does, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ms. Wright, could you identify this shadow for the court?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's see... I believe that's Mr. Hat's shadow. It's from when he's being pulled up from the stage to the catwalk overhead by wire.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then, could this shadow that's shown later in the footage be Mr. Hat, too?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No... that's not possible. After Mr. Hat was pulled up to the catwalk, he stayed up there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">In other words, this second shadow is from some other figure being pulled up.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Some other figure? I'm afraid you'll need to be more specific than that, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He's right. We've come this far. I'll just have to figure it out from the clues I have on hand!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is the second shadow shown in the footage?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How does that have anything to do with a humanoid shadow?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We'll find out when we shine a light on it from a bunch of different angles!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............Your Honor, it would appear... ...that Mr. Justice is seeing things that do not exist. Defense. Please administer a quick therapy session to your partner.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Who, me? A-All right...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">For your own mental health, it's best to acknowledge your own mistakes, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ungrk!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, this shadowy figure appeared during the magic show, right? So if we think back on everything that happened during the show...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If we consider what was happening on the stage at the time, there is only one answer: The shadow belonged to the fake Mr. Reus. In other words, Mr. Manov Mistree.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The victim...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Please take a look at the prank plan script. Mr. Mistree was to pretend to be dead, and then fly up into the air after that. Isn't that right, Mr. Retinz?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Indeed. And what of it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I contend that that's exactly what happened. The victim was wearing a stunt harness around his waist. It was most likely attached to a stunt wire so that he could be pulled up into the air.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So you're suggesting that, after pretending to be dead in the coffin... ...the victim flew up into the air, just as the prank script says?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Exactly. We just couldn't see him go flying up because the dragon was blocking our view. And that last trick, ladies and gentlemen... ...is the true pice de rsistance of the culprit's murderous magic show!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">............Hrrrngh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't tell me... you've got it all figured out?! </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yes, I think so. If we can just look beyond Mr. Retinz's last bit of misdirection... ...we should finally be able to see the real truth. <thought>The victim must've been pulled up to the catwalk, just like Mr. Hat... ...and hit the cushioning up there with considerable force. I just have to figure out what else happened up there at that time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you ready to elaborate, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, Your Honor. I'm ready.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In that case, please answer me this: Why did the culprit make the victim fly up into the air like that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe he did it in order to falsify an alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...And just how was that accomplished, defense?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well... After being pulled up by the wire... ...the victim was zipped off to the TV station, where Mr. Retinz murdered him! All it would take is a really long wire! O-Or...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Just zip it, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Judge: one, Justice: zip.</thought> All right, Your Honor. This time, it's for real.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe the culprit wanted to hide the body up in the catwalk?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But that still doesn't explain how in the world the victim was actually killed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Well, let's see...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And why in the world would the culprit want to hide the body anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, you see...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You should've had all that figured out BEFORE you answered!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Foiled again...</thought> All right, hit me again, Your Honor. I swear I'll get it right this time!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just why DID the culprit have the victim fly up after he appeared in the coffin? And how DID the victim actually die... ...when he was only pretending to be dead in the coffin? If we can figure out how these two questions relate, the answers should become clear.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">C-Could it be...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Mistree must've thought he was still just part of a prank when he appeared onstage. He probably didn't suspect a thing as he was being pulled into the air... ...after Ms. Wright was called backstage, and just as the set piece fell. But the culprit had already planted the real murder weapon in a cushion in the catwalk. It was probably... a knife or blade of some sort.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? You mean...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, it really was a magical murder. Just as the prank script said, Mr. Mistree was whisked up into the air... ...and straight into a blade there in the catwalk. In other words, this murder was committed remotely through the use of a magic trick!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">R-R-Remotely?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Using this method, it wouldn't matter WHERE Mr. Retinz was at the time of death!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">......Ngh... Ngaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But how exactly does it work, Mr. Justice?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just before the murder occurred... ...the dragon set piece was up in the catwalk. It and Mr. Manov Mistree... were connected to each other by a wire at the time. By carrying out the prank plan, Betty made the dragon set piece fall... ...which caused Mr. Mistree to rocket straight up... ...and into the blade in the cushion! The cushion was high up enough to be hidden from the audience's view. That's why nobody saw the blade.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Nnnnnnnnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh...! Then that big gash in Mr. Hat's cape...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The blade must have been set up overhead sometime before the magic show. Mr. Hat must've been slashed by it, too, when he was pulled up to the cushion.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Betty:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were used, Betty -- Roger Retinz used you.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">I... I thought he was my little puppet to boss around, but it was the other way around...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">After the incident occurred, Mr. Retinz arrived at the theater. He got the murder weapon and swapped the rubber sword with the bloodied steel one. That's also when he lowered the victim's body down to the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...But how did he have time to do all that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When the set piece fell, the audience was evacuated from the building. He was able to do all those things after the fact because there was no one around to see.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A horrific murder camouflaged by a spectacular magic show? That sounds like the kind of murder only a magician could pull off.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">As long as the show proceeded as it was scripted, Mr. Mistree was doomed to die. That's why, YOU, Mr. Retinz, the victim -- all the way from the TV station! This prank plan -- or should I say, murder plan -- proves your murderous intent!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">HRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRNNNNNNGH! NNGAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH! Gra... GRAAMAAARYEEEEEEEEEEEEE!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>H-He can't possibly have a counterargument to make! Talk about not knowing when to "let it go and move on"!</thought> Um... Do you have a rebuttal or something, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">No blade of any kind was found in the catwalk.... ...which means you have no evidence to support your theory.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But Mr. Retinz retrieved it after the fact...!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Which still leaves you with no way to prove your wildly fantastic "remote murder" theory.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But...!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Without proof, does it not make more sense to believe... ...that the murder was committed there on the stage? That's where the blood-stained sword was found, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That is a very good point.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">As the only person who could have committed the crime there on that stage... ...Trucy Wright remains the prime suspect!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............Ngh... NNNNGGGGHHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It would appear that what you call "truth" is little more than a cheap parlor trick. In the end, you have done nothing to prove the accused's innocence. It is time at last to let it go... and move on!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Gnrk!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">............H-Ho ho ho ho ho. Are you seeing this, Magnifi Gramarye? My magic is exacting punishment on your granddaughter! The Gramarye name... is done for!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! We need to hit them with a decisive piece of evidence here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know. That's just what I was thinking!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice. Do you or don't you have anything... ...to prove that the witness committed this "remote murder" you proposed?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of course I do, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This entire incident was carried out exactly according to the script.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. So theoretically, there should be no evidence for us to find or use. Which means our best bet is to see if something unscripted happened. <thought>There's gotta be something Retinz couldn't have foreseen... And once I find it, that's how I'll expose his murderous trick!</thought> Get ready, Mr. Retinz, because I'm about to reveal the secret to your magic. There are no tricks or gimmicks here -- just some good old-fashioned logic!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">As long as the magic show went as scripted, the murder would happen without fail. Everything in this case was carefully planned so that no evidence would be left behind. Still, one thing happened that definitely wasn't in the plan. What part of the magic show wasn't a part of the show's original script?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, that can't be it. It was quite a shock when that set piece fell, but that was part of the prank plan. What I have to figure out is what wasn't a part of the culprit's master plan.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, Justice! That's not it! Of course there wasn't anything in the show's script about the victim dying. But that's because his death was only a part of the culprit's master plan. What I have to figure out is what else wasn't a part of the culprit's plan.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Bonny made a mistake during Trucy's escape trick. What mistake did Bonny make during the magic trick?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, Trucy had a hard time because the stage lift she needed was in the raised position. But that wasn't a mistake on Bonny's part since Trucy wasn't supposed to use it anyway. And it was because Trucy had to suddenly use a different lift that she had to move it. So, what was it that Bonny did during Trucy's escape trick?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, no. I should never say a person's life choices are a mistake. I'm sure she can be a great magician someday if she works hard at it. Good luck, Bonny! ...Anyway, getting back to the case... What was it that Bonny did during Trucy's escape trick?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Because Bonny placed Mr. Hat to the right of the coffin instead of to the left... ...Trucy had to reappear on the side of the coffin opposite to the one in the show's script. But the culprit didn't know that when he first arrived at the theater. Which means he was bound to make a slip-up when he tampered with the crime scene. Which part of the culprit's cover-up attempt was affected by Trucy's new position?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, that's not right. Even if Trucy's position changed... ...that wouldn't affect the placement of the fingerprints on the outside of the coffin. Besides, Trucy didn't even leave any fingerprints. So, in that case...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, no! The discrepancy between the two videos proved the footage had been edited. But that didn't have anything to do with Trucy's position. So, in that case...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thinking Trucy had appeared on the left, the culprit must've put the blood in the left hole. But the blood was eventually discovered in the right hole during the police investigation. If the killer had originally put the blood on the left side, that means... ...he must've tampered with the scene again afterwards to make it line up with the facts. To make the crime scene consistent with the facts, the culprit must have...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe he dropped the set piece, hoping to make everything an incomprehensible mess? ...But now that I think about it, I guess that doesn't make any sense. I should focus on what the culprit must've done to put the bloodstain on the right side.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's not it. Wiping off fingerprints wouldn't help make the bloodstain fit the facts. I should focus on what the culprit must've done to put the bloodstain on the right side.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right! The left and right panels of the coffin are interchangeable. The culprit must've switched the two panels to make the bloodstain fit the facts. But the switch might've also given rise to something unnatural... Oh! I remember now! There WAS something unnatural about the coffin! And it's just the evidence I need!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sorry, Mr. Retinz, but I have some very conclusive proof of your guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Another bluff, is it? There's no way you have anything of the kind. My magic is real, no tri--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">After the murder... ...you switched the left and right panels of the coffin, didn't you?!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">...Gah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And because you did, you left behind something very unnatural for us to find. This proves that Roger Retinz tampered with the crime scene after the murder took place!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, Your Honor. And I will explain how in just one sec. <thought>......Uh-oh. I think I might have gotten it wrong...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">...Hmph. What an amateur. I can see right through it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right through what?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Your gimmick, our bluff -- whatever you want to call it. Or should I just call it what it is: a lie!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But I'm not.........</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Burn.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">YEEOOOOOOOW!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! Your forehead! It's on fire!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">P-Put it out! Put it out!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're burning through my patience, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Are you all right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh. I feel like a serving of Apollo au jus-tice, but at least my hair's all right... right? I'll get it right this time, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The fingerprinting results?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What about the fingerprints is "unnatural"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's take a look at the prints the victim left inside the coffin, shall we? If the victim was facing forward in the coffin, his prints should've looked like this. However, what we found was they were facing the opposite direction. It's quite unnatural for the prints to be facing this way, wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">......Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It IS strange, isn't it? But how did they get this way?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They got this way because the culprit thought the magic show had gone according to script. The culprit thought Mr. Hat would be on the left side of the coffin... ...and that Ms. Wright would also pop up to the left of the coffin, as per the show's script. He then assumed she had thrust the sword into the hole on the left side of the coffin. That's why he put blood in the left hole when he was trying to cover up his crime. But some time after leaving the bloodstain, the culprit must've realized his mistake. He found out that, due to Bonny's mistake, Mr. Hat was to the right of the coffin... ...and that despite the script, Ms. Wright had thrust the sword into the hole on the right. In short, the hole with the blood in it was on the side opposite the one that Trucy used. To make the blood's location fit the facts, he had to tamper with the evidence yet again. So he tried to cover his tracks by switching the coffin's left and right panels.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Oh! And that's how the fingerprints in the coffin ended up backwards! Because the culprit switched the two side panels around... ...the prints ended up facing the opposite direction. ......But instead of going to all that trouble with the panels... ...why didn't the culprit just wipe the blood away and redo it on the other side?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm afraid that wouldn't have worked, Your Honor. Because of a little something called "luminol testing."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah! Right. Luminol. I almost forgot... Luminol can detect trace amounts of blood, even if it's been wiped away, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right. Wiping the blood away would've only served as proof of his meddling. How about it, Mr. Retinz? I did a pretty good job figuring out your trick, didn't I?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Nnnnnnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A person who was in the magic show... ...would never have made the mistake of putting the blood on the wrong side. Least of all Ms. Wright, who surely would've remembered she was on the other side.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! You're absolutely right!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nnnnnnngh... Why, you impudent...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sure you've realized by now, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi... ...that your claim that Ms. Wright is the culprit just doesn't hold up.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Feh! You and the accused are most certainly bound for hell!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............ Nnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnngh! Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaannnnnnngggggkkkk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">P-Prosecutor Sahdmadhi! Are you all right?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">As for the true culprit... ...he is someone who knew how the show was supposed to go, but didn't actually see it... ...and someone who had the chance to tamper with the crime scene after the incident. And the only person who fits the bill... ...is you, Roger Retinz!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Gr-r-r-r-r... Gramaryeeeeeeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All of the secrets to your tricks have been revealed. And with no tricks left, I'm afraid your show has been canceled, permanently!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">.........Gnrk! ............... A-All of my secrets have been revealed, you say...? ............... ............Hmph. Don't make me laugh, boy! Mine is the true, real magic. There are no "secrets" to reveal! Behold, ladies and gentlemen, the true power of The Great Mr. Reus! Witness a magic far greater than Troupe Gramarye's! Burn! Crumble! Fall to my furious flames! The Great Mr. Reus... ...will bring an end to you all! And now, for the final heir to the Gramarye name! Right here, right now, you, too... ...shall BUR--! Huh? No! This isn't right! Agh! Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh! No! I didn't do anything wrong! No! It's not my fault! I'm not the one to blame! I-I'm the victim here! Agh! Wh-What...? AAAGH! Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh! Stop! Noooooooooooooooooo! Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh! CUUURSE YOUUU GRAMARYEEEEEEEEEE!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Curse those Gramaryes! It's all... It's all because of them! Even now they wound me...! Curse them all to the abyss!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Does your hatred run that deep? Deep enough to kill an innocent man?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">You're damn right! You have no idea what humiliations I had to suffer! Your grandfather, Magnifi Gramarye, me out after I got hurt practicing my magic! He said I was too unskilled -- that I would mess up on stage! He threw me out of the troupe just because he was worried about his own reputation! Since I was but a child, it was always my dream to become a great magician. But that Magnifi...! He took it all from me!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But... that's no excuse...! That's no reason to do something so evil...! Magic is supposed to make people happy! Not used as a means for murder!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">What's the big deal? I just used what I had available to me, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......I get it now. That attitude toward magic... is why my grandfather kicked you out. You... You don't deserve to call yourself a magician!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">After all, you were completely taken in by my magic, were you not? If not for that lawyer over there, you would be on your way to prison as we speak!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......You're right. I didn't see through your tricks...</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">You see? So in the end, Troupe Gramarye was defeated by The Great Mr. Reus! ............ Ho ho ho. You're not fit to lecture me from on high, Trucy Wright. You don't even deserve to call yourself a magician, you nave greenhorn!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">............</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">......Pfft. Gwahhh ha ha ha ha haaa! Gaaaaah ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha haaa! Take that, Gramarye! You lose!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If anyone needs to learn to "let it go and move on," it's this guy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Gaaaaah ha ha ha ha ha ha haaaa! This court and my prison can both burn in the flames of my creation! Gwahhh ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Aaaaaaaah ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha haaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Take Mr. Retinz away! And bring a fire extinguisher, just to be safe!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I feel as though I've been watching a grand magic show.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It was close, but we just barely made it through somehow...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Huh? Why does Trucy look so down?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">......Ms. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm about to announce my verdict... Could I see that wonderful smile of yours -- that smile of a true entertainer -- as I do?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......Yes, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then. This court finds the defendant, Trucy Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Thank you for everything, Polly!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, Trucy! Grazie a Dio! Now you can open your show tomorrow -- just as planned!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yup! And it's all thanks to you two! ...Oh... but now that Mr. Reus is gone... ...I'll need to find somebody to replace him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ <thought>I don't like the way she's looking at me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Trucy... I'm so sorry about everything...</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Hey! What are you apologizing for?! Roger Retinz used us! We're victims, too! He even made me an accomplice to murder!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">But, Betty, we have to take some of the blame for this, too, you know. Even if we didn't know he was planning to kill Mr. Mistree, we DID cooperate with him.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">......It's... It's all my fault, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Neither one of you is to blame! The only one in the wrong is the person who used magic to commit murder, Roger Retinz!</line>
<line speaker="Betty">......Hmph! Don't you think I know that?! Say what you want, but don't think for a second that... that I don't still hate you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I-I guess she really does hate me...</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">But, Betty, why? You used to be a huge fan of Trucy's.</line>
<line speaker="Betty">H-Hey! Sh-Shut up! I've always hated her!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Really? But if we hadn't seen Trucy's magic show... ...we never would've tried to become professional magicians ourselves, right?</line>
<line speaker="Betty">S-Speak for yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">But, Betty, you still have her autograph from that day--</line>
<line speaker="Betty">GRAAAGH! Just shut up!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Was she acting that way this whole time because she secretly loves Trucy? Wow, Trucy. I never knew that being the best could be so tough...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Betty">C'mon, Bonny! We're leaving! We have to get ready for tomorrow's show!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Hee hee! You're really excited about performing with Trucy again, aren't you!</line>
<line speaker="Betty">Th-That's not true! So zip it, dummy!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......Polly? Do you think I really am... a "nave greenhorn"...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? <thought>......No way. She's not...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">After all, you were completely taken in by my magic, were you not? If not for that lawyer over there, you would be on your way to prison as we speak!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......You're right. I didn't see through your tricks...</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">You see? So in the end, Troupe Gramarye was defeated by The Great Mr. Reus! ............ Ho ho ho. You're not fit to lecture me from on high, Trucy Wright. You don't even deserve to call yourself a magician, you nave greenhorn!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy! Don't tell me you're taking what Retinz said to heart?!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......Well, maybe a little. I didn't see through his tricks and I let myself be taken in by his magic. I... I can't trust myself anymore. Maybe he was right to call me a greenhorn...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......You shouldn't take stock in his words. He doesn't even know the first thing about you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're a wonderful Gramarye magician. You should be proud of yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Thank you, Apollo. But what makes you say that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know you're a wonderful Gramarye magician because of this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The Gramarye creed... "A true entertainer always keeps a smile on their face." When you performed your magic trick in court today... ...you showed the world your dedication to your troupe's creed. Even through all the jeering, you kept a smile on your face, and won the crowd over. You are everything Magnifi could've hoped for in an heir. You're a great magician, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A great magician...? Me?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You really are. That's why... ...you don't have to worry about what Retinz said.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, Polly... Thank you! Still... I couldn't have done it without you. I would've lost my nerve if I'd been alone up there... But I was able to keep on smiling... because of you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Me?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I remembered what you said to me in the detention center.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">After all, you're sure you swapped the swords, right?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yes... I remember doing it...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then I just know it wasn't your fault, Trucy!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">B-But... how can you say that?! We don't have any proof it wasn't me! I-I mean, I know you're a great lawyer, Polly, but...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I believe in you, Trucy. And I believe in your skill as a professional magician. So I'm going to prove your innocence. Don't worry -- you're going to be FINE!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Your words were what kept me going.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......Apollo. Thank you from the bottom of my heart! Now I can be everything I was meant to be! </line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Trucy's real smile is the best... I'm so glad I could help make that happen.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Huh? Wait a minute. Did I get it wrong?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm really sorry, Trucy... for everything...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But why?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, I wasn't able to convince Prosecutor Sahdmadhi what a good person you are. And I had to testify against you, too.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You have nothing to apologize for! You were just doing your job!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Y-You're too kind...!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, I don't know about-- Huh? Is something wrong, Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor Sahdmadhi? What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">......Detective Skye.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I require your forensic expertise in order to close this case. Come, let us go.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Wait! Prosecutor Sahdmadhi!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The trial is over, Mr. Justice. You and I are strangers once more, with no further need to interact.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Strangers...? Have you really... forgotten all about me?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......You've really changed, Nahyuta. Telling me to "let it go" and stuff. What happened to you?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">O lawyer of impure soul... ...I have nothing to say to the likes of you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......Are you serious, Nahyuta?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Now, if you will excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ <thought>There he goes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">What was that all about, Apollo?! How do you know Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Let's just say we're old acquaintances.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">"Acquaintances"? It seemed like something more than that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Y-Yeah, well...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You don't like to talk about your past, do you? Because you always change the subject.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......I, uh... <thought>...I guess I'll have to talk about it someday... But, for now...</thought> C'mon, let's forget about the past, and celebrate Trucy's future!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Sure, if you say so.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">! Hey, it's Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Put him on speakerphone, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Phone">......*beep*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's up, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Apollo!!! How's Trucy?! What happened at the trial?! Did you get a "not guilty" verdict?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright, slow down. Everything's fine!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hi, Daddy! I'm okay now!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">She was found "not guilty" in a VERY dramatic turnabout! Plus, we saved the office! It was a great victory for Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whew, that's a load off my mind! I can't thank you enough, Apollo! Now I know I can trust you to hold down the fort anytime.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">M-Me? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, you. You're a real, full-fledged lawyer now in my eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A f-full-fledged lawyer? <thought>...I still can't wrap my mind around it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank goodness you were there to take care of everything. And thank YOU, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-No need to go that far, boss... <thought>Especially not in front of everyone...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Oh, and by the way... ...I won't be able to make it to tomorrow's show, so I was hoping you could go. You'll do that for me, won't you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of course! I wouldn't miss it for the world!</line>
<line speaker="Phone">......*beep*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Full-fledged...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So Daddy asked you to come to tomorrow's show, huh. As my assistant, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, no. He just asked me to go cheer you on.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Okay. Then I'll be sure to save you the best seat in the house, Polly!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The best seat in the house? I really appreciate the thought, but...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Good! Then it's settled!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Magical Girl Trucy Wright... will now perform her greatest illusion yet! There are no tricks or gimmicks here, ladies and gentlemen! This is REAL magic!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait a minute! You're kidding, right?! There IS a trick or gimmick, right? I'm too young to die!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Now, then, Mr. Hat! You know what to do with that sword!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-No! Wait! Stop! NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And that is how "Trucy in Gramarye-Land" ended on a rousing high note... ...with a big round of applause, and Polly's ear-splitting screams!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What kind of an ending is that?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And just what part of the testimony is inconsistent with this evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Huh. That's funny. I thought I saw an inconsistency a second ago... It disappeared -- like magic! The murder occurred during a magic show, so crazy things like this are bound to happen.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, really? Well, let's see how "magical" you think this penalty is!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-Seems pretty normal to me, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">No, it is not.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, it is not.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Let it go, and move on.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nngh... All right. I'll let it go, and move on.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But not before you take this penalty with you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'll move on, but there's no way I'm going to "let it go" with Trucy's life at stake!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, how about it, Mr. Justice? Do you have an inconsistency to show the court or not?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um, I was just doing some vocal training, so feel free to continue.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And overlook the damage done to our hearing, Mr. Justice? I think not!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ouch. And what about the damage to my pride, Your Honor?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... Nothing's really jumping out at me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And what do we do in a situation like this?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We press the heck out of the witness! Put the squeeze on them to see if we can draw out the testimony we need!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right! Good answer, Athena! <thought>Because I couldn't actually recall, myself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I must be really out of it today...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, there was one statement that I thought was a little strange...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh? Am I witnessing the power of analytical psychology at work?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nope! Feminine intuition! Let me show you which statement I'm talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Okay. Now to try comparing the evidence with the statement that caught her eye.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't think so, Apollo. Are you sure you remember how to do this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well,&amp; maybe not completely sure...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You have to pinpoint inconsistencies between Bonny's testimony and her emotions. For example, if she's saying, "It made me so mad"... ...but the Mood Matrix shows that she was feeling "Happy" -- inconsistencies like that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay. I think I've got it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Now that I've spelled it all out for you, you should be able to do it on your own.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If you're going to spell it all out for me, you might as well just tell me the answer, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Oh, really? And how does it do that? I mean, you CAN explain, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of course I--</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Because if you mess up... ...it will suuuck to be you, if you get my drift.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">..........I can't do it.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Ha! Just as I thought!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm not ready to be her human juice box just yet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid the witness and I disagree on one point, Mr. Justice. Because I'd say it DOES suck to be you right now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! <thought>Well, there goes a pint of blood anyway...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't think that's where the contradiction is, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Apparently not.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But there was that one statement where Bonny let something slip...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. The little hole in her testimony that we've been waiting for... <thought>But do we have a piece of evidence I can challenge her careless comment with...? I'd better take another good, hard look at the Court Record.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The defense's case is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims. This court finds the defendant, Trucy Wright...</line>
</xml>