
<xml>
<title>The Monstrous Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Athena">Having a yokai testify in court is unprecedented to say the least.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"I am Tenma Taro, the yokai you seek!" How could such a straight-laced man like Mr. Tenma suddenly become a demon?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, it's strange. Even worse, Prosecutor Blackquill is playing along. *sigh* I can't even think straight anymore. I need to go out for a run! See you in a bit!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait! What about the--! ...Investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Back! ...Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whoa, whoa! Trucy, welcome back. Oh, you're in your stage outfit. Back from work?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yep! I really nailed this new magic trick I've been working on! ...I also heard about those tricks that were conjured up in court earlier today. You know, the demon-out-of-nowhere trick and Polly's tightrope-style defense trick!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I was seriously considering a disappearing act of my own after all that craziness. ...Anyway, our next trick is to find a suspect other than the mayor. I know the killer must've used the air duct in the escape.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And whoever did that was the Tenma Taro that Mr. Filch and Jinxie saw.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. Maybe there's some evidence in the air duct.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The real fight starts right now!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, before you go, let me make the evidence you no longer need disappear! 3, 2, 1... Ta-dah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I wonder where all that stuff goes?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, let's get over to the scene of the crime! Vamonos, Apollo, Vamonos!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Detective Fulbright! Mind if we search the air duct?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well, since you really are on the side of justice, I suppose I can let you... Plus, my own sense of justice has been called into doubt, so...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wonder if he's been like this ever since the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, his sense of justice HAS been beaten to a pulp. It'll probably take a while for him to recover.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I sorta feel bad for him, but we have work to do! Let's go get the evidence we need!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The air duct is the key. We know the Tenma Taro impersonator used it to make an escape. After murdering the alderman, the killer left the Fox Chamber through the hallway door. Then, after locking the door from the outside... ...the killer entered the air duct in the hallway. Finally, the killer dropped the key into the Fox Chamber through the air vent here... ...then went back through the duct and fled the manor. That's how the illusion of no one entering or leaving the locked room was created!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If the killer passed through the air duct, maybe we'll find some evidence there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, maybe some black feathers or something like that. Well, here's our vent. It's awfully high up.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't worry, I brought a stepladder! Happy hunting!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>How nice of her to volunteer me for the job.</thought> Whoa, it's pitch black in here. Well, here goes nothing! *cough, cough* *wheeze* *sputter* *cough, cough* There's a thick layer of dust in here! *cough, cough* *wheeze* *sputter* *cough, cough* ............ ...I don't... get it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Find anything? Yikes! Apollo, what happened?! You're covered in dust!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, dust... Lots of dust.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, what'd you find?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You know how dust collects on something when nobody uses it for a long time?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, like Mr. Wright's desk back at the office.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... You think it'd be possible to crawl over that sort of dust without leaving a trail?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I seriously doubt it... Wait, you're not suggesting--! No one's gone through that duct lately?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Kinda looks that way. And if it's true, Mayor Tenma is going to be fingered as the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-B-But...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If we don't turn things around quickly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">In justice we trust!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! Sorry, Mr. Justice! But it seems your justice was not the most just, after all! It is MY sense of justice that has prevailed!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Argh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Detective Fulbright sure seems chipper all of a sudden.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh. And I'm back to my old devastated self.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Aw, come on! Where's that never-say-die spirit? Bring it on, Mr. Lawyer Man! Bring it on!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let me suffer in peace.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! Justice prevails once more!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's not over yet! And besides... Kicking someone when they're down is what bad guys do!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ack! A-Are you calling me a... a bad guy?! Me? Bobby Fulbright, champion of justice?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Then how about some information on the investigation? We need some help here!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Information? About the investigation? All right! But I won't have you calling me a bad guy ever again! Understood?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We did it, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but how long can we keep this up?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can't believe Prosecutor Blackquill would stoop that low! I mean, to pinning the blame on a yokai?! He really wants a conviction at all costs!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She could give a yokai a run for its money when she's mad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yes, well... I have him writing a self-reflective essay as we speak!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I doubt that'll teach him anything.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, he'll probably just write "Dotard" a thousand times.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That whole yokai business is most likely a ploy to win a conviction. Truth is, Prosecutor Blackquill believes Jinxie Tenma planted that yokai stuff. Planted it in an effort to protect her father -- the real killer.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, right! I'd like to see him prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Whoa! Calm down! He doesn't have any direct evidence, but we did find this. It was at the base of the cliff just outside Kyubi Manor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait... That isn't the staff Tenma Taro was supposedly carrying, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">The one and only! Ms. Tenma no doubt tossed it over the cliff when she was done.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No way! W-Well, what about prints?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Nope, no prints, but if she was wearing a costume, there wouldn't be any, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, prints or no prints, it's not going to work out in our favor. <thought>Sounds like the staff might have belonged to the mansion. But if that's the case... ...then where in the mansion did Tenma Taro get it from?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did Prosecutor Blackquill figure out that the victim was The Amazing Nine-Tails?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">He did, indeed. He's a sharp one, all right. He figured it out while investigating the municipal merger and the victim's past. The Amazing Nine-Tails sparked the yokai craze and worked against the merger! And Mayor Damian Tenma is the corrupt politician who murdered that great hero! The Amazing Nine-Tails's fans are so angry, they even tried to storm the detention center!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't blame them. I mean, their favorite masked wrestling hero was murdered. They must've been shocked when they found out what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Speaking of which, isn't Jinxie also a fan of The Amazing Nine-Tails?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">A wrestler's mask is more precious than his own life! He'd never unmask himself in front of others. But there ARE matches where wrestlers battle for the right to remove each other's masks. To have your mask torn off is the worst humiliation a wrestler could suffer! That's why their masks are more important to them than life itself.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">She spoke with a passion that only a fan could appreciate. We oughta become fans ourselves and go protest in front of the prison!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? No! Did you forget that Mayor Tenma is not only Jinxie's father, but our client!?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">You be careful, now. You're defending the most hated mayor in history. I just hope you don't find yourself on the wrong end of a figure-four leg lock!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe I should wear a mask to hide MY identity.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Such a grisly crime scene! I won't rest until that murderous fiend is behind bars!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you still think Mayor Tenma is responsible?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's right! Damian Tenma is an evil fiend who must be banished from this world! Now, take my hand and together we will defeat this evil!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, I think you're forgetting that Mayor Tenma's still my client.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, it was the spear that killed the alderman?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's right. He'd been in a drug-induced sleep, but woke the moment he was impaled. That's when he was struck by his attacker!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's almost superhuman.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Justice cannot allow evil to exist unopposed! Even if it means sacrificing one's life!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I bet you two could strike back even if you were impaled! I mean, you're so full of justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? Or are you just saying that because of my name, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are there any other new developments we should know?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hm, now that you mention it... Our suspect is suffering partial memory loss, but he DID manage to remember something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He did? What did he say?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">He said he didn't want to speak with us. His exact words were: "I am under no obligation to speak with you mortals!" ...and other things of that nature.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I wonder what Mayor Tenma remembered.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Too bad you can't go ask him now, 'cause Prosecutor Blackquill's busy questioning him. I know! Why don't you wait down at the playground with the rest of the kids? Ha ha.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What now, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How about regrouping back at the agency?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Good idea. We might get some words of wisdom out of Mr. Wright while we're there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So the crime scene was locked tight at the time. Ugh, this is a tough one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The only people in that locked room were the deceased -- the alderman -- and the mayor.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe the killer hid somewhere in that room.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But is there really anywhere to hide in the Fox Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That was quite a day in court. The news just can't stop talking about how the demon Tenma Taro made an appearance!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's never an exorcist around when you need one.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I heard the judge actually held an exorcism in his courtroom after that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Good. Let's hope it's the last we'll see of that pain-in-the-neck yokai.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't know. I have a feeling Tenma Taro could exorcise an exorcist.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">As an attorney defending a demon, I know exactly how that feels.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can't believe Alderman Kyubi was The Amazing Nine-Tails!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm, maybe that's why the killer targeted him. His popularity among the anti-merger faction would have been a major obstacle.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah... Maybe the alderman felt threatened, and that's why he had to disguise himself.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Do you think the Tenma Taro Jinxie saw was the real killer?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... It's hard to say at this point.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But if that's not our killer, then what was it doing in the manor?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Maybe it just wanted to use the bathroom.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh?! I've heard of monsters in the closet and under the bed. They're in the bathroom, too?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, what I'm saying is the Tenma Taro Jinxie saw was someone dressed up like a yokai. I mean, there is no such thing as monsters in the bathroom. People on the other hand...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, I get it. That was your attempt at a joke. Ha ha, very funny...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>For someone so competitive and smart, she sure get some crazy ideas.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe I'll... go read over some past cases...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And I'll... go do some research on exorcisms...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, what's with you guys? You seem bummed out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How should I put this? It's like we're at the edge of a cliff and the only way is down.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">In other words, business as usual, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I suppose so. Except this time, it's like we're bound and gagged, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't forget blindfolded with our ears plugged up...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh, and monsters at every turn, huh? Sounds rough...</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey, Apollo. Oh, and Athena's here, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How goes the investigation, Apollo, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think it's safe to say that things have gotten hairier than before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? What happened?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was watching the two of you this morning from the gallery. That was one tough day in court, to say the least.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know. I've never had to defend a yokai before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That business about the locked room was another major hurdle.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, and on top of that, Jinxie was accused of being an accomplice!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But at least you figured out how someone could have escaped the Forbidden Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, well, we just found out that our reasoning might be a tad... flawed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, really? Well, that's... bad news.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">How are we going to get out of this one...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The worst of times are when lawyers have to force their biggest smiles.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Force... a smile?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. My mentor taught me that back when I was still learning the trade. She... also taught me to return to the basics whenever I got stuck.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Return to the basics?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. Always believe in your client, no matter what happens. That is a lawyer's greatest and most trusted weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The basics... <thought>Always believe in your client, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, Mr. Wright, how long have you known Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I met her during a trip to Europe.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh!? Y-You were in Europe? <thought>Why haven't I heard about this before?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I went there a few times to study the various legal systems over there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, okay... Er, wait a minute. I thought you worked as a pianist after you quit practicing law.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I did, but an old friend of mine needed help with some legal work from time to time, so...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, I guess you were never very far from the courtroom, then.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It was like fate brought us together! It's thanks to Mr. Wright that I became a lawyer at all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha. I knew she was lawyer material from the moment I met her. And I have high hopes for her ability to analyze people's emotions.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aww, it's nothing special.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... Maybe I've underestimated that analytical psychology of hers.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's just, I thought that if my special ability could help defend innocent people... ...then I had to do everything in my power to bring it to the courtroom! That's when I really started hitting the books hard!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm still amazed she actually became a lawyer. And at the tender age of 18, no less.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, that's almost superhuman. <thought>Or personal -- like she [sic] trying to help somebody she knows.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your attorney's badge, huh... I used to show mine to everyone, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know, I never really thought about it. But I could ask you the same question.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Me? Well, I guess you could say I show it because there's someone to show it to. ...Or something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha ha. When you say it like that, it sounds kind of... I don't know... philosophical?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Heh heh, I guess it does. <thought>.........Or does it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Here's a little souvenir Trucy wanted you to have.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aww, how sweet! I know. I'll hang it in my office once the case is closed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't know, it's pretty creepy looking. We don't want to freak our clients out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... You have a point there. Maybe you should hang it in your room, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">My room?! I don't want this thing in there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't want it, either. It has instant nightmare fuel written all over it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, Trucy got it for you, so stop trying to pawn it off on me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know... The more I look at it, the more I wonder if these are your distant relatives.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey... What's that supposed to mean?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the room was locked tight and the only people in there were the suspect and victim? I headed up a similar case a long time ago.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not only that, the defendant was my assistant.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And not only that, the prosecutor for that trial loved to swing her whip around in court.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A whip?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When I saw that whip... man, I thought it was all over.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, your assistant getting accused of murder hadn't made you think that already...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha ha. You're getting good at this, Apollo. Remember, the way you present evidence in court can really have an impact on the trial. Hmm... But your elbow angle's a little off. It should really be more like this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I'll be fine! I'll be more careful next time. Promise!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">All right! I'm totally pumped up after talking to you, Mr. Wright! It's like you said, the worst of times are when lawyers have to force their biggest smiles!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And don't forget to return to the basics whenever you get stuck.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Keep believing in my client. Right!</thought> Um, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm... I'm going to go visit our client again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think that's a good idea.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Alright, time to see what's new down at the Detention Center!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mayor Tenma, we wanted to talk to you about something!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Caw-shaaaaaaaaw!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeek!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Caw caw-caw-caw! So, my minions have returned!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, he still thinks he's a yokai!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wonder if we'll ever be able to talk to Mayor Tenma again.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Silence, peddler of the legal trade! Free me from these imprisoning walls with great haste!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow... He's sounding more and more like a real demon with every sentence. I'm starting to wonder if we should even be helping him win his freedom.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Still, we can't let Mayor Tenma stay possessed, you know what I mean?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">If you can clear me of these charges, I shall help in whatever manner I may. Now, ask of me what you will!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I suppose it's worth a shot.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Were those feathers and tracks at the scene of the crime really your doing?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Indeed! The remnants of Tenma Taro, King of the Underworld, they be! The day when I once again dominate the mortal world is at hand, caw caw-caw-caw!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The prosecution claims the feathers and tracks were planted by Jinxie.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">What's this?! I must breach these walls and go defend my little Jinxie at once!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? Mayor Tenma, is that you?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">! ...Grr! Well, now! Damian appears to still reside within this body. But I should have expected as much from a descendent of mine! Be silent, now, Damian!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess a little thing like demonic possession won't stop a father's love for his daughter.</thought> You didn't kill Alderman Kyubi, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">I have killed no one! The remnants of my presence have been misconstrued. The murderer is not I! For if I had slain that mortal... ...raging hellfire would have consumed him, leaving naught but ash!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yikes! ............S-So... S-So... you're saying, there must have been somebody else there? <thought>Come to think of it, the mayor had mentioned that he'd been clubbed with this statue. I'd better ask about this, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Detective Fulbright mentioned that you might have something new to tell me.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Indeed, I have. I regurgitated this key but a short while ago. Behold, the key to the Forbidden Chamber!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa! Is regurgitation one of your demonic powers, too?!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Bah! I do not waste my powers on such parlor tricks! Take the key from the killer did Damian, whereupon he swallowed it. He sought to bar the killer entry to the Forbidden Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So, he wanted to keep it shut tight?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tenma">But no fingerprints shall you find upon that key.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How do you know that? ...Wait. Is THAT another one of your demonic powers, then?!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Foolish mortal! You would have me, Tenma Taro, act as some asinine alchemist?! I but asked the jailer and my will was done -- quite eagerly, I must add, caw caw-caw-caw!</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Always an honor to serve, Your Malevolence!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Guess I'm not the only one he scares the living daylights out of.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um, can we ask how you use this key? We couldn't find a keyhole anywhere in or around the door.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Curse that infernal door! But if I had known its manner of opening, long, long ago would I have made my return!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He has a point there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe Jinxie knows something about how the whole thing works...</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">What, might I ask, is that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This statue was found at the scene. Someone hit Mayor Tenma over the head with it. It had been wrapped in a large cloth before the alderman's murder.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Let me see whether Damian knows about such a thing... Hrmmm, yes... Something wrapped in just such a cloth does he recall. A secret gift from Alderman Kyubi it would seem. He, however, had not a chance to see it till now, for the cloth did conceal it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe the cloth fell off or was removed after the mayor was struck.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Hrmmm, of that Damian does not know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A secret gift? Interesting... Maybe Jinxie knows something about it...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Ages has it been since I've seen that. We often battled it out like this back in the day.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I've been meaning to ask, which one of you was stronger?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Caw caw-caw-caw! That would be me, of course! For I am the demon lord of the yokai! Caw-shaaaaaaaaw!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, but the Nine-Tailed Fox imprisoned you in--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena! Don't encourage him! It's already hard enough as it is.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aw, I just wanted to find out which one was really the strongest.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Why, that is a photo of me soaring through the heavens. Hrmm, but look at my wing angle. It's all wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, you're really a stickler for details.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">I even gave a big smile for the camera... ...but so small am I in this shot that one can't even see it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Never knew demons were so interested in how they're presented by the media.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Hrmmm... A descendent of old Nine-Tails, perhaps? It would seem he's doing quite well these days.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, he's a huge hit from kids all the way up to their grandparents.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Hrmmm... It seems I've been resting on my laurels for far too long. It is time I, too, debut in the mortal world and rekindle my struggle against that wily fox.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's the spirit! You can make your debut as soon as we get you that not-guilty verdict!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Then I had best return to top form! Pushups and sit-ups should do for now. Caw caw-caw!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is he planning a new career as a pro wrestler?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Umm... I was hoping you'd take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Hrmmm... An offering to me. Quite admirable. But the best thing you could offer me is to win me my freedom! Caw caw-caw-caw!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">R-Right, right... I'll do my best!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Why this--! This is that accursed blackmail letter that was sent to Damian.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apparently, somebody slipped it into the alderman's pocket. We believe someone, probably the killer, stole it from Mayor Tenma's briefcase. You wouldn't happen to know anything about that, would you?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Caw caw-caw-caw! You have questions, do you? Very well, ask away, mortal!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who placed this in the alderman's pocket?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Hrmmm. Very few were they who knew the letter was in Damian's briefcase.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, whoever knew about the blackmail letter being in the mayor's briefcase... ...is a potential suspect in its theft and placement in the alderman's pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Ah! Could it have been... HIS doing?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Mayor, er... I mean, Mr. Taro! Did you just remember something?!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Indeed, I did. There was but one other who knew of that letter: Damian's aide Florent L'Belle. Full knowledge of that briefcase's contents did that aide possess.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then he may be the blackmailer and the murderer we're looking for!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">That is preposterous! He's a most trusted advisor. He would never betray Damian!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It seems like Mayor Tenma is a bit too trusting of those around him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Still, this is HUGE! Now we know who might've slipped that blackmail letter in the alderman's pocket! Look out, Florent L'Belle, here comes Justice!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's go find Mr. L'Belle and rake him over the coals!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thanks for the help. You've just given us a major lead!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... There's something that still bothers me. If Mr. L'Belle is the killer... ...what could have motivated him to open the Forbidden Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We should probably search it for clues.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Only one problem. How do you open a locked door that doesn't have a keyhole?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's go talk to Jinxie. Maybe she can help.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, isn't that...?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Grrr. You dare imprison me?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Jinxie! She's... acting really strange.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">That loathsome, no-good Nine-Tailed Fox. He shall know the terror that is mine and despair. Grrr... Grrr. You shall pay. Oh, you shall pay dearly! ......All of you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">J-Jinxie, are you all right?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">! Eeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Oh! Is that you, Mr. Demon Lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Morning, Jinxie.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Morning? Isn't it already past noon? And what am I doing here? Last I remember, I lay down to take a nap back at the manor. ......Oh, no! It must've been the Makuragaeshi!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Makura... gaeshi?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Ever wake after a restless night's sleep to find your pillow in an unusual place... ...or that you've been sleeping on the floor or in the hallway? Well, it's that yokai's fault! The Makuragaeshi preys on people when they're asleep!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It sounds like you just need to be tucked in really tight, or maybe a snug sleeping bag.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Jinxie, how come you don't have any charms on your forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">I don't? Oh, they must've fallen off. Without them, evil things can creep into me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'd say we had a more than adequate demonstration of that just now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">I'd better reapply them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Jinxie, there's something we wanted to ask you.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Ah! There was something I wanted to tell you, too! I... I remembered something else!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You did? What was it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Jinxie, can you tell us what you remembered?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Well, after the trial I remembered lots of stuff. But there was one thing I thought was really weird.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm almost afraid to ask, but here goes...</thought> Really? What?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Um... It's about the yokai feathers and tracks. They weren't there when I first opened the door!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, whaaat?! Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. My memory's crystal clear now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you're saying they were left at the crime scene after you found it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This could spell major trouble, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Because Jinxie is already accused of leaving the feathers and tracks at the scene. If they weren't there when she discovered the crime scene... ...it will totally fuel the claim that she fabricated the evidence later on.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Jinxie's fuzzy memory of the whole incident is really working against us. The prosecution will probably say she doesn't remember planting the evidence. Good luck rebutting that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, man, this is not good. <thought>I sure hope she didn't plant the evidence while she was sleepwalking or something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Jinxie, you wouldn't happen to know how to open the Forbidden Chamber, would you? That door doesn't even have a keyhole.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Well, it's supposed to have a secret mechanism. They say you have to figure it out before the keyhole will appear.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A secret mechanism?! Really?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. It's hidden in the Fox Chamber. But only Alderman Kyubi knew what it was, and how it worked.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The alderman of Nine-Tails Vail [sic] sure loved his secrets.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, let's go see if we can find that secret mechanism!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa, slow down! There's something else I need to ask about. Jinxie, is there only one key to the Forbidden Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. Even the manor's master key won't open it. That's because it's a very special room... that must never be opened.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Guess that means nobody entered the Forbidden Chamber after the murder. After all, we know Mayor Tenma took the key from the killer and swallowed it, so...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So the mayor's efforts to keep the killer out of the Forbidden Chamber... ...were not in vain!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Alderman Kyubi made that statue. It's a token of goodwill... ...I think it was meant to be for Nine-Tails Vale and Tenma Town.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A token of goodwill? But the two yokai are fighting.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Fighting? Oh, I see what you mean! The cup portion is missing. This statue... ...originally depicted the two yokai holding up a cup in celebration. But it sure doesn't look that way now, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe it broke when it was used to hit Mayor Tenma on the head.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">That would explain it. I guess the only two people who knew what it really looked like were the alderman and I. Now it's just me, but its symbol of goodwill will be forever etched in my mind!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">...No... That's about it...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! <thought>My bracelet! It's reacting!</thought> Jinxie, you wouldn't happen to be--</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">In justice we trust!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yikes!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Eek! A ghost!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Argh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Detective Fulbright! What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">I have business with this young lady, if you must know. Prosecutor Blackquill has asked me to question her.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Question me? ...Sorry, not interested.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are you here to ask about that whole yokai affair?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's right. Specifically, we want to ask-- Ah, but I can't tell you that, now can I? Ha ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, come on, please? We're partners in justice, right?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">No no, Prosecutor Blackquill specifically told me, my questions were of the utmost justice. I will not fall for your lies! In justice we trust!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The Twisted Samurai sure has him on a short leash.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">So you're not a ghost? Maybe some sort of urban troll, then?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Now, come along, Ms. Tenma. To the station with you!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He took her away.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Missed my chance to see what she was lying about.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, at least we found out there's a secret mechanism for opening the chamber! Let's go check it out!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I just hope they let us in now.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Oh, what an absolutely FABULOUS scent! I'm SO glad I had these carnations imported from England. Nothing but the FINEST will do. Perhaps I should place one aside for our DEARLY departed alderman.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, it's Mr. L'Belle! Apollo, let's ask him about you-know-what!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh yeah, before we search the Fox Chamber we should ask about the blackmail letter.</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Why, if it isn't the mayor's little lawyers. What do YOU want with ME?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, um, there's something we wanted to ask... <thought>Where's that ringing coming from?</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">You'll HAVE to excuse me. ...Hello? L'Belle here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What the--?! <thought>Those things on his shoulders are cell phones?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">...Yes, about that. You MUST forgive me! This WHOLE matter with Mayor Tenma has been a COMPLETE nightmare.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">......Where do you buy clothes like that?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! Surprised? This is my OWN special design. It's the ULTIMATE in functional beauty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Functional beauty? Are you sure about that? Looks a bit unwieldy to me. Ack!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! You simply don't have an eye for beauty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...If having an eye for beauty means looking like this guy, I'd rather be blind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">So, what DO you want with ME?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Both Jinxie and Mr. Filch said they saw Tenma Taro. But what about you, Mr. L'Belle? If you were there in the foyer, why didn't you see-- Ack!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! Very well, I ADMIT it. That's right! I, Florent L'Belle, SAW the demon Tenma Taro!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... <thought>So he did see something.</thought> Then why did you lie about not seeing him?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">I was SIMPLY trying to protect dear little Jinxie.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Protect Jinxie? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Why, don't TELL me you haven't heard of that strange little HABIT of hers?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Which one are we talking about...?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">The ONE where she wanders around making mischief without knowing WHAT she's doing! Rumor has it she's possessed by Tenma Taro.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That one's new to me.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! Well, THERE you have it! Anytime you HEAR about a Tenma Taro sighting... ...little Jinxie should be your PRIME suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Tell us more about that rumor!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, what was that rumor about Jinxie?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">They say she's possessed. Not ALL the time, of course. It hits suddenly, then she starts WANDERING around doing strange THINGS.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-Is that so...? <thought>Although, come to think of it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">That loathsome, no-good Nine-Tailed Fox. He shall know the terror that is mine and despair.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That certainly would explain how she was acting earlier.</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Once, she EVEN put on a Tenma Taro costume and wandered around the woods at night.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She did?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Ugh. Beware you who sealed me away.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh. I wish I'd never asked.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Does she remember anything while she's possessed?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Unfortunately, no. She doesn't seem to remember a THING during these EPISODES.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Memory loss during possession... Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Come to think of it, her MEMORY of the MURDER scene was QUITE fuzzy. I suppose THAT, too, was caused by her possession.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Ah! Then maybe--</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! So you DO understand! That whole yokai business was ENTIRELY of her own making!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now wait a minute! <thought>Although... that yokai evidence wasn't there until after she discovered the crime scene... Did she leave those black feathers and strange tracks there herself?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, let's ask Mayor Tenma about Jinxie's episodes the next time we talk with him!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Jinxie thinks she saw Tenma Taro near the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! That little dear is ALWAYS talking such nonsense. After all, she's ALWAYS calling you a red demon, is she not?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gngh!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Plus, she has the nerve to call ME of all people a yokai! She even has a name for me: Baron Powder Face! Pffft! I've NEVER been so insulted!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>How could anyone look at him and NOT think monster?</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Now, if she had named me the BEAUTIFUL Baron Powder Face, I could've forgiven her.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, THAT's your sticking point?!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">WHAT is THAT?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's the blackmail letter, but it wasn't sent to Alderman Kyubi. It was sent to Mayor Tenma.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">AND? ......Your point BEING?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Someone took the letter from the mayor's briefcase... ...and then placed it in the alderman's pocket after he was murdered.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Oh, you don't say...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You wouldn't happen to be the one who made the switch, would you? After all, you're the only one who knew that the blackmail letter was in his briefcase... ...so, naturally, you-- Ack!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! PERHAPS that shot of cologne will MAKE those scales FALL from your eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Or my eyes fall from their sockets.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Is it possible that you would like to FRAME me as a potential SUSPECT? What would MAKE you raise such an OUTRAGEOUS allegation in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, uh, well...</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! My ONLY crime is being born as BEAUTIFUL as you see here! In other words, YOU have NOTHING! Now, let me show you what to DO with this garbage!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ahhh! You can't destroy evidence like that!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">What do you mean I CAN'T? I just DID, ah ha ha ha! Feel a little lighter now?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>You've just won a one-way trip to the top of my "most annoying people ever" list, buddy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*sigh* <thought>I guess that's it for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Hello, L'Belle speaking! ...Really? You wish to carry MY new product at YOUR store? Oh, but I'm afraid it's my own PRIVATE brand. It's NOT available to the public. ...What? Then I </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>Stop the bus. I'm getting off.</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! EVERYONE wants my EXCLUSIVE "Je suis L'Belle!" brand products! It's the crown jewel of MY collection, born of my LONG, RELENTLESS pursuit of beauty! But now that it's become SO popular, it's been an ABSOLUTE nightmare!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You don't say.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Well, they CAN'T have it! It's just for ME! It's not meant for you PEASANTS.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Peasants?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">This is my LATEST product! I'm calling it "Couleur Me L'Belle!" A DAZZLING hair color that you can wash out with just water!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Guess that means you can't sweat.</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">I have SEVEN colors in all. You can find out more in my commercials and magazine ads.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Yet, it's not available to the public? Great sales strategy there, genius.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Come to think of it, Mr. L'Belle... ...your hair color's changed since the last time we met.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! The little lady has QUITE the discerning eye! Here's a little sample. Consider it a gift for one who TRULY appreciates beauty.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, uh... Apollo, what should I do?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Better take it before you get a face full of cologne.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Good point. ...Wow, thanks, Mr. L'Belle.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, let's head over to the Fox Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We've still gotta find the secret mechanism for opening the Forbidden Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Dazzling hair color that you can wash out with water. Isn't it magnificent?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What if you start to sweat? Won't that wash the color out, too?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! I assure you, Florent L'Belle, embodiment of beauty, does NOT sweat!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then what about rain? Even if you don't sweat, you never know when it might-- Ack!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Pffft! Peasants like YOU fail to GRASP the truth. Rain and other forces of nature draw back in awe of my beauty!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sure they're not being repelled back by your narcissism?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Before clearing all Talk options and presenting Blackmail Letter at Kyubi Manor - Garden">April 18</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Hey, we're trying to conduct an investigation here! Come back later once we're done.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*sigh* <thought>Oh, well. Guess we'll have to find a way to kill some time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's go talk to Mr. L'Belle while we wait. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, there was something I wanted to ask him, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">If you're looking for Mayor Tenma's aide, I saw him in the garden earlier. We won't be here much longer. Go keep that narcissist company in the meantime.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, let's find that secret mechanism for opening the Forbidden Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, this is so exciting! I can't wait to see how it works! But do you really think the killer entered the Forbidden Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We'll just have to open it to find out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We should also see if there was anywhere the killer could've hid in this room! Okay, let's get started. ¡Apúrate, Apollo, Apúrate!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Still no keyhole, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, and the door won't budge, just like those spiky bangs of yours.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, all it takes is some water, but I don't think that would work on the door.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, I know! I'll break it down with a body slam!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ha ha ha. I seriously doubt you could do that.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Tsk, how do you know if I haven't even tried?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, wait, don't!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aaaagh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>As much as you hate losing, Athena, I think the door would win this match...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe the killer hid under this table!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That would be a terrible hiding place. The alderman's body would've been right above.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm, maybe you're right. Guess the underside is a bit... Wait, there's something under the table.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's check it out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, look! There's something down here!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It looks like a piece of something. Only question is, a piece of what?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... Oh, I know! It might be a piece of this statue. Remember what Jinxie said? The statue originally depicted two yokai holding up a cup. It was a symbol of goodwill.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, this piece broke off and rolled under the table?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What have we here... It's the piece that broke off of this statue. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">You think it broke off when the mayor was clobbered on the head?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'd say that's the most likely explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a carving of the Nine-Tailed Fox over the door and statues of him on either side. The way those two statues are glaring, it's like they're guarding the door from us. Come to think of it, there are two foxes on the folding screen as well. It can't be a coincidence, can it...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, this statue moves!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't get carried away, now. I mean, who knows? It might trigger a trap.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Heh heh. I can handle it. If a spear comes shooting my way, I'll snatch it out of the air! After all, I have the reflexes of a regular karate kid!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess if you can catch something that fast out of mid-air, you can accomplish anything. Still... There might be something to the fact that these fox statues rotate. Maybe there's something around here that shows the position they should be in.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look at all these feathers...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...And bloody tracks, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Then we have Jinxie and Mr. Filch's eyewitness reports...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...And a newspaper photo.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Our yokai's definitely not the shy type, that's for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is bad! Mayor Tenma is scary enough without people thinking he's a yokai!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't think we'll find anything else on this chair.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I just remembered this mystery novel I once read. The murder occurred in a locked room... ...and the perpetrator made sure to hide behind the room's door when it was opened. Then, when no one was looking, he made his escape.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A clever trick, but it would've been impossible in this case. See this broken tanuki statue here? The door must've banged into it when it was opened.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, I get it. The killer couldn't have been there because of the statue.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Better take a look behind this door, too... Oh, look. The doorknob banged into the wall. Made a big dent, too. That wouldn't have happened if the killer had been hiding there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right... I guess that rules out the old hide-behind-the-door trick.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There really is no escaping here through the air duct.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And here we went through all the trouble of bringing a ladder to check it out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's not a ladder, Apollo. It's a stepladder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's the difference? They both have the word ladder in them.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's the difference...? ............ Oh, I know! Let's play rock, paper, scissors to decide who's right!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're way too competitive. And it's not even related to the original issue, either!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a cliff outside this window. Makes it pretty impossible to get out this way.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">When I hear things like that, it just makes me want to try! Never say never, right? I bet I could get out this way. Hrrrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, wait! Do you have a death wish or something?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Tsk, it won't even open wide enough for me to squeeze through! Guess I lost that bet.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That loss just saved your life.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This statue originally depicted the two yokai holding up a cup in a gesture of goodwill.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe Alderman Kyubi was planning on smoothing things over with Mayor Tenma.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But he was murdered instead... ...by somebody who intervened.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The mayor was only pursuing the municipal merger because he'd been blackmailed. Who knows? If this murder hadn't occurred, maybe they could've come up with a solution.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Two foxes standing back to back are depicted on this elegant folding screen. Could this have something to do with the keyhole? Hmm... Wait a minute... Two foxes... There are two fox statues in front of the Forbidden Chamber as well. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe the keyhole will appear if we do something to this folding screen. Hmm... But I don't see anything unusual about it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, it does have two foxes on it, and there are two fox statues in front of the door.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Then maybe there's a clue somewhere in this room. Let's turn the whole place upside down!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's as excited as a kid in a candy store.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I can't think of anywhere else to look. You find anything, Apollo? We'll never find the keyhole to the Forbidden Chamber at this rate.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's something about that folding screen. You know how those fox statues in front of the Forbidden Chamber move? That screen might be a clue as to how we're supposed to position them or something.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, I bet you're right! Let's go over that screen with a fine-toothed comb!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">On closer inspection... ...I think there's more to this screen than meets the eye.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's check every last inch of it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tap and slide on the bottom screen to rotate the folding screen. I can also tap on something of interest to inspect it further.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You can also zoom in and out to get a better look. Now, let's check every last inch of it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, doesn't it look like the picture here has been cut off on both ends?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm, now that you mention it...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It looks like there are supposed to be doors on both ends, but they're cut in half.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe those doors symbolize the Forbidden Chamber's door.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... It definitely feels like something significant, but the question is, what?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's this? Looks like a keyhole or something.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You think it could be the keyhole to the Forbidden Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, it's just a picture.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Still, you know what they say: a picture's worth a thousand words.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's this? Looks like a keyhole or something.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You think it could be the keyhole to the Forbidden Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, what about that key drawn on the end of the screen? You think the two are related?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a picture of a key. Hmm, that shape looks awfully familiar. Oh, I know! It's shaped like the Forbidden Chamber's key.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... We're definitely getting warmer...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, let's take an ever closer look.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a picture of a key. Hmm, that shape looks awfully familiar. Oh, I know! It's shaped like the Forbidden Chamber's key. Hmm... Wait! What about that keyhole drawn on the center of the screen? You think the two are related?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A key and a keyhole? Ooh, I just got an idea! If we folded the screen up just right, the key and keyhole should overlap!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, I think you're right!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's give it a try!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look, a door!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, and it's open, too!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The two foxes are now facing each other, so... Hey, what if we made those fox statues face each other?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! Let's go check out the two statues!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay! Help me move the two statues so they face each other -- just like on the screen. Look! A lock appeared!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Now we can use that key!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, here goes nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It worked!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Time to see why this chamber's so forbidden!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What secrets could it hold, I wonder...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">These doors need some serious oil.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aaah! That was like nails on a chalkboard!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right. Forgot about those super good ears of yours. Look, more feathers...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What the heck is that...? ...Is that a Tenma Taro... statue? But there's... something odd about it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh... All I know is I don't like it, but I can't explain why.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You okay, Athena? You look kinda pale. You're not scared, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What, of this thing? Don't make me laugh, heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? ......Hey, look!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wh-What?! What is it?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Over there on the left. There's a bunch of staffs on that rack. They kinda look like the staff we saw earlier...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You mean the one Jinxie said she saw Tenma Taro carrying?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. I bet our Tenma Taro impersonator really did come in here at some point.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well? What are we waiting for? Let's search the place!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa, that's one big statue. Must be something like fifteen feet tall. And look! THIS Tenma Taro has a staff! But the Tenma Taro in the scroll didn't have one.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... I wonder why.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I feel like this could be significant, but why...? Let's take a closer look. First, to go around this table here...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ah! Apollo, are you sure that's a good idea?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, it looks like there's some sort of compartment in the base of the statue.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't open it! Who knows what might be in there!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's just a big empty compartment. And from all the dust and cobwebs... ...I'd say it hasn't been opened in a really long time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's enough, Apollo. Let's shut it and--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, there IS something in here! Looks like some sort of figure. But it's so dusty, I can't tell what it's supposed to be. Wonder what it's doing here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This statue's probably twice as tall as Prosecutor Blackquill.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yeah, and he towers over me as it is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's like if you took something really scary, like a spider, and made it fifteen feet tall.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A fifteen-foot tall spider?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? I was just exaggerating for dramatic effect.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, Prosecutor Blackquill may be scary, but a fifteen-foot spider is utterly terrifying!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like an old scroll... and there's something drawn on it! Unless I'm mistaken, it looks like an old guy... Some sort of monk, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A monk? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You know, people that take walks in the mountains as a form of spiritual training...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wouldn't that just be a hiker?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The guy in this picture doesn't look like he's doing it for fun, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... Oh look, there's some yellow... thing strapped to his back.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa! It's turning into Tenma Taro!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's this scroll getting at? Is this how Tenma Taro was born?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, whatever it is, it's definitely creepy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The yellow thing the one guy had transformed into Tenma Taro!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... Or maybe the picture's showing Tenma Taro getting caught in a yokai trap. I bet that yellow thing is a trap to catch the demon before he ravages the entire mountain!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I highly doubt yokai are things you can catch like a bear or wild boar.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Then maybe that yellow thing is some leftovers that didn't get put in the fridge. They got all gross and moldy and out popped Tenma Taro!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You have a really active imagination. First off, they probably didn't have fridges back then... ...and second, we'd be swimming in yokai if they spawned that easily.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, Mr. Smarty-Pants, what is it, then?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, umm... That yellow thing could've been a bomb containing Tenma Taro. And the old guys were terrorists who used yokai to further their cause.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Apollo, if I have an active imagination, yours is hyperactive.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Black feathers... They looks exactly like the ones in the Fox Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That means the killer must've been in here at some point. The question is, why?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe... Maybe the Tenma Taro costume was hidden here. I mean... ...if someone carried it through the manor, it would've stuck out like a sore thumb.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But when did the killer get in here? The mayor snatched the Forbidden Chamber key when the killer hit him on the head. That means the killer could've only gotten in here before the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, this is one tough riddle, all right.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A stone lantern...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Like those Japanese garden lamps? Where's the switch?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamps like these are lit by fire not electricity, so there is no switch.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, here it is!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It was hidden out of sight.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I see Tenma Taro's cell has been outfitted with all the amenities a yokai could want.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, look. There's an air vent here, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess even forbidden chambers need proper ventilation.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... But I don't think anyone could reach this one, either.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, and there's nothing to stand on around here. I wonder where this vent leads.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, the Fox Chamber's vent didn't branch this way, so...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe it doesn't have anything to do with this care, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, there's a bunch of staves here. And it looks like one's missing. The Tenma Taro Jinxie saw must've taken it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'd have to agree. These look like the one Detective Fulbright showed us.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why do you think there are so many here?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe they're spares. Tenma Taro might be, you know, absent-minded or something. But the fact that he has spare staves handy, well... ...it shows that he's aware of his faults, and is trying to deal with them. Or at least that's my take on it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe this will remind her to deal with her own faults. But I won't hold my breath.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">These look like the staff Detective Fulbright showed us.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That must mean that the Tenma Taro Jinxie saw... ...took this staff from here. I wonder what all these staves are doing here in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like a gravestone or something.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It reads, "Here lies Tenma Taro, Age 80. Cause of death: Choked on a chicken bone."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*gasp!* Say it ain't so! ...Besides, that sounds more like an autopsy report than an epitaph, if you ask me. Wait, you're joking around because you're scared! It's your coping mechanism!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm n-not scared!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Freak-out central! Right here, baby!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Cut it out, Widget!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Denial is strong in this one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's this? Whatever it is, the packaging is really gaudy. And the fact that there's no dust on it means it hasn't been here very long.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! It's hand cream. Let's see what brand it is......... "Je suis L'Belle!"?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">L'Belle?! <thought>What the--?!</thought> But then, wouldn't that mean Mr. L'Belle was here?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess so... but why?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, whoever was dressed up like Tenma Taro... ...must have taken a staff from here in the Forbidden Chamber. And that same person probably dropped this hand cream at that time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">In other words, the Tenma Taro impersonator we're looking for is none other than...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Florent L'Belle! This might be a big break for us in court tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Now all we have to do is get the truth out of Mayor Tenma!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. L'Belle's private brand of hand cream. He must've been here in the Forbidden Chamber at some point.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This could be the big break we need.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Guess that about wraps it up. What now?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We should probably talk to some of the witnesses again.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You mean like Mr. Filch... and Jinxie?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. I really want to ask Mr. Filch about the village superstitions and Tenma Taro.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Any good ideas yet, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Good ideas? You bet I do! Umm... Well, there's that thing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thing? What thing? ............</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............ Ugh, you saw right through me, didn't you?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? You mean you really have nothing for me?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, sorry! I just got a little carried away!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, boy. Bluffing is obviously not her strength.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Seems we finally have the real killer in our sights. The only person to threaten Mayor Tenma, push for the municipal merger...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...And to be identified at the manor disguised as Tenma Taro... ...is none other than Mayor Tenma's aide, Florent L'Belle! We're in for a fight tomorrow! Let's banish Tenma Taro, both literally and figuratively!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah! We'll be fine between the two of us! We'll send that yokai packing, along with that twisted samurai of a prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Let's do this!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I was shocked to hear a demon appeared at your trial.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were shocked? I was the one questioning him!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wish you would've called me in.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? You would've come to my rescue?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">With a demon like that, your tightrope-style of defense... and my magic tricks, we would've had it all. We could've been The Three Great Illusions! The audience would've been in the palm of our hand!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'd settle for convincing the judge with some solid evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's everyone's favorite, Trucy's Two Cents! Go ahead, ask me anything!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">My client has turned into a demon. I don't know what he's thinking, and I have no idea what to do.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm, I think this calls for... placing yourself in the other person's shoes. In other words, think of what it's like to be a demon. That should be easy for you, Polly!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... Okay, here goes.........</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Eeeeeek! A red demon!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aaaaaaugh!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Return to the black pit from whence you were spawned!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It ain't easy being a demon, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, the fox statues are part of the keyhole mechanism.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's try moving them around. Maybe something will happen!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But what if it's a trap. Who knows? The ceiling might come crashing down.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, will you relax? If it comes to that, I'll just dash out of the way!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but what about me?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I would've never guessed the screen was the clue to the keyhole mechanism. That alderman sure was an interesting guy. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'll say! Makes me want to implement a secret locking mechanism into the office door!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What, are you planning to turn it into a Forbidden Chamber II or something?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If I were, I'd need a demon to imprison...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ha ha, very funny. But no, I'm not going to imprison myself.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">It's the curse, the curse! The curse of Tenma Taro!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">You outsiders are ignoring them superstitions at OUR peril! Mind yer own business, will ya?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aagh! Youch! What's all this about a curse?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Tenma Taro's gonna curse us all 'less ya stop sticking yer nose where it don't belong! Stop the investigation! Listen to what them superstitions say!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right... Umm... How about obeying the law... before you go obeying the superstitions?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, what are you doing with Widget around your neck? He's mine! You know better than to go around stealing people's stuff like that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The same goes for my bracelet!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">S-S-Sorry, sorry! I promise I won't do it again!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Tsk, he almost kidnapped my sweet, little Widget.</line>
<line speaker="Widget">The big jerk!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">I'm sorrrryyyy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*sigh* I guess you can't teach an old raccoon dog new tricks. <thought>As long as we have him here, I guess we should ask him about what happened.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can't believe you did that! It's one thing to steal a pair of shoes, but to steal Widget!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Grrr!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yiiipes! Mercy, mercy! I can't seem to control myself! It's that thieving blood running in my veins!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thieving blood? What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Eh heh heh. Glad ya asked. The infamous bandit Azuki Kozo was my grandpappy! Take a gander at this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What exactly am I looking at? Looks like another one of those yokai to me.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">It's none other than THE Azuki Kozo! Robbed from the rich to give to the poor, he did! And he'd leave one o' these figures at the scene of the crime! What's more, I'm his grandson 'cause he was my grandpappy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, you don't say!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Thieves' honor, it's the honest truth! Ah... The sloshing sound of azuki beans scrapping together in the dead o' night... It's the magical sound of dirty money getting washed clean for givin' out to the poor! I'm Azuki Kozo, washer of money, giver-outer of wealth, reborn!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">......... Forget the money. You should be washing yourself of this nasty habit.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait a second. This figure looks familiar.</thought> Yes! It looks just like that old, dusty figure we found in the Forbidden Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Hey! Whaddaya doing with that there figure?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, this? We found it in the Forbidden Chamber. Looks like it'd been there practically forever.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Hmm... Could mean my grandpappy broke into the Forbidden Chamber way back. Hey, that reminds me. He once told me there's treasure in that there chamber!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Treasure?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you know about the treasure in the Forbidden Chamber?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Eh heh heh. Only that it's the greatest get-rich-quick chance in the universe. Grandpappy told me all about it. Said there's an amazing treasure in there!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's something amazing in there? <thought>Didn't see anything like that, though.</thought> Your grandfather didn't, by chance, already steal it, did he?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Seein' how there was one o' his figures in there, that just might be. Eh heh heh, that's Grandpappy for ya! Bet he washed that treasure up real good before handing it out to the poor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, of course, because he was so righteous...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">In court, you mentioned seeing Tenma Taro near the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Sorry I didn't come clean right away, but them superstitions got the better o' me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The people of Nine-Tails Vale sure seem like a superstitious bunch. I'm not surprised you wouldn't want to talk about seeing Tenma Taro.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Darn right! Them superstitions scare me outta my wits, I tell you! That's why I'm gonna do exactly what they say from now on.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you plan on staying here in Nine-Tails Vale?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yep. I'm gonna keep living right here 'n' keep with the old ways, just like Grandpappy did. Them superstitions are like a rulebook to me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, so you're saying you actually believe in those old wives' tales?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Ain't you been listening to a word I said?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're going to do "exactly what them superstitions say"? Well, I say that's baloney.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Filch:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">I don't have much school learnin', but I ain't no dummy. That there ain't got nothing to do with me. But I'd be happy to take it off yer hands if ya wanted, eh heh heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't think so. <thought>Let's try that one again.</thought> I heard every word of what you had to say... ...but I don't believe them for a second.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's clearly written right here: "Ignoring the superstitions will cost you your soul. There is, however, one way to save it: your immediate departure from the village."</line>
<line speaker="Filch">...Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So according to this, you shouldn't even be here, let along talking with us. You said you plan on staying right here in Nine-Tails Vale. But if you really believe in the superstitions, you would've been long gone by now.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Uwaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know you've been lying to me! Time to come clean, Mr. Filch!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yiiiiiiiiipes!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were lying about believing in the superstitions, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Sorry, but I didn't have no choice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, what was the real reason why you couldn't talk about seeing Tenma Taro?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">It's all that pretty boy's fault -- Mr. L'Belle, if ya know what I mean. He told me not to say a word 'bout seeing Tenma Taro. Said if I did, he'd do to me what them superstitions said would happen.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, it was Mr. L'Belle who muzzled you? Why would Mr. L'Belle want to scare you into silence?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Mr. L'Belle was trying to protect that little maid gal! It was on account o' that rumor! The one about her being possessed!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That rumor again...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess we really do have to talk to Mayor Tenma about the possession rumor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ouch! Hey, watch it!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">I'll be taking this back now, eh heh heh heh. Kinda like family to me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You could've just asked instead of stealing it...</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Hey, I know that picture! That's my Amazing Nine-Tails glossy! How dare you steal from me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, this is the one you gave me. Remember? You said you had lots more.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">I did? Well, it was never really mine in the first place, so... You can go ahead and keep it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Don't tell me I'm now guilty of receiving stolen goods...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, your grandfather was a famous thief?</line>
<line speaker="Filch">That's right. He stole for the rich to give to the poor. Just like your Robin Hood. But in these parts, he's known as Azukikozo! He washes his loot clean before handing it out to the poor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's hard to imagine Mr. Filch has such noble intentions. I bet he was planning on keeping my bracelet for himself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Was that all we wanted to ask Mr. Filch?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I think that was it. Let's go see "Mr. Tenma Taro" one more time. <thought>Just thinking about dealing with that yokai again makes me want to say, "Pass!"</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Lord Tenma! Your attorneys are here to see you, Your Malevolence!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Umm.........</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">.........Why are you speaking like that?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, Mayor Tenma! You've returned...!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Yes, well, Jinxie came by earlier to apply a new charm to my head. It seems to be suppressing the demon within me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's a relief. Maybe we'll actually get somewhere this time.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">So, what can I do for you today?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We'd like to ask about the rumor that Jinxie is possessed.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She allegedly left the yokai evidence at the scene while under a demon's power. At least, that's what the prosecution is going to claim at tomorrow's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">.................. Heh heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Caw caw-caw-caw! No match is this warding charm for me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aagh! Th-The charm!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Tenma Taro's back!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Those foolish mortals! They shall regret blaming that child for my doings!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Argh, I blew it! That question brought that yokai back. <thought>And he probably won't drop the act until Jinxie's name is cleared either.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We'd like to ask you about something your aide Florent L'Belle mentioned. Did you know Jinxie is rumored to be possessed?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">I know not of what you speak.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're not trying to protect Jinxie, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">I, Tenma Taro, demon lord of the yokai, protect a mere mortal? Caw caw-caw-caw! No affections do I possess for your race of humans.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Please! We already proved there was a third part disguised as a yokai at the scene. But if you deny that tomorrow, we'll never be able to clear Mayor Tenma's name.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">.........But I have already told you, I know not of what you speak!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't think we'll get anything more out of him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's all over unless we can somehow prove that Jinxie didn't plant that yokai evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">.........Hey, Apollo? I think I've got this one. I think I can prove that she didn't do it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sure! I should be able to use psychology to explain that whole possession thing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Knock yourself out, then! <thought>Wow, Athena's really something. I can really count on her when it counts!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mayor Tenma, Jinxie isn't possessed. I believe her so-called possession episodes are a form of somnambulism.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Somnambulism? You mean sleepwalking?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, I believe she is exhibiting a rare form of the disorder. It's usually brought on by repressed stress. Mr. Mayor, didn't her symptoms start soon after she began her job in Nine-Tails Vale?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">...Hrmmm. When the child visited last... ...she did speak of dreading yokai, and how they rob her of sleep each night.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I knew it! That lack of sleep is causing her to enter an unconscious state. And that means she can't be trying to protect you -- at least not on a conscious level.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So then, the Tenma Taro that was spotted at the manor wasn't Jinxie.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Sleepwalking, eh? Hrmmm. That would, indeed, explain the matter.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look! Tenma Taro's spirit! It's left the mayor's body.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Can you tell us the truth now, Mayor Tenma?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Very well. It's the least I could do for a superb exorcist such as you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mayor Tenma, you didn't leave those feathers and tracks at the scene, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">I did not. Neither I nor Jinxie have anything to do with that. That was... the killer's doing, no doubt.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I knew it!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">You suspect Florent is behind all this? But why? Did he really want Nine-Tails Vale that badly?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can you think of any reason why?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Hmm... Looking back, he did seem fixated on Tenma Taro for a spell. Ah! Could it be...?! Perhaps he was... attempting to release Tenma Taro.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's crazy! Are you saying that yokai is real?</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Whatever the case, Tenma Taro brings nothing but pain and misfortune. It's as the superstitions warn. You must not gaze upon him nor free him from his prison!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But... <thought>How can people actually believe that?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, at least we know who's behind this whole Tenma Taro thing now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, and I think we need to have another nice, long chat with Mr. L'Belle.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">You d-d-dinner is ready, Your Malevolence!</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Ah, an offering to the demon king. You may place it right there.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">The kitchen crew poured their heart and soul into making it.</line>
<line speaker="Tenma">Did they now? Souls happen to be a favorite of mine. Just, hold the hearts next time! Caw caw-caw-caw!</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Y-Yes, Your Malevolence! I'll remember that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>How long is he planning to keep up this yokai charade?</thought> Well, we've already talked to Mr. Filch and Mayor Tenma, so... Why don't we go see Florent L'Belle next? Now that we know the truth... ...he won't be able to claim that the Tenma Taro was Jinxie or the mayor anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But the real question is: how are we going to get him to admit it was him?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Okay! Now, let's PRACTICE that AGAIN, Filchy! From the top!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Errr... Mr. L'Belle was in the foyer at the time of the crime... ...and when we, uhh... heard a scream, uhh... Aw, heck! What was the next part again? Aaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">You have the memory capacity of a FLEA! This is the THIRTIETH TIME, you know! Now, a hundred times more and we're done!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What on Earth are they practicing?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Filch">Aww, I ain't cut out for this. ......Whoopsie daisy!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ouuuw!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Oh, begging yer pardon, Mr. L'Belle, sir. It's just, all this practice-- Yipes!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Unbelievable! What if you had sullied MY outfit with those GRUBBY paws of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>Did Filch filch L'Belle's wallet just now...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So... what do you think they're up to this time, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Hm? Oh, it's YOU two. Eavesdropping, are we? Pffft, you peasants are SO tacky. Well, what do YOU want with ME?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Your confession to being the Tenma Taro imposter would be nice right about now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Filch filled me in on a conversation you two had. And about how you told him not to say a word about seeing Tenma Taro.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">......... Filchy, you FOOL!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yipes!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">I TOLD you nothing good would come of you RUNNING your mouth!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So why did you want to keep Mr. Filch quiet like that, Mr. L'Belle?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha! Why to PROTECT darling little Jinxie, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But Jinxie was never really possessed. She was sleepwalking. Being asleep at the time, she couldn't have been consciously trying to protect the mayor. That also means she couldn't have possibly been Tenma Taro.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Interesting... But where ARE you going with this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Since you asked so politely... I believe you have a different reason for trying to keep Mr. Filch quiet. That reason would be to deflect doubt away from the one who was really Tenma Taro.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Ah ha ha ha ha ha ha! Now THIS is getting interesting! Are YOU insinuating that I'M Tenma Taro? So SORRY to disappoint, but I'm NOTHING of the sort!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">That's right! Mr. L'Belle even told me Tenma Taro was a jinx, so why would he-- Youw-ouw-ouw-ouw-ouw-ouch!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">I SAID Tenma Taro was JINXIE, you fool! Honestly! You have the memory capacity of a FLEA! Practice it a hundred times more times [sic]!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Yiiipes!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, um, have you been called to testify tomorrow?</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Yes, and I'm SO looking forward to my COURTROOM debut. But you'll JUST have to wait until then, ah ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, I'll be waiting -- with a special piece of evidence I've been saving just for you.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait, this is our trump card. Better not show it off too soon.</thought></line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">You wanted something?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, um... No, never mind.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Pffft.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">FILCHY! Wake up, you lazy bones!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Huh? What? Was I sleeping? *yawn* Musta been that sweet cologne o' yours, Mr. L'Belle. Made me right sleepy, it did.</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Well, it's TIME for your LESSON on what to do and say tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Oh, I'm beggin' ya! Not another lesson! I ain't cut out for this thinkin' and rememberin' stuff! Arrrrrrrrrrrrrrrgh! RIght up the schnozzola!</line>
<line speaker="L'Belle">Keep quiet and do EXACTLY as I say!</line>
<line speaker="Filch">Noooooo! Pleeeaaase! Anything but another lessooooooooon!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There they go... Missed our chance to get the truth out of him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but we'll get the proof we need in court tomorrow, one way or another! <thought>All that's left now is that lie Jinxie told. We'd better go clear that up before tomorrow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">You think they're done questioning Jinxie?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe. Let's see if she's over on Yokai Lane shopping for more charms.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Accursed Nine-Tailed Fox! The time for settling the score is nigh! My grudge has but festered over time. At last, vengeance will be mine! Grrr... Grrr...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">She must be possessed -- er, sleepwalking again!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Maybe if I speak softly, I won't startle her and get a charm plastered on my forehead.</thought> Pssst... Jinxie?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">......Huh?! ......Oh, hello, Mr. Demon Lawyer. Ah! My charms must've fallen off again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Phew... Guess I can avoid a charm slap by toning down my Chords of Steel.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Are they done questioning you, Jinxie?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. And on the way back, I stopped here to buy a new charm that was just released.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, which one?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Oh, um, the one with the Nine-Tails Fox and Tenma Taro. It shows them dancing together!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really?! Two bitter rivals dancing together?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uh-huh. It's a charm for rebuilding burnt bridges!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right. For the municipal merger issue.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">No, it's for the Demon Lawyer and the Insomniac Prosecutor. It'll stop you two from fighting like you did in court this morning.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We weren't fighting. It was just a spirited debate. It's what we lawyers-- Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">No fighting.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*sigh* Charm-slapped again.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, if you're done playing around, let's find out what she was lying about!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Jinxie, it seems like you're starting to remember things. You already said the feathers and tracks weren't there when you discovered the crime. Have you remembered anything else that seems important?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Eek! L-Like what?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tell us what you saw that day. Maybe you'll remember something else this time.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">...Eek! When I opened the door, Papa and Alderman Kyubi were collapsed in the Fox Chamber. That's when Papa told me to call an ambulance and the police. That's all he said before he passed out in the chair.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I knew it... She's holding something back.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Jinxie:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Arrragh!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">D-Don't shout like that. Nearly scared the wits out of me. Uhh... And d-don't stare at me like that, either. It's creepy...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Guess that wasn't right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were very nervous when you said, "That's all he said," weren't you? I know because I saw your fingers move as if you were going to slap someone with a charm.</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Listen to me, Jinxie. This is very important. Did Mayor Tenma say anything else to you?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">I-It was... It was nothing. He was just talking in his sleep...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Talking in his sleep? So you admit that he DID say something else!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">E-Eeeeeek! How could you tell?! Only... Only a demon could have such powers!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Uuuh... Uuuuuuuh... L-Like I said, he was just talking in his sleep! I mean, why else would Papa say something like that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could you be a little more specific?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">Before he f-fainted, he said... "Forgive me, Jinxie. I killed Alderman Kyubi."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He said whaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The mayor actually confessed to the crime?!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">B-But he didn't mean it. He couldn't possibly have known what he was saying! He was probably possessed or maybe he was in the middle of a nightmare!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A nightmare? No, THIS is a nightmare...! <thought>This is one statement I wish I'd never heard. What in the world are we going to do now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Return to the basics?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. Always believe in your client, no matter what happens. That is a lawyer's greatest and most trusted weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Right... Just believe in my client, even if all I can see ahead is darkness and despair.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Jinxie, does Prosecutor Blackquill know about your father's confession?</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">I didn't mention it when he was questioning me. I mean, there's no way Papa's the killer!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why would the mayor confess like that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could he really have been dreaming, or simply delirious?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Who knows, but I sure feel like I'M in a living nightmare right now.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, what are we going to do about tomorrow's trial? The crime scene was locked tight until Jinxie arrived, and our client's even confessed! Not only that, Jinxie has been accused of planting the yokai evidence. Both the mayor and Jinxie are going to prison if we don't do something!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I know, I know...</thought> Well, let's see here... Our lack of a third part in the locked room is a major problem. Jinxie has testified that when she first opened the door... ...Alderman Kyubi and Mayor Tenma were the only people she saw in the Fox Chamber.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But the real killer must've been hiding in there as well.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Considering the room was locked tight, that's the only logical explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Our mystery person must've fled the Fox Chamber when it was opened. And that's when Jinxie saw what she thought was Tenma Taro!</line>
<line speaker="Jinxie">B-But... Papa and the alderman were the only people there. I didn't see anyone else.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's going on here? L'Belle's extremely pale, but he's far from transparent. So just how did he hide himself at the scene of the crime?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whatever it takes in court tomorrow, Apollo... ...we have to take down that dirty, rotten "Tenma Taro" Florent L'Belle!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. We'll get him with a legal exorcism, Justice style!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, it doesn't look like there's anything particularly interesting here.</line>
</xml>