<xml>
<title>The Return of the Great Departed Soul</title>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Good morning to you, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, good morning, Professor. Ready for today's proceedings?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... I hope so... I should be... Even I, with nothing left to-</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Good morning, my dear fellows!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, Mr Sholmes! You're here!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Why, naturally! A true gentleman stands shoulder to shoulder with his friends in battle at all times!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you. I really appreciate it. ...I'll...see you later, then. Now, Professor... We really need you to remain calm in the courtroom today.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes. Do try your hardest not to enter the witness stand uninvited again.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yes! I will! I, I realise it was a mistake, but I-</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellows, I must interject!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...you're still here, Mr Sholmes. What's the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Surely you've overlooked some praise, have you not? To be cast in my direction, hm?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry? I don't follow.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Must I spell it out? I, the great Herlock Sholmes... The greatest detective, of worldwide acclamation... ...arose at some ungodly hour to be here now! First thing in the morning! A miracle, you must agree!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...if I must agree, then...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As you know, my sleep is quite impregnable. Iris had to employ her full gamut of tactics: She pulled the covers off, shook me, poked both cheeks, punched me and kicked me from the bed. Then she poured a boiling cup of her latest experimental blend on my face and at last I was bestirred!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my... Iris has been busy.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Iris doesn't have it in her to go that far. She's too nice.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ah, I sense the spirit of a fellow scientist! One who relishes the infinite possibilities of blending tea!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm the one worthy of praise here! Not Iris! This is my victory!</line>
<line speaker="???">Sorry to cut in...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, Inspector Gregson! Good morning!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Gregson, my dear fellow, why the grim expression at this delightfully early hour?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Oh, I don't know. Maybe because I've been confronted with a grimmer expression, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Dear me... Are you going to take that insult lying down, Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Wha...? WHAT...? I DOOON'T KNOOOW!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Poor Professor...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Anyway, here's the paperwork you asked for.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What paperwork?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, I took the liberty of requesting it yesterday. I have a feeling it may prove useful.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">You wouldn't believe the hoops I had to jump through to get this brought out of the archives. It's the Professor's autopsy report.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That... That mass murderer's?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Who killed five members of the aristocracy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">He was found guilty in a closed trial ten years ago now. It was all done under wraps. And he was quickly executed soon after the trial. ...It's all in here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I don't know what to say! Thank you, Inspector!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, much obliged, Gregson.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Us lowly lot at the Yard are just doing what we can...in the shadow of the great detective Sholmes, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well then, Professor Harebrayne...this is it! Today we're going to lay all this to rest at last.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I wish you the best of luck, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... I suppose...he'll be in there today, will he? Drebber...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes. We expect the prosecution to summon him as a witness.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I'm still amazed that you managed to find him in just one day... I really owe you both so much!</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Counsel! And the defendant! The trial is about to resume. Kindly make your way into the courtroom at once!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This is it then. The final chapter. Funny. My heart's racing a little... I've not felt this before, actually. This strange foreboding... As if...something's going to happen in this trial that I'm not ready for. But I can't let that distract me from the only thing that really matters... Finding the truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">In the name of Her Majesty the Queen, I hereby declare this court to be in session again. We resume the public hearing of Albert Harebrayne, here present, who stands accused of murder. Are the counsels for the prosecution and defence ready to proceed?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The prosecution is ready, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... The defence is ready, My Lord. <thought>As promised, Lord van Zieks has his apprentice with him. His apprentice with memory loss...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If I may, Lord van Zieks...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yes, My Lord?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There appears to be someone standing at your side...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Ah, yes. My apprentice and assistant. The prosecution believes today's proceedings will see the complexity of this case rise considerably. I therefore instructed my assistant to attend to ensure the smooth running of the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And the smooth running of liquid refreshments, by the look of it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">The way he holds himself... The way he moves... It couldn't be anyone else...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But he's still suffering from amnesia...so there's really nothing we can do at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I know, but... Oh, this is so very hard.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would appear the prosecution has done a fine job in responding to the demands of the court made yesterday. I understand you have successfully secured the engineer who disappeared from the scene on the day in question.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...Yes, My Lord. I intend to call him as a witness shortly.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very good, very good. Now then, ladies and gentlemen of the jury... ...who have been chosen at random to represent the will of the people in this courtroom today... ...are you ready and willing to proceed?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Of course, My Lord. I'm sure we all understand the importance of doing our civic duty.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">I do so despise deception and deceit. I find it so very wearing...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">To take a man's life with a conjuring trick... It is against the magician's code, not to mention the law.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Any fake scientists should feel the wrath of God, if you ask me!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Um, we 'ave to listen to what's said on both sides 'the fence, and um...then settle on one... That's it, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Wasn't like this in my day. Wasn't like this at all...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If all parties are ready to proceed, you may begin, Lord van Zieks.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Before I do, My Lord, there is a report I must read to the court. Yesterday at the Great Exhibition grounds, the evidence of primary importance in this case... ...the super-high-voltage instantaneous kinesis machine, which was installed on the experimentation stage... ...was deliberately destroyed in an explosion effected by an unknown person or persons.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">It was...WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">An explosion?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">This...is an outrage!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I heard this grave news yesterday. Scotland Yard submitted a report to my office in the evening. I read that the machine was blasted to smithers, and the wreckage reduced to ashes in the flames.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I have here a photographic print of the scene, taken in the wake of the explosion. It shows what little remains of the machine.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm, yes... A terrible business...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He did it to destroy the evidence, did he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">That Enoch Drebber...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will take this print as evidence, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Late yesterday afternoon... ...the protection afforded to the machine by the Special Dispensation for Scientific Equipment Act was revoked. However, before a thorough investigation could begin, the invention was obliterated from existence. As such...this will become a very different trial.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">As it stands now, with no evidence on which to draw meaningful conclusions... ...the authenticity of the kinesis machine will remain forever in obscurity.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm, indeed... A most unfortunate state of affairs.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">However, one thing remains clear: The victim's death was the result of the actions of the accused. Of that we can be certain. For it was the accused himself who was operating the machine and who ultimately caused its loss of control.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As Lord van Zieks rightly says, this is a very different trial now.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The accused accepts responsibility for his part in the events that transpired. He acknowledges that Mr Asman died as a result of the accident caused by his machine's malfunction. However, unbeknownst to the professor... ...he was being deliberately deceived by a pair of very clever fraudsters.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Names, Counsel, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The engineer, Mr Enoch Drebber, and the victim himself, Mr Odie Asman.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So what exactly were these two men up to behind the defendant's back?! The defence intends to expose that information, thus establishing the unequivocal innocence of the defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, Counsels. The positions of the prosecution and defence have been clearly stated. Lord van Zieks, summon your first witness, please.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">At once, My Lord. The prosecution calls the engineer, Mr Enoch Drebber, to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">State your name and occupation for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Name...Enoch Drebber. Occupation... ...hard to pin down, I would say.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your file indicates that you are currently being investigated in connection with another case. The theft...of a waxwork model, is it? A most extraordinary-sounding business.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">...But that has no bearing on this trial, I assure you. Cleave it from your mind.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">You're familiar with the public experiment carried out at the Great Exhibition some days ago? The accused's super-high-voltage instantaneous kinesis demonstration.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Yes...you could say that. I am aware of it. There was a terrible accident, wasn't there?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It was you, Mr Drebber, who constructed the vast machine used in the experiment. Or so our investigations indicate. Can you confirm your involvement?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Yes, I constructed it. In precise accordance with the blueprints. But that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Then the court would be very interested to hear your thoughts about the machine, I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">......... An amazing device, if you ask me. The pinnacle of modern science, making instantaneous kinesis a reality at last.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good... Good gracious! Do you mean to say... ...that the experiment was bona fide? Is that your belief, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Yes, that is very much my belief. Such a waste that it blew up.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But we've already established the machine was nothing more than a prop for an elaborate conjuring trick!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">All that was shown during yesterday's proceedings... ...is that the same outcome could have been produced by means of stage trickery. The defence merely proposed a method and demonstrated its feasibility, nothing more.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...but...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We've procrastinated long enough, I feel. Witness, you will now give your formal testimony... ...about the machine that you constructed for the purpose of the demonstration at the Great Exhibition.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">...Understood.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">I met the young professor approximately one year ago, through Mr Asman's introduction.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A, a body double?!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">That goes without saying, surely? To give the impression that something has moved when in reality it hasn't. It's a basic conjuring principle. The deception cannot be achieved without substituting the original with a fake at some point in the performance. But would I be right in saying...you haven't managed to establish anything along those lines?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Incidentally... ...the prosecution has already confirmed that Mr Asman had no twin siblings.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... It's my understanding that this witness is well-versed in conjuring artfulness. But such talents do not indicate that he was actually able to accomplish what he claims. Namely the construction of what, by all accounts, must have been an extremely complex scientific machine.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">...Whatever do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yesterday's proceedings brought the true nature of your past exploits to light, Mr Drebber.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Indeed it did, My Lord! As a swindler who preys on innocent scientists to elicit government grant money through conjuring know-how.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">...Yes, it's true that I possess considerable knowledge of stage magic. But crucially, my scientific knowledge more than matches that of any academic in the field.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Investigation of the witness's workshop attests to that claim, My Lord. As evidence, the police found this Royal Society trophy for young talent in science there.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's true. We spotted it there ourselves!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">If a hypothesis is sound, it can always be forged into a physical manifestation...with sufficient skill. Though I may have sold the secrets of some deceptive wiles to snivelling, talentless scientists in the past.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Would, would you therefore assert...that the explosion of the machine was...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">An unfortunate accident. ...Or, of course, a deliberate act of murder carried out by misuse of the science.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel for the Defence...your cross-examination, please!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">I met the young professor approximately one year ago, through Mr Asman's introduction.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you were already acquainted with Mr Asman himself?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Not really. By chance, I'd seen his name mentioned in the papers, that's all. But I had no interest in his private affairs. If he was an unscrupulous investor, it was no concern of mine. As long as people pay their bills, I take up my tools and construct what they ask for.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So why did Mr Asman approach you in particular, then?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Who can say? I presume because my name is associated with excellence in engineering.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Not to mention excellence in fraud.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Hard to gauge. But the point is, all I did was construct the machine according to the blueprints I was given.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">In other words, the kinesis machine was built on solid scientific principles.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Yes, you might say that. Professor Harebrayne certainly has a mind like no other.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">He provided me with the blueprints and I constructed the machine to his precise specifications. It was no trick.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's clear that you have both scientific knowledge and knowledge of conjuring magic, however.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">The more knowledge you have, the better equipped you are to handle whatever comes along. But your implication is that I furnished the machine with some trickery, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's a possibility that we have to explore.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Unfortunately though, the machine has been blown to kingdom come. So there's really nothing left to explore...is there?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It appears that the kinesis machine was fitted with a timed explosive device of some kind.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">And there's nothing left of that device either. Not a single shred of evidence remaining...I hear.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He must have planned all this from the outset.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Drebber">But in any case, it's abundantly clear that the experiment couldn't have been a trick.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">If the whole show was a fraud, it would have required a body double. Tell me...did the victim have a twin?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of course! That's it! Mr Asman was a twin!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, I heard you before. ...But the thread of hope hadn't quite left me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The demonstration could have been a trick, if there was somebody who looked sufficiently like the victim. But Dr Sithe absolutely ruled that out as a possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It is beyond question that the victim himself, Mr Asman, did move from the stage to the Crystal Tower. The fingerprints found at the scene attest to the fact.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So it can't have been orchestrated using someone who looked identical to Mr Asman then.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What are you thinking, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! No...nothing. Just that the idea of someone who looked identical to the victim is playing on my mind...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">All the spectators saw the birdcage appear above their heads and then crash headfirst into the Crystal Tower.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It crashed 'headfirst', you say?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">According to the many witness reports from those there at the time, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Were you not there at the exhibition grounds on the day?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Hm...unlikely. I rarely leave my workshop.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yet another of your unique inventions was found at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">......... Well...it was the unveiling of a machine I'd laboured over for many months. I saw it clearly with my own eyes. The birdcage plummeted headfirst into the tower.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What a surprise...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">I believe the victim's neck was broken from the headlong fall, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How would you have come by that information?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Even an infernal recluse like me reads the newspapers, you know. According to the reports, two injuries were apparent on the victim's body.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, he'd been stabbed in the chest by a screwdriver believed to belong to the defendant... ...and he had broken vertebrae as a result of a fall from a considerable height.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...Correct. My learned friend has been doing his research, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do we know which injury was the fatal one?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Sadly not. Forensic science is not yet at a level where such things can be determined.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What we do know is that the victim died having sustained both injuries at some point during the experiment. And since he was found in the birdcage with his neck broken...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">...It's obvious that he fell from a considerable height.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Hm... I suppose that's hard to deny...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We've examined the birdcage that crashed into the Crystal Tower ourselves. As you can see, the cage, which is a wooden construction, has sustained damage in one particular spot.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Following the explosion, it fell some thirty feet into the glass of the Crystal Tower. That level of damage is to be expected, surely.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I agree. The damage itself is entirely understandable. What doesn't make sense... ...is the location of that damage.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">All the breakages in the wood are at the base of the birdcage, not the top!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">What are you saying?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's the opposite of where they should be!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right, My Lord. The birdcage that was at the scene is damaged at its base. So we have reports of the birdcage falling headlong into the Crystal Tower, yet the damage is at the bottom. The only way to reconcile these two facts is to accept... ...that there were two birdcages in play that day, which were at some point switched! Switched during what wasn't a scientific experiment at all...but an elaborate piece of stage trickery!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Gaaaaaaa...gh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious! Explain yourself, witness!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">I...well...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">If we examine the facts, there's only one logical conclusion we can draw. The damage on the base of the birdcage clearly indicates that it crashed tailfirst into the tower.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But multiple witness reports claim it fell headfirst!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The birdcage materialised in the sky next to a balloon flying over the stage, following a spontaneous explosion. At an altitude of some sixty feet above ground level.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Which is approximately eighteen metres.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It then proceeded to fall some thirty feet into the Crystal Tower in the ensuing deflagration. Witness reports amid such chaos...are notoriously unreliable.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But the victim's neck was broken!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">......... Kuh kuh kuh kuh kuh... A riveting scientific analysis of events from the prosecution there. Though to be even more rigorous, you would have to say it was only one vertebra, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>He wasn't quiet for long...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I find it hard to see what's motivating Lord van Zieks. This witness is clearly a swindler, and one who deceived a personal friend of his.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... 'If you're going to establish this deception, do it right.'</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I feel like that's the undertone here.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Ah yes, and there's one more point the defence appears to have forgotten. It obviously wasn't a trick...as a certain truth very plainly demonstrates.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems to me that the cross-examination had better continue until we resolve this matter. Mr Drebber, you will amend your testimony with details of this 'truth'.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Of course. We must treat the matter scientifically, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Agh, I nearly had him there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">The kinesis clearly took place, because there's nowhere else thirty feet high for the birdcage to have fallen from.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Well, before the demonstration began, the victim was alive on stage in front of the audience.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...there are lots of witnesses who saw Mr Asman on the experimentation stage, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">And the victim's neck broke as a result of an impact following a fall. Logically, therefore, the victim must have fallen from somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The balloon that exploded was at an altitude of sixty feet. The point of impact on the tower was thirty feet up. That difference of thirty feet is therefore the total distance the birdcage fell.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">And there's no other location from which the cage could have fallen that distance if it didn't drop out of the sky. Ergo... ...the victim himself must have been beamed from the stage into the sky above the Crystal Tower.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmmm... A trenchant, scientific analysis. Dear me, every time I hear it explained, it sounds increasingly plausible.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Oh yes. It's all very well thought out.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Certainly all the spectators on the day saw it. The birdcage plummeting thirty feet through the air, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Irritatingly, yes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Drebber">A terrible accident, I grant you. Perhaps the science on which the machine was built was flawed somehow?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you understood the science, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Not in the slightest.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Right...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">As I've said a number of times, I'm an engineer. My job is to manufacture according to the blueprints I'm given. I would be inviting manifold problems if I foolishly allowed my brain to digest the ideas behind them. I could be accused of stealing those ideas, for example.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But how is it possible to construct a machine without really understanding the principles it relies on?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Well, you're practising law without really understanding the principles it relies on, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... A very good point.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Stand up for yourself, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The point is, the experiment resulted in instantaneous kinesis taking place. As such, the science must be sound.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Yes. And really, experimental results are all that matters when it comes to proving a hypothesis.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He's certainly very sure of himself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">What do you think, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, now that the machine has been completely destroyed by yesterday's explosion... ...it's going to be impossible to argue its authenticity one way or the other.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But if we're unable to establish that it was a piece of stage trickery rather than genuine science... ...we will have no grounds on which to demonstrate Professor Harebrayne's innocence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Both Mr Asman and this man in the stand tricked the professor and used him. They took advantage of his naivety and his unbending belief in his work...and I won't let them get away with it! <thought>And seeing as the professor is an old friend of Lord van Zieks... ...what on earth must he be feeling towards Drebber?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is a diagram of the experimentation stage and its surroundings.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We know that somehow, the birdcage appeared in mid-air before falling down into the Crystal Tower. A fall of about thirty feet...or nine metres. However, if you examine the diagram carefully... ...you'll see that there is one other possible location from which the birdcage could have fallen... ...the same distance of thirty feet.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">No!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, it appears the defence has a possible explanation to put forward. Go ahead, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, My Lord. Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You will indicate the place to which you are referring on this same diagram. The alternative location from which the birdcage could possibly have fallen the requisite thirty feet!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And you may consider this a parting gift, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... I feel like I've just hit the deck from thirty feet up anyway now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Don't give me recourse to make the next fall from sixty feet up, hm?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The place I'm referring to...is here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But that's... ...where the birdcage would have been to begin with!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Which is exactly the point, My Lord. Yes, the birdcage was in the machine on the stage. But what we must also consider, is the height of the stage itself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Go on, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It turns out that the experimentation stage was built at a considerable height above ground level. If you look at the diagram, in fact... ...you'll see it's at about the same height above the ground as the balloon was above the crash site.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When the experiment got underway, the machine and the birdcage were engulfed in steam. At that moment, the floor of the stage gave way and, if we assume there to be a void underneath... ...this birdcage and the one seen by the audience would have fallen almost exactly the same distance! Once again, My Lord... ...this all points to the fact that there was not one birdcage, but two!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Someone is responsible for the criminal destruction of the kinesis machine itself, it's true. However, the stage still stands. And take a moment to look at the photographic print of the scene following yesterday's explosion.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good Lord! The metal grille that formed the floor of the machine is undone!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, most likely blown open by the force of the explosion that destroyed the rest of the machine. The defence calls for the space below the stage to be investigated...immediately! Mr Drebber!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It was you who built the kinesis machine. Which means that it was you who built the two birdcages that were used to carry out this deception.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Uh...ughhh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Whether Professor Harebrayne's hypothesis is sound or not makes no difference. Because it's the construction of this machine that matters. A machine designed to take Mr Asman's life... ...and lay the blame firmly at the professor's door. Something that could only have been carried out... ...by you, Mr Enoch Drebber!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Grrr... UWAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Your argument fails to hold water... ...on two counts.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Two?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Firstly... ...before and after the experiment, this witness went nowhere near the kinesis machine. Every relevant member of staff from the exhibition has attested to that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And I believe members of Scotland Yard have also been on watch duty at every public experiment.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">In other words, Mr Drebber had no opportunity to switch the alleged pair of birdcages.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But I've already explained why he wouldn't have needed to!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The nonsense with the crossbow? That doesn't bolster your case at all. The man who disappeared from the stage and the man who crashed into the tower are one and the same. The Forensic Investigation Team's report is unequivocal on that point!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And the second flaw in your assertion... ...is a distinct lack of motive. Why would this man have wanted to take the victim's life? He had no reason to do so.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A...a motive...? <thought>Do I have to think of everything myself?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I have here a contract provided by the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What contract is this, Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The contract into which Mr Drebber entered with the victim, Mr Asman. It reads: 'Mr Drebber is to receive thirty percent of all remunerations from government grants or other income.'</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thirty percent? Certainly very favourable contractual conditions.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">But there was one very important provision bolted onto that clause.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What provision?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">'Mr Drebber may only uphold this right on condition that both contracting parties are alive.'</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">In other words, if either of us were to die, the contract would become null and void. So you see, I had nothing to gain from Mr Asman's death. The diametric opposite, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Need I say more? The witness had neither an opportunity nor a reason to commit the alleged crime. In short, the possibility of Mr Drebber having done as you suggest...is nil.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... UWAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm... It seems the defence's assertion was somewhat wide of the mark. Lord van Zieks...you will submit the contract as evidence, please.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It's true... If Drebber had no opportunity to switch the birdcage under the stage with the one in the Crystal Tower... ...he couldn't have done it. And in any case, I have no idea what his motive might have been!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">There is one aspect of your argument... ...that still holds true, however.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">There were two birdcages. The prosecution is unable to deny that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So I'm sure you're on the right lines, Mr Naruhodo. And I've no doubt there are other aspects of your assertion that are undeniable truths, too!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, it would seem... ...that the defence has no rejoinder to offer.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">......... Kuh kuh kuh... Well, I must say I'm a little surprised. I came here to testify about the machine I built, and instead my reputation is defiled. But the prosecution's counter has set the record straight, I think. It's impossible that I'm the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">At the beginning of this trial, we believed that there was only one birdcage. Yet now we know there must have been two. In other words, there was more to the demonstration than we realised at first.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think it's abundantly clear that the same applies to the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Get to the point.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The stage demonstration... ...was constructed and set up in its entirety by you, Mr Drebber. Therefore it's inconceivable that you had no hand in the events that transpired.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So if circumstances mean it's impossible that you could have carried out the crime yourself... ...it points to the fact that someone else was involved.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Someone else? Counsel, are you suggesting...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, My Lord! Mr Drebber had an accomplice!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">If these accusations turn out to be false... ...then make no mistake: The prosecution will demand an equally serious punishment for your slander!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Counsel? Do you intend to pursue this course, and formally accuse another party of involvement in this matter?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>What do I do here? At the moment, this is little more than a hunch on my part. I don't know for sure if Drebber had an accomplice, or even if he really is the culprit here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>One way or another, though, I have to make my position clear. ...As a lawyer. So what's my stance going to be? Did Drebber have an accomplice...or not?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Let's face it, I have no idea who is accomplice might actually have been. Which isn't the strongest position to be in, is it, Ryunosuke?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo, think of the sword at your side. Karuma is crying out.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Crying out for you to show the strength of your conviction now as a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes, you're right. This sword that I inherited, which embodies the will of my best friend... ...is my own accomplice!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm not sure that's quite the right word, but...that's the spirit, certainly!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The defence is ready to name Mr Drebber's accomplice! <thought>Somehow the two birdcages must have been switched. Everything points to that. Yet according to the coroner's report, that's not a possibility. But that inconsistency itself is a clue!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm? ...My Lord?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You have received a stark warning already. If you are nevertheless determined... ...then I must now ask you to identify this alleged accomplice by name. So...your answer, please. Who do you claim to have been Mr Drebber's accomplice?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Someone intimately related to the crime, My Lord...and someone you surely wouldn't say you don't know!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, thank you, I am aware of the person, obviously. But on what basis do you claim felonious involvement?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">You surely wouldn't say you don't know...would you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Uwaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm sure you simply slipped and pointed to the wrong person, didn't you? There's no other explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No 'slip-ups' this time, please, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The name of the person in question is...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What's wrong, my Nipponese friend? Surely fear doesn't bind your tongue now. It's a little late for that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Of course I'm afraid. After all, naming her in this capacity is definitely going to make waves. ...A lot of waves. I could very well turn every single person in this courtroom against me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm sure it will be alright, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Thank you, Miss Susato.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The enemy always appears larger than life. But you'll appear exactly the same to the enemy!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Alright then, here goes...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">You've kept us waiting long enough. Your answer, Counsel...now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The person who colluded with Mr Drebber in order to carry out this wicked crime... ...is Scotland Yard's coroner, Dr Courtney Sithe!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What, what the blazes are you talking about? Dr Sithe?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The head of the Forensic Investigation Team, and the coroner who conducted the autopsy on the victim?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We know there were two birdcages. So who could have carried out the switch to complete the illusion? The 'accident' happened in front of a huge crowd of spectators, and the area was immediately sealed off. Then everyone, police officers included, were banished to make way for the Forensic Investigation Team. When else could the switch have occurred? It can only have been in that team's presence.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's essential that the court determines exactly what happened following the incident. The defence demands that Dr Sithe be summoned to the witness stand at once to testify!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">You've got a nerve, lad! Standing up there, dragging the Yard's name through the mud!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I didn't mean to...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">I know the woman veeery well. There's no better dead room worker out there! How dare you call her a criminal?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">My learned friend's imagination appears to be wilder than the East End at night.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">But the recklessness of your accusation aside, there's another grave problem with your argument. One which the prosecution demands you address at once.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A grave problem?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my word...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Who do you claim acted as the victim's doppelgänger?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">W-What?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Certainly, if the 'birdcage' containing the body of the victim was exchanged for another... ...that cage must also have contained a body.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And yet... ...no missing persons or accidental deaths of anyone even remotely resembling the victim have been reported. Which means there was no one, dead or alive, who could have fulfilled the role of a body double for Mr Asman.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... <thought>That's true! If my argument is that there were two birdcages, then there must also have been one person inside each! But I don't know if I've got an answer to this yet, have I? What can I do to reveal how this body double stunt was achieved?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Very well. The defence will address my learned friend's concerns... ...by revealing the identity of the person who acted as Mr Asman's body double!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Be my guest. Give us a name.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The body double and the birdcage were hiding inside the balloon that was floating above the stage. Which means that any witnesses would only have seen them from sixty feet away. ...So who was it that appeared out of that explosion some eighteen metres above the spectators...?</thought> ......... Aha! In place of Mr Asman in the second birdcage was...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I would not.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Would anyone?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm sorry, Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Even you're turning your back on me, Miss Susato? I must be really wide of the mark!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...You have a head. Try using it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I must ask you to reconsider your answer, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Very well. The defence will address my learned friend's concerns... ...by presenting evidence that reveals the true nature of Mr Asman's body double!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious! Evidence? I do hope this isn't filibustering, Counsel. The court is expecting a name.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">If you think you have relevant evidence, present it now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The body double and the birdcage were hiding inside the balloon that was floating above the stage. Which means that any witnesses would only have seen them from sixty feet away. ...So who was it that appeared out of that explosion some eighteen metres above the spectators...?</thought> ......... Aha! The body double inside the second birdcage was...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Susato">He's suggesting you and the evidence die together, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes, that came across. <thought>It's hard to see how another person could have been inside the second birdcage. Which means the body double must have been something else...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I shall have to ask you to reconsider your answer, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't explain that at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Oh really. And when can the court expect an explanation?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Maybe tomorrow?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Then you can take your leave of us until then.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">People who procrastinate lose everything in the end, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Isn't that slightly over-the-top?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We can discuss that later. But for now, you ought to consider what you can do, not what you can't.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright, yes. I'll think again...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We know that the victim, Mr Asman, was in the birdcage that was situated inside the kinesis machine on stage. And therefore he couldn't have been inside the second birdcage. Instead, that contained something else... What's been described as a 'body double', which is what fell from the sky and crashed into the Crystal Tower.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Counsel, according to your somewhat elaborate version of events.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And that 'body double' inside the second birdcage was in fact... .........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's alright, Mr Naruhodo. You're ready for this. Just steel yourself...and come out with it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Thank you, Miss Susato! I needed that. As I was saying...the 'body double' inside the second birdcage was... ...as unbelievable as it may seem...that thing there!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Stand firm now, Ryunosuke! This is the time to show your Japanese spirit!</thought> As the court will observe...this is a waxwork model. A model, in fact, of an infamous London murderer from ten years ago: the Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes! That's about the size of it.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">But why? And why THIS waxwork? It looks nothing like the victim. In fact, it could hardly resemble him less! What possible justification can you give?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you want to know why... ...ask Mr Drebber.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just days before Professor Harebrayne performed his public demonstration... ...Mr Drebber abducted this model from Madame Tusspells.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Did, did you say...abducted?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And two days after the incident at the Great Exhibition... ...he returned it to the museum.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Then the timing...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is this true, Mr Drebber?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Ugh... Urmm...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">At first, I couldn't see why Mr Drebber would have stolen the waxwork and then given it back again. But now, the reason is clear. He took it so that he could put it inside the second birdcage...as a body double for Mr Asman!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Guh...............!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">That the witness fabricated this vast machine with the intention of deceiving some wretched scientist. That he did so in collusion with the country's finest coroner, on a public stage in front of a vast audience.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And that, to effect the deception, he used a waxwork model that in no way resembles the victim. Are we really to believe this far-fetched tale? What do you decide?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait! Yes, if you put it like that, of course it sounds implausible!</line>
<line speaker="???">My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">I need to speak, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Go ahead, Mr Foreman.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Myself and my colleagues have reached an agreement.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very good. In that case... ...ladies and gentlemen of the jury, you will state your leanings for the court to hear now!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, as indicated by the foreman, the jury has reached a consensus.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I knew that was going to happen.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">We shall get through this, Mr Naruhodo, as we always do. And uncover some new truths along the way, I'm quite sure.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I agree. I'm going to have to appeal to the jurors as usual, and see if I can persuade them to change their minds!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence will now embark on a summation examination. Are you and your fellows ready to proceed, Mr Foreman?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">We are, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. In that case, I ask you now to state clearly for all present to hear... ...the grounds on which each of you has decided that the defendant is guilty of the crime of which he is charged.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">I've known that woman for years! She'd never be an accomplice to anything!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">It's utter nonsense to think those two would ever be conniving with one another.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Oh dear, this is most troubling... But surely the waxwork the man stole is nothing to do with the coroner, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">I have had my own problems with members of the police. I do not trust them much...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">I've seen no rigorous proof that this waxwork was ever inside the birdcage. It's conjecture!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Accusin' someone without right evidences? Ee's not a proper job, is ee? I won't 'ave it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Somewhat unsurprisingly... ...it seems the introduction of this waxwork model to the proceedings has polarised opinion.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Given that its face is obscured and its build in no way resembles that of the victim... ...I can only applaud my learned friend's temerity at suggesting it as Mr Asman's body double.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, the applause is deafening. ...And yes, I know it seems extraordinary. But that's the point. That's why I have a strong feeling it's actually a greater clue than anyone yet realises...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">What are you thinking, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't explain why at the moment... ...but I feel as though there's a specific reason why it was used. Why it had to be this model.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Really? A reason why nothing else would do, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. And I'm convinced... ...it's something far more significant than whether or not the model looked like the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well...if that's the case... ...we must prevent the trial from ending prematurely at all costs!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, agreed. <thought>I have to find a way out of this...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you are ready, Counsel, you may proceed with the summation examination.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">I've known that woman for years! She'd never be an accomplice to anything!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...the order of things seems to have changed around here for some reason...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">I'm a copper, lad. It's a copper's discretion to bend the rules sometimes, when needs must. What's wrong with that?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Where do I start?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">I've been working at the Yard for forty odd years!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's...even more than I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">We've only had a metropolitan police service in town for seventy years, you know. 'Course, times have changed. The public didn't trust coppers back when I started. It was rough. We had to fight crime, and we had to fight to win the public's trust as well. And win we did. Forensic science was in its infancy too, even more than it is now. And she spearheaded the revolution!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Dr Sithe, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">That's right. About ten years ago now, it was. When I was still a youngish bobby on the beat. That's when she started making a name for herself as a top-class coroner. And now look at her! Head of the Forensic Investigation Team. And a woman, no less. Well you won't hear me complain! It's what we all dreamt of back then, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Could you tell me without holding that gun in the air?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">We were all out to uphold justice, lad! Full of vim, we were. Full of vim.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That's coming across loud and clear.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">She was Courtney Stevens back when I knew her, of course. A legendary coroner, even then.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">She was legendary, was she?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">What did you say?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">That woman is still the best coroner in the land! Head of the Forensics Investigation Team!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...'legendary' was your description, sir, not mine.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Rubbish! That word never passed my lips! I'd never describe anybody that way! Ever! Not if they were still in the game!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... ...I think the point you're trying to make is that Dr Sithe is an extremely talented coroner. Would that be fair?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">It would! If it weren't for the fact that you're trying to drag that legendary woman's reputation through the mud!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'm going to pretend I didn't hear that 'legendary'.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Those two statements clearly contradict each other!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious! To whose statements do you refer, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...juror number two.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Oh gosh! Me? W-What can I do for you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I presume that you heard what juror number six said in his statement? It's brought to light the maiden name of the coroner, Dr Sithe. Which in turn has revealed a connection that wasn't apparent before.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Well naturally, as a woman of society, I find such connections and relationships irresistible. But oh golly... I'm afraid I fail to see what you mean.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Dr Sithe's maiden name is Stevens. And through that name, the coroner is very definitely linked to the waxwork of the killer. The defence has evidence to prove it.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">My goodness! Evidence, you say? How, how utterly enthralling!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel, the court cannot overlook that last remark. I very much hope there is substance to your claim.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of course, My Lord. I would ask the court to look at this: The evidence that clearly links Dr Sithe to the mass murderer known as the Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A ten-year-old autopsy report? What relevance does that have?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It is of course from the autopsy of the person portrayed in the waxwork: the killer known as the Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The Professor's...? But the man was a capital offender, so...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right. This is the certification of death that was drawn up after the convict's execution. The identity of the killer was never made public, so the report gives few details. But what's important is the name of the coroner who wrote it: Courtney Stevens.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Oh my! Courtney Stevens?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Strike a light!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It appears that the Professor's autopsy was conducted by Dr Sithe ten years ago. And a few days ago, Mr Drebber very deliberately stole the waxwork of the Professor from Madame Tusspells. A waxwork that doesn't in fact resemble the victim, Mr Asman, at all.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">And do you suppose...there's some unsavoury relationship between those events?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Absolutely! I'm sure of it! There's no doubt in my mind that the Professor case... ...is at the heart of a link that we have yet to uncover... ...between Dr Courtney Sithe and Mr Enoch Drebber!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">......... Hidden links...mysterious connections...secret relationships... This is all most extraordinary. We're surely obliged now to explore this further.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Quite right. We can't let this trial come to an end now. Not while there's this cloud of suspicion hanging over the Yard's best coroner. It wasn't like this in my day! But we're still here to uphold justice in the end!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Juror No. 2:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think...my lack of colour must reflect my lack of confidence...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Hmph. Wait till you hit my age, lad. You won't have any colour left to drain.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I said before that the court could not overlook your claim of evidence. But it seems to me that overlooking it would have been the more preferable choice by some margin.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh. I was sure I had something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Oh gosh! There's, there's wax dripping from your brow! You're melting!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just a cold sweat. Nothing new.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let us return to the jurors' statements and put this debacle behind us.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">If a Yard coroner's under suspicion, then we're not done here yet, are we? Clearly!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">It's utter nonsense to think those two would ever be conniving with one another.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But we're only just starting to understand this case!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">W-What are you reading there, sir?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">The man behind those murders on Solar Pons Street was caught in two days flat. That's real policing for you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's...really not relevant to this case, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">You're wrong there. Because it was Dr Sithe in charge of examining the bodies. And it was evidence arising from her work that led to the arrest of the scoundrel responsible.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">That's right, 'Oh.' That woman is at the forefront of this country's fight against crime. The idea that she's somehow involved in this murky business is a load of old tosh.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I thought it was up to me to 'press' the jurors, not the other way around...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Oh dear, this is most troubling... But surely the waxwork the man stole is nothing to do with the coroner, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why would you assume that?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Well, quite simply because...that unsettling swindler has no relationship with the woman, does he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">True. As it stands, we don't know of any connection.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Oh gosh, but it would be delightfully romantic if they were somehow to have a mutual interest in the waxwork.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Romantic?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">A woman of society such as myself views everything in terms of relationships, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, you learn something new every day! <thought>Even if you don't want to.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">One might wonder about a possible relationship between the defendant and this coroner woman. Or perhaps between the defendant and the handsome prosecutor just there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This woman...may be more astute than I've been giving her credit for.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">If that's the woman's stance... ...then perhaps demonstrating some connection between the waxwork and Dr Sithe would be enough...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I agree. As soon as we have even a whiff of a connection, she'll be the first to know!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Those two statements clearly contradict each other!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious! To whose statements do you refer, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...juror number two.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Oh gosh! Me? W-What can I do for you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I presume that you heard what juror number six said in his statement? It's brought to light the maiden name of the coroner, Dr Sithe. Which in turn has revealed a connection that wasn't apparent before.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Well naturally, as a woman of society, I find such connections and relationships irresistible. But oh golly... I'm afraid I fail to see what you mean.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Dr Sithe's maiden name is Stevens. And through that name, the coroner is very definitely linked to the waxwork of the killer. The defence has evidence to prove it.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">My goodness! Evidence, you say? How, how utterly enthralling!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel, the court cannot overlook that last remark. I very much hope there is substance to your claim.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of course, My Lord. I would ask the court to look at this: The evidence that clearly links Dr Sithe to the mass murderer known as the Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A ten-year-old autopsy report? What relevance does that have?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It is of course from the autopsy of the person portrayed in the waxwork: the killer known as the Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The Professor's...? But the man was a capital offender, so...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right. This is the certification of death that was drawn up after the convict's execution. The identity of the killer was never made public, so the report gives few details. But what's important is the name of the coroner who wrote it: Courtney Stevens.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Oh my! Courtney Stevens?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Strike a light!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It appears that the Professor's autopsy was conducted by Dr Sithe ten years ago. And a few days ago, Mr Drebber very deliberately stole the waxwork of the Professor from Madame Tusspells. A waxwork that doesn't in fact resemble the victim, Mr Asman, at all.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">And do you suppose...there's some unsavoury relationship between those events?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Absolutely! I'm sure of it! There's no doubt in my mind that the Professor case... ...is at the heart of a link that we have yet to uncover... ...between Dr Courtney Sithe and Mr Enoch Drebber!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">......... Hidden links...mysterious connections...secret relationships... This is all most extraordinary. We're surely obliged now to explore this further.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Quite right. We can't let this trial come to an end now. Not while there's this cloud of suspicion hanging over the Yard's best coroner. It wasn't like this in my day! But we're still here to uphold justice in the end!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Juror No. 2:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think...my lack of colour must reflect my lack of confidence...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Hmph. Wait till you hit my age, lad. You won't have any colour left to drain.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I said before that the court could not overlook your claim of evidence. But it seems to me that overlooking it would have been the more preferable choice by some margin.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh. I was sure I had something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Oh gosh! There's, there's wax dripping from your brow! You're melting!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just a cold sweat. Nothing new.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let us return to the jurors' statements and put this debacle behind us.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">It's the Professor! That's what links that frightful swindler and the coroner!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">I have had my own problems with members of the police. I do not trust them much...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What sort of problems?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Let's just say we have run into each other on numerous occasions while I've been performing on the street.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Obviously artists such as myself cannot appear on stage as we work in close proximity to our audiences. So we perform our great magic in parks...on street corners...and the like. But the police use any excuse to make our lives difficult. Sometimes they even cook up a story to extort monies from the poor.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you have something to say in response to that... Mr Ottermole?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Who are you calling a mass murderer?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Sorry, my mistake! I, I got confused because I heard you look like him...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">I don't look anything like the man! You wanna be locked up, sonny?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Thanks, Mr Sholmes...</thought> Perhaps we could move on... I was really wondering if you had something you wanted to add in response to what juror number three just said. And clearly you do.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">......... Back in my day... Back in the good old days... ...it wasn't like this!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What was it like, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">We worked our fingers to the bone to earn the public's trust, we did! And by Jove we earnt it! People respected us back then!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Respected you? Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">No one would've called a coroner into question in them days! A coroner's report was the hallmark of an investigation done right! Especially when Dr Courtney Stevens put her name to it! She was the best of the best! And the apple of the force's eye!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">H-Hold on a minute! What are you talking about? Who's Courtney Stevens?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Ah... Sorry. Got a bit carried away there.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Stevens is Dr Sithe's maiden name.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Her maiden name... <thought>So that was before she was married...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">O' course, yes. Silly me. It's Sithe now, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Stevens... I'm sure I've seen that name somewhere recently...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Anyway! The point is, those were the great days of policing! Not like now...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry to interrupt, sir... ...but do you think you could change your statement to include that name?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Well, yes...I don't see why not.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, that's definitely not right.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Yes, and it is why I say that if you trust the police, you will have trouble. But here you are, claiming this waxwork model was stolen to star in an illusionary spectacular. The idea is so wild, I think I will take my chances and believe the authorities on this occasion.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This is how the public at large view Scotland Yard, is it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Our own police force in Tokyo is not even twenty years old yet, is it? Perhaps we should view what's happened here in London as a measure of what may happen at home.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes... Like a Scotland Yardstick. <thought>I wonder how a policeman would feel listening to the way this juror speaks about the force... I'm sure he'd have a word or two to say in response.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">I've seen no rigorous proof that this waxwork was ever inside the birdcage. It's conjecture!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But you claimed the whole instantaneous kinesis demonstration was a trick!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">That I did. But there's more than one way to pull a rabbit out of a hat, isn't there?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">I grant you, given that this cage appeared from amidst an explosion, there'd have been no need to use a real person. But if a waxwork had been used, the culprit could at least have had the decency to make it look like the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm not sure exactly how much criminals are governed by decency...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">The point is, if you're going to make a claim about that waxwork being inside the birdcage... ...you need to give us some evidence. Without that, it's just not science!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I suppose we should expect nothing less than a logical argument from a fellow of the Royal Society. But that perhaps means his mind could be changed if we managed to present suitable evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Evidence that the Professor waxwork was inside that birdcage. Hm... Can I produce that or not?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Actually, I have something I'd like you to see, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Oh? I must warn you that I firmly believe it's only wise to trust men in white coats. So given your jet-black outfit, I don't mind admitting to a sense of trepidation here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So you don't trust anyone in black? Looking in the mirror must be very trying...</thought> I do have some evidence that proves the waxwork was inside that birdcage. Namely...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">......... It's an unimpressive opening, if I'm honest.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, well, um... What comes next is the real point!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's already apparent that what comes next is equally disappointing, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... <thought>How about after that...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">If the waxwork of the Professor was inside the second birdcage... ...I would assume that means it must have crashed into the Crystal Tower.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's right. I'd managed to think it through to that point myself.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, it's really only a tiny leap from there, I would think!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">What's that? A piece of glass? Though it's unusually thick for glass...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, it's a piece of broken glass that we found inside the jacket on the waxwork. As you say, it's not ordinary glass, though. It's very thick, and clearly made for extra strength. Much like the special glass that was developed for the construction of the Crystal Tower.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">The Crystal To- Holy smoke!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Exactly! The centrepiece of the Great Exhibition, where the very incident we're talking about took place! On the day in question, the birdcage fell from above and smashed through a window of that special glass.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">From whence this small piece originated...is that it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Precisely. So, what do you say... ...now that clear evidence in support of the assertion has been placed before you?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">......... Well, as I said, I only trust men in white coats as a rule. However... ...when the reasoning is sound, it's fair to say colour shouldn't come into it. In light of what you've shown me here, yes, I feel obliged to change my position on the matter.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In that case, juror number four, you will amend your statement now, please.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I can state quite categorically, sir, that we have no such evidence at the present time!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">That much was abundantly clear before that brassy proclamation, I assure you! And why you can count on the fact that I shan't be changing my leaning!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... That proclamation was even brassier than yours, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>If only we had some evidence, things might be different, though...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">The presence of that piece of glass leaves me in little doubt that the waxwork was indeed inside that birdcage.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you for reconsidering your position, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Your words are misplaced, boy. My opinion is governed by logic and science and nothing else. Yes, science is where you should direct your words of gratitude.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">What's the matter with you?! Too good to say some words of thanks to the mother of all academic subjects?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...What is it about scientists? Honestly.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Those two statements clearly contradict each other!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious! To whose statements do you refer, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you could put down your corn for a moment, juror number five...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">......... Ooh, you mean me?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You've pointed out that it's wrong to make an accusation without evidence. But the accusation that the waxwork model was inside the second birdcage on the day in question... ...is not without supporting evidence. As the defence demonstrated to the juror sitting beside you.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">......... Ooh, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Would it be fair to say... ...you didn't follow the argument?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">I don't understand much besides Colonel Cob, to be honest.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>Of course you don't...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">If I could interject here...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Please do, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Now that this assertion of yours about the waxwork has been backed up by some solid evidence... ...it would be wrong of me, as a man of science, not to pursue the matter further.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Ar, well, me too, then!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">If this brainy gentleman says ee's right, then ee must be! See...I, um... ...I wouldn't dream of goin' against Colonel Cob or anyone who's got stuffin' between the ears!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Success! ...If you can call it that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">The possibility has been established reasonably and logically. It now warrants further research.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Accusin' someone without right evidences? Ee's not a proper job, is ee? I won't 'ave it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I've got to ask...why have you brought that corn into court with you?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Colonel Cob? Ee's bin growin' back on the farm. Picked 'im off on me way into town. Ee's a proper nibbler, ee is.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, the nibbling seems to be taking quite a while. Maybe it could wait until after the trial?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Ooh, I don't like the sound o' that. You need colonels at times like these. Whenever I've summat big to decide, the colonels always point me in the right direction, see.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Y-You're talking about your cob of corn?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Nibble nobble guilty bobble, nibble not guilty out. Nibble nobble guilty bobble, nibble not guilty out. Nibble nobble guilty bobble, nibble not guilty out. Nibble nobble guilty bobble, nibble not guilty out.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Perhaps it's akin to fortune-telling with flower petals like people do back home?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So Professor Harebrayne's fate is to be decided by a cob of corn...</thought> Could you not at least wait until we've had more time to find the truth before deciding on the defendant's guilt?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Ooh, I don't know about that. Me tum's awfully full already.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>A-maize-ing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Those two statements clearly contradict each other!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious! To whose statements do you refer, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you could put down your corn for a moment, juror number five...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">......... Ooh, you mean me?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You've pointed out that it's wrong to make an accusation without evidence. But the accusation that the waxwork model was inside the second birdcage on the day in question... ...is not without supporting evidence. As the defence demonstrated to the juror sitting beside you.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">......... Ooh, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Would it be fair to say... ...you didn't follow the argument?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">I don't understand much besides Colonel Cob, to be honest.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>Of course you don't...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">If I could interject here...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Please do, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Now that this assertion of yours about the waxwork has been backed up by some solid evidence... ...it would be wrong of me, as a man of science, not to pursue the matter further.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Ar, well, me too, then!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">If this brainy gentleman says ee's right, then ee must be! See...I, um... ...I wouldn't dream of goin' against Colonel Cob or anyone who's got stuffin' between the ears!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Success! ...If you can call it that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Well, 'course if ee's got some evidences, that's a whole other cob o' corn, innit? Lovely job!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I know it seems a little far-fetched to think that the waxwork model of the Professor was in that birdcage... ...but on the other hand, it explains a lot.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">If there really is a reason why that particular waxwork had to be used as Mr Asman's double... ...we must do everything we can to make the jurors understand it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The truth is, I'm sure that's the key to this, but it's the most puzzling part of it, too.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">In that case, you should see what additional information you can glean whilst trying to change the jurors' minds. If you can read a book whilst eating a rice cracker, Mr Naruhodo, I'm sure you can do this!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Right. Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We, we did it!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, well done, Mr Naruhodo! Another wonderful victory!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm, a waxwork of the despicable Professor... ...used as a 'body double' for the victim in this quite extraordinary case... I must say, it's extremely hard to believe the assertion could possibly be true. However, it would appear that it does at least warrant further investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's the waxwork of the Professor that links Mr Drebber and Dr Sithe. And I'm convinced that there's a special significance to that link!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">I don't know what you're hoping to prove, lad, I really don't!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The truth, sir. By using evidence and testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">If the court is to delve deeper into the alleged involvement of the waxwork in this case... ...then the prosecution calls for the owner of the model to be summoned as a witness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The owner?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Madame Tusspells.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>I, I really thought... ...that Lord van Zieks would object to this whole line of enquiry...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, I concur. Make arrangements for Madame Tusspells to appear as a witness with immediate effect.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Listen carefully, my learned friend.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh... Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">You should know... ...that you're on the brink of opening Pandora's box. .........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court shall now adjourn for forty-five minutes. During that time, the prosecution will summon the new witness and prepare her for taking the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Madame Tusspells, yes. I shall see to it at once, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, the knight-errant himself!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, have you been watching from the gallery, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I've been on the edge of my seat the entire time! Courtroom trials are fascinating affairs. As a spectator, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm glad you've been enjoying yourself...</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I, I have to ask... ...what on earth is going on?! It makes no sense! What's this Professor business all about? He doesn't look like any professor I've ever met before! Who even is he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, of course... ...you were in Germany already ten years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, the Professor... When I discovered 'he' was the one who had been abducted, a sense of foreboding stirred within me. But who knew the monster would come knocking at your door? My heartfelt sympathies! Ah ha ha ha ha hah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As it turns out... ...Lord van Zieks is even more intimately tied to this case than any of us realised, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, how true. His great friend from university in the dock...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...And now a waxwork of the killer who took his esteemed brother's life makes an appearance, too. I imagine even the shrewd Mr Reaper failed to foresee that kick in the teeth. An extraordinary move on your part, my dear fellow, to throw that in front of the man.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You make it sound deliberate...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I can't help feeling... ...that this Professor case is really very puzzling.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Oh yes? In what particular manner?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, there's Mr Drebber, Dr Sithe and Lord van Zieks... It seems that everybody in the trial has a link to the case somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yes, in fact I, alone, am not a member of the set! Though that leaves me as an empty set...all alone with no intersection to any other...</line>
<line speaker="???">Excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">D.........D.........Dr Sithe!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, Dr Courtney Sithe, née Stevens. Good day to you.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Hello, Sholmes. That was very shrewd of you.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...What in particular, pray?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">You requested that ten-year-old autopsy report from Gregson, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Why would you assume such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Because Gregson told me.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">To think it's been ten years... Ten years in the laboratory, wielding my scalpel. I smell of nothing but corpses and disinfectant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A policeman on the jury had a lot to say about you as it happens, Dr Sithe. And I've...accused you of being complicit in what happened. I'm hoping that you'll take the stand and tell the truth about what really happened.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">That certainly won't be possible.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Lord van Zieks won't be summoning me as a witness. Lord Stronghart has forbidden it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord Stronghart?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">The Pandora's box you were warned about...is the Professor case. But please don't make the mistake of thinking you'll get any information about it out of me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But attempting to hide from the truth... That's cowardice!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">I've always fought crime in the way that I see fit. I have no regrets. None at all. And that's all I came here to say. So...good day to you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... She mentioned it, too. This Pandora's box...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Whatever does it all mean?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">There's really no cause for concern. I assure you, when the trial resumes... ...the meaning will become all too apparent, whether you'd like it to or not.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Now then, I believe it's almost time. I must make my way back to the public gallery. The edge of my seat awaits!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I think maybe you're enjoying yourself a little too much...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah yes, one word of warning before I go: If, in the course of the trial this afternoon, you perceive even a shadow of doubt about the truth... ...don't let it out of your sight. Pursue it like a dog with a bone.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">To the bitter end, you understand. Do not falter, whatever may come to pass.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Alright, I understand. ...Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Good. I shall make myself scarce, then. I purchased a bar of caramel earlier, so I shall be gnawing on that as you gnaw away at the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What did that warning from Mr Sholmes really mean, I wonder? Especially the bit about 'whatever may come to pass'... .........</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">In the name of Her Majesty the Queen, I hereby reconvene the proceedings of this court. Counsels for the defence and prosecution, are you ready and able to continue?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The prosecution is ready, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, My Lord. The defence is also ready.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As the court is aware, the case under our scrutiny began with a damaging incident at the Great Exhibition. Yet we now find ourselves embroiled in the details of a convicted felon who was sent to the gallows a decade ago. This trial has certainly defied all expectation.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">As seems to be the fate of all trials in which this Nipponese is involved, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So then... ...let us begin our exploration of the defence's assertion that the waxwork was cardinally involved in this matter. Lord van Zieks...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">My Lord?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are we still awaiting the arrival of Madame Tusspells?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Not at all. She is in the antechamber as we speak and ready to be summoned.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Bring in the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">At once, My Lord. Bailiff! Show Madame Tusspells to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Things are about to become a lot more intense. If Drebber is responsible, as I'm sure he is, it means he must have had an accomplice...in Dr Sithe.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">And what connects the pair of them...is the waxwork.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, the model of the Professor... That's the key to the link between these otherwise unrelated individuals. It's a tenuous link, admittedly. But at present, it's all we have to go on.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">State your name and occupation for the court, please.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">My name is Madame Esmeralda Tusspells. I am a waxwork artisan. And the proprietress of the Madame Tusspells Museum of Waxwork. You will have to pardon me for working as I testify. My new exhibit must open very soon.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>Oh, so he finally gets a statue, does he? Now there are two of them in the world...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my... What expression is she carving onto that face?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">A number of days ago, a particular waxwork model was stolen from your museum. Can you confirm this?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Oui. That is true. At first, we believed it had been kidnapped.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A waxwork model? Kidnapped?!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Yes, My Lord. There was a demand for ransom money left behind by the culprit. However, according to what I have just been told outside the courtroom, that was not the true reason. I understand it was utilised as a substitute for the body of a murder victim?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">At present, that is no more than conjecture proposed by the defence. This is the victim of the case in question. Mr Odie Asman.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">But of course, I know him well. He is a part of my odious personages exhibit. ...I detest to say what is evident, but Mr Asman does not resemble the Professor at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, but...perhaps! Perhaps their faces are very similar!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Are you suggesting that we should see now the demasked visage of the Professor? I have here the key, but it is strictly forbidden to open the lock.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">This is absurd!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I don't know what face you've carved onto your fancy figure beneath that mask... ...but clearly it won't be that of the actual killer.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. The man's identity was never made public, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The trial took place in a closed court. The proceedings were strictly confidential. The condemned man was summarily executed. His identity remains a closely guarded national secret. There is no possible way that a repository of tawdry exhibits could get its hands on that information.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">......... Quel dommage. It would seem you are unaware of the Tusspells' principles.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What principles?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">The family Tusspells has always prided itself on sculpting its models à la perfection. Every detail, including the visage, is fashioned with complete fidelity. ...Et voilà: our principles.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">There is a well known legend about the Tusspells waxworks from the time of the French Revolution. A member of the Tusspells family is said to have made a waxwork of the queen who was executed.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Oui, that is true. It was a century ago now.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I believe the queen's face was carved in the minutes following her death, actually at the guillotine site.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">You are correct. The model is on display still today in the House of Horrors. We Tusspells will stop at nothing to obtain a faithful replica of our subjects.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Dear me... A somewhat disturbing tenacity of purpose.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">It is the only way to obtain a truly lifelike representation of the subject. And it has been my family's secret for generations.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do, do you mean to say...that beneath that mask...?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Oui. The true visage of the killer is there.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...This is ludicrous. It's out of the question!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">The Professor spread terror throughout Great Britain. As a result, the Madame Tusspells Special Exhibit remains extremely popular even today. The killer...emerging from his own grave... It is a sight to behold. You should come.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think, madame, it would be beneficial to hear your formal testimony on this matter. You will explain every detail of this macabre model. And your personal involvement in its creation.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">...With pleasure.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">The special exhibit in the House of Horrors is based on a rumour that shocked society in London.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The gravedigger?! The man sanctioned this?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Oui. I will do all that is necessary to achieve the true resemblance my family is celebrated for. Nobody else knew. Only the gravedigger. What harm did it do, uh?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">So you truly saw it? The face of that monster!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">......... Naturally, I was aware at the time that his identity was a secret. But Tusspells would not be Tusspells if we did not insist on absolute fidelity to our sculptures.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I don't believe this...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I myself have seen the special exhibit at your museum, madame. A truly blood-curdling scene, in which the murderer is emerging from his own grave.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">The scene it depicts was the subject of many rumours in London ten years ago. I have here a newspaper from the time. The special exhibit was based upon the picture in this article. It was the most detailed account of what happened, as reported by the eyewitness who saw it.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">'Man Rises from the Grave!'... It's too absurd for words.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">The public enjoy absurdity, monsieur. That is why I have reproduced the scene as carefully as possible in my museum.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And it's a waxwork from that exhibit that was stolen some days before the incident at the Great Exhibition, wasn't it.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">That is correct. The Professor you see before you here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm... Most puzzling... Counsel for the Defence...proceed with the cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This waxwork links Drebber to Dr Sithe... And there has to be some reason for that, which hasn't yet come to light. But I'll find it. I'll get to the bottom of what really happened. I'll prove that Dr Sithe and Drebber were in on this crime together!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">The special exhibit in the House of Horrors is based on a rumour that shocked society in London.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And that rumour would be...?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">A ten-year-old tale now...but one that no Londoner would ever forget.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Ah, right. I know just what you're talking about, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Of course, it couldn't be anything else...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Yes, that story will never disappear.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">The tale of the condemned killer rising from the dead... That is the central attraction of my House of Horrors. The rumour was whispered all over the city. And it was like this...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The, the corpse climbed out...of his own grave...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And then somebody shot him? Who, who was it?!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Nobody knows, even today. But remember, it was just a rumour. ...Perhaps nothing more than a ghost story. The good people of London, they love stories like this. That is why it was in every newspaper across the capital.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but was it just a story? I mean, this is exactly the scene that can be seen today at your museum, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Oui. The special exhibit was modelled on that very illustration. For a while afterwards, the contents of that article were reproduced in every newspaper imaginable.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Madame, might I say something?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Please, go ahead, mademoiselle.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">When something is described as a rumour, it doesn't necessarily mean that it's entirely made up. I believe that often...rumours contain elements of the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Ah, I see that people from the East can be just as astute as the people of Europe.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Can we be sure, for instance, that the Professor's execution was successful?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">......... It is not possible for the dead to come back to life.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Ten years ago, I was there in Lowgate Cemetery. After the criminal known as the Professor was killed by hanging... ...I took a wax impression of his visage from the corpse just before it was interred. So I can assure you... ...the man was dead.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I see.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... It would certainly appear that the condemned man suffered the intended fate.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">An impression of the visage was taken directly from the corpse...in accordance with Tusspells family principles.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is, is that true of every waxwork in your museum then?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">It is...assuming the subject is dead, of course. Live subjects have to cooperate in a similar way. I have letters from imprisoned criminals all the time, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What sort of letters?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">'When my time comes, please make a waxwork of me.' ...Comme ça.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">My museum is famous, monsieur. To be made into a waxwork is an honour. And for some criminals, a symbol of status, even.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Because nothing says hardened criminal better than... wax.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">And it is thanks to one killer in particular, that my museum has gained such popularity in London. I refer to the star of the special exhibit, of course. The Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...Whose form you claim to have captured by taking an impression from the actual corpse.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">...There are no exceptions to the principles of Tusspells.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">I enlisted the aid of the gravedigger, and created a mould for the head in the cemetery just before the interment.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Surely that's illegal...isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It would seem the proprietress of this repository of novelties was blinded by monetary good.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">It had nothing to do with money. The man is part of London's criminal history. That is why I had to sculpt him. To record this history. It is the raison d'être of the Tusspells museum.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But if the man was convicted in a closed court and sent for immediate execution... ...then surely nobody but the members of the judiciary present know the killer's true identity.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">I can assure you, behind that mask is hidden the true face of the Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Do you realise what you're saying?! The Professor's identity is a national secret!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">...I understand. And now that the truth about the special exhibit has been revealed, it must perhaps close.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Of course it will. As will your entire museum, if you don't tread very carefully, madame.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">That could be another interesting chapter in the history of my family, I think, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So ten years ago, on the night of the Professor's execution, you took a wax impression of his face from the corpse?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Oui. Exactement.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">I hid myself until he gave me a signal. ...I was there for a very long time that night.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You were there longer than you expected to be?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">...I had some...difficulties in capturing the subject's form correctly. As I removed the mask, the mouth of the cadaver fell open and I had some problems with the chin.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Dare I ask...?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">The man had been dead for a short while already, you see. His muscles were relaxing and consequently his chin would not align itself correctly.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear...what a horrible thought...</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Under normal circumstances, I would have an assistant with me. However, that night, I was alone. And as a consequence, I missed my preferred window of time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">When I take the impression of the visage of a cadaver... ...I always wait until three hours after death.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why three hours? Is that amount of time significant?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">It is because of rigor mortis.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A...wriggly mortice?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's the name given to a phenomenon that occurs in recently deceased bodies. As a rule, three hours post death, the muscles in the body begin to stiffen. By approximately ten hours post death, the entire body is completely rigid and inflexible. And then from that point on, the muscles slowly start to revert to their relaxed state. The effect is often used to estimate the time of death when a body is discovered!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Well, that was an education. If a slightly scary one.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">As the mademoiselle says, rigor mortis commences three hours after death...and it starts in the jaw.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I see. So that's why you wait.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Before that time, the mouth falls open...and it is very difficult to do my work.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...it's getting hard for me to do my work with all this talk of corpses... <thought>Hm...I wonder about that information the court's just heard from Madame Tusspells...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...the information about rigor mortis that you just shared with us... Would you mind including it in your formal testimony? I believe it could be significant, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Of course. I do not mind at all.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I can't help feeling that after this latest topic... ...the atmosphere in the courtroom has become extremely...grave.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...This is no time for jokes, Miss Susato.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Madame, kindly amend your testimony as discussed.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Bien sûr.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I think I'd rather pretend I didn't hear any of those grim details and try to forget all about it.</thought> Thank you, madame. Please continue.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Certainly. So, you comprehend a little of the process now, and why it took me so long that night.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">It took me a very long time because it was before the onset of rigor mortis.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Rigor mortis being the phenomenon you described whereby the corpse becomes stiff after death? I think you said that it starts at the jaw, about three hours post death. Is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Oui, c'est ça. Of course the exact duration depends a little on the season.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I didn't realise a waxwork artisan would be so well versed in the subject.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Non non, that is only elementary knowledge in the field of legal medicine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well I had no idea about it. But maybe I won't admit to my ignorance about forensic science.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Hm... I could ask my father to give you a very simple primer, if you like!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I think corpses should be your domain. I'm...not good with them.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear...I'll do my very best.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">As dawn approached, I was very worried that I could be discovered.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You say that dawn was approaching? What was the time of day, then? Approximately.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Well...I could not say. But when I left the cemetery with my utensils and wax, the morning light was becoming visible.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The execution took place on 17th June...which had the earliest sunrise of that year.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed it did. First light would have been at around 4:40 in the morning.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That really is early.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">The fact is, I had very little time. So I finished my work in a half hour. It was necessary to complete the impression and bury the body before daybreak, of course. If somebody had discovered me there, it would have been a catastrophe. So I had to hurry.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Is it me, or does Mr Sholmes seem to be taking shape more quickly now, too?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm... You certainly appear to go to extraordinary lengths for your work, madame.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I wonder... is what she just said particularly significant?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Madame, those details about how long it took you to complete the sculpture and the early sunrise... Could you include them in your testimony? I believe they may be significant.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Of course, if you would like me to.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You're quite right, Mr Naruhodo. It is intriguing. A sunrise at four in the morning would be absolutely unimaginable at home, wouldn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That's not quite what I meant by 'significant'.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Kindly amend your formal testimony then, madame.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">With pleasure, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>All it really told us is that sunrise in Great Britain is extremely early at the height of summer, I suppose</thought> Thank you, madame. That's all clear now.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">How frustrating, I was not concentrating on Mr Sholmes here and I have taken away too much wax.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">I hurried to finish my work in the half hour before sunrise. Then I left as soon as the corpse was interred.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Did you have reason to believe you might be discovered once the sun came up or something?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">I had paid the gravedigger money to keep my little secret, of course. But with the morning light, I knew that the warden from the prison would commence his patrol of the area.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Couldn't you just have paid off the warden too, then?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">I had already paid the gravedigger, as I said. You cannot buy the silence of everyone, or the secret is no longer a secret, uh?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The sunrise was at 4:40 a.m. that day. Which means that it would have been around four when you began your sculpting work.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Oui, that must be correct. That would be when the gravedigger gave me the signal to come out of hiding.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So that's all I have to go on...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">What's your feeling, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">For some reason, Dr Sithe went along with Drebber's plan. Now, if that's really true... ...then the Professor is the only other thing we know of that links the pair of them. So I feel sure that waxwork must be a clue to this mystery somehow...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">In that case, we must use this cross-examination to uncover exactly what it means! Otherwise the jurors are sure to revert their leanings and the trial will be over!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I agree. But interestingly... ...uncovering what the Professor has to do with all of this means more to Lord van Zieks than anyone. That's...the impression I'm getting, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, as do I...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>After all, he has a profound connection to the Professor as well...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Madame Tusspells... I have here an autopsy report that was filed ten years ago now. It confirms the death of the Professor following his execution at the gallows.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">And...is that a problem?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I believe it is. Because your testimony, and a particular detail in the report... ...completely contradict one another.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Quoi?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Are you going to explain yourself, my Nipponese friend?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">According to her testimony, Madame Tusspells was creating her wax impression just before dawn. And at that time, rigor mortis had not yet set in. Am I correct so far, madame?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">You are, yes. As I said, the stiffening of the jaw is the first sign of rigor mortis, two to three hours after death. But the man's chin was limp, so he cannot have been dead for a long time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But on the other hand, if you look at Dr Sithe's report... ...it quite clearly states the following: 'Death by hanging confirmed at midnight, 17th June.'</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">No...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If the Professor indeed died at midnight that day... ...then by the time you were sculpting his face, rigor mortis would already have set in.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Oui! Yes, you are right. The chin, it would have been completely stiff.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In other words, this report...is wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In that case, there's only one possible conclusion: The execution didn't actually take place at the stated time!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Im...Impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Counsel, this is beyond folly! Not only do you indict the author of the report, Dr Sithe... ...but you also implicate members of staff at Barclay Prison where the execution took place!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">By heck!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Extraordinary!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Not in my day!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What fact?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The Professor died that night. Without question!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">He did! Of course he did! I moved the man's limp jaw with my own hands! There was no-</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, the Professor died that night. But what if he didn't die at the gallows?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Didn't die at...? Are you insane?! What...what exactly are you suggesting did happen in that case?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It's almost impossible to believe, but it would explain the link... ...between Dr Sithe, the Professor...and that one other person of interest!</thought> I have evidence that will explain exactly what I'm suggesting happened that night!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel, present the evidence at once! The evidence that allegedly explains what really happened on the night of the Professor's execution!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Quite. The next time you present such a nonsensical article, Counsel... ...you may find that tonight is the night of your own execution!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Great. I'm so looking forward to trying again now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I won't let anyone execute you, Mr Naruhodo! Not tonight!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What happened that night is written very plainly in this newspaper article! 'Executed criminal returns in the dead of night at local cemetery!'</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">You're suggesting it was a corpse, coming back from the dead now?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, if this article is to be believed, yes. The Professor, assumed dead following his execution, emerged from his grave...and was killed again!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Can you be certain of that?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Are you serious?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The point is, as the article says, there was a witness to what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">My word! Yes, indeed!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Mais oui! The young man who stole into the cemetery by chance that night!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And in any case, this was ten years ago now. There would surely be no hope of finding him.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">On the contrary, My Lord. We all know this witness well!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you suggesting, Counsel, that you've identified the person in question? That you know who claims to have seen these utterly incredible events take place?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, My Lord. <thought>In fact, you could say that he's right here before my very eyes!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You will substantiate your latest claim now then, Counsel. Who is the alleged witness of this staggering scene from the cemetery ten years ago?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">At least have the decency to open your eyes and face the result of your blunder, for heaven's sake.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gyaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And perhaps you should keep your eyes open when you collapse on the bench like that, too. For safety's sake.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'll bear it in mind.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The man in question...is Mr Enoch Drebber!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Drebber?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The, the previous witness?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The special exhibit in the House of Horrors at Madame Tusspells Museum of Waxwork... ...recreates that decade-old scene in great detail. The condemned criminal emerging from the grave... And beside the tomb... ...a young man with a lantern stumbling upon the terrifying sight. And that young man... ...is a ten-year-younger Mr Enoch Drebber!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Ordaaaaaar!!! Surely not, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Drebber was there? In Lowgate Cemetery?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Um... What is all this talk about Mr Drebber? Is the name significant?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Of course. Madam [sic] Tusspells doesn't know, does she?</thought> Yes. It's extremely significant, madame. To your situation as well, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">What situation?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The theft of the Professor waxwork from your museum some days ago... ...was perpetrated by the very same man.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Non! But...but that would mean...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Madame Tusspells... ...it would appear you know the name...Enoch Drebber.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">......... Oui. yes, I know it. But from long ago in the past.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Explain yourself! Tell us everything you know!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Yes... Yes, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">The Daily Circus. It is the paper from which comes the article I have already shown the court.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're saying that his full name was only publicised in that article?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Goodness me! Yes, here it is! 'The university student who experienced this shocking event is Mr Enoch Drebber... ...a disciple of science at the University of London, and a resident of its student dorms.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Unbelievable!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">When I read the article, I went to meet with the man. His discovery of the condemned criminal coming back to life in the cemetery in the dead of night... ...would make a perfect exhibit for my House of Horrors, whether it was the truth or not.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. So you went to meet Mr Drebber in order to sculpt a waxwork of the man, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Exactement. He was studying science at the University of London in those days. He was just a poor student. I paid him five pounds to model for the waxwork. And since that time, it has been in my museum to recreate the scene of terror from the cemetery.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So, ten years ago, a young man appealed to the public about an extraordinary event he'd witnessed: A criminal who had been put to death, re-emerging from his grave in the middle of the night. But the public treated his claim as nothing more than an amusing anecdote...that was soon forgotten. Ten years later... ...the same man steals a waxwork model of the executed criminal... ...ostensibly to use as a body double for the victim in the case we're discussing here today. Even though the waxwork's build is a poor match for the victim, and its face is obscured by a mask. So the question is...why would the man do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Which brings us to three days ago, when the birdcage crashed into the Crystal Tower. If the birdcage had in fact contained not the body of Mr Asman, but that same waxwork... ...the coroner from Scotland Yard who investigated, Dr Sithe, would have noticed immediately. And yet she submitted this autopsy report for the victim, which the court has seen earlier. Why?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Because the waxwork was that of the Professor, is that what you're saying?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Dr Sithe put her name to a document confirming the death of a condemned criminal who was still alive. A criminal whose apparent 'resurrection' was witnessed by Mr Drebber. But that misconduct was a deadly secret the coroner would do anything to protect. Which is precisely why Mr Drebber used that particular waxwork as the body double!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Aaaaaargh...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My Lord! This court must summon Dr Sithe to the stand! The defence is determined...to find out exactly how the coroner and Mr Drebber are connected!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But according to the missive I received this morning through the Prosecutor's Office... ...Dr Sithe is unable to participate in these proceedings. Is that not the case?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">She told us so herself, didn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Lord van Zieks won't be summoning me as a witness. Lord Stronghart has forbidden it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord Stronghart?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">The Pandora's box you were warned about...is the Professor case. But please don't make the mistake of thinking you'll get any information about it out of me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Something happened on the night of that killer's execution ten years ago. And surely nobody would want to get to the bottom of that more...than Lord van Zieks!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... The prosecution calls...for the instructions in that missive to be scrapped!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But, but Lord van Zieks! The missive was issued from the Lord Chief Justice's office.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Let Enoch Drebber and Dr Sithe...both take the stand together.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Very well, I will uphold your request. Bailiff! Send a subpoena with immediate effect, addressed to Dr Sithe of the Forensic Investigation Team. The woman is compelled to attend on Her Majesty's orders!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Alright then. Enoch Drebber and Dr Sithe... If they weren't colluding with one another, this crime could never have been committed. I'm just a stone's throw away, I can feel it. The truth behind all of this is about to come out!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Thank you for your attendance at such short notice... Dr Sithe.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">I'm disappointed in you, Lord van Zieks. You've completely betrayed the agreed policy of both Scotland Yard and the Prosecutor's Office.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Betrayal is not in my nature...as long as the truth isn't compromised. If it is... If there's even a hint of wrongdoing...then no matter whom it concerns or disgruntles... ...I will pursue the matter to the bitter end. As would any prosecutor worth his salt.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Drebber... ...you took the victim's life by means of a machine that you constructed in your workshop.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And Dr Sithe... ...as the investigating coroner, you were the first on the scene to examine the victim's body. It is the belief of the defence... ...that you collaborated with each other and were both complicit in this crime.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">And where's your evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">At present, we have no definitive evidence. But we do have a very significant clue.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm talking, of course, about the waxwork! This model of the killer known as the Professor...who was sentenced to death ten years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">You don't need to tell me. I witnessed the man's execution with my own eyes. And officially pronounced him dead.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That remains to be seen.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Is that so?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">According to newspaper reports from the time, on the night following his execution... ...the killer came back to life.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Tsk! Don't waste my time!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And the sole witness to that mysterious event... ...was you, Mr Drebber, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If what you saw in the graveyard that night ten years ago wasn't some chilling fiction, but reality... ...it would make you privy to a very great secret of Dr Sithe's. A secret so profound, it could compel the coroner to agree to collaborate in your evil scheme, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Drebber, tell the court! Tell everyone the truth of what you saw that night in Lowgate Cemetery!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">What an interesting twist.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">When at the time, not one person would take me seriously. Yet now here we are, ten years later, and suddenly my story matters. And in a court of law, too. Very well, then. If everyone so wishes. Let's be frank. I'll tell you the truth of what happened that night...for what it's worth.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">.........</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, Mr Drebber... ...your testimony, please. About the events of that night ten years ago. You will tell the court exactly what you stumbled across in Lowgate Cemetery!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Yes of course. As you wish.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">The reason I was in Lowgate Cemetery at all ten years ago was for...a spot of moonlighting, shall we say?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait a minute! You're, you're claiming you didn't actually see the Professor now?!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Of course. You'd have to have a screw loose if you believed a corpse could come back from the dead.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But... So you're saying this article is...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">...Not worth the paper it's printed on? I think that would describe it perfectly, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">If the details in the article aren't true... ...it nullifies your argument for why Mr Drebber and Dr Sithe would have been working together.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So he's discrediting himself to cripple my argument?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Tell me, witness... ...you claim to have been in the cemetery on some... auxiliary business. Can you elaborate?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">That's right. Graverobbing, to be precise. As you know, Lowgate Cemetery is at the rear of Barclay Prison. So among students at the university, it had a reputation for being haunted by the ghosts of condemned convicts.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">G-Graverobbing, you say?!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Yes. Exhuming fresh corpses to sell is reasonably lucrative. Of course, I never laid a finger on any valuables buried with the dead.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">So you were one of the so-called Resurrectionists. A particularly unpleasant scourge on society. </line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Actually, my fellows and I went by another name: 'The Repurposers'.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That, that is quite beyond the pale! You would invite divine retribution, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Yes, well...I think I suffered retribution enough. The Daily Circus...eventually unearthed my name and put it in print. It caused me a great many headaches. In the end, I had to leave the university. ...That was the only paper with the bad grace to identify me unambiguously, I might add.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Out of interest, who drew the illustration for this article?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Ah yes, that was the reporter who exposed me. He sketched that right in front of me as I described the scene. Obviously, as time ticked on, I bitterly regretted what I'd done. Claiming to have seen something I never truly saw... Foolish. Very foolish.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Well, Counsel for the Defence...you may proceed to the cross-examination now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">At once, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">The reason I was in Lowgate Cemetery at all ten years ago was for...a spot of moonlighting, shall we say?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">By 'moonlighting', you mean graverobbing, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Surely you only need to look at the graveyard scene and my appearance to gauge the answer to that?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The lantern and spade...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But who on earth would want to buy a dead body?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Any major hospital.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A hospital?!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">In order to better understand the human body, the study of anatomy is crucial to medical science. But there isn't a hospital in the world that has enough 'specimens' to work with. ...Though obviously they can't openly express an interest in obtaining more by dubious means.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">As aspiring scientists, we young research students had no money to work with, as I'm sure you can imagine. So we made surreptitious arrangements with a hospital via some of our medical student acquaintances. We would never take anything of value from the graves. This was all for the furtherance of science, you see. That's what we all told ourselves every time we stole into the graveyard at night, spade in hand.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">You realise body-snatching is a serious crime. If you were caught, you could expect the gravest of consequences.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">We students were caught between the hammer and the anvil. We needed funds for research.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Professor Harebrayne said exactly the same...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm quite speechless at the apparent levity with which you've revealed this abhorrent behaviour.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Well, if you wanted to know why I was there at Lowgate Cemetery, that's the reason. But I never expected it to end the way it did. That...I regret to this day.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Yes, the illustration in that newspaper article was based on what I witnessed that night.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The strange happening at Lowgate Cemetery...which you now deny.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Not entirely. I ran to fetch the police at the time, you know. I was shaking like a leaf. But they didn't believe a word of it. In fact, I was very nearly arrested myself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you went to the papers instead?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">I started big, with the London News. But unsurprisingly, they didn't want to know, either. In the end, though, it was reporters from the gossip rags, the gutter press, that came to get my story. And it spread like the plague through the capital, as gossip-hungry Londoners lapped up the tale.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The story was in every single paper at the time, with the exception of some broadsheets.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">And yet only two or three of them actually interviewed me personally. Most of the accounts turned out to be very...interpretive ghost stories.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What about the article in the Daily Circus?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">That particular journalist found me at my dormitory. I don't know how, but he'd discovered my name. So I recounted to him exactly what had happened that night.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And from your description, he drew this illustration?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Precisely. That's how I learnt that the condemned man was the infamous Professor. Because the reporter told me so. I had no idea myself, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Newspaper reporters are wont to snoop around in matters that don't concern them. So the scene portrayed in the illustration is accurate, then?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Well...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Thinking back now, I realise that I never actually saw the Professor at all, though.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">I think I explained already, didn't I? Lowgate Cemetery is at the rear of Barclay Prison. So it was renowned among us students at the university for being haunted by the ghosts of condemned convicts. For some absurd reason, I was scared of the graveyard at night. And as a result...only too willing to believe that nonsense about the dead coming back to life.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But you said you actually saw it.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">I said what I'd seen in my mind's eye. After all...resurrection is impossible, isn't it? You'd have to be unhinged to think otherwise. Unless of course... ...you have some evidence that proves I encountered the Professor that night?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>I don't know. Is there any material evidence that could show he really did see the Professor?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">If we have anything at all, Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know. I need to present it against that irritatingly backtracking statement of his!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">The point is, that night was a pivotal moment in my life.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry, Mr Drebber, but I don't believe that.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Don't believe what?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your latest claim. You did see the Professor on that night ten years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Hm, oh dear, we seem to be at odds. But I was there. And you were not. I know what I didn't see.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The illustration with this article... ...was drawn based upon what you told the journalist that you witnessed. A figure emerging from a tomb...wearing an iron mask.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yes, when the killer was tried ten years ago... ...it was decided in the closed court's ruling that the man would wear the mask to hide his identity. It wasn't to be removed even during his execution and subsequent burial.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not even the prison wardens were to see the man's face. But obviously, the provision of this mask was not public knowledge.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So, Mr Drebber, as you've just heard...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...a lowly student of the University of London certainly wouldn't have known about the condemned man's mask. So unless you'd actually seen the Professor that night... ...it's inconceivable that the artist would have included the mask in that illustration!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Aaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Orrrdaaar! ...Well, Mr Drebber?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">......... It's a vile scene, isn't it? If you look closely.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">And as I've already been at pains to point out, I was utterly petrified. Which is why I had it in my head that I'd seen such a blood-curdling sight. But afterwards, I came to my senses. And realised that I'd been mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You... You're still saying you didn't see it?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">If you're stubbornly sticking to that story, witness... ...then amend your testimony to explain exactly how you think your eyes deceived you.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Of course, of course. Only too happy to oblige.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I can't believe he's still not going to concede the point!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">What I in fact witnessed, was a fellow graverobber at work.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A fellow graverobber? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Well, I wasn't the only one busy in the cemetery that night, you know. Other body snatchers were at work. Of course, when I saw one emerging from the hole he'd dug, my heart very nearly stopped. So that's the terrifying sight I actually saw, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">You're claiming it was just another student on equally insalubrious business as yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Many of the medical students would wear metal masks to protect them from bacteria during dissections. Clearly the fellow was using such a mask to protect his anonymity...wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But there's more to the story, isn't there? The article goes on to say: 'In the next second, a gunshot rang out suddenly from behind. The bullet pierced the resurrected man's chest, whose breath then stilled once more.'</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We might assume that the sexton discovered the miscreants at work, perhaps? And fired upon one of them.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If a gravedigger had shot someone in the cemetery, I think it might have been rather big news, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah! Yes, well...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">I can only assume it was an embellishment bolted on later by the reporter.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Madame Tusspells! ...Don't take it out on Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">......... Oh là là! Pardon. I was...lost in my thoughts.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Would it be fair to say that Mr Drebber's last remark... ...was significant to you in some way?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">......... I thought it was a little strange, that is all. How Monsieur Drebber could claim this now.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">If you don't mind me saying, madame... What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Well, when I met you ten years ago at your university dormitory... ...you recounted to me about your adventures in the cemetery, non? Including the gunshot...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Stop! You might want to watch your tongue, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Grrr...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Please, Madame Tusspells, carry on.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Of course. According to what Monsieur Drebber told me at the time... ...he did hear a gunshot from behind him, and the bullet hit the condemned man.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">I said nothing of the sort!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Non, you were very explicit about the details. About the mask that the figure was wearing... ...and the blood that splattered over you when he was shot.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Enough! Shut up, woman! You're making all this up!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That will do! Mr Drebber...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Hm? Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You refute the account just given by Madame Tusspells?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">......... I have no recollection of ever saying those things.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Come on! Do you really expect us to believe you?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Control yourself, Counsel. I will not permit baseless accusations in my courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Under the circumstances... ...I think it best that you supplement your testimony with a statement to clarify your position on this, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">V...Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">An embellishment?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">As I explained earlier, most of what the papers published about those events was fabricated nonsense. The journalists had a great time fashioning it into a horrifying ghost story.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...now you're saying there was no gunshot?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">That's right, yes. I'm afraid so.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">I mistakenly thought I'd seen a corpse coming back to life and then fled the scene. That's really all that happened.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">There was no gunshot from behind me at all. Nor any splattering blood.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yet Madame Tusspells has testified that you told her about both of those details.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Not true. I said nothing of the sort.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Ten years have passed. Without material evidence to the contrary, you have no grounds on which to question the witness's word.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh! Tell me, Madame Tusspells...</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Oui?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...what exactly did Mr Drebber say about the blood that apparently spattered on him?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Alors, this is what he told me: All of a sudden, he heard a very loud gunshot from behind his back. The bullet hit the figure who was emerging from the tomb in the middle of the chest. In his heart.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm... One dreadful sight after another...</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">And since Monsieur Drebber was at that time facing towards the condemned man... ...the blood sprayed from the wound and spattered on his body. That is what he told me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...not an experience you would ever forget, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Precisely. And I didn't forget it. Because, as I've already said... ...it never happened in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He's clearly lying. If only I had some evidence to prove it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">We can't let him win, Mr Naruhodo! So we mustn't overlook a single detail, no matter how small!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Soon afterwards, I was visited by a young woman who sculpted a model of me from wax.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That young woman being Madame Tusspells, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Precisely. I must say, I didn't expect to run into her again like this ten years later.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">As I have explained... ...I went by the name published in the article, and... comme ça I found the man.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, the article in the Daily Circus, I think you said.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">I was a poor student with barely a penny to my name at the time. And the young lady put five pounds in front of me.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">So you readily consented to having a waxwork of yourself made and gave permission for it to be put on display.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">I did. I should sell what little I had to sell, I concluded.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Ah, oui, I remember now... ...I purchased something else from you that day, n'est-ce pas?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Did you? I can't say I remember.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What was it, madame?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">His camera.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Oh yes. I made a point of taking it with me whenever I... made an excursion into any cemetery.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You took a camera with you, sir? To what end?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">To record the details of the bodies I disinterred. But I had no intention of ever visiting a graveyard again after that night...so I sold it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">But I still have it, monsieur. It is part of the special exhibit in my House of Horrors. I am very meticulous about such details. It is the Tusspells way.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It would seem, then... ...that this is the very camera Mr Drebber took with him to Lowgate Cemetery on the night in question.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. Interesting...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That young woman being Madame Tusspells, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Precisely. I must say, I didn't expect to run into her again like this ten years later.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">As I have explained... ...I went by the name published in the article, and... comme ça I found the man.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, the article in the Daily Circus, I think you said.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">I was a poor student with barely a penny to my name at the time. And the young lady put five pounds in front of me.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">So you readily consented to having a waxwork of yourself made and gave permission for it to be put on display.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">I did. I should sell what little I had to sell, I concluded.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Ah, oui, I remember now... ...I purchased something else from you that day, n'est-ce pas?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Did you? I can't say I remember.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What was it, madame?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">His camera.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Oh yes. I made a point of taking it with me whenever I... made an excursion into any cemetery.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You took a camera with you, sir? To what end?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">To record the details of the bodies I disinterred. But I had no intention of ever visiting a graveyard again after that night...so I sold it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">But I still have it, monsieur. It is part of the special exhibit in my House of Horrors. I am very meticulous about such details. It is the Tusspells way.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It would seem, then... ...that this is the very camera Mr Drebber took with him to Lowgate Cemetery on the night in question.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. Interesting...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is where the photographic plate goes, I think, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's right. Isn't it incredible to think that this is the actual camera Mr Drebber used that night? I certainly never imagined a piece of evidence would be on display in Madame Tusspells!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">She's very keen on everything being as true to life as possible though, isn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Then I gave up on my dream of becoming a scientist. And it was all because of that newspaper article.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This article, you mean? Published in the Daily Circus?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Yes. Somebody informed the dean that it was my name that appeared in the article. And carelessly let slip that night after night, I was digging up graves. Hardly a model student, you might say. The university's reputation was execrably defiled, and I was expelled as a result.</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Mon Dieu, I had no idea...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And having been run out of university, you found employment in a somewhat...specialist trade.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You combined your knowledge of science with your knowledge of stage magic... ...to create various 'experimental machines' intended to demonstrate never-before-seen technology. And you used those deceptive machines to trick the government and private investors into giving you money.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Professor Albert Harebrayne was just your latest victim, wasn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Whatever are you talking about? I have no recollection of doing anything of the sort.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What's Drebber up to? Why would he suddenly change his tune and recant his claim?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I wonder if perhaps...it's because his circumstances have changed now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What circumstances?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well...if he admits to having seen the Professor emerging alive from his grave ten years ago... ...it will expose a secret in Dr Sithe's past that she would desperately want to hide.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, of course! If Drebber and Dr Sithe are working together now... ...then if Drebber were to betray her, there would be no reason for her to continue to cooperate. <thought>In that case, there's only one way around it. I'll have to prove he really did see it. Prove he really did see the Professor's corpse coming back from the dead as he originally claimed!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, Mr Naruhodo! Exactly!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Drebber, do you remember this camera?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">...!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">But...that is the camera from that fateful night!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, we...borrowed it from the House of Horrors. It's the camera you took with you to the cemetery that night, Mr Drebber.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">......... And...is that supposed to be significant?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This kind of camera is rarely seen in our homeland, so my colleague and I were keen to examine it closely. We noticed that the lens extends forwards on the end of some bellows... ...like this.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right. It's a rather conspicuous mark here on the bellows, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good Lord! Are you suggesting...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, My Lord. It would appear to be a spatter of blood.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Something that could be confirmed with a simple chemical test. Isn't that right, Dr Sithe?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">...! It would be difficult to determine if it was human blood and not the blood of some animal. But yes, to test whether or not it's blood at all is simple enough.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I propose that Madame Tusspells's testimony was correct. And that on the night in question ten years ago...you were spattered with blood from the gunshot wound.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Well I...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And that furthermore...you really did witness the condemned Professor emerging from his tomb!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Grrr... Gaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's simply no way you could have forgotten such a traumatic experience! In other words, the only explanation... ...is that you're trying to hide the fact that you saw the Professor that night!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...not for his own gain, it would seem.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">For whose, then? Who could benefit?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Drebber is obviously lying in order to protect somebody.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">My goodness! He's shielding someone?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, My Lord. And clearly... ...it's someone who doesn't want the truth about the Professor 'coming back to life' to be exposed!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Counsel, who is it then? Who is this witness trying to protect by lying about what he saw that night?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Uh-oh! That's not the reaction I was expecting either.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I suggest...you go and crawl into a tomb. Maybe then you'll emerge with a better grasp on the case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Uwaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Fear not, Mr Naruhodo! I'll shield you, even if I must lie to do it! I'll tell them that such a terrible mistake is completely out of character!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...I can't have Susato-san committing perjury for me. No. No more mistakes. I need to get this right now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The obvious answer...is Dr Sithe!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Sithe...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What, whatever do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Imagine if the convict who'd been sentenced to death was not in fact killed... Imagine if that was to come to light...</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">What are you insinuating?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And imagine if the convict in question was the country's most hated mass murderer... ...if it was the Professor...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That, that would be an unprecedented scandal!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's exactly what it would mean.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But the fact is...there was a witness to the fact that the man did escape his hanging!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that were really true, Counsel, the implications of misconduct would not stop at the supervising coroner. It would taint the honour of the entire judiciary, from the ground up!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And it's exactly because of those monumental repercussions... ...that Dr Sithe would consent to any demand made of her by someone who threatened to expose the secret. Even if that meant being complicit in a crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You, you mean...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I mean that Dr Sithe wasn't collaborating in Mr Drebber's wicked scheme... ...she was coerced into collaborating! In order to protect her decade-old secret... ...she switched the dead body of Mr Asman with the waxwork model and fabricated the autopsy report!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">L-Lord van Zieks!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Pray forgive my freshly filled hallowed chalice...and a whole raft of other discourtesies now.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Goodness me!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It's just the sort of tall tale Londoners would enjoy, I grant you. An executed killer rising from the dead... A Scotland Yard cover-up... A conspiracy at the highest levels... So let me ask you one thing...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">If the condemned man really did emerge from his tomb that night only to be shot in the chest... ...who pulled the trigger and disposed of him forever?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Uh, well... <thought>I have no idea at the moment!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">We have too little information to work that out at present, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I couldn't agree more...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The Old Bailey is no place for wild fantasies.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And have you considered this, my learned Nipponese friend?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Considered what?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Do you realise just what a dangerous endeavour it would be to coerce this woman into such criminal activity? It's tantamount to declaring war on the entire British police force and judiciary.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Quite. Hard to imagine any sum of money being offered for research could warrant it.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">To rely on some stage deception when so much is at stake would be madness.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, well I suppose...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And this was no petty crime, either. The victim was murdered. A man who'd already invested money in the venture, and would be instrumental in future profits, too.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Yes, I had no reason to kill Mr Asman at all. Or are you forgetting that his death results in me receiving not a single penny? The court is already aware of the contract between myself and the victim, no?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... There is the contract, that's very true...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>The motive for this case runs deep, though. I can feel it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Using threats to force the head of the Forensic Investigation Team to cooperate is extreme. Especially for a government grant he had no guarantee of receiving in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...If the research grant was the aim, taking Mr Asman's life would have made no sense anyway. Which means... ...Mr Drebber's motive wasn't money at all. He was...just trying to kill Mr Asman! <thought>But why? What WAS his motive, then?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Your time is up, my learned friend. I'd say you have one last chance before the jury lose their patience with this charade.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Let's see if you can back up your heady proposal, shall we? How do you explain why this engineer would throw all caution to the wind and threaten his own country?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">At this point, I'm not prepared to listen to more of this outlandish conjecture without proof. So, Counsel...present your evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Alright... Who exactly was Mr Asman to Drebber? There's a connection there that no one's seen yet. And I'm going to have to present two pieces of evidence to show what it is.</thought> Yes, My Lord. The evidence that establishes a motive and explains why the witness wanted the victim dead is right here!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Yes, that's right. The very document, in fact... ...that proves I had no reason to kill the man.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, I'm afraid not. As it turns out... ...this contract actually helps to establish the real motive for the murder you committed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It does? Well I never!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">What are you talking about? Read it again, you idiot!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm not finished. In order to demonstrate what your motive really was... ...I need this contract...and one other piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What other evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel, you will present your supplementary evidence without delay. The evidence, which when cross-referenced with the contract, establishes a motive for the deed!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right, My Lord. Which is why I just presented another piece of evidence to complete it!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Clearly my learned friend only had half an education. And irony wasn't included on the syllabus. So let me put this in words of zero syllables that even you will understand.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... Wait! I see it now! It's a play on 'syllabus' and 'syllables'! That's the irony!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...That was just a pun, Mr Naruhodo. The irony was...elsewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your argument clearly does not stand without this second piece of evidence, which remains elusive.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, yes! Sorry, My Lord! <thought>The evidence I need to supplement the contract... I know it's right in front of my eyes!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's this newspaper article, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">That was written ten years ago...and every detail has been examined already. What can it possibly tell us?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">That drivel should never have been written! It's typical gutter press nonsense that means nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But there's something significant that this newspaper article and the contract have in common.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">That was written ten years ago...and every detail has been examined already. What can it possibly tell us?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">That drivel should never have been written! It's typical gutter press nonsense that means nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, on its own, it isn't particularly significant. However... ...when considered alongside another piece of evidence... ...it will completely explain your motive for wanting Mr Asman dead.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What other evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel, you will present your supplementary evidence without delay. The evidence, which when cross-referenced with the newspaper article, establishes a motive for the deed!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right, My Lord. Which is why I just presented another piece of evidence to complete it!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Clearly my learned friend only had half an education. And irony wasn't included on the syllabus. So let me put this in words of zero syllables that even you will understand.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... Wait! I see it now! It's a play on 'syllabus' and 'syllables'! That's the irony!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...That was just a pun, Mr Naruhodo. The irony was...elsewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your argument clearly does not stand without this second piece of evidence, which remains elusive.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, yes! Sorry, My Lord! <thought>The evidence I need to supplement the article... I know it's right in front of my eyes!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's this contract, My Lord. Mr Drebber, this is the contract you signed with Mr Asman.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Yes, that's right. The very document, in fact... ...that proves I had no reason to kill the man.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, I'm afraid not.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's something very significant that this newspaper article and the contract have in common.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......... 'If', Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........Yes. If it did...it would be great, I was thinking. Or hoping, anyway. ...Well, wishing, really.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you treating my courtroom like a fountain that grants wishes when you throw money into it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I knew I should have thrown more than a farthing in last time I was at the park...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I don't think this has anything to do with your offerings to the gods, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And it's that common link... ...that shows very clearly why you were determined to kill Mr Odie Asman!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It seems the defence has uncovered something the rest of us have missed. So, my learned friend...point out what these two pieces of evidence have in common. Where exactly is the link between this newspaper article and the contract?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What am I supposed to be seeing there?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">J-J-Just here...is what the two...have in common!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......... That they're both made of paper won't do, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo, I feel sure you've already noticed what the contract and article have in common. But just in case it's slipped your mind...look closely at the illustration!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think perhaps you had better try that again.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...For what good it will do.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What these two pieces of evidence have in common... ...is a signature.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A, a signature?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The signature on the illustration that accompanies the ten-year-old article and the signature on the contract... ...belong to the same person!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Agh...............</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As the court has heard, this illustration was drawn ten years ago... ...by the newspaper reporter who found Mr Drebber and interviewed him about his ordeal. If you look closely, the reporter's signature can be seen in the bottom-right corner of the drawing.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And if you look at the contract here, which was signed between the witness and the victim last year... ...you can clearly see Mr Asman's signature at the bottom.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let me see now... Good Lord, yes! They're identical!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In short... ...the journalist who drew the illustration and wrote the article published about Mr Drebber ten years ago... ...was the victim of this case...Mr Odie Asman!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Ugh... URAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, if you think back... ...you'll remember that Mr Drebber talked about that article in his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">G-Graverobbing, you say?!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Yes. Exhuming fresh corpses to sell is reasonably lucrative.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That, that is quite beyond the pale! You would invite divine retribution, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Yes, well...I think I suffered retribution enough. The Daily Circus...eventually unearthed my name and put it in print. It caused me a great many headaches. In the end, I had to leave the university. ...That was the only paper with the bad grace to identify me unambiguously, I might add.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Then I gave up on my dream of becoming a scientist. And it was all because of that newspaper article.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">At the time, you were a student of the University of London who dreamt of becoming a scientist. However... ...this single newspaper article changed your entire life.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So Mr Asman used to be a newspaper journalist, did he?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">He did, My Lord. In fact, it's a widely held belief that Asman managed to position himself at the heart of his criminal network... ...thanks to the many dubious connections he made during his time as reporter.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you had to give up on your dream and leave university. You lost everything. Eventually you found yourself working in the field of science, but only in the shadows. And all because of that article...written by Mr Asman!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">ENOUGH! ......... Stop this endless drivel about my life!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Explain yourself, Mr Drebber!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Yes, it's true. I had to leave the university as a result of that article. But it was just the straw that broke the camel's back.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Almost every student of science in the faculty was too poor to actually conduct any research. But they struggled on with their hypotheses anyway. We all did. Only to have them taken by vultures. Sooner or later, you knew your ideas would be stolen and patented by some wretch or other, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Making a name for yourself as a scientist in a climate like that... ...was a miracle only a select few geniuses could ever hope to achieve. Personally, I wasn't one of those geniuses. So it was hardly a wrench. Being forced out of the university because of Lowgate was the best thing that could have happened to me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Drebber... ...do you genuinely believe that?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Of course I do! Who's better placed to know whether or not I possess a talent for science than me?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm sorry to say...that your words don't ring true at all.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">...How dare you?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And I have evidence to prove it.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">How are you in a position to say anything about me? I don't know you from Adam! Fine, if you think you have evidence, go ahead. Show it! What could you possibly have to disprove the idea that I was happy to leave university because I lacked talent?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">...In describing your own lack of talent, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Believe me, I've seen many a young man's dreams crushed in the vice of life.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">My advice is for you to do what you Nipponese do best: bow out, and go back home to the farm.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>But my 'farm' is a fifty-day boat ride away...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">If Lord van Zieks is trying to imply that Tokyo is some small, provincial agricultural town, he's sorely mistaken!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As I said, the idea that you left university without looking back because you thought you had no talent is nonsense.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you remember this, Mr Drebber? We found it at your workshop.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I-Is that...a Royal Society trophy for excellence in science?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...What exactly is this trophy, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's the greatest honour that can be bestowed on a young scientist, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">There is no higher accolade. It recognises emerging talent and promises a bright future.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your prospects for the future were excellent, weren't they, Mr Drebber? Because even then, you were a genius in your field.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But you lost everything. You had no more future. Your talents would go to waste. All as a result of this one newspaper article.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't know when you realised who Mr Asman was. But when it dawned on you that he was the same journalist who ten years ago ruined your life... ...it's abundantly clear...that you had no intention of forgiving the man!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">......... .................. The truth...is...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Finally, he's going to fold.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Haaah... Fine. Clearly this has run its course now.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">I admit it. All of it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Drebber">W-What are you doing?!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">It's exactly as the Japanese man said. I was coerced into going along with this man's plot to murder the victim. On the condition that he kept my dirty secret from ten years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">No...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">GOOD LOOOOOOOOORD!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Dr Sithe! Do you realise what you're saying, woman?!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">......... It's all true. That day... ...when I arrived at the Crystal Tower and saw the birdcage... ...my heart nearly stopped beating. That memory from a decade ago that I'd done my best to bury deep inside myself... It was the Professor again, staring me in the face. And then, before I had a chance to react, I noticed something else. There was a note tucked inside the model's jacket.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">All the instructions were there in the note. Every detail was meticulously written out. I had no choice but to do what it said. I made the necessary 'alterations' to the scene and fabricated the autopsy report as instructed. There was really no other choice. It had to be done to protect the judiciary. ...I can only apologise now.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Why on earth would you buckle now?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">......... Well there's no point trying to hide it any more, is there? I would have done anything to stop it coming out. Even collaborate in a murder. But the great lie about that execution ten years ago has been exposed. Whatever happens...I'm finished.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So then, Mr Drebber, what do you say to that? Your accomplice has admitted everything.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">......... Surely it goes without saying.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You admit your part in it too, then?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">I admit nothing! At all!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Have you forgotten that the kinesis machine was ripped to shreds by an explosion? Short of me admitting to a crime, there's really no possible way for you to prove I did anything wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Nnn...NOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Ordaaaaaar!!!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Whatever this man says, I admit everything. He threatened to expose my secret, so I went along with his plan. And Lord van Zieks...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">I hope you'll accept my apologies. ...What happens next is in your hands, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I have heard more than enough now. I hereby present the final findings of this court.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This trial is not the proper forum in which to pursue the alleged wrongdoings of Mr Drebber. The defendant is Professor Albert Harebrayne.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Very true. It had slipped my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Isn't he one of your closest friends?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As the court has heard, Dr Sithe has admitted to the allegations brought by the defence... ...thereby absolving the defendant of any possible guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! You, you mean...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">At the present time, it is the conclusion of this court that the defendant was not involved in any wrongdoing. Does the prosecution have any objection?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... ...None, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, congratulations, Mr Naruhodo! You've proven Professor Harebrayne's innocence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Without further ado then, the adjudication. Unless the prosecution or defence have any other matters to discuss?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>I don't know... This doesn't feel quite right. Why did Dr Sithe suddenly admit to it like that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Is everything alright, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Like you said before, the way the trial is set to end now... ...the judge will certainly deliver a verdict of not guilty. <thought>But is that really what we want? What the defence should be pushing for now is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>If the judge gives his verdict now, Professor Harebrayne will be found not guilty, without any doubt.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Is something troubling you, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes... But it's probably nothing. <thought>In the antechamber during the recess earlier... ...I did give Mr Sholmes my word though, didn't I? I told him I'd pursue any doubts I had about the truth to the absolute last.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">If you gave Mr Sholmes your word, then it most certainly isn't nothing! And it means there's only one right answer here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes, you're right. <thought>I don't know why I was ever wavering.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The defence objects to the trial ending at this time, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I beg your pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We demand...one final testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAT?! You do realise I'm about to adjudicate in favour of your client, I presume?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What are you playing at now, my Nipponese friend? Why would you want to obstruct the conclusion of the trial at this point? No defence lawyer in his right mind would do that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo, what exactly are you thinking?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The truth - the whole truth - and a way to bring it all out into the open.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Right!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>Yes, in hindsight...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah yes, one word of warning before I go: If, in the course of the trial this afternoon, you perceive even a shadow of doubt about the truth... ...don't let it out of your sight. Pursue it like a dog with a bone.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">To the bitter end, you understand. Do not falter, whatever may come to pass.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...I'm sure Mr Sholmes knew. He must have deduced that this would happen.</thought> Yes, I'm here in court to advocate for my client. And to secure an acquittal.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Obviously.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But that's not all. I believe that I have a duty to the court... ...to pursue the whole truth of the case until every last detail is laid bare!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And that is why the defence calls for further testimony from Dr Sithe.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Testimony from me? About what?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">About the nature of your collaboration with Mr Enoch Drebber!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Hah! In case it's escaped your attention, I've already admitted to everything I did. The whole truth has already been revealed. So stop wasting everyone's time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">As His Lordship made very plain, your client will get the acquittal you wanted for him. There's simply no point protracting this business further with another tedious cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's what you call it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-What is your objection, Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The prosecution... ...also calls for supplementary testimony from the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Don't be stupid!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">If there is more to this case than has yet come to light... ...then I will join my learned friend in pursuing the facts until the bitter end.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">You'll what...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord van Zieks...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is most irregular, to say the least. However, as the prosecution also calls for it, I will uphold the request. Dr Sithe, you will testify for the court... ...explaining the full extent of your involvement in the murder apparently committed by Mr Drebber.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">I... ...Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">It all began at the scene when I saw the waxwork and the note tucked inside its jacket.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So I was right: the stage and the machine were all specially designed for the deception.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">So it seems. And all meticulously prepared. You did well to see through it. You're a very shrewd boy.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So kind of you to say...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And what about this autopsy report, then?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">All I did was record the location of the body as being in the Crystal Tower instead of under the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's all...? That's a terrible corruption!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Only my team were aware of the deceit, and then only under my explicit instructions. Nobody else at Scotland Yard knew anything about it, I assure you.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm...we must be thankful for small mercies, I suppose. Well, I believe that testimony has clarified everything. There's no particular need for a cross-examination, I would say...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>No, I disagree. I can't shake the feeling that something's wrong. Just look at that expression on Dr Sithe's face.</thought> It's the defence's right to cross-examine any witness following testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Tsk! What is it about you Japanese that makes you all so doggedly persistent?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. If you so desire, Counsel, proceed with the cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">It all began at the scene when I saw the waxwork and the note tucked inside its jacket.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">From what you described before, it sounds like the note was anonymous. Did you have any idea of who was behind it?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">There are very few people in the know about what really happened ten years ago to start with. But anyway, I'd never heard of this engineer. So no, I had no idea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yet despite not knowing who was behind the plan, you went along with it?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">I had no choice. Protecting the Professor secret was my only concern.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">But the horse has bolted now. And the stable door will never shut again. Scotland Yard's reputation will be immeasurably damaged as a result of all this.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Yes, thank you, Lord van Zieks. I'm well aware of that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, as I understand it, what you found in the birdcage was the waxwork model. Where, then, was the victim's body?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">The actual body of the victim, as indicated in the note's instructions, was beneath the experimentation stage.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you knew about the special construction of the stage used to carry out the trick, then?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">It was quite obvious what had happened with the victim and the waxwork.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And you switched the two over, didn't you? In other words... ...you recorded the victim's body as having been discovered in the Crystal Tower. And the waxwork...?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">I wrapped it and sent it by carriage to the specified address at the specified time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And why were you given such directions?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Presumably so it could be recovered by Drebber and returned to Madame Tusspells.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I see. And then you put the birdcage back on the experimentation stage?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Yes. Although someone obviously made a mistake about which cage should go where. I thought I'd made it perfectly clear to the team, but still...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I suppose you were focused on the victim's body, that being a more important detail.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">The body had to be 'arranged' in certain ways to implicate the defendant...which was my job.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When you say 'arranged', I presume you mean with this?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Yes. The instructions in the engineer's note said something along the lines of: 'Fabricate some evidence to make it clear that Harebrayne alone could have killed Asman.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you mean that was your doing?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">I fetched Harebrayne's ridiculous screwdriver from the stage... ...and took it with me - alone - to the 'abyss' under the stage where the birdcage had fallen.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Alone, Doctor?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">......... I didn't feel it would be appropriate to involve anybody else in that particular part of the deception.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And then you noted that in your fake autopsy report... ...as a fictitious cause of death.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">So the actual cause of death was...?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">......... The trauma resulting from the thirty-foot drop.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">My word...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What is it, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Something about Dr Sithe's last statement... ...is playing on my mind, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...mine too. Dr Sithe!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">There's really no need to shout. I can hear you perfectly well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The defence calls for you to add what you just said to your formal testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Oh? Which part?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What I want her to supplement her testimony with is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The real cause of death being the fall of thirty feet! That part!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Fine, if that's what you want. Just stop yelling, please.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...The prosecution concurs.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. You will supplement your testimony now, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">If you wish, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How you stabbed Mr Asman in the chest! That part!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Fine, if that's what you want. But there's really no need to point.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...The prosecution...concurs.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. You will supplement your testimony now, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">If you wish, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean what you did with this, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">I was merely carrying out the engineer's instructions. In his words: 'Fabricate some evidence to make it clear that Harebrayne alone could have killed Asman.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And so you went, without any of your team, to where Asman had fallen.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">That's right, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'm sure there's something here in this testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">You know, if you think it would be appropriate... ...I'm sure you could ask Dr Sithe to change the supplementary testimony she gave before. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Hm, what should I ask her to do with the statement she added?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Dr Sithe, what you said before about what you did to the victim's body... I believe that may be significant, so could you change your supplementary statement to explain that instead?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">...Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Dr Sithe, what you said before about the real cause of death... I believe that may be significant, so could you change your supplementary statement to explain that instead?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">...Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't think there's any need to ask her to change it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Of course, I'm sure you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">The actual cause of death was the neck trauma Asman suffered from the thirty-foot fall.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're quite sure of that? It was as a result of a broken neck?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Yes. As a professional, that was more than apparent.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You'd never know just by looking at the photograph of the victim though, would you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, that's very true.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Obviously not. Which is precisely why coroners are needed to determine the actual facts.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, assuming they can be trusted.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">There's no point calling her assessment into question without evidence. Let's get back to the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">...Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">I stood over the victim's corpse where it lay in the toppled cage and plunged the screwdriver into the chest.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So it was you who stabbed Asman with this!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Yes. Far easier than dissection, I assure you. No precision required.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What a welcome change...</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">The victim died instantly from a snapped neck. All I did was carry out the instructions I'd been given.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">As unflinchingly as ever, no doubt. I imagine you didn't bat an eyelid when you drove the weapon into his body.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">There was no need to bat my eyelids.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And what else did you do to twist the facts? Remind the court, why don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">...If you wish.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sithe">I enlisted the help of the entire Forensic Investigation Team to dress the scene appropriately.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The entire team? In perverting the course of justice?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">......... My team consists of the very best investigators there are. I demand loyalty from all members. We operate on a code of chivalry of sorts.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You aid and abet a murderer, commit perjury and dare to talk of chivalry?!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">It was a matter of priorities.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Nothing was more important than protecting the secret of the Professor. My team did what was necessary without losing sight of the primary goal. I consider their conduct exemplary.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Don't concede the point, Mr Naruhodo! You mustn't let her win!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I need a lawyer...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sithe">I'll take that silence as tacit acceptance. Now...can we move on?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">The truth about the execution ten years ago is a state secret of the highest level. I had to protect it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But at what cost? Faith in Scotland Yard is going to suffer a terrible blow as a result of this.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And your precious secret is out now anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">......... Yes, as you say. And I take full responsibility.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Blow me down... Dr Sithe!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Surely there was some other way you could have protected the secret?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">No, there really wasn't. I've done my utmost, believe me. In many ways, I respect your determination.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Whew. I nearly froze under that cold stare as she said that.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I do believe she was being genuine though, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So that's her story...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">She's admitted everything and revealed her full involvement in the crime. I do wonder if there could really be much more to it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I don't know. But...I just have a feeling.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Do you, Mr Naruhodo? The truth is, I find it strange, too. How those two are reacting to this in completely opposite ways, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, exactly. <thought>For some reason, I feel sure they're still trying to hide something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>I've got a nasty feeling... ...that this inconsistency points to an extremely uncomfortable truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What on earth is the matter, Counsel? Have you lost your tongue?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I apologise, My Lord. Dr Sithe, in that last statement of yours, there's just one point... ...that seems to defy explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Out with it, my learned friend.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's an obvious inconsistency between your description and this photograph... ...which shows the victim in the birdcage following the events that led to his death.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, we have already considered it, that's true. But we now know the facts to be different!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe we should let the defence explain. Where in this photograph would we see the alleged inconsistency with the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Is the one being made at this very moment by your index finger.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Apparently the victim was lying dead in the birdcage when Dr Sithe stabbed him in the chest. That was the essence of her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know. And hearing that is when I thought, 'Got it!' But then somehow I lost my train of thought at the last moment and it turned into a 'not it'...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Don't worry, Mr Naruhodo, I'm sure if you try again it will turn back into a 'got it'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look closely at the bloodstain on the victim's chest. It clearly extends in a downwards direction, towards the man's feet.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And why is that significant, Counsel? If the victim was stabbed moments before the kinesis machine was set in motion, that's entirely expected... Aaaah! Of course, no, that's not what happened!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Exactly, My Lord. Dr Sithe made it very clear in her testimony just now... ...that the point at which she stole Professor Harebrayne's screwdriver and stabbed the victim... ...was after the grand deception was set in motion, when the birdcage had fallen below the stage out of sight. From the shape of it, it's clear that the birdcage would have fallen on its side after the thirty-foot drop. And if the victim had really been stabbed whilst inside the birdcage in that position... ...the blood from the wound would have spread out equally in all directions. For it to have formed the longitudinal appearance we see in the picture...is inconceivable!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">......... Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Given that the victim's blood seeped vertically downwards from the wound... ...it must be the case that when you stabbed Mr Asman... he was standing up. In short, Dr Sithe... ...your latest testimony was a total fabrication!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Agh... AAAAAAAAAAAAAAARH!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I knew it. I was right. Now I've identified that contradiction, there's only one way to explain the facts.</thought> We've all been under a great misapprehension here.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What?! What sort of misapprehension?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Dr Sithe...</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You claim you were coerced into helping Mr Drebber as a result of the note he left in the waxwork. You claim that you made changes to the scene of the crime to implicate the defendant. And you claim that you authored a fake autopsy report to cover your tracks. But one of those claims is an out-and-out lie! Because the question of what the bloodstain really tells us...has only one possible answer!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">If that is the case...what is it, man?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel, you've clearly struck upon a revelation. Now tell the court what it is! Which part of Dr Sithe's story is shown to be a lie by the contradiction in her testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Dr Sithe...clearly you weren't really coerced by some letter at all.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you were, where is the note? It's nowhere to be seen!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Hmph. That's as may be.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So why don't you present it to the court...if the assertion vexes you?!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Obviously I've already disposed of it. And I'm not vexed in the slightest.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel, need I remind you that it was you yourself who established the coercion?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid that little cry is insufficient recompense for such a blunder. I shall have to penalise you.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Feeling vexed, my Nipponese friend?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Very... But there's no question that the coroner's testimony was built on a tremendous lie!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You say that you examined the body and wrote this report based on your findings. But that's a blatant lie, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">......... I'm sorry, but I simply can't fathom what you're attempting to say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The truth is you had your subordinates do the work for you, and they authored the report! But then you wielded your superiority over them and claimed the credit for yourself! Can you honestly say that's not what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Yes, I can honestly say that's not what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Well. Good. Glad to hear it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......... What on earth was the purpose of that exchange, Counsel?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Will this farce never end?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But there's no question that the coroner's testimony was built on a tremendous lie!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The answer is very simple if you consider the sequence of events. If, when the victim was stabbed, the blood from the wound seeped downwards, as it did... ...we can be sure that the victim must have been either sitting or standing upright at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">But as you rightly pointed out, the birdcage would have fallen on its side when it fell beneath the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, it would. Which tells us... ...that the victim must have been in that position of his own accord.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No! That is the misapprehension! When the birdcage fell from the stage into the void below, it must have hit the ground with considerable force.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If the victim was in fact alive at that point in time... ...it changes everything.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Ah.........AAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Odie Asman's killer wasn't the defendant, Professor Albert Harebrayne. Nor was it the mastermind behind the stage trickery, Mr Enoch Drebber. It was you...Dr Courtney Sithe!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Grrr......... AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Ordaaaaaar!!! Can, can this possibly be true?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Have you been taking me for a fool?! It was you, was it? You killed him?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You hoped that by admitting to being an accomplice in Mr Drebber's scheme, the trial would end... ...before you were accused of a far worse crime: Cold-blooded murder!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Oh do shut up! You're so desperate now, you're making all this up! As if I would do something like that!</line>
<line speaker="Susato"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I assure you the defence is not desperate, Doctor! Mr Naruhodo has established the facts using evidence and logic alone!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Hah! Logic? Don't make me laugh. Sadly your 'logic' has a gaping hole in it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Tsk! I'd have thought it was obvious. A motive, boy. You're lacking a motive. What possible reason would I have to kill Mr Asman?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Asman was involved in any number of criminal activities, from coercion to theft to murder... But there is no known connection to Dr Sithe there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... I'm rather relieved to say it does seem somewhat far-fetched.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>True, there's no obvious motive. But there's still something in the back of my mind. I feel sure I've seen something somewhere that hints at why the coroner might have done this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Yes, I might have tampered with the crime scene and concocted a fake report. But murdering someone for no reason is a very different story!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... No, when you questioned what possible reason you could have for wanting to kill Mr Asman... ...something did come to mind.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">What?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What was it, Counsel? Enlighten the court at once!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, we saw it yesterday, didn't we? Something that seemed strange, but we had no reason to suspect it at the time...</thought> There's a particular object that explains why Dr Sithe would have wanted to kill Mr Asman!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's the iron mask.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">......... You've lost me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Um, sorry, Mr Naruhodo, but why the iron mask?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...of all the things I saw yesterday, it left the greatest impression, so...</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Clearly you have no idea what you're talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh! <thought>I think I must have said the wrong thing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Forgive the interruption, Dr Sithe... ...but what my colleague meant to say was 'scalpels'. Perhaps that makes a little more sense to you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah... <thought>Of course!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's a scalpel. Or rather...scalpels.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's the screwdriver! Or should I say 'Master Andrew'?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">......... You've not making any sense.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Um, sorry, Mr Naruhodo, but how is Professor Harebrayne's trusty tool related to the motive?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I...can't really explain that myself actually...</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Clearly you have no idea what you're talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh! <thought>I think I must have said the wrong thing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Forgive the interruption, Dr Sithe... ...but what my colleague meant to say was 'scalpels'. Perhaps that makes a little more sense to you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah... <thought>Of course!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Did you say 'scalpels'?!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">...Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It would appear that word has struck a chord, Doctor.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">You... Come on, out with it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It was yesterday, when we visited your laboratory...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at this big thick book here.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, it appears to be an accounting ledger. It's a record of the Forensic Investigation Team's spending, I think. ......... Oh...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's clear that the team purchases various equipment and supplies on a monthly basis, but... Well, one entry seems rather strange.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? In what way?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">They're buying five hundred scalpels every month!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Five hundred scalpels...a month?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">At first, I wondered what on earth you could be using that many scalpels for. But actually, I realise now it's not the scalpels themselves that are significant. It's the money for them...disappearing every month from the department's accounts!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Asman's criminal organisation relied heavily on extortion for its funding. Tracing the money from the Forensic Investigation Team's account to find out where it was going... ...would be extremely straightforward.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">Ugh...uuugh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ten years ago, when Mr Asman was still a journalist and wrote this article about Mr Drebber... ...he may well have stumbled upon information as he was researching the story. Information relating to Dr Sithe's darkest secret that he would use to rack money from her for the next decade.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Her darkest secret? Good Lord! You mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't know what happened on the night of that execution ten years ago... ...but clearly the opportunity to rid yourself of that menace was too tempting to pass up.</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So in the end, you weren't coerced at all, were you? You did it entirely of your own free will. You stabbed Mr Asman in the heart with all your might... ...to silence the blackmailer who knew your dark secret forever!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">You'll never understand! None of you! What we've had to keep covered up all these long years...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As very little of the machine remains after it was ripped apart by the bomb... ...the truth of this case can never be properly established unless you speak out.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And if you decide not to... ...it's very possible that Courtney Sithe will escape punishment for her crimes. Please, sir...own up to what you've done and tell the court the truth about what happened!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Ten years ago you told the truth...and you were robbed of a bright and successful future as a result. I can certainly understand your bitterness...and your consternation now. However... ...this is surely the chance you've been waiting for...to sever the hold that fate's had over you all these years.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">......... Super-high-voltage instantaneous kinesis? I mean, really...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">......... It's the addle-brained mock scientists that are the worst, you know. They don't recognise the fact that they don't have talent. They can't even get that right. And so they end up chasing impossible dreams, having unbridled faith in their abilities. They go on and on about their wonderful hypotheses, their stupid eyes shining like a little child's. They make me sick! I can't abide their foolishness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Careful, Mr Drebber.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">......... I was particularly pleased with the kinesis machine. It made for quite a show, didn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you admit it? You admit that it was nothing more than a sham made for the purpose of killing the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Yes, I admit it. I did it all...in the name of revenge.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Revenge for the future that Mr Asman's article had deprived you of ten years earlier. But the revenge you sought didn't stop at Asman, did it?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Which is where that very particular waxwork comes in. Yes, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The condemned convict that you saw rising from the grave in Lowgate Cemetery ten years ago... If your account of those events was all true...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...Then obviously Scotland Yard couldn't afford to acknowledge what had happened. Even if it meant discrediting a bright young man and crushing any future career he might have had.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So your plan required that you abduct that particular waxwork model... ...in order to exact your revenge on Scotland Yard as well. Or on Dr Sithe, to be precise.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">......... It was a year ago... By some extraordinary twist of fate, Asman turned up at my workshop. He didn't remember who I was, of course. He just wanted to employ my services as an engineer. And he happened to have a paper with him. An article on the front page caught my eye. About the coroner who'd handled that bogus autopsy being appointed head of a new forensic team. ...When I learnt that news...my cognitive processes started to devise the plan.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What a horrid tale...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">He robbed me of my future, so I wanted to use the man's own wiles against him...for revenge. And have that rotten Scotland Yard eating out of my hand at the same time. I wanted them all to suffer the same humiliation I'd had to suffer!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your actions against those who'd ruined your future were justified as revenge. At least, to yourself. Certainly, no one has the right to destroy another's prospects, especially for purely selfish gain. And yet... ...in carrying out your plan, you did exactly that to someone else, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Did I...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Professor Harebrayne's only crime was passion for his hypothesis! But you had no compunction about sacrificing his future to effect your revenge. You knew that he would be forever branded a failure and a fraud.</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Perhaps life treated you unfairly ten years ago, and others' misconduct left your life in tatters. But remember this... ...your own actions...resulted in exactly the same thing for another perfectly innocent young man!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">......... I... I... .........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Lord van Zieks, what of Dr Sithe?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">An immediate warrant for her arrest has been granted and she's been remanded in custody, My Lord. I presume she will face trial in the coming days, along with Mr Drebber.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......... A most regrettable situation indeed... She's made great contributions to her profession over the years. It really is a hard truth to swallow. However...that is a topic for some future occasion. For now, Professor Harebrayne...</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Oh, um...yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems there was a great deal more to your experiment than you realised. However, I think we can assume now that all the sordid details have been brought to light. This has been a very long and profound trial, but I'm pleased to say...you are absolved of all guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... This whole experience has taught me a very great but painful lesson. I've, I've been... I mean, me, this dedicated scientist... This, this devotee of natural philosophy... I've been selfish and self-centred and above all...a fool.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I've spent my life thinking of nothing but my research. Misguidedly believing that I could do whatever I set my mind to, despite my lack of talent. And the worst of it is, in the process, I've caused others pain and misery! Others who are far, far greater people than I...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">No, Professor, that's not true.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Don't tar yourself with the same brush as Drebber. What happened was his doing and his alone. This outcome is his fate, not yours. ...You're not to blame in any way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord van Zieks...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And the derision with which he referred to you earlier... Calling you a fool... Talentless, even...</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The man has no idea. To believe in yourself and work your fingers to the bone to realise your dreams... That's laudable, not laughable. No one has the right to deride another for such choices.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Oh... Thank you, Barok.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, ladies and gentlemen of the jury...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Yes, My Lord?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is this court's expectation that you find the defendant not guilty of the charge of which he stands accused. I presume there are no objections?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">None from me, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Certainly not.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">This trial has really made me think. But...this is the right decision.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">It's all been proven methodically and rigorously. I have no misgivings whatsoever.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Hm? What's that? Ee's done, is ee? It's all over?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">I don't know what's become of the Yard these days. I don't recognise the place.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. In that case, I hereby pronounce the defendant...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It's over... ...That was some trial.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Professor! What a splendid outcome, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, it is, it is! Congratulations, Professor Harebrayne!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... Mr Naruhodo... Miss Susato... I am truly...truuuly... ...beside myself with gratitude! How can I ever thank you enough?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm just glad it's all been cleared up. That you realise you were just caught up in a bad situation.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">AAAAAAH! Right now, you know...if I had that research grant money... AAAAAAH! I'd give the whole lot to you! Every penny!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...that's very kind, but...I'm just a student, so...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We don't need any financial reward. Your acquittal is more than enough.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Oh dear... Oh what can I do...? Aha! How about this? As a memento? The paper about my hypothesis is inside!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Well, just as a memento then. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I've been wondering, Professor... ...what are you going to do now?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Oh, oh my... Yes... What am I going to do? My hypothesis and my great machine lie in ruins... But still, it's been too long since I was last in London, so perhaps I'll enjoy some sightseeing. I must explore the Great Exhibition whilst I'm here, too, and see if new inspiration hits me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes, that's a wonderful idea, I-</line>
<line speaker="???">I can't allow that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">L-Lord van Zieks! What are you doing in here?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Barok!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I'm sorry you had to go through that, Albert.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Well, if I'm honest...it, it was terrifying! You were like a great demon behind your bench there, snarling down on your prey!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... You're one of the few true friends I have. I couldn't leave it to anybody else to handle the prosecution...or the defence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry? <thought>Or the defence? Did, did I just hear that right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I always knew that you had my best interests at heart, don't worry. Ah, how about you show me around while I'm here in town? It's been a long time since we left university. We have a lot to catch up on.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Listen, Albert... ...in a few days, your acquittal will be made official. When that happens... ...you must head straight to Dover. I'll accompany you.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">What?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">From there, you'll cross the Channel and make your way back to Germany. I've already purchased the tickets.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">But, but no! Hold on a minute, Barok! What about the Great Exhibition? This is the chance of a lifetime for me! I want to look around.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">No, no sightseeing, Albert. Give up on the idea.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ugh... S-Sometimes it's hard to see any warmth in those eyes, Barok...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Lord van Zieks... ...what's all this about?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">A necessary precaution.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I...think I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You do?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, Iris told me that when you met Lord van Zieks at his office some days ago... ...he asked how Mr Natsume was doing.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's right! I remember being surprised at the time... and thinking it was nice of him to ask.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The point is...Mr Natsume is still alive and well! Even though it's been more than six months now since he stood trial with the Reaper as the prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! You, you mean... ...the Reaper's influence doesn't stretch overseas?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Those in the Reaper's sights meet their ends days or sometimes months after their acquittal. That's been the pattern up to now.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But of course, we know that both Mr Natsume and Gina were completely innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... True. And perhaps that governs the Reaper's actions. The truly innocent are spared. But I don't want to take any chances with a close personal friend.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">B-B-Barok...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Like the moustached Nipponese...this man should leave the country without delay. That's why...I'm packing him off to Germany at once!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">R-Right... <thought>Does your friend-shaped package get any say in it...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Goodness! Was this your intention all along then, Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>In court, where people think of him as the Reaper, this man seems absolutely merciless...and yet... ...sometimes I feel as though I don't understand him at all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It's time to go, Albert. Back to the prison for the time being.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ah, yes, alright. Well then, Mr Naruhodo... ...thank you so much for everything!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Not at all, Professor! It was a pleasure getting to know you!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Best wishes, Professor Harebrayne.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Well, once the dust has settled...you MUST come and visit me in Germany! Anyway, goodbye for now!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Now, my Nipponese friend...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Yes? <thought>I thought you'd gone too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...we have matters to discuss. Can you spare me some time?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You want to talk with me?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I'll be waiting in the courtroom in ten minutes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well that was strange. For some reason I didn't get that sense of impending doom as he walked away this time. The enigma, Barok van Zieks... What does he want to discuss, I wonder? The answer awaits in the courtroom, I suppose. Here goes then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">So, are you satisfied? You saved a guileless scientist from a great injustice.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...yes! I think so. I'm relieved, at least, that the man's innocence could be proven.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Anyway... ...I imagine you've been wondering where my animosity towards you Nipponese comes from.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Well, at first I thought you just didn't like me. I imagined you saw me as a pretentious child from an unimportant land, who had no business being here. But now I think differently.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You clearly know our ways. So I would guess that some specific incident led to your thorough dislike of my race. Will you tell me what happened, please?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... The Professor... I thought I'd never hear that name in this courtroom again, to be honest.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">He, he took your brother's life...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Klint. My brother was Klint van Zieks. Sixteen years ago, when I was still just in my teens... ...he was already the Director of Prosecutions, and a key member of the judiciary. I looked up to him. He was everything I aspired to be.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">He was involved in the establishment of justice systems in foreign countries, as well. There were exchange programmes between Britain and other nations then too, to share knowledge and ideas. As part of one of those programmes... ...three judicial students came to Britain from your homeland, the Empire of Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! If it was sixteen years ago, then...one of them could have been my father...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Of course, I remember Doctor Mikotoba well.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I had no idea...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I was a minor at the time, training at the Prosecutor's Office. One day Klint introduced me to the three visiting Nipponese.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So...you've actually met my father...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">He and his colleagues were polite and amicable. They were adept at their work and exacting in their standards. It was my first encounter with the Nipponese spirit, and it made a very great impression upon me. But six years later... That's when it happened. The investigation was going nowhere. There were no suspects, even. Just an ever-growing list of victims. And in the end...my brother became one of them. The last in fact, before the case was finally resolved.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm so sorry, Lord van Zieks. Truly...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Klint was always ready to put his life on the line for justice anyway. So he wouldn't have wanted it any other way. He lost his life to the killer, but it was his victory in the end. For me personally, though, it was a great loss. I found myself in a very dark place indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">When I finally found out the killer's identity... ...the reason why no one had been able to catch the man sooner ceased to be such a mystery. He'd been hiding in plain sight all the time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In plain sight?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Are you aware of political events ten years ago? It was a period of extremely sensitive diplomacy between the British and Japanese empires.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A new treaty was being forged, I think?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Correct. The Anglo-Japanese Treaty of Friendship and Navigation was being concluded. The leaders of both countries were deep in extensive political discussions. Which is why this particular killer's appearance in court was conducted as a closed trial. If the British public had known the identity of the killer... ...not only would the treaty have been in jeopardy...but our two nations could very well have ended up at war.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! A, a war...between Britain and Japan?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But that would mean... Oh my! You mean to say the Professor was...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">When the trial reached its conclusion earlier, I thought to myself, 'Yes, it's time.' Time for you to come face to face with this hideous monster.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I borrowed the key for the mask from the proprietress of the waxwork museum. So see for yourselves now. Confirm it with your own eyes: the truth that's been hidden this past decade.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Th...That's the Professor?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yes...that's him.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Until now...the thought never even crossed my mind... ...that the mass murderer whose crimes shook Britain as never before... ...was Japanese!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">W-Wait a minute! That face... I feel as though...I've seen it somewhere... It's strangely familiar...</line>
<line speaker="???">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="???">Fa... Father...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! Wha...? 'Father'? Kazuma! <thought>My best friend, Kazuma Asogi... After a whole year... finally, his memories returned... ...as he stood there before me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ryunosuke...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hello again... ...my friend.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Kazuma-sama!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Judicial Assistant Mikotoba... ...it's been a very long road. Thank you. Thank you for guiding my friend here when I could not.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It...it was an honour.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I knew you wouldn't die that easily, Kazuma.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...I owe you thanks, too. ...for taking good care of that in my absence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm? ...Oh! <thought>Karuma, the great blade of the Asogi clan, passed down through the generations... When we left Japan, this sword was at my friend's side. A Japanese man's katana is his soul. And he couldn't be parted from it. But then, when the incident happened... ...it was Susato-san's wish that I inherit the sword. And I've kept it with me ever since...along with my memories of the friendship we shared.</thought> With this by my side, I always felt that you were watching over me somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I've made it at last...Father.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Are you saying...? Surely not! You mean...y-you knew all this time?! <thought>I'm looking at it, but I still can't believe it... This mass murderer...is Kazuma's father!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">K-Kazuma-sama...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... Ryunosuke... ...we have much to talk about, but now is not the time. ...I'll be seeing you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's all Kazuma said... ...before he turned and left us there in the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">So he's the living 'afterimage' of the man who took my brother's life, is he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, Kazuma Asogi. My best friend.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Three months ago, when Lord Stronghart introduced us... ...I had an inkling there was something there. Some connection.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>But why did Lord Stronghart do that? Why did he make Kazuma Lord van Zieks's apprentice? And when he was suffering amnesia, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The man was apprehended... Even executed... ...but his legacy just won't die. That's the sad truth. Anyway, that's all I had to say. I thank you for meeting with me as I asked.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ten years ago... ...my grandmother took me to the railway station. We were there to meet my father from the train. For me... ...it was the first time I'd ever seen him.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Poor Susato-san. All this is tied up with painful memories for her, too. She's never talked about this with me before, though...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It took time to adjust to having Father around. But just when I was starting to get used to it... ...he called me into his study one day. He told me that a great friend of his had passed away in London. And that the friend had left behind a son. A boy, seven years my senior. Father told me the boy had made a promise to his late father... ...so he was studying to become a defence lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't find anything out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Surely something about that last statement seems odd, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Would you care to mull over precisely what you find odd about it on your return journey to Japan?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I wouldn't be back to give the court an answer for about four months, though.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Rest assured, we should be happy to carry proceedings forward in your absence, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He sounds serious! I have to prove my worth before he really does send me back home!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That last statement would seem to be at odds somehow with the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is your task, Counsel, to explain the 'somehows' to the court, not the other way around.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...It just seems to jar, though. Don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What I think, is that this whole exchange has been extremely jarring, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Perhaps I need to reconsider this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The defence would have to object to that last statement, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And I would have to overrule your objection, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The defence...would have to accept the penalty given.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Glad to hear it. And you would also have to think again, hm?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you have something to say about that, juror number one?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Did something about that last remark strike a chord with you?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Do you think I'd be reading the paper like this if it did?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">'You see, but you do not observe, Wilson.' ...Words of a famous detective, those. Perhaps if you did a little more observing, we could save us all some time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Believe me, I've seen that detective observing things, and it doesn't save anyone any time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Has that given you pause for thought, juror number two?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Madam!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Oh, I do apologise. I was quite lost in thought for a moment there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I noticed. Clearly something about what was just said made an impression on you.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Oh golly, I'm afraid you misunderstand. I was thinking about this evening's menu.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Menu?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">That's right. My dear Daley will be ravenous by the time I'm home.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well for starters, perhaps you could listen to what's being said here in the courtroom?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...And perhaps if what you set before the jurors was more appetising, you'd keep their attention better.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Something you'd like to say, juror number three?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Please...draw a card. Any card, but do not show me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">I will astound you by telling you the card you have taken.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Sorry, but my arms don't magically extend, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Then how about this?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What would really surprise me is if you would focus on the proceedings.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you have something to say, juror number four?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Have I observed any interesting reactions, is that what you're asking?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">W-What made you say that?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Science is all about making observations and drawing conclusions, young man. And I've drawn plenty about you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You have...?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">At any moment, some catalyst is likely to make you explode with a cry of '<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'm not that much of an unstable substance.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you have something to say to that, juror number five?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">......... I love a good bit of corn, me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You don't say.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">But what I really love more than anythin' is bitin' into a fresh radish.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But then...why the corn?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">I forgot 'im at home...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">A lesson...in life. There may well be more to people than meets the eye.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm really not sure that applies here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Did something about that strike a chord, sir?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Juror number six!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">.........</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">...Don't suppose I could 'elp, could I? Always enjoy a natter, me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>Well this is new.</thought> Perhaps you could wake up the policeman next to you?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Ar, no problem. I'll do it dreckly. Just get through some more o' this first.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Those two statements are fundamentally at odds with one another! Well, Mr Foreman?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">...Ah, there's to be a new Herlock Sholmes adventure published next month, by the looks...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My, My Lord! The foreman of the jury isn't listening!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is that so? Well, I shall have to reserve myself a copy at the local newsagent, in that case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Susato, no one is listening to what I'm saying...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps this would be a good opportunity to have a rethink then, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Fear not, my learned friend. I heard every sorry word.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... It sounds like I'm on the wrong track here. I'd better think again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Drebber! Is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Drebber!</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It would appear his only answer is that rather bewitching mechanical wiggle.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...He could have just said no.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Dr Sithe!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You were clearly just lost in thought about something!</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">......... Your jet-black Japanese hair.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Sithe">It made me wonder if perhaps your head was filled with equally jet-black Indian ink. And that the only way to know for sure, would be to cut your head open and see. That's what I was thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Alright, mental note in black sumi ink: never pursue Dr Sithe again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! You mustn't be intimidated!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Madame Tusspells!</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">Oui?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is there something about that last statement that you'd like to remark on?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">I am afraid to say that I am rather whimsical at heart.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, really?</line>
<line speaker="Tusspells">So when something bothers me, I pour hot wax over it first and think about it afterwards.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Perhaps a less...well, deadly approach might be worth considering?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, Counsel, that will do.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but, My Lord, wait! The defence is still in the process of establishing its argument...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No further analysis is necessary, I feel. As such, I shall be requesting the final decisions of the members of the jury.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">It's been an honour to serve, My Lord. And we know exactly what we think now. Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr Albert Harebrayne, in accordance with the findings of this court, I pronounce you...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I applaud the jurors for doing their civic duty and for finding a swift resolution to this matter. That is all. Court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>